Red Green: ISN'T IT GREAT TO
BE ABLE TO HELP THE BIRDS
THROUGH THE WINTER
WITH THESE BIRD FEEDERS?
WE ALL WANT THE BIRDS TO BE
HEALTHY AND HAPPY
BECAUSE IT'LL BE HUNTING
SEASON BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
I'M KIDDIN'.
BUT YOU KNOW, THIS YEAR,
WE'VE HAD THE WORST WINTER
WE'VE HAD IN A WHILE.
I'M JUST AFRAID NORMAL
BIRDSEED WON'T DO THE JOB.
THEY NEED FOOD THAT'LL
HELP THEM GENERATE A
LITTLE EXTRA HEAT
IN THOSE TINY BODIES,
AND THAT'S WHY I'VE MIXED UP
THIS BATCH OF JALAPEÑOS,
CHILI PEPPERS AND
EXTRA, EXTRA HOT SAUCE.
GIVE THIS BIRDSEED A LITTLE
BOOST IN THE HORSEPOWER
DEPARTMENT.
[birds chirping]
I THINK IT'S GONNA BE A LITTLE
WARMER IN THE NEST TONIGHT.
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
[applause continues]
ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
I KNOW YOU'RE EXCITED
BECAUSE TOMORROW IS THE
DAY THE TOWN HAS
THEIR ANNUAL
MASQUERADE PICNIC.
IT USED TO BE
JUST A NORMAL PICNIC.
WE HAD THE POTLUCK
SUPPER IN THERE,
BUT WE HAD SO MANY FOOD
POISONING CLAIMS
THAT NOW EVERYONE WEARS A
COSTUME TO PROTECT THE GUILTY.
SPEAKING OF PROTECTING
THE GUILTY...
SO, UH,
WHAT'S UP, MIKE?
I'M NOT MIKE.
NO.
OH, REALLY?
I'M AN INTERESTING STRANGER
FROM A FARAWAY TOWN.
THERE'S NO ONE NAMED MIKE
LIVING IN THE PLACE OF
WHICH I SPEAK.
REALLY?
YEAH. MM-HMM.
WHAT'S THE
PROBLEM?
YOU GOTTA HELP ME,
MR. GREEN!
ABOUT TEN YEARS AGO
I RATTED ON THIS GUY
NAMED BIG AL
FINKLEMAN.
I SENT HIM UP TO
THE SLAMMER.
AND I HEARD YESTERDAY
HE JUST GOT OUT,
AND HE'S COMING TO
GET ME TO PAY ME BACK.
WHAT AM
I GONNA DO?
YOU KNOW, MAYBE
YOU'RE NOT MIKE.
OH, YEAH.
I'M MIKE.
I AM MIKE.
YOU HAVE A LOOK.
"DALTON HUMPHREY."
YEAH, YOU'RE MIKE
ALL RIGHT.
LOOK, MIKE, HERE'S
ALL YOU GOTTA DO...
TOMORROW'S THE
MASQUERADE PICNIC, RIGHT?
SO GO OUT AND GET
YOURSELF A DECENT COSTUME,
AND YOU'LL BLEND
RIGHT IN.
THIS BIG AL GUY'LL
NEVER FIND YOU.
OH, THAT'S A
GREAT IDEA.
I'M GONNA GO RIGHT TO
THE COSTUME STORE.
HOW LATE ARE
THEY OPEN?
OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
THERE'LL BE SOMEBODY
THERE TILL SIX.
OKAY, I'LL WAIT.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
[cheers and applause]
AND TONIGHT'S LUCKY
WINNER WILL RECEIVE
THIS STRIKING FLUORESCENT
BICYCLE HANDLE GRIP.
IDEAL FOR
HITCHHIKING AT NIGHT.
OKAY, CLOSE YOUR EARS.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS TO
GET HAROLD TO SAY THIS WORD...
ALL RIGHT,
DALTON.
AND GO.
OKAY, HAROLD, WHAT'S THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING ON A CAR?
CUP HOLDERS.
NO, THIS IS A
PERFORMANCE THING.
HO! HO!
RECLINING SEATS?
OKAY, WHEN I STOMP DOWN ON
THE POSSUM VAN GAS PEDAL,
IT GIVES ME LOTS OF...
FUMES.
OKAY, WE HAVE TO MOVE
SOMETHING LIKE A PIANO,
WE ALWAYS PUT MOOSE THOMPSON
ON THE HEAVY END,
BECAUSE HE HAS MORE...
INSURANCE.
OKAY, HAROLD, WHEN YOU'RE
DANCING WITH A BEAUTIFUL GIRL,
YOU GOT HER IN YOUR ARMS,
SUDDENLY BOTH OF YOU FEEL
THE SOMETHING OF LOVE.
[gasping]
TIME'S ALMOST UP, RED.
HAROLD, I THINK
WE'RE SCUPPERED HERE.
NO! NO! NO!
DON'T GIVE UP!
JUST USE THE POWER
OF POSITIVE THINKING.
THAT WAS IT!
STATE OF THE ART WASTE
WATER REMOVAL VEHICLE...
$95,000.
HARD HAT: $20.
TRADEMARK: $14.95.
HEADING HOME
WITH CLEAN BOOTS
AFTER FOUR PUMP-OUTS
AND AN OVERFLOW...
PRICELESS.
FOR CITY FOLKS
THERE'S PUBLIC WORKS;
FOR EVERYONE ELSE THERE'S
ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
SOME MEN ARE SO COMPETITIVE,
EVEN WITH DUMB THINGS
LIKE BARBECUE GRILLS.
THEY GET THOSE BIG UNITS WITH
THE EXTRA SIDE BURNERS
AND A ROTISSERIE
AND A WET BAR.
WELL, LET'S SHOW THEM
A THING OR TWO, HUH?
HERE'S A WAY TO BUILD YOUR OWN
MEGA-GRILL USING SOMETHING
EVERYBODY HAS RIGHT
IN THEIR OWN BACKYARD...
A PREVIOUSLY
ENJOYED AUTOMOBILE.
OH, SURE, YOU HAVE TO MAKE
A FEW ALTERATIONS TO
THE VEHICLE;
BUT, YOU KNOW, THE TRULY
WORTHWHILE THINGS IN LIFE
ARE ALWAYS WORTH
A LITTLE EXTRA EFFORT.
NOW, FIRST YOU WANNA
TAKE OFF THE SPARK PLUGS,
BUT LEAVE 'EM HOOKED UP
TO THE IGNITION WIRE.
THEN YOU WANNA
DISCONNECT THE FUEL LINE
FROM THE CARBURATOR.
NOW, YOU GOTTA
TAKE THE ENGINE OUTTA HER.
IT SHOULDN'T BE THAT HARD,
ESPECIALLY IF THE VEHICLE'S
BEEN SITTING THERE
FOR A WHILE.
OKAY, YOU MOUNT THE
FUEL LINE ON THE TOP THERE.
THEN YOU RUN YOUR SPARK
PLUGS THROUGH THE SIDE
OF THE UNIT.
THEN YOU PUT THE WHOLE
DEAL DOWN INTO THE CAVITY
WHERE THE ENGINE
USED TO BE --
KIND OF LIKE A
HEART TRANSPLANT.
ALTHOUGH, I BELIEVE
WITH A HEART TRANSPLANT,
THEY CLEAN THEIR
SHOES OFF FIRST.
ALL RIGHT, NOW WE NEED
SOMETHING TO USE AS A GRILL.
HOW ABOUT THE GRILL?
OKAY, I THINK WE'RE ALL
READY TO START BARBECUING.
FIRST THING YOU WANNA DO
IS PUMP THE GAS A FEW TIMES
TO SOAK THE CHARCOAL.
NOW YOU JUST
START HER UP.
OKAY, WE'RE ALL SET TO GRILL
UP SOME DELICIOUS STEAKS.
YOU KNOW, IF SALAD
IS SO GOOD FOR YOU,
HOW COME YOU CAN'T
BARBECUE IT,
CAN YOU ANSWER ME THAT?
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
SO HERE I AM SITTING
IN MY DELUXE BARBECUE GRILL.
OUT OF THE RAIN,
SITTING IN PLUSH COMFORT.
GOT THE FM/AM STEREO,
IF I SO CHOOSE.
WHAT'S THAT YOU SAY?
HOW DO I ADD MY
FAVOURITE STEAK SAUCE?
WELL, HEY, ISN'T THAT WHAT
WINDSHIELD WASHERS ARE FOR?
AND JUST SPREAD IT
AROUND WITH THE WIPER.
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
THIS ISN'T A BARBECUE;
IT'S A CARBECUE.
GETS OVER 50
MEALS TO A GALLON.
EVEN MORE IF I GOOSE IT.
[cheers and applause]
WHEN YOU'RE HIT WITH AN AROMA
THAT BUCKLES YOUR KNEES,
WHEN YOUR PROPERTY SMELLS
LIKE PREHISTORIC CHEESE,
CALL US.
WE'LL HANDLE
THE PROBLEM WITH EASE,
BEFORE YOUR
NEIGHBOURS KEEL OVER
WITH EACH PASSING BREEZE.
WELL, EVERYBODY'S ALL DRESSED
UP FOR THE MASQUERADE PICNIC.
MOST OF THEM ARE MONSTERS AND
ANIMALS AND THINGS.
ACTUALLY, THAT WE BEFORE THEY
EVEN PUT THE COSTUMES ON.
HEY, RED, HUH?
DO YOU
RECOGNIZE US?
WHY SURE.
IT'S CURLY, LARRY
AND MIKE.
AH, GEE,
IF I CAN'T FOOL YOU,
I CAN'T FOOL
ANYBODY.
BIG AL'S GONNA COME,
AND HE'S GONNA FIND ME,
AND HE'S GONNA
KILL ME.
BOY, YOU'RE GONNA
LOSE THE DEPOSIT
ON YOUR COSTUME.
HEY, I GOT AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T YOU
DRESS UP AS A WOMAN?
THAT'LL FOOL HIM.
WELL, THAT'S
KIND OF RISKY.
HE'S BEEN IN PRISON
FOR TEN YEARS.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
MIKE?
IF BIG AL CAME THROUGH
THAT DOOR RIGHT NOW,
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
I'D PROBABLY
SOIL MYSELF.
YOU'D LOSE THE DEPOSIT
ON YOUR COSTUME.
AND I'D RUN.
EXACTLY.
AND THAT'S HOW WE
WOULD HIDE YOU, SEE?
WE'LL GET EVERYONE TO RUN,
AND YOU'LL GET LOST
IN THE SHUFFLE.
BEFORE WE HAVE THE PICNIC,
WE'LL HAVE A
MASQUERADE MARATHON.
KINDA LIKE THE
BOSTON MARATHON.
YEAH, EXCEPT WE
WON'T GO 26 MILES.
AND IT WON'T BE
IN BOSTON, RIGHT?
WHAT ABOUT A PRIZE?
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED TO OFFER
SOME KIND OF PRIZE, HUH?
I THINK THAT'S MIKE'S
RESPONSIBILITY.
I MEAN, WE'RE DOING
THIS FOR HIM,
SO I THINK HE'S GOTTA
OFFER THE PRIZE.
OKAY, THE WINNER GETS
TO CHOOSE HIS OWN PRIZE,
AS LONG AS IT'S
AVAILABLE LOCALLY
AND IT CAN BE
CARRIED BY ONE PERSON.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERTS
PORTION OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE ADDRESS
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
THOSE ARE
THE WORDS.
OH, TODAY'S LETTER
IS FROM A LADY.
"DEAR EXPERTS: MY HUSBAND
IS A TOTAL EMBARRASSMENT --"
WELL, THAT COULD'VE
BEEN WRITTEN BY EVERY
WOMAN I KNOW.
"ESPECIALLY WHEN HE EATS.
"HE PICKS HIS TEETH;
PUTS HIS ELBOWS ON THE TABLE;
"AND MAKES RUDE NOISES.
"IT'S GOTTEN SO BAD
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO
"GO OUT TO EXPENSIVE
RESTAURANTS WITH HIM ANYMORE."
WISH I'D THOUGHT
OF THAT.
OH, BOY, I JUST
HATE DINING OUT.
THERE'S JUST SO
MANY LITTLE RULES OF
ETIQUETTE TO REMEMBER.
AH, DALTON, IT'S SIMPLE.
YOU JUST START WITH THE
SMALLER CUTLERY ON
THE OUTSIDE
AND WORK YOUR WAY IN.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
SEE, DALTON'S USED TO CUTLERY
THAT COMES IN A PLASTIC BAG
WITH A MOIST TOWELETTE.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT
THE PROBLEM IS, DON'T YOU?
THIS TOWN DOESN'T HAVE ENOUGH
FINE DINING ESTABLISHMENTS.
THAT'S WHY I'M THINKING ABOUT
OPENING UP MY OWN, EH.
YEAH.
OH, YEAH?
WINSTON'S HIDEAWAY.
YOU KNOW,
FOR PEOPLE LIKE ME.
OH, YEAH?
LONELY SEWAGE SUCKERS
WITH NO CHANCE
FOR ROMANCE?
I'M KIND OF PICTURING A
LOT OF TABLES FOR ONE
THERE, WINSTON.
NO, NO, NO.
IF SOMEONE COMES IN ALONE,
I WOULD JUST SEAT THEM WITH
ANOTHER ELIGIBLE SINGLE.
YOU KNOW, KIND OF A DATING
SERVICE/RESTAURANT THING.
SOUNDS MORE LIKE A BAD
IDEA/LAWSUIT THING.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT
THIS LADY NEEDS TO DO.
SHE NEEDS TO BE ABLE
TO IGNORE HER HUSBAND,
AND GO TO A RESTAURANT WHERE
THEY HAVE REAL LOW LIGHTS
AND LOUD MUSIC, YOU KNOW?
IF SHE CAN'T SEE HIM
AND CAN'T HEAR HIM,
SHE'S PROBABLY GOING TO GET
ALONG WITH HIM A LOT --
OR BETTER YET --
BETTER YET.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
JUST STAY HOME.
THAT'S WHAT
BERNICE AND I DO.
AND BERNICE IS ABLE TO
IGNORE ALL YOUR FAULTS?
OH, SURE, YEAH.
SHE'S SITTING AT ONE END OF
THE TABLE IN THE DINING ROOM,
AND I'M LYING ON THE
COUCH IN THE LIVING ROOM.
Red: WE HAVE THIS
THING WE DO EVERY YEAR.
WE TRY TO SEE WHO CAN BE THE
FASTEST COMING DOWN
THE BIG HILL.
WE SET UP A CLOCK
AND SET IT ON 12.
YOU SEE THE MARK THERE?
THE 23-SECOND MARK.
THAT IS THE WORLD RECORD FOR
COMING DOWN OUR HILL.
SO WE SET IT,
AND I STOP THE CLOCK
RIGHT ON THE 12.
THEN I HANG
A PAINT CAN ON THERE.
ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS
KNOCK THE PAINT CAN OFF.
THAT STARTS THE CLOCK.
AND THEN WE TRY TO GET DOWN
THE HILL AND HIT THE TIMER.
PULLS HER TO STOP --
WELL YOU'LL SEE WHAT
I MEAN IN A SECOND.
SO I'M GONNA TAKE THE FIRST
RUN, GET ON THE TOBOGGAN.
DALTON -- I TELL DALTON,
GO AHEAD, I'M READY.
SO HE WHIPS A SNOWBALL ALL
THE WAY DOWN THE HILL,
KNOCKS THE CAN OFF,
AND THAT STARTS THE CLOCK.
AND DOWN SHE COMES.
SO I'M DOING PRETTY GOOD.
I BELIEVE THERE'S A ROCK
SOMEWHERE.
THERE IT IS.
NO, MISSED THAT.
WE COMIN' ALONG.
LOOKIN' GOOD. LOOKIN' GOOD.
AND...
I LIKE THIS, BABY.
OH, BEAUTIFUL.
AND I GO CHECK MY TIME.
THAT'S ABOUT 37.
I'M A GOOD 14 SECONDS
OFF THE RECORD.
NOW, THE THING ABOUT
TOBOGGANING, FOR THOSE
OF YOU WHO HAVE DONE IT,
YOU KNOW THAT THE MORE WEIGHT
YOU HAVE ON THE TOBOGGAN,
GENERALLY,
THE FASTER SHE'LL GO.
SO I'M FIGURIN' I'M GONNA
ADD A BIT MORE WEIGHT NOW.
UNFORTUNATELY,
WINSTON WAS WITH US,
AND NOBODY WANTED
HIM IN FRONT OF THEM.
SO WE HAD TO
KEEP SHOVING HIM BACK.
NO, BACK YOU GO, WINSTON.
YOU DON'T WANNA BE DOWN
WIND FROM WINSTON,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
OKAY, SO WE PUT
WINSTON ON THE BACK THERE.
AND WE SIGNALLED DALTON.
OKAY, DALTON, WE'RE READY.
FIRE AWAY.
WELL, THAT WAS UNFORTUNATE.
OKAY, WE'LL GO
WITHOUT WINSTON THEN.
ALL RIGHT,
AND TRY HER AGAIN.
I THINK THREE OF US,
WE'RE GONNA MAKE A
DIFFERENCE.
AND AWAY WE GO.
DOWN WE GO.
AND I'M FEELING
PRETTY GOOD.
I'M FEELING THE
EXTRA SPEED ALREADY.
AND IS THIS ENOUGH
WEIGHT, DO WE THINK,
TO BREAK THE WORLD RECORD?
WELL, WE'LL
SOON FIND OUT.
CHECK IT -- NO.
WE GAINED SOME,
BUT NO, NOT YET.
SO WE NEED TO DO SOMETHING
THAT ADDS EVEN MORE WEIGHT,
AND WE GOT A GREAT IDEA.
OKAY, AND EVEN DALTON
CAN GO WITH US ON THIS,
'CAUSE HE CAN SIT RIGHT
ON THE PICNIC TABLE.
FIRE AWAY, DALTON.
AND WE'RE JUST OFF LIKE A
ROCKET DOWN THE HILL,
UNBELIEVABLE.
LOOK OUT FOR THE ROCK,
AND WATCH IT.
WE'RE LOOKIN' GOOD.
WE'RE LOOKIN' GOOD!
UH-OH.
OH, MAN.
OKAY, GUYS,
I KNOW YOU'RE HURTIN',
BUT HERE'S THE GOOD NEWS...
WE'RE NOW THE
WORLD CHAMPS.
[applause]
HI, EVERYBODY,
RANGER GORD HERE.
YOU KNOW, IN TONIGHT'S
EDUCATIONAL FILM,
WHICH, OF COURSE,
I WROTE AND DIRECTED,
AND WELL, I DID
ALL THE VOICES
AND DREW ALL THE PICTURES,
AND WELL, I CHOREOGRAPHED
MOST OF THE LOVE SCENES.
TONIGHT'S EPISODE IS ALL
ABOUT TEACHING YOU
HOW TO TALK TO THE ANIMALS.
I LIKE TO CALL THIS EPISODE
"RANGER DOOLITTLE,"
WHICH IS, OF COURSE,
JUST A CATCHY NAME
FOR THIS FILM
AND NOT ANY INDICATION OF
WHAT I DO UP HERE
ON A REGULAR BASIS.
REALLY, IT'S NOT.
SO ANYWAY, THAT'S THE END OF
THE INTRODUCTION PORTION
OF THE PRESENTATION.
NOW WE MOVE ON TO NEXT PORTION
OF THE PRESENTATION,
WHICH IS, OF COURSE,
THE MIDDLE PART OF
THE PRESENTATION,
WHICH COMES RIGHT
AFTER THE INTRODUCTION
AND OF COURSE,
JUST BEFORE THE, UH,
ENDING.
HERE WE GO.
[quirky upbeat music]
WELL, FOLKS, TODAY I'M GONNA
SHOW EVERYONE IN OUR
SOLAR SYSTEM
THAT I CAN TALK
TO THE ANIMALS.
THAT'S AWESOME,
RANGER GORD.
YES, IT IS,
HAROLD.
HAVE EITHER OF YOU
EVER TALKED TO ANIMALS?
UH, I HAVEN'T
PERSONALLY, NO.
I SPEAK TO A JACKASS
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
ANIMALS DON'T APPRECIATE
THAT KIND OF HUMOUR.
THIS IS A MOOSE, HAROLD.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
TALKING TO IT?
ALL RIGHT.
HELLO.
UM, MY NAME IS HAROLD.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
I THINK MAYBE YOU'RE
GEING JUST A LITTLE
TOO PERSONAL.
I THINK HAROLD'S IN
REAL TROUBLE HERE.
MOOSE ARE VEGETARIAN.
OONGA! WONGA!
DINGY DINGA.
THANK YOU,
RANGER GORD.
WHAT DID YOU
SAY TO HIM?
I SAID, OONGA WONGA
DINGY DINGA.
OH, UH, AND WHAT
DOES THAT MEAN?
NO IDEA, HAROLD.
JUST BECAUSE I SPEAK MOOSE
DOESN'T MEAN I UNDERSTAND IT.
LET'S GO, HAROLD.
NO, HANG ON
A MINUTE.
LET'S SEE IF I CAN GET
THAT MOOSE BACK HERE
TO APOLOGIZE.
[speaking gibberish]
THAT'S A DUCK.
CLOSE ENOUGH.
TRY TO SAY
SOMETHING TO HIM.
UH, NO THANKS.
OH, COME ON.
YOU CAN DO IT.
UH, NO THANKS, GORD.
I DON'T WANT PEOPLE SEEING ME
TALK TO A DUCK.
YOU'RE A SNOB,
YOU KNOW THAT, RED?
[speaking gibberish]
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL GIVE IT A SHOT HERE.
SO DUCK, HOW WOULD
YOU DESCRIBE RANGER GORD?
QUACK.
[applause]
IF YOUR GROUND
SEEMS UNUSUALLY SOFT,
IF EACH TIME YOU BREATH,
YOU LET OUT A COUGH,
IF THE COWS ROLL THEIR EYES
AND BARF IN THE TROUGH,
YOU BETTER CALL ROTHSCHILD'S
BEFORE THE LID BLOWS OFF.
[horns honking]
Red: YOU KNOW WHAT
REALLY FRIES MY BACON?
WHEN I'M CRUISING
ALONG THE HIGHWAY,
AND CAR AFTER CAR
COMES UP BEHIND ME
AND SWERVES OVER
THE LINE TO PASS.
TO ME IT'S AN INSULT,
LIKE I'M JUST GOIN' SLOW
FOR SPITE OR SOMETHING.
ANYONE WHO KNOWS ME
COULD TELL YOU
I'D GO FASTER IF I COULD.
IF ONLY THERE WAS A WAY TO
STOP THEM FROM PASSING ME.
WELL, THERE IS.
NOW, YOU'RE THINKING I'M MAYBE
GONNA SWITCH TO JET FUEL
OR SUPERCHARGE THE ENGINE
OR MAYBE BUILD SOME KIND
OF A FLAME THROWER
INTO THE BACK OF THE VAN.
AND WHILE THOSE
ARE GREAT IDEAS,
I'M GOING WITH SOMETHING THAT
CAPTURES MY TRADEMARK
CREATIVE SUBTLETY.
I'M GOING TO BUILD A GIANT
BALLPOINT PEN.
NOW, ALL YOU NEED IS ONE
OF THESE SAFETY PILONS.
I FOUND THIS ONE
JUST UP THE ROAD.
[tires screeching to a halt]
[crash]
OKAY, THEN YOU
JUST GET A HARDBALL,
AND YOU DROP THAT IN THERE.
THAT'S THE BALL OF
YOUR BALLPOINT PEN.
YOU'VE ALREADY GOT THE POINT,
WHICH IS TO STOP PEOPLE
FROM PASSING YOU.
OKAY, NOW, TO HOLD
THE BALL IN PLACE
YOU NEED A BIG SPRING.
THIS HERE'S A COIL
SPRING OFF A CAR.
YOU CAN FIND THOSE
BESIDE ANY POTHOLE.
AND THEN TO HOLD THE WHOLE
ASSEMBLY IN PLACE,
YOU WANNA ATTACH
A FEW PAINT CANS,
ONE ON TOP OF THE OTHER.
AND THEN PUNCH A HOLE IN THE
BOTTOM OF EACH ONE.
I'LL EXPLAIN A LITTLE BIT
MORE ABOUT THAT LATER.
ATTACH THEM ALL TOGETHER WITH
THE HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
NOW ALL WE DO IS ADD THE INK,
WHICH IN THIS CASE IS PAINT.
THESE PAINT CANS
ACTUALLY WERE EMPTY,
SO I HAD TO ADD
PAINT TO THEM,
AND IT JUST SO HAPPENS IT'S
EXACTLY THE SAME COLOUR
AS THE STUFF THEY USE TO
PAINT HIGHWAY LINES.
THERE'S A
COINCIDENCE, HUH?
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO SEE IF THE
PEN IS MIGHTIER THAN THE
TAILGATER.
[horns honking]
REMEMBER NOW,
NO PASSING ON THE SOLID LINE.
[horns honking]
WELL, THE MASQUERADE MARATHON
IS OFF AND RUNNING.
WEIRD TO SEE PEOPLE IN ANIMAL
COSTUMES RUNNING THROUGH TOWN.
LOOKS LIKE FIRE DRILL
AT DISNEY WORLD.
ONLY, THEY STARTED OFF
EARLY FOR SOME REASON.
I GUESS THEY TOOK A LOOK AT
THE CONDITION OF THE ATHLETES
AND DECIDED TO ALLOW A LITTLE
MORE TIME FOR IT OR SOMETHING.
HEY, RED, LOOKS LIKE MIKE'S
GONNA WIN THE MARATHON.
YOU NOT IN IT,
DALTON?
OH, NO, NO.
JUST GOT THE BAD BACK.
WELL, YOUR FRONT'S
NO TREAT EITHER.
HOW COME THEY
STARTED EARLY?
OH, BIG AL SHOWED UP.
OH, YEAH, MIKE
STARTED RUNNING,
AND EVERYONE THOUGHT
THE RACE HAD STARTED.
OH, GEEZ, MIKE WAS
REALLY MOTORING.
I DIDN'T THINK HE
COULD RUN IN THAT
MATADOR COSTUME.
OH, NO,
HE DIDN'T.
HE CAME UP WITH A WHOLE
DIFFERENT OUTFIT.
[laughter and applause]
I WON.
[bemused]
CONGRATULATIONS.
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
I FORGOT TO TELL
YOU, MR. GREEN,
I THINK BIG AL MAY
HAVE FOLLOWED ME HERE.
[banging at door]
WHAT'S UP,
MIKE?
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I'M NOT -- I'M NOT --
I'M --
I'M RED GREEN,
AND THIS IS MY --
THIS IS MY --
I'LL SHOW YOU
MY LICENSE.
MY --
MY WALLET'S GONE.
SO MIKE WAS HERE?
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
HE JUST LEFT.
OKAY, IF MY
WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AND WATCH OUT FOR SOME GUY
DRESSED LIKE ME.
HE'S AN EX-CON.
HE'S TRYING TO SUB IN
ON MY CONJUGAL VISIT.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE...
[banging at door]
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Mike as Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT MEN, ALL BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, HAS ANYBODY SEEN
BIG AL'S CAR KEYS?
OH, RIGHT.