"IT'S THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW!"
AND NOW HERE'S A MAN
WHO LOVES THE GREAT OUTDOORS
BECAUSE THERE'S NO DOORKNOBS
TO BANG YOUR HEAD ON,
MY UNCLE,
YOUR HERO
AND HOST,
RED GRE-E-E-N!
(APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU. APPRECIATE IT.
TOOK MY WIFE, BERNICE, OUT LAST
NIGHT FOR AN ANNIVERSARY DINNER.
YEAH, YEAH, I HEARD ALL
ABOUT YOUR KITCHEN FIRE.
WELL, I TRIED TO SURPRISE
BERNICE WITH SOME HOME COOKING,
AND I ALMOST COOKED OUR HOME.
FIRST OF ALL, NEVER
FLAMBE A WHOLE GOAT.
AND, YOU KNOW, I THINK IT'S
THE DARN COOKBOOKS NOW.
THE PRINT IS SO FINE
IN THEM, YOU KNOW?
I THOUGHT FOR SURE IT
SAID 40 OUNCES OF BRANDY.
YOU KNOW, I KNOW NOW YOU NEED A
MUCH BIGGER OVEN TO COOK
AN ENTIRE GOAT LIKE THAT.
IT ENDED UP THE TAIL GOT
HOOKED INTO THE ROTISSERIE
SOCKET THERE.
I WOUND UP WITH A
FLAMING GOAT CARCASS
DOING ABOUT 30 RPM IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE KITCHEN FLOOR.
I GUESS THAT'S WHY
ALL PARTIES END UP
IN THE KITCHEN.
YEAH, BOY, THAT WAS A MESS,
I'LL TELL YOU.
ANYWAY, I DECIDED
THE HECK WITH THAT.
I TOOK BERNICE OUT TO A MOVIE.
WHAT A DISAPPOINTMENT.
THE LAST TIME I WENT, I WENT
TO SEE "CHARIOTS OF FIRE."
NOW, I EXPECTED THAT TO BE
A REMAKE OF "BEN HUR" WITH
FLAME THROWERS.
AND THIS ONE WAS, "WHAT
DINOSAURS WOULD DO IF THEY
WERE AROUND TODAY."
I KNOW. I KNOW
WHAT THEY'D DO.
THEY'D FORM A LODGE AND THEY'D
ALL SIT AROUND AND WONDER WHY
WOMEN DON'T UNDERSTAND THEM.
THAT'S NOT JUST FUNNY,
IT'S WITTY.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT'S
NOT FUNNY ABOUT THAT?
EIGHT BUCKS.
EIGHT BUCKS!
AND THE MOST LIKABLE CHARACTER
IN THE MOVIE WAS MADE
BY A COMPUTER
AND BITES PEOPLE'S HEADS OFF,
HOW DOES THAT HAPPEN?
WELL, IT'S SIMPLE BECAUSE
HOLLYWOOD ONLY CARES
ABOUT YOUNG PEOPLE
BECAUSE WE ACTUALLY
GO TO THE MOVIE.
THE ONLY TIME THEY GET YOUR
EIGHT BUCKS IS WHEN YOU
SET YOUR HOUSE ON FIRE
WITH GOATS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
SOMEBODY NEEDS TO
MAKE A MOVIE FOR
PEOPLE LIKE ME,
AND I'M GOING TO
DO IT MYSELF.
ALL RIGHT.
FORREST GRUMP.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
HERE'S A FEW SCENES
FROM THIS WEEK'S EPISODE.
THAT'S OUR GAME WITH EDGAR.
AND I HAVE A HEAVY-DUTY
CAPPUCCINO/ESSPRESSO
MAKER THERE.
AND HERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
THAT'S REALLY HARD TO DO...
A CLEAN SHOW UNDER A
LOT OF PRESSURE.
WELL, THINGS ARE REALLY STARTING
TO COME TOGETHER FOR MY MOVIE.
NO BLOOD AND GORE,
NO SPECIAL EFFECTS,
NO OBSCENE LANGUAGE
AND NO NUDITY.
Audience:  A-H-H-H!
WELL, NO, NO, NO.
I'VE SEEN THE KIND OF
PEOPLE AROUND HERE;
NUDITY WOULD BE
COUNTERPRODUCTIVE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT,
UNCLE RED?
YOU'RE GOING TO
NEED A SCRIPT,
AND I, MYSELF, HAVE WRITTEN
OVER 38 DIFFERENT SCREENPLAYS.
ALMOST SELLING ONE TO THE
COMMUNITY ACCESS CHANNEL.
ALMOST.
PERHAPS I COULD
WRITE YOUR SCRIPT.
NO, I DON'T NEED
A SCRIPT, HAROLD.
THAT'S WHY I GOT THESE.
I COULD USE ONE OF
THESE FOR MY SCRIPTS.
NO, NO, YOU
CAN'T DO THAT.
YOU HAVE TO, YOU KNOW,
PAY FOR THE RIGHTS
AND STUFF.
OH, NO, I'LL JUST CHANGE THE
STORY A BIT, YOU KNOW.
LOOK AT THIS THING HERE,
FOR INSTANCE.
I'LL TAKE THIS ONE.
OKAY, YOU'VE GOT A
SOUTHERN BELL NAMED
CHARLOTTE O'HARA;
SHE FALLS IN LOVE WITH BRET
RUTLER IN THE CIVIL WAR
AND THEN --
AND NO, NO, ATLANTIS
SINKS INTO THE SEA AND,
SHE MAKES A DRESS OUT
OF A VENETIAN BLIND.
THAT'S "GONE WITH THE WIND,"
AND EVERYBODY IS GOING
TO KNOW IT.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
WE'LL JUST MAKE A STORY
ABOUT OURSELVES...
"THE RED GREEN STORY...
"A LITTLE GUY TRIUMPHING
OVER VERY BIG ODDS."
DON'T YOU MEAN, "THE BIG ODD GUY
TRIUMPHING OVER VERY LITTLE?"
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, I'M JUST
THINKING I'M GOING TO BE
CASTING FOR THE PART
OF HAROLD LATER.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
BE A LITTLE NICER TO ME.
I'VE GOT TO AUDITION
TO PLAY MYSELF?
WHO COULD POSSIBLY PLAY ME?
YOU KNOW,
PORKY LANSFORD?
PORKY LANSFORD LOOKS
NOTHING LIKE ME.
NO, BUT HIS WIFE IS
A DEAD RINGER.
HEY, KIDS, CAN YOU
TURN THE MUSIC UP?
CAN YOU PLAY THAT SONG
A BIT LOUDER?
CAN YOU PUMP UP THE
BASS AND THE TREBLE
AND INCREASE THE
OUTPUT POWER?
HEY, KIDS, CAN YOU
TURN UP THE BOOM BOX?
CAN YOU FIND LOUDER
MUSIC TO PLAY?
BECAUSE I HAVE JUST DONE A
REALLY STUPID THING
AND I'D RATHER NOT HEAR
WHAT MY WIFE HAS TO SAY
IT'S THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
AND THIS WEEK'S GRAND
PRIZE IS A BEAUTY.
OH, YEAH. THIS IS --
YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE THIS.
THIS WEEK'S GRAND PRIZE IS
FOR A PAIR OF BRASS HANDLES
ON THE COFFIN OF YOUR CHOICE
FROM DEMPSEY'S FUNERAL HOME.
DEMPSEY'S, WHERE OUR
MOTTO IS, "GOOD GRIEF."
UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE
30 SECONDS TO GET LOCAL
EXPLOSIVE EXPERT,
THIS FELLOW HERE, Mr. EDGAR
MONTROSE, TO STAY THIS WORD.
EDGAR, YOU'VE GOT
TO COVER YOUR EARS.
EDGAR, YOU HAVE TO
COVER YOUR EARS!
I THINK WE'RE ALL RIGHT.
YOU THINK WE'RE ALL RIGHT?
THE WORD IS UNSAFE.
UNSAFE.
30 SECONDS AND GO.
EDGAR, EDGAR.
I'M ALL EARS, RED.
I KNOW, JUST NO EARDRUMS.
YOU STAND TOO CLOSE
TO AN EXPLOSION THAT'S...
HARD ON YOUR CLOTHING.
IF YOU JUST LEAVE DYNAMITE LYING
AROUND THAT WOULD BE...
HANDY.
LET'S SAY NUTBARS AND LUNATICS
GET AHOLD OF DYNAMITE,
THEN THAT WOULD BE...
TEXAS.
ALL RIGHT, TRY THIS ONE...
YOU'RE JUGGLING
BOTTLES OF NITRO,
YOUR CLOTHES ARE
COVERED IN GAS,
THEN IT'S...
OH, THE WEEKEND.
NO, NO, IT'S --
ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
UNCLE RED.
OKAY, OKAY.
I GOT SEVEN STICKS OF LIT
DYNAMITE IN MY MOUTH,
MY CLOTHES ARE
COVERED IN GAS,
I'M ROARING DOWN THE HIGHWAY
ON THE ROOF OF A CAR,
I WOULD BE...
A COPYCAT!
DON'T BE STEALING
MY PARTY TRICKS, RED.
VERY UNSAFE.
(FRANTIC BELL RINGING)
A LOT OF PEOPLE THESE DAYS ARE
DRINKING THE ESPRESSO COFFEE.
APPARENTLY, THIS IS ENOUGH
TO FILL SOME PEOPLE UP,
BUT NOT LODGE PEOPLE.
THIS IS MORE WHAT
I HAD IN MIND,
IMPRESSO-ESPRESSO.
SO THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A
MAN-SIZED MACHINE
TO MAKE MAN-SIZED ESPRESSO OUT
OF THIS HOT WATER HEATER HERE.
SEE, THE HOT WATER HEATER IS
BUILT TO TAKE LOTS OF WATER
AND LOTS OF PRESSURE,
SORT OF LIKE THE LODGE
ON NICKEL BEER NIGHT.
SEE, THERE, YOU'VE GOT
A SAFETY VALVE, RIGHT?
HEY, IF WE WERE WORRIED ABOUT
SAFETY, WE WOULDN'T BE
DRINKING ESPRESSO.
ALL RIGHT. WE'VE JUST GOT
TO PLUG UP THE BUNGHOLE THERE.
WOW! NO SAFETY VALVE.
GETTIN' A CAFFEINE RUSH ALREADY.
NOW, ALL RIGHT DOWN HERE
IN THIS AREA,
YOU'VE GOT YOUR THERMOSTAT.
IT'S SET ON HIGH, BUT I'M GOING
TO SEE IF I CAN'T JUST COAX THAT
A LITTLE BIT FARTHER.
OH, BABY.
ALL RIGHT.
WHILE THAT'S HEATING UP NOW,
I'LL START WORKING ON
THE FILTER.
WE'VE GOT THAT UNIT SET
FOR NUCLEAR MELTDOWN,
I'M THINKIN' PAPER FILTER
IS NOT GOING TO DO IT.
I'D RATHER GO WITH
A CAR RADIATOR.
IT CAN TAKE THE HEAT
AND THE PRESSURE,
AND I'VE GOT THE BLEEDER VALVE
HERE TO DISPENSE THE COFFEE.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I THINK I'M
GOING TO CALL THAT A
DISPENSING VALVE
BECAUSE WHEN I'M
WORKING ON A PROJECT,
YOU DON'T REALLY WANT
TO HEAR THE WORD "BLEEDER."
NOW, IF YOU LIKE
YOUR MILK STEAMED,
JUST TAKE OUT THE TANK.
THERE'S BOUND TO BE A POT
RIVET ON THERE SOMEWHERE.
OH, YES, SIR,
THAT IS HOT!
ALL RIGHT, OUR WORK
HERE IS DONE.
LET'S HAVE SOME COFFEE.
OH, BOY, YUP.
OH, OH, OH,
ESPRESSO.
OH, YEAH, ALL I NEED NOW IS
JUAN VALDEZ AND HIS DONKEY HERE.
OH, THAT LOOKS GOOD.
NO, I THINK THE DONKEY'S
ALREADY BEEN HERE.
OH, FOR GOD -- I FORGOT
TO PUT THE COFFEE IN.
I FORGOT THE COFFEE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
THE RAD CAP OFF HERE.
SHE'S RUSTED ON A BIT.
OH, HERE SHE COMES.
BOY, GOT A STING TO HER THERE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, YOU COULD USE
THE GOURMET COFFEE ON THIS,
BUT I THINK YOU'LL AGREE WITH
WHAT WE'RE DOING WITH IT,
YOU'RE BETTER OFF TO GO AHEAD
WITH THE CHEAP STUFF.
OKAY, THERE WE GO.
SHOULD BE ALL SET.
AND LET'S HAVE
A LITTLE ESPRESSO.
GOT MY CREAM AND SUGAR.
OH, MAN. WELL, IF THAT ISN'T THE
BEST COFFEE YOU'VE EVER TASTED,
THEN MY NAME IS MUD.
REMEMBER, IF WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
THINK I'M GONNA PAINT
THE SHED BROWN.
I WANNA TALK TO YOU OLDER GUYS
ABOUT YOUR BUSY SCHEDULE.
I'M GUESSING YOU'RE SPENDING
A BIG PART OF YOUR DAY
YELLING AT TEENAGERS TO TURN
THE DARN MUSIC DOWN, HUH?
I BET YOU CAN'T BELIEVE IT, HEY?
BECAUSE 20, 30 YEARS AGO,
YOU REMEMBER, YOU USED
TO LOVE YOUR MUSIC LOUD?
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN YOU CAN'T
STAND THEIR MUSIC THAT LOUD.
AND WHEN YOU REALIZE
YOUR HEARING IS OFF 40%,
IMAGINE HOW LOUD
IT REALLY IS, HUH?
BUT LET'S BE HONEST HERE.
VOLUME IS NOT THE PROBLEM.
YOU LIKE SOME THINGS LOUD...
YOUR CAR EXHAUST, MATLOCK,
YOUNG WOMEN SAYING HOW GOOD
YOU LOOK FOR A MAN WITH
YOUR LIFESTYLE.
THE TRUTH IS, YOU DON'T
LIKE THE NEW MUSIC LOUD
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
LIKE THE MUSIC, PERIOD.
SO STOP YELLING AT
THE KIDS TO TURN IT DOWN.
START YELLING AT THEM
TO TURN THE DARN STUFF OFF!
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(SHOUTING)
I SAID, REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU!
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER!
AUDITIONS, "BEHIND THE BEARD:
THE RED GREEN STORY,"
TAKE 1.
I'M HAROLD GREEN, AND I AM
AUDITIONING FOR THE PART
OF HAROLD GREEN.
NEXT.
I'M DALTON HUMPHREY, AND I AM
AUDITIONING FOR THE PART
OF HAROLD GREEN.
WATCH OUT. THERE'S ANOTHER
WILD BEAR CHARGING YOU.
I'D HELP, BUT I'M A COWARD.
NEXT.
STATE YOUR NAME.
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD, AND I'M
AUDITIONING FOR THE PART
OF RED GREEN.
DON'T WORRY, MA'AM.
SAVING 100 ORPHANS IS
ALL IN A DAY'S WORK FOR ME,
THE BASHFUL BACHELOR
OF POSSUM LAKE --
NEXT.
AND YOU, ORPHANS, REMEMBER
WHEN YOU GROW UP,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
NEXT.
WHAT?
I'M HAP SHAUGNESSY, AND I'M
AUDITIONING FOR THE PART OF RED.
DON'T WORRY.
UH -- THE --  PACK -- OF --
RABBID WOLVES -- ARE DEAD.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN EASIER IF I
HAD SOME KIND OF WEAPON,
BUT WHAT ARE A FEW SCARS
COMPARED TO KNOWING YOU
SAVED A BUSLOAD
OF ORPHANS?
OH, COME ON. THE DIALOGUE
SHOULD BE BELIEVABLE.
IT'S LIKE WHEN I WAS
WITH MERYL STREEP --
NEXT.
HUH? OH, I'M EDGAR MONTROSE,
AND I'M AUDITIONING FOR
THE PART OF BERNICE.
NEXT!
WE'RE AUDITIONING FOR
THE CROWD SCENE.
NEXT.
OH, (BLEEP!)
THIS WEEK ON
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL,"
HE SET UP KIND OF A CHARITY
CARWASH THING,
AND Jr. SINGLETON
HAD LEFT HIS CAR.
THAT WAS THE FIRST ONE
WE WERE GOING TO WASH.
BILL, THERE'S QUITE A FEW --
MAYBE TOO MANY ITEMS IS
WHAT COMES TO MY MIND.
MUST BE GETTING PAID BY
THE HOUR HERE,
RATHER THAN BY THE --
BRINGS ALL THAT STUFF
AND PUTS IT IN THE GARBAGE.
WELL, THAT MAKES A
LOT OF SENSE.
BILL, WHY WOULD YOU --
WHY WOULD YOU --
YEAH, YEAH. WHY WOULD YOU THROW
ALL THAT STUFF IN THE GARBAGE?
OH. OH, MY.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
OH, YEAH, HE'S GOT ONE
OF THOSE POWER --
YOU SEEN THIS THING?
IT'S A POWER SPRAYER.
HE DOESN'T LIKE ADVICE.
HE JUST LIKES TO START
THINGS ON HIS OWN.
GIVE HER A PULL THERE.
GIVE HER ANOTHER ONE.
BILL, AT THIS POINT COULD --
ALL RIGHT.
OH. YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I BELIEVE THAT'S
CALLED NEMESIS.
BILL, THERE'S A LITTLE
ADJUSTMENT ON THE MACHINE,
IT'S CALLED THE "CHOKé."
IT'S A FRENCH WORD.
PUSH THAT AND LOOK AT THAT.
SEE THAT? THERE YOU GO.
YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH. GREAT.
ALL RIGHT, AWAY WE GO.
THESE THINGS CAN PUT UP TO
300, 400 POUNDS OF OF PRESSURE
WHERE IS --
I DON'T --
WHERE IS BILL?
WHERE IS THE SPRAYER?
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHERE IS HE?
BILL? BILL?
OH, HANG ON.
HANG ON.
HANG ON, BILL,
HOLD HER.
OKAY, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, THERE WE GO.
HERE WE GO.
THAT'S A TWO-MAN UNIT,
RIGHT THERE.
AND NOW WE'RE REALLY SPRAYING.
OH, OH, MY GOLLY.
OH, OH.
CAN WE MAYBE TURN
THE PRESSURE--
BILL, BILL, DO YOU THINK --
I THINK MAYBE WE SHOULD --
I THINK WE SHOULD TURN DOWN --
I THINK WE SHOULD TURN --
TURN -- TURN THE --
TURN THE PRESSURE DOWN A BIT.
WELL, WE HAVEN'T JUST
WASHED THIS CAR,
I THINK WE'VE INCREASED
HIS GAS MILEAGE
BECAUSE SHE'S ABOUT
500 POUNDS LIGHTER.
MAYBE CLOSING THE WINDOWS MIGHT
HAVE BEEN A PLAN.
I JUST THOUGHT IT
WAS REALLY CLEAN.
GEE, I HOPE Jr. PAID TO
HAVE THE INSIDE DONE TOO.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW, BILL?
YEAH, YEAH, WE'RE
GOING TO BLUFF.
(APPLAUSE)
COME ON.
YOU'RE THE
RETURNING HERO.
OKAY. WAIT.
WAIT. WAIT.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S GOOD.
LOOK OUT THE
WINDOW NOW.
WAVE GOOD-BYE
TO THE SHERIFF.
ALL RIGHT.
BLOW A KISS TO
THE SHERIFF'S DAUGHTER.
SHOW HER YOUR LOVE.
NO? OKAY, GOOD CALL.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW LOOK AROUND
FOR YOUR UNCLE RED.
HEY, YOU CAN'T SEE HIM.
WHERE IS HE?
YOU REALIZE HE MUST HAVE BEEN
KILLED DURING THE FOOD FIGHT.
YES, EXACTLY.
SUDDENLY YOU'RE
VERY SAD.
PUT YOUR HAT OVER
YOUR HEART.
A COUPLE OF TEARS,
HAROLD, WOULDN'T HURT.
MORE TEARS.
NO, NO.
CRYING,
CRYING.
AND YOU REALIZE, HAROLD,
YOU'VE LOST THE GREATEST
MAN WHOEVER LIVED.
AND CUT.
ALL RIGHT. I THINK
WE'VE GOT ENOUGH.
BEAUTIFUL.
WE'VE GOT ENOUGH?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
GOOD WORK.
THAT WAS GOOD.
IT WAS FINE.
WE DID ENOUGH?
WE ONLY SHOT AN HOUR'S
WORTH OF FILM.
THAT'S ANOTHER
THING, HAROLD.
I THINK THE MOVIES
TODAY ARE WAY TOO LONG.
I MEAN, HAVEN'T THESE
MOVIEMAKERS HEARD OF
KIDNEY STONES FOR GOSH SAKE?
YEAH, BUT YOU LEFT
THE LENS CAP ON FOR
THE FIRST 15 MINUTES.
I WAS JUST ESTABLISHING
THE MOOD, HAROLD.
PLUS I CAN'T
SHOOT ANY MORE
BECAUSE I INVITED A
DISTRIBUTOR TO COME
AND LOOK AT THIS.
YOU INVITED A MOVIE
DISTRIBUTOR UP HERE?
NO, WELL, HE'S AN
AUTO PARTS DISTRIBUTOR,
BUT HE KNOWS
SOME PEOPLE.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW,
THE PART OF THE SHOW WHERE WE
EXPLORE THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY.
(AUDIENCE:)
"I DON'T KNOW."
TRES EXCELLENT.
OKAY, JOINING ME AND UNCLE
RED IN THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW THIS WEEK
IS A MAN WHO'S BEEN IN
THE FOREST FOR OVER
18 YEARS, RANGER GORD.
HI, EVERYONE.
I MISSED YOU.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
OUR FIRST LETTER GOES
AS FOLLOWS:
"DEAR EXPERTS:  MY HUSBAND AND I
LIKE TO GO CAMPING,
"ESPECIALLY SINCE THE RECESSION.
"I NOTICE THAT THE
CAMPGROUNDS --
"I NOTICE THAT THE CAMPGROUNDS
ARE GETTING DESTROYED FROM
THOUGHTLESS CAMPERS
"WHO I HAVE NEVER SEEN
ONCE AT OUR CHURCH.
"WHAT ARE YOUR FEELINGS
ON THIS MATTER?"
ALL RIGHT, WELL, THE
THING WITH GARBAGE IS
YOU DON'T WANT IT ALL
CONCENTRATED IN THE ONE SPOT.
SO WHAT I DO IS I JUST PUT IT
ALL UP ON THE ROOF OF THE VAN,
AND I MAKE SURE I LEAVE MY
CAMPSITE AT NIGHT.
UNCLE RED, THAT'S
THOUGHTLESS.
THAT'S CRIMINAL.
IT'S AN ASSAULT
ON MOTHER NATURE.
OH, I'M JUST TRYING
TO GET EVEN FOR WHAT
SHE DID TO YOU.
NO, RED.
HAROLD IS RIGHT.
FOLKS, WHEN YOU'RE CAMPING,
YOU'RE LIVING IN SOME
ANIMAL'S HOME.
YOU KNOW, IT COULD
BE A SQUIRREL.
IT COULD BE A CHIPMUNK.
YOU KNOW, THEY HAVE
PERSONALITIES AND FEELINGS.
OH, ESPECIALLY THE CHIPMUNK.
ANYWAY, NO, SO YOU CAN'T JUST
DUMP GARBAGE IN THEIR HOME.
OH, AND YOU CAN'T EAT A CHIPMUNK
BECAUSE IT WILL BE MONTHS
BEFORE THE OTHER CHIPMUNKS
WILL FORGIVE YOU.
THAT'S CERTAINLY
GOOD ADVICE.
I KNOW.
YEAH. SO WHEN YOU
LEAVE A CAMPSITE,
YOU HAVE TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU LEAVE IT EXACTLY
THE WAY YOU FOUND IT.
EXACTLY.
YOU KNOW, PICK UP ANY
BOTTLES OR NAPKINS.
IF YOU'VE DROPPED ANY
BREADCRUMBS, PICK THEM ALL UP.
AND, OF COURSE, YOU HAVE TO
DOUSE THE FIRE PROPERLY.
AND AFTER IT'S DOUSED,
YOU PICK UP ALL THE LITTLE
PIECES OF WOOD, YOU PUT
THEM TOGETHER,
YOU FORM THEM INTO A LOG
AND REBUILD THE TREE.
HOW THE HECK DOES
THAT WORK, GORD?
BECAUSE THE LOGS,
MOST OF THEM, ARE BURNED
AWAY AT THAT POINT.
RIGHT. OF COURSE,
YOU HAVE TO USE FILLER,
AND FILLER IS MADE OUT OF PINE
CONES, SPRUCE NEEDLES AND
MUSKRAT MILK.
MORE GOOD ADVICE.
MAYBE NEXT TIME WHEN
RANGER GORD IS HERE,
HE CAN ACTUALLY TELL YOU HOW
TO MILK A MUSKRAT.
WELL, CERTAINLY NOT
ON A FIRST DATE.
YEAH, I'LL NEVER
DO THAT AGAIN.
WHO BRINGS TOMATOES TO
A MOVIE THEATRE?
I WOULDN'T CALL THAT
A MOVIE THEATRE;
THAT WAS A VEGETABLE
BARN, THAT WAS.
JUST BE THANKFUL IT WASN'T
WATERMELON SEASON.
YOU BROUGHT IT
ON YOURSELF.
YOU DID,
YOU DID.
WITH ALL THOSE CREDITS
IN THE MOVIE...
WRITTEN BY RED GREEN,
CONCEIVED BY RED GREEN,
STARRING RED GREEN,
DIRECTED BY RED GREEN,
KEY GRIP... RED GREEN.
GET A GRIP, RED GREEN!
BUT, YOU KNOW -- YOU DIDN'T
EVEN GIVE THAT MOVIE
A CHANCE, HAROLD.
WELL, I KNOW.
I KNOW.
CRITICISM CAN BE HURTFUL.
IT CAN BE, YES.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
YEAH,
YEAH.
YEAH, YEAH.
I'M GLAD I COULD
SNAP YOU OUT OF IT.
AND YOU LEARN SOMETHING
FROM IT SOMETIMES TOO.
YEAH, I LEARNED --
I LEARNED SOMETHING.
I LEARNED YOU DON'T
HAVE TO BE A HOLLYWOOD
HOT SHOT,
SPENDING MILLIONS
OF DOLLARS TO MAKE
A BAD MOVIE.
I CAN DO IT RIGHT HERE
FOR NEXT TO NOTHING.
WELL, MAYBE NEXT TIME
SOMEBODY WANTS TO MAKE
A REALLY BAD MOVIE,
MAYBE THEY'LL CALL YA.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
(POSSUM CALL)
OH, OH, MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
AWAY YOU GO, HAROLD.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETIN',
AND SORRY ABOUT THE
MESS ON MY CLOTHES.
I TRIED TO MAKE A
SPAGHETTI WESTERN,
ENDED UP WITH A FACE FULL
OF TOMATO SAUCE.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING,
AND ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTER]
Harold: EVERYBODY
TAKE THEIR SEAT.
SIT DOWN.
HAVE A SEAT.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
Harold:  OKEY DOKEY, WE JUST
HAVE THE ONE ANNOUNCEMENT
TONIGHT.
IT'S FROM WINSTON ROTHCHILD
OF ROTHCHILD SEWAGE AND SEPTIC
SUCKING SERVICES.
HE WANTS TO REMIND ALL OF US
THAT WITH CORN ON THE COB SEASON
HERE AND THE HIGH TEMPERATURES,
MAKE SURE YOUR HOLDING
TANKS ARE WELL VENTED.
WHY DO I READ THESE?
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
SOMEONE'S GOT TO PROOFREAD
THESE BEFORE I START DOING IT.
BUT IT'S GOOD ADVICE THOUGH,
YOU KNOW.
IT IS A HIGH SEASON,
SO TO SPEAK.