(Car alarm going off)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
IF YOU LOVE THE GREAT OUTDOORS
AND THE BEAUTIFUL WILDERNESS,
WATCH IT ON T.V.,
WITH YOUR HOST, MY UNCLE,
RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
(Whistling)
(Cheering)
(Applause)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIT OF EXCITEMENT AT THE LODGE.
BUSTER HADFIELD'S CAR
HAS BEEN STOLEN.
UNCLE RED, THE CORRECT TERM
IS "REPOSSESSED".
NO, THIS IS AN ACTUAL THEFT.
BUSTER REPORTED IT TO THE COPS.
I BET IT'S NOT
CRIMINAL PURPOSES.
MAYBE IT'S KIDS ON A JOYRIDE.
'79 PACER? I DON'T THINK SO.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): TODAY, I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW TO BURGLAR-PROOF YOUR CAR.
HAROLD'S GONNA DO
SOME WOOD CARVING.
WAY TO GO, YOUNG FELLA.
DALTON TRIES
TO GET ME TO SAY "ART",
WHICH IS A STRETCH.
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW
TO WORK ON YOUR LAWN-MOWER.
THE POLICE ISSUED A BULLETIN
FOR BUSTER'S STOLEN CAR.
LUCKILY, ANYONE DRIVING A PACER
WILL ATTRACT SOME SUSPICION.
NO CAR IS SAFE THESE DAYS.
THEY DEVELOPED
THIS ANTI-THEFT DEVICE
YOU MIGHT BE INTERESTED IN.
IT'S CALLED A DOOR LOCK.
(Audience laughing)
IT'S ON THE DOOR!
(Laughing)
LOCKS ARE A WASTE OF TIME.
YOU LOCK YOUR CAR.
YOU GOTTA FIND A HANGER
TO GET THE KEYS OUT.
NEXT TIME YOU LOCK HER,
YOU NEED ANOTHER HANGER
'CAUSE YOU LOCKED THE FIRST ONE
IN BESIDE THE KEYS.
YOU GOTTA BUY BURGLAR TOOLS
TO BREAK IN TO YOUR CAR.
SOMEWHERE DOWN THE ROAD, YOU
LOCK THE TOOLS IN THE TRUNK.
YOU SEE WHY IT DOESN'T WORK?
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT --
MY FAULT.
I ASSUMED SOME INTELLECT
AND ATTENTION TO DETAIL.
I WAS WAY OFF BASE,
LOST MY HEAD.
(Audience laughing)
(Red): BILL'S GONNA SHOW US
SOME TRICKS WITH HIS BIKE.
DIDN'T LIKE THAT ONE.
WHAT ELSE YOU GOT, BILL?
YOU'RE JUST IRRITATING ME.
OH! OH!
OHHHH!
OH, I LIKE THAT ONE.
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
COME ON OUT, BILL.
DO THAT ONE AGAIN, WOULD YOU?
(Laughing)
THIS IS FOR THE BIG ONE!
TODAY'S PRIZE IS A BUY-ONE,
GET-ONE-FREE GIFT CERTIFICATE
FROM HERBIE DOUGAN'S
HOUSE OF DOORKNOBS.
MR. DALTON, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MY UNCLE TO SAY
THIS WORD.
(Laughing)
THIRTY SECONDS, AND GO.
AN OIL
PAINTING.
TWO COATS WITH
A PRIMER.
SOMETHING YOU BUY
AT AN AUCTION.
BROKEN STOVE.
THINK
FANCY AUCTION.
A WORKING STOVE.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT PICTURES
OF A HORSE AND ANGEL AND NUDES.
CUSTOMIZED VAN.
SOMETHING... SOMETHING
COLLECTABLE,
SOMETHING MORE VALUABLE,
SOMETHING...
OH, OH, OH, HUBCAPS.
YOU'D HANG THIS ON A WALL.
STUFFED BASS?
THEY'RE NICE,
THEY'RE LOVELY.
YOU GO TO
A GALLERY.
THEY HANG THESE ON WALLS
AND PEOPLE LOOK AT IT.
THEY HANG UP!
MOON?
THEY HANG THEM IN GALLERIES,
WITH SCULPTURES, PAINTINGS!
THESE ARE...
OH, THEY'RE
WEIRD,
AND THE
ABSTRACT STUFF--
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
THE KINKERMAN GUY,
HIS FIRST NAME.
BILLY?
NO, HIS BROTHER, THE DRUNK!
OH, THEY'RE BOTH JUICERS.
THE MECHANIC,
THE ONE THAT STOLE!
OH, ART.
(Ringing bell)
(Strums acoustic guitar)
WHEN LIFE HAS GIVEN YOU
A TASTE OF REJECTION
GETTING A DOG
IS AN EXCELLENT SUGGESTION
HE'LL BE YOUR BUDDY,
YOUR SERVANT, YOUR FRIEND
HE'LL BE THERE
WHEN YOU'RE AT THE END
MAKES YOU FEEL BETTER
WHEN YOU'RE OUT OF DOUGH
WHEN YOU'VE DONE ALL YOU CAN
WITH THE LITTLE YOU KNOW
'CAUSE NO MATTER HOW FAR
DOWN LIFE'S LADDER YOU GO
YOUR DOG WILL ALWAYS BE
ONE RUNG BELOW
(Howling)
(Laughing)
WITH CARS GETTING STOLEN
AT THE LODGE,
THOUGHT I'D SHOW YOU HOW
TO MAKE YOUR CAR BURGLAR-PROOF.
YOU'RE THINKING THE BEST WAY
IS TO HAVE A CAR
NOT WORTH STEALING.
THAT DOESN'T ALWAYS WORK.
TO A BURGLAR,
FOURTH-CLASS RIDING
IS BETTER THAN
FIRST-CLASS WALKING.
SO YOU'RE BETTER OFF
WITH A MULTI-STAGE
ANTI-THEFT PROGRAMME.
THE FIRST STAGE
IS THE DOOR HANDLE.
YOU WANT TO
MAKE THAT UNFRIENDLY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I SUGGEST?
WIRE 'ER UP, LIKE I HAVE,
TO THE CIGARETTE LIGHTER.
YOU PLUG THAT IN
AND WITHIN A COUPLE OF MINUTES,
THAT DOOR HANDLE
GETS BLAZING HOT.
THIS NOT ONLY
MAKES THE BURGLAR UPSET,
IT ENABLES THE COPS
TO CATCH HIM RED-HANDED.
OK, FOR THE NEXT STAGE,
YOU WANT TO DISABLE
YOUR STEERING WHEEL SOMEHOW.
GET YOURSELF A CRUTCH.
YOU CAN GET ONE FOR FREE
AT THE WAITING ROOM
AT THE GOUT CLINIC
WHEN NOBODY'S WATCHING.
HOOK THIS UP
TO THE STEERING WHEEL.
(Sizzling)
YOW!
YOU MOUNT THE CRUTCH
SO IT COMES DOWN
BETWEEN THE DRIVER'S LEGS.
WHEN THE BURGLAR DOES
A LEFT-HAND TURN,
HE'LL HAVE TO PULL OVER
FOR MEDICAL ATTENTION.
HERE'S ANOTHER LITTLE FEATURE.
I'VE RUN MY RAD HOSE
UP INSIDE THE CAR.
WHEN I LEAVE THE CAR,
I TAKE THE CAP WITH ME.
WHEN THE BURGLAR
STARTS 'ER UP,
STEAM GOES ALL OVER HIM --
INSTANT SAUNA.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, WE GOT ANOTHER FEATURE
TO SHOW YOU IN A MINUTE.
OK, YOU WANT
TO FIGURE OUT SOME WAY
TO IMPEDE THE ROTATION
OF THE TIRES.
I WOULD THINK ABOUT LETTING
THE AIR OUT,
BUT THAT'S INCONVENIENT,
SO INSTEAD,
WHAT YOU DO IS TAKE A NUT OFF
EACH WHEEL ON ONE SIDE,
BUT NOT JUST ANY NUTS.
MAKE SURE IT'S THE TWO NUTS
CLOSEST TOGETHER --
THE FARTHEST ONE BACK
ON THE FRONT WHEEL,
AND THE FARTHEST ONE FORWARD
ON THE BACK WHEEL.
HERE, I'LL SHOW YOU.
(Cracking)
THAT WAS MY BACK.
ALL RIGHT, THERE WE GO.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED SOME CHAIN,
WHICH YOU CAN PORK OFF
A TOW TRUCK
WHILE THE GUY'S IN THE DOUGHNUT
SHOP WORKING ON HIS WAISTLINE.
SEE HOW I'VE MOUNTED THESE
TO THE NUTS THAT ARE CLOSEST
TO EACH OTHER?
WHEN THE BURGLAR TRIES TO MOVE
THE CAR, THE WHEELS LOCK UP.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO
TO STAGE FIVE -- ANCHORS.
SEE HOW THIS WORKS?
JAM THESE ANCHORS
INTO THE GROUND.
WE'VE ATTACHED ONE
TO THE BACK BUMPER
AND ONE TO THE FRONT BUMPER.
WE'RE READY
FOR THE FINAL STAGE --
NOISE CREATION, MORE OR LESS
A SPECIALTY FOR LODGE MEMBERS.
YOU'LL NEED THIS SPECIAL WIRE
THEY USE
TO RING THE BELL
AT GAS STATIONS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BUY THIS.
MOST STATIONS
LEAVE IT OUT ALL NIGHT,
SO CRUISE BY WITH WIRE CUTTERS,
LET NATURE TAKE ITS COURSE.
STRIP ONE END OF THE WIRES.
CONNECT THESE
TO YOUR HORN RELAY.
MAKE SURE YOU CONNECT
THE RIGHT WIRES
TO THE RIGHT TERMINALS.
NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT THE HORN RELAY.
HERE WE GO.
(Horn honking)
(Shouting): BOY,
THAT IS LOUD, ISN'T IT?
GREAT ACOUSTICS UNDER THERE!
ANYBODY SAY ANYTHING?
NO?
OK!
SPREAD THAT HOSE WHERE
THE BURGLAR WILL STEP ON IT.
THERE'S YOUR ANTI-THEFT CAR.
ISN'T THAT GREAT?
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO PICK
BERNICE UP AN HOUR AGO!
OH! OHHHH!
OH!
THERE YOU GO.
(Laughing)
(Grunting)
(Horn honking)
(Coughing)
STAY TUNED
FOR HAROLD'S HANDICRAFTS.
AND YOU THOUGHT
YOU WERE USELESS.
I THOUGHT "IRONY" WAS
HOW OUR TAPWATER TASTES.
BUSTER HADFIELD
HAD ME CONVINCED
TO GET AN ALARM SYSTEM
INSTALLED IN THE VAN.
HE KNOWS A GUY,
GETS A GOOD PRICE.
I THINK THEY MIGHT BE HOT.
HOT? STOLEN CAR ALARMS?
(Laughing)
YOU WANT A CAR ALARM
THAT CAN BE STOLEN?
THE PRICE WAS RIGHT.
DOESN'T MATTER ANYWAY.
BEFORE I COULD
GET THE THING INSTALLED,
SOMEBODY STOLE THE VAN!
THEY STOLE
THE POSSUM VAN?!
YEAH.
WHY?
YOU KNOW WHAT THE EFFECT
OF A FIVE-BEAN CHILI IS ON YOU.
(Audience laughing)
WE ALL DO.
AND SHE CERTAINLY DOES.
SHE WARNED YOU
AT THE COMPANY PICNIC
THAT IT WOULD BE GOOD
TO STAY AWAY FROM THAT CHILI.
YOU HAD TO SAY,
"NO, RELAX, WOULD YOU?
"IT WON'T HURT
TO TRY A LITTLE."
MAYBE A LITTLE
WOULD HAVE BEEN OK,
BUT YOU HAD TO HAVE
THE THREE BOWLS.
NOW WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
MMM!
IF YOU HAD ANY MORE GAS IN YOU,
YOU'D BE FLOATING AROUND
WITH A STRING TIED TO YOUR TOE.
(Laughing and applause)
AND SHE GETS TO SAY,
"I TOLD YOU SO,"
OR SHE WILL,
ONCE THE TROUBLE STARTS.
DON'T TAKE THE OFFENSIVE.
TAKE THE DEFENSIVE.
BUY YOURSELF A DOG.
STAND RIGHT NEXT TO HIM.
HE'LL COVER FOR YOU.
(Laughing and applause)
IF THINGS GET REAL BAD,
BRING IN A PACK OF STRAYS
FOR A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
YEAH, OR A TRIP TO THE ZOO
IS GOOD COVER.
THE ZOO, THE ZOO.
RECENT RESEARCH HAS PROVEN
THAT THE BIGGER AND UGLIER
THE ANIMAL,
THE MORE YOU CAN GET AWAY WITH.
THIS IS VERY GOOD ADVICE.
WE KNOW WHAT
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
WE KNOW THE SCORE.
YEAH, WE KNOW
WHICH WAY THE WIND'S BLOWING.
ATTENTION, HANDYMEN.
THIS IS A FINISHING NAIL.
THIS IS A CONCRETE NAIL.
THIS IS A THUMBNAIL.
DON'T EVER CONFUSE THEM.
WELCOME TO HAROLD GREEN'S
HANDICRAFTS,
WHERE CRAFTY HANDS
MAKE HANDICRAFTS!
(Laughing)
TODAY I'M GONNA BE MAKING
A DECORATIVE DECOY.
AAHHH!
NOW, STEP ONE, AS ALWAYS,
IS THE FIRST THING YOU DO,
SO I SUGGEST THAT YOU GET
A PIECE OF WOOD
THAT'S MUCH LARGER
THAN THE ACTUAL DECOY
THAT YOU WANT TO MAKE.
(Grunting)
(Audience laughing)
OK, THIS IS STEP ONE.
(Laughing and applause)
(Laughing nervously)
NEXT WEEK, I'LL SHOW YOU HOW
TO MAKE A STRONGER WORK BENCH.
IN THE MEANTIME,
LET'S GET CARVING.
TO DO THAT,
WE NEED A POCKET KNIFE.
THE POCKET KNIFE IS A, UH...
IT'S A KNIFE, AND, UH...
I KNEW WHERE IT WAS
BECAUSE A POCKET KNIFE IS
THE INSTRUMENT OF--
WELL, SEE, THERE YOU ARE.
HENCE THE TERM "POCKET KNIFE".
(Laughing)
ALL RIGHT, SO
ONCE YOU GET THIS OPEN,
THE BLADE WILL DETERMINE
THE STROKE THAT--
THE BLADE WOULD COME OUT
AND THAT'S WHEN
YOU REALLY GET AT IT,
WHEN THE BLADE'S OUT.
THAT'S WHEN
THE WHITTLING BEGINS,
I'LL TELL YA, WHEN THE--
THAT'S-- THAT--
UNCLE RED!
(Laughing nervously)
EXCELLENT.
(Applause)
OK, SO YOU HAVE TO DETERMINE
IS IT SHARP?
OH, IF TREES COULD CRY.
ALL RIGHT, NOW...
(Audience laughing)
YOU GOTTA--
(Grunting)
OH!
ALWAYS REMEMBER,
ALWAYS REMEMBER --
THIS IS THE IMPORTANT THING.
CUT WITH THE GRAIN.
(Audience laughing)
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT -- VOILA!
THAT WASN'T SO TOUGH, WAS IT?
OK, NOW WE'RE GONNA PAINT IT.
WE'RE GONNA MAKE IT
EVEN MORE LOOK LIKE A DUCK.
SO I'M GONNA USE
THIS ORANGE HERE.
I'M GONNA USE ORANGE.
AND THEN YOU CONTINUE
TO PAINT IT
IN A DUCK-LIKE FASHION.
(Audience laughing)
THERE YOU HAVE IT!
A BEAUTIFUL DECOY DUCK,
AND YOU MADE IT YOURSELF.
THAT'S THE BEST PART.
CAN'T YOU JUST HEAR IT QUACK?
(Red):
WE SURE CAN!
THE POSSUM VAN
IS STILL MISSING.
THE COPS FOUND BUSTER'S PACER
IN THE RAVINE,
THE INSIDE TOTALLY GUTTED,
JUST TORN TO SHREDS.
THE COPS FIGURED
IT WAS SENSELESS VANDALISM
BUT BUSTER SAID
IT WAS LIKE THAT BEFORE.
HAROLD, HE SHOULD GET
HIS DOG'S TOENAILS CLIPPED.
OR GET THAT MUTT
TO STOP LINE-DANCING.
SO NO WORD ON
THE POSSUM VAN, HUH?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO GO OUT
AND GET YOURSELF A NEW ONE.
NO, I DON'T
WANT A NEW VAN.
I WANT
MY OLD VAN.
I LOVE
THAT VAN.
NEW VANS ARE GREAT, TOO.
THEY DON'T SMELL
LIKE A WET GOAT.
NO, HAROLD,
MY VAN IS A CLASSIC.
MADE VANS BETTER
BACK IN THOSE DAYS.
YOU KNOW, THE OLD-FASHIONED
WORKMANSHIP...
CRAFTSPEOPLE TOOK PRIDE
IN THEIR WORK.
1985 -- THE GOLDEN AGE
OF AUTOMOBILES, WAS IT?
BESIDES, TODAY, ALL THEY GOT
IS THOSE MINIVANS.
MEN ARE NOT COMFORTABLE
IF ANYTHING'S GOT
THE WORD "MINI" IN IT.
WELL, HOW ABOUT
MINISKIRTS?
WELL, NOW, TO MY GENERATION,
THOSE ARE FOR WOMEN, HAROLD.
MINISKIRT, MINIVAN,
MINNIE MOUSE...
THERE'S NOT AN OUNCE
OF TESTOSTERONE IN THE BUNCH.
IN HONOUR OF ME LOSING MY VAN,
BILL BROUGHT OVER A UNICYCLE.
NO, THAT'S TOO HARD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
BILL SEEMS TO STORE EVERYTHING
HE DOESN'T USE IN HIS PANTS.
THAT'S AMAZING --
HOW DID HE DO THAT?
HE'S GOT SOMETHING ELSE.
MY GOSH, WHAT IS THAT?
SOME MEDICAL PIECE OF EQUIPMENT
OF SOME KIND?
WHAT IS IT?
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES!
WELL, MUST BE SOME KIND
OF SPECIAL MATERIAL.
YES, ANYWAY, IT'S--
OK, YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
I GET THE IDEA, BILL.
BICYCLE BUILT FOR TWO,
HALF THE PEDALLING.
THE ONLY THING
I DON'T LIKE IS -- OW --
BILL'S GOT THE BRAKES
AND STEERING.
ALL I GOTTA DO--
OK, AWAY WE GO.
THE THING--
YEAH, THAT'S THE HORN.
WHAT I DIDN'T REALIZE IS THAT
IF YOU DON'T--
BILL, WE'RE PEDALLING
BACKWARDS.
BILL, WE GOT OFF ON THE--
OH, OH, OH!
BY GOLLY, NOW,
AT LEAST I--
LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT!
OK, FINE.
I'M THINKING I DON'T HAVE
CONTROL OVER ANYTHING,
ESPECIALLY BILL.
THEN I REALIZE I'VE GOT
A BACK-PEDAL BRAKE.
OH, BOY, UP SHE COMES!
OH, DOWN SHE GOES!
BILL'S GOT THE BALANCE
FROM HIS UNICYCLE DAYS.
LOOK AT THAT.
LOOK AT THAT SHOW-OFF.
THAT'S AN ODD THING.
YOU PRAY FOR A LOW BRIDGE.
THERE'S A ROCK THERE, BILL!
LOOK OUT!
YOU ALL RIGHT, BILL?
HONK IF YOU LOVE FUN.
(Laughing)
OH, YOU'RE FINE.
STAY TUNED --
HAROLD HAS GOOD NEWS!
OH, MAN.
LOOKED AT THEM NEW VANS.
COUPLE OF THOSE BABIES
ARE PRETTY SHARP.
THEY LOANED ME ONE
TO USE FOR A DAY.
YEAH, IT REALLY DOES
LOOK SHARP.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I-I-IT'S NOT
VERY BIG, THOUGH.
OH, IT'S BIG ENOUGH --
SEVEN-PASSENGER.
OH, YEAH,
BUT I MEAN,
FROM THE OUTSIDE,
IT'S NOT VERY BIG.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE, UH...
A MINIVAN.
IF A PERSON SAW IT,
THEY'D THINK IT'S A... MINIVAN.
NO.
IF THEY SAW IT, THEY'D ASSUME
YOU WERE THINKING OF PURCHASING
A... MINIVAN.
I DISTINCTLY REMEMBER YOU SAYING
THAT MINIVANS ARE FOR WOMEN.
IS THAT A MINIVAN?
(Audience laughing)
WELL, TECHNICALLY, YES,
IT IS TECHNICALLY A MINIVAN.
OHHHHH!
BUT, HAROLD, TECHNICALLY,
YOU'RE A HUMAN BEING
SO THERE'S A LOT OF LEEWAY
WITH TECHNICAL DEFINITIONS.
ALL RIGHT, GET BALANCED.
KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN.
SLOWLY ON THE BACK SWING.
KEEP THE LEFT ARM STRAIGHT.
STOP AT THE VERY TOP,
AND ACCELERATE
AS YOU COME THROUGH
AND MAKE CONTACT.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERTS PORTION.
THIS WEEK'S EXPERTS
IS MY UNCLE RED
AND HIS GOOD FRIEND
MR. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD.
(Applause and cheering)
OK, FIRST LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS:
"DEAR EXPERTS...
"MY SON HAS DECIDED HE DOESN'T
WANT TO FOLLOW IN MY FOOTSTEPS.
"I WANT HIM TO JOIN
THE FAMILY BUSINESS,
"BUT HE HAS OTHER IDEAS.
"WHAT CAN I DO?"
WAHHHH!
I GUESS YOU HAVE TO START
LIVING WITH THE FACT
YOUR SON HAS HIS OWN LIFE.
WELL, THAT'S
NO KIND
OF ADVICE, HAROLD.
A MAN'S PAYING A COMPLIMENT
TO HIS SON,
INVITING HIM
INTO THE FAMILY BUSINESS.
THIS IS A SHOW OF FATHERLY LOVE
WE'RE LOOKING AT.
AM I RIGHT, WINSTON?
YEAH, OF ALL THE TIMES
I WISHED MY OLD MAN
HAD BROUGHT ME INTO HIS FAMILY
BUSINESS, INSTEAD OF
GETTING ME TO BRING HIM
ASHTRAYS AND BOTTLE OPENERS
AND GOING TO ANSWER
THE FRONT DOOR
AND TELLING THE COPS
HE WASN'T THERE.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING.
IF MY SON ASKED TO BE
IN THE FAMILY BUSINESS,
I'D DO ANYTHING
TO GET HIM IN THERE.
I'D MAKE FUN
OF EVERYTHING ELSE HE DID.
I'D CUT HIM OUT OF THE WILL
AND THREATEN HIM
AND SLASH HIS TIRES
IF HE DIDN'T COME
INTO THE BUSINESS.
IN A FRIENDLY WAY,
MAKE HIM TOE THE LINE.
WELL, I COMPLETELY DISAGREE.
WAHHH!
(Audience laughing)
I MEAN, IF YOU ASK ME,
I WOULD DISAGREE.
I THINK THE SON
SHOULD LEAD HIS OWN LIFE,
LIKE MR. ROTHSCHILD DOES.
WELL,
I GOTTA ADMIT,
I GOT NO REGRETS, EH?
SURE, I FLOUNDERED AROUND THERE
FOR A WHILE,
HAD MY SHARE OF FAILURES.
AT ONE POINT, I WANTED
TO BE A BANK PRESIDENT,
THEN A SUPREME COURT JUDGE,
AND THEN I JUST DOVE
INTO THE SEWAGE BUSINESS
AND I'VE BEEN
UP TO MY EYEBROWS EVER SINCE.
(Audience laughing)
IT WAS A BIT DISAPPOINTING
THAT THE OLD MAN
NEVER ASKED ME.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING.
IF I HAD A KID,
HE'D BE MORE THAN WELCOME
TO JOIN ME
IN MY FAMILY BUSINESS.
HE MIGHT NOT BE INTERESTED
IN STARTING AT THE BOTTOM.
WHATEVER -- I THINK
THE POINT HERE IS
THAT SOME SONS JUST, YOU KNOW,
DON'T MEASURE UP
TO THEIR FATHERS.
SOMETIMES THE SON IS FIVE TIMES
THE MAN HIS FATHER IS.
YEAH, YOURS
WILL BE.
(Laughing and applause)
HAROLD?
ALL RIGHT, HE'S NOT HERE,
BUT KIND OF MADE UP MY MIND
THAT I'M GONNA GO AHEAD
WITH THIS NEW VAN.
SOMETHING ABOUT THE SMELL
OF A NEW VEHICLE, THERE,
AND BOY, THE CONTROLS
ARE SOMETHING ELSE.
THIS THING'S GOT
MORE ADJUSTMENTS
ON THE WINDSHIELD WIPER CONTROL
THAN THE POSSUM VAN HAD
ON THE WHOLE DASHBOARD.
EVEN JUST TO HAVE THE CARPETING
ALL THE ONE COLOUR, YOU KNOW?
IT'S A CRIME THAT
THE POSSUM VAN WAS STOLEN,
BUT LIFE GOES ON,
SO I'LL DUCK OUT EARLY,
GET DOWN TO THE DEALERSHIP
AND I THINK I'M--
UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED!
UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED,
UNCLE RED!
UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED!
UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED,
UNCLE RED!
WHAT?
THEY FOUND THE POSSUM VAN!
WAHHHH!
ISN'T THAT
GREAT?
YEAH, IT'S GOOD, YEAH.
IT WASN'T EVEN STOLEN,
WASN'T EVEN STOLEN.
IT WAS BUSTER HADFIELD.
HIS FRIEND WAS GONNA SELL YOU
THE CAR ALARM SYSTEM.
BUSTER BORROWED THE VAN
AND HE'S GONNA HAVE THE SYSTEM
PUT IN AS A SURPRISE.
YOU LOVE THAT VAN.
IT'S BACK!
YEAH, NO, YEAH, OH, YEAH, NO.
HAROLD, I'M THINKING
THE SAFETY'S NOT UP TO SNUFF.
THE NEW VANS, THEY GOT
THE DRIVER'S-SIDE AIRBAG
AND THE A.B.S. BRAKING SYSTEM.
THE GUY WHO NEVER WEARS
A SEATBELT IS MR. SAFETY?
IT'S NOT JUST THE SAFETY.
THE NEW VANS HAVE
AIR CONDITIONING
AND THE SEEK-CONTROL BUTTON
ON THE RADIO
AND COFFEE-MUG HOLDERS.
WE'RE INTO A NEW AGE
OF TECHNOLOGY.
BUT YOU LOVE
THE POSSUM VAN.
YEAH, BUT IT'S A PIECE OF CRAP,
BASICALLY.
YOU SAID IT'S A CLASSIC.
IT'S GOT A V-8 ENGINE,
LOTS OF CARGO SPACE,
STILL RUNS PRETTY WELL.
IT'S A GOOD, SOLID VAN.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO BUY IT?
NO.
(Laughing)
(Possum squeal)
IT'S MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
(Laughing)
THINK IT OVER.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I'VE BEEN DOING
A LITTLE THINKING LATELY
ABOUT HOW YOU KIND OF GET
THE SHORT END OF THE STICK.
I'M THINKING HOW MUCH EASIER
YOUR LIFE WOULD BE
IF YOU HAD A BRAND-NEW VAN.
I'M GONNA BE BRINGING ONE HOME
TONIGHT,
BUT I ALSO KNOW HOW NERVOUS
YOU GET WHEN YOU'RE DRIVING,
SO I'M THINKING MAYBE
WHY DON'T YOU DRIVE
THE POSSUM VAN FOR A WHILE,
AND I'LL DRIVE THE NEW MINIVAN,
JUST FOR A LITTLE BIT...
TILL IT'S PAID FOR.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
OH, HURRY UP!
HEY, STAND UP,
STAND UP!
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
SIT DOWN, BOYS.