ONE OF THE BIG DISADVANTAGES
OF HAVING A CAR WITH ALL
THE FANCY EXTRA FEATURES IS...
YOU'VE GOTTA PAY FOR 'EM.
BUT, MOST OF THEM CAN BE FAKED.
FOR EXAMPLE: "THE KEYLESS,
REMOTE DOOR ENTRY SYSTEM."
JUST GET YOURSELF
A PAIR OF PRUNING SHEARS
AND JUST SNIP THAT THING OFF,
SO IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S
DOWN ALL THE TIME.
THEN, GET YOURSELF
A CHILD'S SQUEAKY TOY.
NOW, YOU CAN FAKE BEING RICH.
WELL, MOST PEOPLE GOT
RICH FAKING SOMETHING.
[squeak, squeak]
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW.
AND NOW, HERE'S THE MAN
WHO CAN APPRECIATE JAZZ
IF IT WAS JUST A BIT
MORE REPETITIVE.
YOUR HOST AND HERO
AND MY UNCLE:
RED GREEN!!!
[applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
IT'S VERY, VERY SPECIAL DAY
FOR A CERTAIN SOMEBODY UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
WHAT, WHO ME?
WHAT, I DIDN'T
TOUCH ANYTHING
AND IF I DID
I PUT IT BACK.
NO, HAROLD.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
"THE BIG MOVE."
DON'T YOU HAVE
A BIG MOVE TODAY?
OH, YEAH.
THIS GUY RIGHT HERE,
BLOOD RELATIVE OF MINE,
FULL FLEDGED MEMBER
OF THE GREEN FAMILY.
I'D SHOW YOU THE CREST,
BUT SOME OF THE IMAGES ARE NOT
SUITABLE FOR FAMILY VIEWING.
THIS GUY, HAROLD GREE,
HAS BEEN ACCEPTED
INTO COLLEGE.
CONGRATULATIONS, HAROLD.
[applause]
HE SHOOK MY HAND!
I DON'T THINK YOU'VE
SHOOK MY HAND BEFORE.
NO, THAT'S A HANDSHAKE
I WOULD REMEMBER, HAROLD.
SO, I GUESS YOU'RE
WORRIED ABOUT MOVING
INTO YOUR DORM?
I'M MOVING INTO A HOUSE
WITH THREE OTHER STUDENTS.
WELL, I GUESS YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED SOME WAY OF GETTING
YOUR STUFF DOWN THERE?
YEAH.
DON'T WORRY, HAROLD.
I'LL BE GLAD TO TAKE YOU
AND ALL YOUR STUFF IN
THE POSSUM VAN.
WHAT THE HECK,
I'M YOUR UNCLE,
FOR GOSH SAKES.
YOU'RE GOING TO MOVE ME AND
ALL MY STUFF INTO THE CITY
IN THE POSSUM VAN?
IN BROAD DAYLIGHT?
YEAH, SURE.
IT'S TIME TO PLAY
"THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME."
AND THIS WEEK OUR FRIEND
RANGER GORD IS PLAYING FOR
A BRAND NEW SET OF DUMBBELLS.
SET OF DUMB BELLS,
WE'VE GOT THEM.
THERE'S TWO DUMB BELLS.
OOPS!!!
THEY'RE THERE,
YOU CAN SEE THEM.
UNCLE RED...
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET RANGER GORD
TO SAY THIS WORD:
OKAY, GO!
CABBAGE.
WHAT?
UH... LETTUCE,
I MEAN GROCERIES!
I HAVEN'T GIVEN YOU
ANY CLUES YET, GORD.
YOU MEAN, IT'S NOT
LETTUCE OR GROCERIES?
DARN, I THOUGHT
I HAD IT THERE.
OKAY, ANDROID.
YOU BETTER GIVE HIM
A CLUE, UNCLE RED.
SOMEBODY BETTER
GIVE HIM A CLUE.
I COULD USE
A QUICK BREAK.
I NEED TO THINK.
IT'S A SHORT GAME,
ONLY THIRTY SECONDS.
ONLY 15 LEFT, NOW.
COME ON GORD,
THIS WORD'S EASY.
COUCH.
I MEAN, THAT'S A REAL
EASY WORD, YOU KNOW?
THERE'S NO WEIRD
PRONUNCIATION RULES
OR SPELLING THINGS.
IT'S EASY: COUCH.
GORD, YOU CAN'T JUST
SAY WORDS AT RANDOM.
SPAGETTI.
FLORIDA?
WAIT 'TIL I GIVE YA
A CLUE AND THEN
YOU SAY IT.
ANDROID... COOKIE.
GORD, DO YOU KNOW
HOW MANY WORDS THERE ARE
IN THE ENGLISH LANGUAGE?
I KNOW... NOSTRIL.
[ring, ring, ring]
FIRE, FIRE!!!
I'M SORRY IT TURNED
OUT THAT WAY, HAROLD.
THOSE COLLEGE BOYS
POINTING AND LAUGHING
AT YOU LIKE THAT.
ME?
THEY WERE LAUGHING
AT THE POSSUM VAN.
NOW, WHY WOULD
THEY DO THAT?
IT'S A POSSUM VAN.
I GOT TO TELL YA
SOMETHING FOLKS,
THE WHOLE TIME
THAT WE'RE MOVING
HIS JUNK IN THERE,
THERE'S THESE THREE
GIRLS IN THERE.
I GUESS YOUR ROOMMATES
HAVE GIRLFRIENDS, HUH?
OH, NO!
THOSE THREE GIRLS
ARE MY ROOMMATES.
PARDON ME, HAROLD?
YOU GOT THREE GIRLS
AS YOUR ROOMMATES?
HOW DOES THAT WORK?
PRETTY WELL.
NO, I DON'T WANT YOU
LIVING IN SIN THERE.
NO, NO, NO, THERE'S NO SIN.
EXCEPT, MAYBE THE CABLE HOOK UP.
I SHOULD GET BACK BECAUSE...
HAROLD, LIVING
WITH THREE GIRLS.
YOU'RE GOING TO
GO CRAZY THERE.
NO, UNCLE RED, NO.
THERE'S NO SWEAT,
NO PROBLEM.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S MODERN TIMES,
UNCLE RED, C'MON.
STUDENTS ARE DOING
THIS ALL THE TIME.
I'M VERY CASUAL WITH IT.
WELL, YOU KNOW...
I TELL YA SOMETHING,
HE'S LOT COOLER THAN
I THOUGHT HE WAS.
[laughter and applause ]
IF YOU TIE A STRING
TO YOUR FINGER
TO REMEMBER WHAT
MIGHT BE FORGOT
IT'S A LITTLE TRICK
THAT I LIKE TO CALL
A HANDYMAN'S
FORGET-ME-NOT KNOT
JUST MAKE SURE
IT'S A BIT OF A SLIP KNOT
THAT WILL FALL OFF
AS THE WEEK GOES BY
OTHERWISE YOU'LL SIT THERE
WITH A STRING ON YOUR FINGER
AND NEVER REMEMBER WHY
SAW A SHOW ON THE SPACE
PROGRAM LAST NIGHT.
APPARENTLY, DOGS WERE
IN SPACE BEFORE HUMANS.
OH YEAH, WAY BACK WHEN,
THE RUSSIANS FIRED A DOG
INTO A LITTLE CAPSULE AND
LAUNCHED HIM OFF INTO ORBIT.
I BET EVERYTHING WENT FINE
'TIL HE STUCK HIS HEAD
OUT THE HATCH
TO FEEL THE BREEZE ON HIS FACE.
DOGS LOVE HANGING OUT
OF MOVING VEHICLES, DON'T THEY?
SO, THIS WEEK, ON
"THE HANDYMAN CORNER,"
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A KIND
OF BABY SITTER FOR YOUR DOG.
A MECHANICAL THING,
A KIND OF "PUPPY-GO-ROUND."
THE FIRST THING WE NEED
IS A CAR WINDOW.
AND, OF COURSE, TO DO THAT,
WE HAVE TO FIND A CAR WINDOW.
WELL, HERE'S ONE HERE.
THIS CAR JUST SEEMS
TO BE SITTING HERE.
NOBODY AROUND.
I WONDER IF IT'S OPEN.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO NEED...
A HAMMER AND A CHISEL.
[bang, bang, squish]
ALL RIGHT, GOING TO NEED
A SLEDGEHAMMER, I GUESS.
[glass smashing]
WELL, I LOOSENED 'ER.
THE PRY BAR.
[metal squeaking]
[red grunting]
[snap!]
[metal squeaking]
[banging and crashing
of metal on metal]
NO, NO, I NEED ONE OF THOSE
BIG ORANGE COLOURED THINGS.
[laughter]
[glass breaking]
[metal tearing]
[glass shattering]
OH, MAN!
LIKE I SAID:
GET YOURSELF A CAR DOOR.
[ Laughter and applause]
NOW, WE NEED SOMETHING TO
USE AS A MERRY-GO-ROUND
AND I'M THINKING, YOU'RE NOT
GOING ICE FISHING FOR AWHILE,
SO, WHY DON'T WE USE
OUR POWER AUGER, HUH?
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED SOMETHING
FOR THE DOG TO RIDE AROUND IN.
HOW ABOUT A GYMBAG?
HERE WE GO, GYMBAG.
WE CAN MAKE IT A "DOGGY BAG."
[auger motor running]
[crash!]
NOW, WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS
MOUNT THE AUGER OVER THERE.
THIS BECOMES YOUR
MERRY-GO-ROUND, SEE?
THAT'S WHY I PICKED HARD GROUND,
TO GET IT JAMMED UP INTO A ROCK.
IT'S PERFECT.
NOW, ALL WE GOT TO DO
IS JUST ADD OUR DOOR
AND OUR "DOGGY BAG."
WE'VE GOT OUR POOCH POUCH THERE
AND WE'VE GOT THE DOOR ON THERE.
AND I'VE GOT THE COUNTERWEIGHT.
SHE'S ALL PERFECTLY BALANCED.
ALL WE NEED IS THE DOG.
C'MON PRINCE, COME ON BOY.
HERE, PRINCE.
NO, PRINCE, HERE, COME HERE.
COME.
HERE, HERE.
I GUESS PRINCE REMEMBERED
WHERE HE LIVED.
SO, NOW, HE'S THE DOG
FORMERLY KNOWN AS PRINCE.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT,
I GOT AN IDEA.
JUST USE THIS UNIT HERE.
THIS IS JUST LIKE A DOG.
IRISH SETTER, HUH?
ALL RIGHT, GOOD BOY.
STAY, STAY, SIT, SIT,
PLAY NICE, PLAY NICE.
GOOD BOY, GOOD BOY,
GOOD BOY, GOOD BOY.
THERE'LL BE A TREAT
FOR YOU LATER.
ALL WE GOT TO DO NOW IS START
'ER UP AND GIVE HIM A RIDE.
SO, REMEMBER...
"IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,"
"THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY."
[motor running]
[smash!]
I WANT TO TAKE A MINUTE AND TALK
TO SOME OF YOU MIDDLE AGED GUYS.
YOU KNOW, I READ SOMEWHERE
THAT PEOPLE TAKE LONGER TO
GET OUT OF THEIR PARKING SPACE
IF THEY KNOW THERE'S SOMEONE
THERE THAT WANTS THE SPACE.
NOW, IF YOU'RE LIKE ME,
AND I KNOW YOU ARE,
THEN, THIS IS NO BIG SURPRISE.
WE'VE ALL BEEN THERE,
HAVEN'T WE?
COMING OUT OF YOUR
PARKING SPACE,
YOU LOOK IN YOUR
REARVIEW MIRROR
AND THERE'S SOME DORK
WAITING FOR YOUR SPOT.
YOU JUST GET ANGRY,
JUST LIKE THAT,
FOR NO REASON AT ALL, REALLY.
AND YOU THINK: I'M GOING TO TAKE
MY OWN, SWEET TIME ON THIS.
MAYBE, POLISH THE HORN.
REFOLD ALL THE ROADMAPS
THE RIGHT WAY.
THE SCIENTISTS SAY THAT
THIS IS A HOLDOVER
FROM THE EVOLUTIONARY DAYS
OF THE OLD CAVEMAN, THERE.
WHERE THEY WOULD PROTECT
THEIR TERRITORY.
THINGS HAVE GOTTEN SO PITIFUL
THAT OUR TERRITORY NOW,
COMES DOWN TO TWO PARALLEL LINES
ON THE ASPHALT IN FRONT
OF THE 7-11.
SO, IT'S AN
EVOLUTIONARY PROBLEM.
SO THAT GUY, THE OTHER DRIVER,
IS JUST GOING TO HAVE TO WAIT
FOR US TO EVOLVE A LITTLE
AND BOY, THAT COULD
TAKE A WHILE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YA.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, HAROLD'S BEEN
AT COLLEGE A WHOLE WEEK
AND HE DIDN'T CALL ME
TO COME AND GET HIM,
SO, I GUESS HE'S ADJUSTED TO
HAVING ALL THOSE WOMEN AROUND.
I KNOW HE WENT FOR AN EDUCATION,
BUT I BET HE'S GETTING MORE
THAN HE BARGAINED FOR.
[laughter and applause]
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU LOOK LIKE?
YOU LOOK LIKE THE GUY FROM
SATURDAY NIGHT FAVOUR.
FEVER - SATURDAY NIGHT FEVER.
WITH YOU, IT WOULD BE
A FAVOUR, I'M THINKING.
HOW'S IT GOING WITH
YOUR NEW ROOMMATES?
OH, GOOD, YEAH.
THEY SAID I'M NOT LIKE
ANY OTHER GUY THEY'VE
EVER MET.
THEY SAY, THEY FIND
ME NON-THREATENING.
SO, IT DOESN'T BOTHER YOU
THEY SIT AROUND WEARING
THEIR PYJAMAS, HAROLD,
OR HAVE THEIR
FRIENDS OVER,
OR BRUSH THEIR HAIR
IN FRONT OF THE MIRROR?
BRUSH THEIR HAIR,
HA! HA! HA!
I CAN'T EVEN SLEEP!!!
I'M GOING CRAZY!!!
THEY GOT CURVES,
UNCLE RED.
THEY TALK TO ME
WITH THEIR VOICES.
[ Hysterically]
I GET NO WORK DONE.
I CAN'T DO THE WORK.
THEY WALK AROUND
WITH THEIR LEGS.
UNCLE RED, YOU KNOW
WHEN THEY WALK?
THEIR LEGS MOVE.
HAROLD, COME ON OUTSIDE,
THE LAKE IS REALLY COLD.
OH GOOD!
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
IT'S NEW MEMBER NIGHT
AND ARNIE DOGAN,
THE LOCAL ROOFER,
HAS BROUGHT A FELLOW
HE'D LIKE TO PROPOSE.
LOOKS LIKE THIS GUY IS
A FEW SHINGLES SHORT
OF A DORMER TO ME.
TAKE 'ER AWAY, ARNIE.
THANKS, RED.
I'D LIKE TO PRESENT,
FOR YOUR CONSIDERATION,
A FELLOW WHO'S BEEN
WORKING WITH ME IN
THE ROOFING BUSINESS:
LOONIE.
ACTUALLY, IT'S
HECTOR SAMUELSON.
WE JUST CALL HIM LOONIE
BECAUSE HE FALLS SO FAST.
[laughter]
NOW, LOONIE'S GOT
MANY GOOD POINTS.
HE'S NOT AFRAID
OF ANYTHING
AND HE'S GOOD WITH
A HAMMER AND A NAIL.
YOU GIVE HIM A HAMMER,
A NAIL AND A SHINGLE
AND HE GETS INTO
A BIT MORE TROUBLE.
I SEE SOME OF YOU RECOGNIZE
LOONIE AS THE DRUMMER
IN MY BAND:
"ARNIE DOGAN AND
THE CHARTREUSE RIDERS...
THE SAGE BRUSH, STORMY MOUNTAIN,
MIDNIGHT RAMBLING BOYS."
FEATURING ARNIE DOGAN.
SO, IF LOONEY GETS IN,
WE GET A FREE DRUMMER FOR ALL
THE LODGE WEDDINGS AND FUNERALS.
SO, THANKS FOR
YOUR CONSIDERATION.
ALL THOSE IN FAVOUR?
I SHOULD MENTION THAT
IF LOONEY DOESN'T GET IN,
I'LL BE SINGING PROTEST SONGS
IN FRONT OF THE LODGE,
24 HOURS A DAY.
ALL THOSE IN FAVOUR?
[lodge members]
AYE.
[narrated by Red]
I WAS UP BEHIND THE LODGE,
THINNING THE HERD,
AND I THOUGHT BILL WAS GOING
TO COME OUT AND HELP ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE HE IS.
DON'T, JUST DON'T!
BOY, YOU COULD GIVE
A GUY A HEART ATTACK.
YOU CHOP FOR AWHILE, BUD.
I'VE GOT TO RELAX.
NO, THE TREE'S OVER HERE, BILL.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
OH, MY GOD!
YOU BROUGHT A CHAINSAW.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
BILL, BILL.
BILL, EXCUSE ME, BILL.
THAT'S AN ELECTRIC CHAIN SAW.
GOT AN IDEA?
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
OH, MY GOSH!
HOW LONG DOES IT TAKE YOU
TO DRESS IN THE MORNING?
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED TO PLUG
THAT IN SOMEWHERE, BILL.
HOW IS THAT GOING TO WORK?
OH, ALL RIGHT.
SHE'S SHORTED OUT, BILL
YOU GOT A DEAD SHORT THERE.
IT'S PULLING ALL THE WIRING IN.
DON'T TOUCH IT, BILL.
BILL!!!
YOUR WIFE IS IN FOR
A SURPRISE TONIGHT, BILL.
ALL RIGHT?
NOW, WHAT?
OKAY, WE'VE GOT NO AX,
WE'VE GOT NO ELECTRIC CHAINSAW.
OH, YOU GOT THE METAL JOB.
THERE'S A GAS ONE.
THERE YOU GO, ALL RIGHT, BILL.
START THAT ONE.
IT LOOKS LIKE A BEAUTY, EH?
START THAT BABY UP.
OH, THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
NOW, THAT'S FUNNY.
THERE WE GO, YOU GOT 'ER GOING.
BILL, YOU'VE GOT YOUR FOOT
THROUGH THE HANDLE.
GET YOUR FOOT OUT OF THERE.
GET YOUR FOOT OUT, BILL.
EASY, EASY, EASY.
OH, OH, OH, MAN!
WHERE DID SHE GO?
I'M FINE, ARE YOU OKAY?
I THINK I SEE IT,
I THINK I SEE IT.
OH, BOY!
OH, BILL.
OKAY, STAND STILL, STAND STILL!
IT'S A BOY!!!
OH NO, IT ISN'T.
UNCLE RED,
I'M SO IN LOVE.
I MET THIS GIRL.
IT'S PEEWEE HERMAN.
SHE'S TOTALLY AWESOME
AND TOTALLY COOL.
I MET HER AT
THE LAUNDROMAT.
WERE YOU WASHING
THAT OUTFIT?
YEAH.
DID YOU WASH IT WITH
YOUR RED LONGJOHNS?
YEAH, I DID ACTUALLY.
SHE'S SO COOL.
HER NAME'S HARRIET,
LIKE OZZIE AND HARRIET.
OZZY OSBOURNE
HAS A GIRLFRIEND
NAMED HARRIET?
OH, THAT'S THE NAME
OF THE BAT THAT HE
BIT THE HEAD OFF?
WHY DID I THINK
THAT WE COULD HAVE
A CONVERSATION, HAROLD?
SHE'S THE BEST.
OH REALLY?
YEAH.
HOW DOES SHE FEEL ABOUT
YOUR FEMALE ROOMMATES?
DID YOU TELL HER?
WELL, IT HASN'T COME UP
IN CONVERSATION, YET.
SO, NO.
BUT, SHE WON'T
MIND, RIGHT?
BECAUSE THESE ARE
MODERN TIMES.
ABSOLUTELY,
SHE WON'T MIND.
I'LL TELL HER
THE NEXT TIME
I SEE HER.
YOU JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
THE MODERN, LIBERATED WOMAN.
SHE WILL BE TOTALLY
COOL WITH THIS.
SHE'LL BE WAY PAST COOL,
ALL THE WAY TO FROSTY,
I WOULD SAY.
[laughter]
THIS IS THE REPAIR PART
OF THE SHOW THAT WE CALL:
"IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
WE'VE GOT WATER TAXI DRIVER
HAP SHAUGHNESEY HERE TODAY.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
FOR US TODAY, HAP?
WELL, I'VE GOT AN
OLD PAINTING, RED.
IT'S GOT A BIT
OF A TEAR, THERE.
NOW BE CAREFUL.
THIS IS A FAMILY HEIRLOOM.
GOES BACK A WAY, DOES IT?
THIS LADY HAS BEEN
IN OUR FAMILY SINCE
THE 16TH CENTURY.
I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT TO SAY, HAP.
JUST TELL ME YOU CAN
FIX THE TEAR, RED.
OH YEAH, THE TEAR.
I CAN FIX THE RIP OFF - RIP UP.
I'LL PUT SOMETHING ON THERE
THAT WILL LAST ANOTHER
FIVE CENTURIES.
I'M THINKING OF
THE RENAISSANCE MAN'S
SECRET WEAPON:
DUCT TAPE.
THIS PAINTING LOOKS A LOT LIKE
THE MONA LISA BY DA VINCI?
I DON'T KNOW
THE DETAILS.
I JUST KNOW, SHE'S
BEEN IN OUR FAMILY
SINCE THE SHAUGHNESSEYS
LIVED IN FLORENCE IN 1510.
YOU KNOW, I BELIEVE THERE'S
AN IMITATION OF THIS PAINTING
HANGING IN THE LOUVRE, IN PARIS.
[laughter]
YEAH, THAT'S
ALSO AN ORIGINAL.
OH, THERE'S THE TWO ORIGINALS.
I SEE, I SEE.
LEONARDO DID A COUPLE OF THESE
AND THIS IS THE BETTER ONE
BECAUSE HE DID IT ON
GLOSSY, POSTER PAPER.
OR MAYBE, HE INVENTED
THE COLOUR PHOTO COPIER
AND JUST DIDN'T
TELL ANYBODY.
NO, THIS IS A POSTER.
I GOT IT IN THE FRAME SHOP
IN PORT ASBESTOS.
SO, THIS PAINTING HASN'T
BEEN IN YOUR FAMILY
FOR FIVE CENTURIES?
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I SAID THE LADY HAS.
THIS LADY MARRIED MY...
GREAT, GREAT, GREAT,
GREAT, GREAT...
YEAH, YEAH.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
MONA LISA'S LAST NAME
WAS SHAUGHNESSEY?
YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME?
HAVE A LOOK.
LOOK AT THE FAMILY RESEMBLENCE.
[laughter]
BOY, I DON'T KNOW HOW
SHE KEEPS A STRAIGHT FACE.
Red:
OH, BOY!
HE'S BACK TO NORMAL.
WHAT WENT WRONG, HAROLD?
I BROKE UP
WITH HARRIET.
SHE'S NOT MY TYPE.
WOW, YOU HAVE A TYPE?
LIKE A FONT OR SOMETHING?
SHE SAID: "OH, I DON'T CARE
IF YOU LIVE WITH THREE GIRLS."
WHY SHOULD I?
I LIVE WITH FOUR GUYS.
FOUR GUYS!!!
WELL HAROLD,
IT'S MODERN TIMES.
WELL, TIMES UP!
FOUR GUYS!!!
YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
YOU'RE STARTING TO
SOUND LIKE A MAN TO ME.
I THINK YOU COULD BE
A POSSUM LODGE MEMBER.
OH, NO!
I'VE GOT TO
PHONE HARRET.
I'VE GOT TO APOLOGIZE.
I'M BEING TOTALLY UNREASONABLE.
DON'T CALL HER,
DON'T CALL HER.
NO, I TRUST HER, UNCLE RED.
I THINK WE COULD MAKE UP
AND WE COULD FIX THINGS
AND EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
NO, I MEAN IT'S LONG DISTANCE.
HELLO, HARRIET, DON'T HANG UP.
I JUST WANT TO APOLOGIZE
FOR THE THINGS I SAID.
OH, REALLY!
WHAT?
NO, THAT WAS THE CRY
OF THE POSSUM.
IT'S MEETING TIME,
SO I GOT TO GO,
BUT I'LL SEE YOU AT SCHOOL.
OKAY, YOU TOO.
BYE.
[squeal of the Possum]
IT REALLY IS
METTING TIME.
HAROLD, I THINK YOU
DID THE RIGHT THING
WITH HARRIET.
REALLY?
YEAH?
OH, NO.
C'MON, NOW.
IT WAS SO CLOSE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I THINK WE SHOULD APPRECIATE
THAT WE GREW UP
IN SIMPLER TIMES.
BEFORE THERE WAS "FREE LOVE"
AND "POLITICAL CORRECTNESS."
AND, YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO TREAT
ANYBODY FAIRLY UNTIL YOU WERE
FORCED TO, THROUGH MARRIAGE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU:
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND ON
BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD,
AND THE WHOLE GANG
AT POSSUM LODGE.
"KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE."
[applause]
ALL RISE.
[lodge members]
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
NOW, YOU ALL KNOW THAT
I HAVE A NEW GIRLFRIEND
AND SHE PHONES ME ALL THE TIME.
WITH IMPORTANT MATTERS
AND ISSUES, AND STUFF.
SO, DON'T CLOG UP MY VOICE MAIL
WITH YOUR INSULTS AND ADVICE.
MR. HATFIELD,
YOU QUIT PHONING TOO.
THAT'S THE WORST BEA ARTHUR
IMPRESSION I'VE EVER HEARD.