WE'RE MOVING TOWARDS BECOMING
A NONVIOLENT SOCIETY,
AND THAT'S A GOOD THING,
ESPECIALLY FOR LAWYERS,
BECAUSE NOW WE DO ALL
OUR FIGHTING IN COURT.
LAWSUITS ARE NOT AS IMMEDIATE
OR COST EFFECTIVE AS PUNCHING
YOUR NEIGHBOUR IN THE HEAD,
BUT I THINK IT'S BETTER
TO LOSE MONEY AND HAVE
TO GO EARN MORE
THAN TO SPEND YOUR LIFE WITH
A PERMANENTLY BENT FACE.
WELL, NOW WE'VE GOT SO MUCH
MATURITY AND NONVIOLENCE
THAT WE'VE TURNED
INTO A BUNCH OF GUYS
WHO WILL SUE ANYBODY
ABOUT ANYTHING.
IT'S NOT SMART OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT MAKES US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red:
COMING UP ON TODAY'S SHOW,
I'M GOING TO TAKE ALL THE
ELASTIC OUT MY UNDERWEAR
FOR NO REASON REALLY,
THEN I'M GOING TO
DO A LITTLE BIT --
LOOKS LIKE I'M
SAWING SOMETHING THERE,
AND THEN I'LL
DO A LITTLE BIT OF --
ACTUALLY, IT'S HOW TO USE YOUR
LEGS AS A VICE I THINK
THIS WEEK,
AND BILL'S GOING
FOR A LONG DRIVE.
AND NOW LET'S HAVE A BIG HAND
FOR THE HANDIEST HANDYMAN
WITH THE HAM-HANDED HANDS
IF YOU HAD TO HAND IT
TWO-HANDEDLY,
MY UNCLE RED GREEN!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AND HOW ABOUT A BIG FIST
FOR MY NEPHEW, HAROLD?
[ PENNY WHISTLE ]
Harold: LIGHTS, CAMERA,
STAND THERE AND TALK.
BIG WEEK FOR
MOOSE THOMPSON THIS WEEK.
HE FINDS OUT TODAY WHETHER
OR NOT HE'S A MILLIONAIRE.
YOU SEE, LAST WINTER
MOOSE WENT OVER
TO THE POSSUM PRECIPICE
SKI RESORT AND GOLF CLUB.
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS WITH
THAT IS THAT DURING
THE SUMMER
IT'S ABOUT THE HILLIEST GOLF
COURSE YOU'VE EVER SEEN,
AND DURING THE WINTER
IT'S KIND OF A LAME
SKI RESORT.
ANYWAY, MOOSE WAS OVER
THERE LAST FEBRUARY
COLLECTING WORMS
FOR FISHING.
I NEVER REALLY UNDERSTOOD,
WHY WAS HE COLLECTING
WORMS IN THE WINTER?
ICE FISHING.
THAT'S OUR MOOSE.
YEAH.
SO HE WAS LEANING
DOWN THERE,
YOU KNOW, DIGGING AROUND
FOR THE WORMS THERE
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE
GIANT SLALOM DOWNHILL,
WHICH IS ALSO A PAR TWO
DURING THE SUMMER,
AND A SKIER COME DOWN
AND NAILED HIM RIGHT
IN THE HEAD.
WHOA, LUCKY IT WASN'T HIS
FOOT OR SOMETHING HE USES.
WELL, MOOSE IS NOW
SUING THE OWNERS,
'CAUSE HE SAID
THEY SHOULD'VE HAD
A SIGN THERE SAYING,
DON'T LEAN DOWN AND STICK
YOUR HEAD IN THERE
'CAUSE YOUR EAR WILL
STICK TO THE ICE,
AND THEN A SKIER WILL
COME DOWN AND HIT YOU
RIGHT IN THE HEAD.
AND HE'S SUING FOR A
MILLION DOLLARS
IN DAMAGES?
YEAH, HE SAYS THE COLLISION
AFFECTED HIS THINKING.
IMPROVED IT?
EXACTLY.
AND NOW IT'S HARDER
TO FIND A GIRL OR BE HAPPY
OR GET A DECENT JOB.
HOW DID HE FIGURE THAT?
APPARENTLY HIS LAWYER
IS USING YOU AS A
LEGAL PRECEDENT.
YOU ARE WATCHING
THE RED GREEN SHOW.
[ CHUCKLES ]
PEOPLE WILL BUY
ANYTHING, WON'T THEY?
WELL, IF YOU EVER NEED
TO PROVE YOU'RE A MAN
HERE'S SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD TRY
SHOULD TRY
SEE IF YOU CAN
CLIMB UP TUCKER'S MOUNTAIN
WHEN THE SUN
IS HOT AND HIGH
AND HIGH
IT'S 300 FEET
AND IT'S ALL STRAIGHT UP
AND IT FEELS LIKE
IT'S GOING TO COLLAPSE
TUCKER BUILT THE WHOLE
MOUNTAIN HIMSELF
AND BELIEVE ME THAT'S A
LOT OF BEER BOTTLE CAPS
NOT THE FIRE!
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
THERE ARE CERTAIN THINGS
THAT THE WOMAN IN YOUR LIFE
IS GOING TO ASK YOU,
AND YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
HAVE TIME TO THINK
OF AN ANSWER.
AND THE WORST ONE
OF THESE IS, AM I FAT?
OH BOY.
NOW, FOR SURE YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO SAY YES, EH,
UNLESS YOU HAVE A
DEATH WISH, EH?
BUT YOU EVEN GOT TO SAY
NO THE RIGHT WAY, EH,
OR THIS CONVERSATION
IS GOING INTO TRIPLE
OVERTIME.
JUST SAY NO RIGHT AWAY.
JUST NO.
DON'T THINK ABOUT IT,
DON'T PAUSE,
JUST SAY NO.
DON'T SAY, WELL...
NO, NOT REALLY.
BUT YOU KNOW
SOMETHING,
YOU DARENS'T GO TOO
FAR THE OTHER WAY
NEITHER, EH?
LIKE, FOR INSTANCE,
YOU CAN'T GO, WHAT,
YOU, FAT?
TELL ME ANOTHER ONE.
GET SERIOUS.
WHAT ARE YOU,
OUT OF YOUR MIND?
OH SURE ALL YOUR FRIENDS
ARE FAT AND BOTH
YOUR SISTERS,
AND YOUR MOM, BUT YOU,
YOU'RE LIKE AN
UNDERFED CHICKEN, EH?
IT'S SCARY HOW
SKINNY YOU ARE.
AS THE GREAT WILBER
SHAKESPEARE ONCE SAID,
METHINKS THE LADY
DOTH PROCESS TOO MUCH.
WHAT?
JUST SAY NO
AND THEN RIGHT AWAY
INVITE HER OUT FOR
DINNER, HUH?
THAT WAY YOU'RE GOING
TO LOOK LIKE A HERO,
AND SHE'S OBVIOUSLY
THINKING ABOUT HER WEIGHT,
SHE'S PROBABLY NOT EVEN
GOING TO TAKE YOU UP ON IT!
IT'S A WIN WIN.
YEAH.
AM I FAT?
OH YEAH.
WELL, WITH MOOSE THOMPSON
GOING AFTER THE SKI
AND GOLF RESORT,
IT GOT ME THINKING ABOUT
SOME WAY YOU COULD BE
GOLFING YEAR ROUND
WITHOUT HAVING TO PHONE IN
SICK TO THE OFFICE
FROM FLORIDA ALL WINTER.
OF COURSE THIS WOULD
MEAN YOU'D HAVE TO BE
GOLFING INDOORS.
AND FOR THAT, OF COURSE,
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED A
PRETTY BIG HOUSE,
PROBABLY 140 MILLION
SQUARE FEET,
MAYBE GO WITH ONE OF THEM
OPEN CONCEPT THINGS
AND THE HIGH CEILINGS
'CAUSE YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
SOME MATURE TREES IN THERE
AND MAYBE A
BATHTUB WATER HAZARD
AND A DOG LEG IN AT LEAST
THREE OF THE ROOMS.
I TELL YOU
WHAT YOU CAN DO,
YOU CAN HAVE AN
INDOOR DRIVING RANGE.
ALL'S YOU NEED IS ONE OF THESE
OLD-FASHIONED GOLF BALLS,
THE KIND THAT INSIDE IS AN
ELASTIC WOUND AROUND, AROUND,
AROUND, AROUND,
AROUND, AROUND.
YOU GOT TO
UNWIND ALL THAT.
I'LL TELL YOU,
WHEN I WAS A TEENAGER,
OFTENTIMES WE WOULD SPEND
AN ENTIRE SUMMER
JUST UNWINDING THE
ONE GOLF BALL.
IT WOULD BE MAYBE
FOUR MILES LONG.
THAT'S THE KIND OF FUN WE
HAD WITH RUBBER WHEN
WE WERE KIDS.
TIMES HAVE CHANGED,
HAVEN'T THEY?
ALL RIGHT, SO STEP ONE IS
YOU GOT TO GET THE OUTER
CASING OFF THE BALL.
CLUB SELECTION
IS IMPORTANT.
I'M GOING TO GO
WITH MY TREE WOOD.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FORE!
OKAY.
PLAN B.
WHAT AM I THINKING OF?
SAFETY FIRST, HUH?
ALL RIGHT, WELL, I GOT
IT ALL TAKEN APART HERE,
AND I GOT THE
ELASTIC UNWOUND,
BUT I MAY HAVE CUT A
LITTLE DEEP
JUST ABOUT EVERYTHING THERE.
SO A HANDYMAN HAS
TO BE ABLE TO ADAPT,
SO ANOTHER
SOURCE OF ELASTIC,
YOU KNOW, I GOT THE ELASTIC
IN THE UNDERWEAR WAISTBAND.
AND I'LL JUST --
I'LL BE RIGHT
WITH YOU ON THIS.
THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
YOU TAKE THE END OF THAT,
AND YOU JUST ATTACH
THAT TO THE BALL,
USING THE HANDYMAN SECRET
WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, YOU WOULD
DO THIS OF COURSE WITH
A GOLF BALL,
BUT HAROLD WANTED ME TO USE
SOMETHING A LITTLE BIT BIGGER,
SO WE GOT A
CROQUET BALL HERE.
HAROLD SAYS THAT READS
BETTER ON TELEVISION,
WHICH IS KIND OF
CONFUSING TO ME.
I THOUGHT PEOPLE WATCHED
TV SO THEY DIDN'T
HAVE TO READ.
THE OTHER END OF THE ELASTIC
YOU WOULD ATTACH TO A
NORMAL GOLF TEE HERE.
AND GOSH, I WOULD PUT A REAL
GOOD KNOT ON THAT IF
I WERE YOU.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO USE
A TEE, IN FACT,
YOU COULD USE A CANDLE
OR A BEER BOTTLE.
BUT WITH MY
MEDICAL INSURANCE,
I THOUGHT I WOULD
GO WITH THE TEE.
AND YOU CAN SET THE WHOLE
UNIT UP HERE ON A
CRIBBAGE BOARD,
AND THAT WAY YOU PUT THE TEE
INTO THE CRIBBAGE BOARD,
AND YOU DON'T
ACTUALLY HAVE TO
DRILL A HOLE IN THE FLOOR
OF YOUR FAMILY ROOM.
UNLESS YOU REALLY ENJOY
DOING STUFF LIKE THAT.
ALL RIGHT, AND WHEN
YOU PICK YOUR AREA,
TRY TO MAKE SURE
THAT IT'S, YOU KNOW,
AWAY FROM SOME FURNITURE THAT
YOU HAVE SOME VALUE IN,
THE CHINA CABINETS
OR A CHANDELIER THAT
TYPE OF THING.
AND THE TARGET NOW SHOULD BE
SOMEWHERE OUT THERE,
MAYBE ONE OF THEM BIG
DOUBLE SLIDING DOORS,
GET THEM OPENED UP.
OR AT LEAST HIT IT INTO
A ROOM YOU DON'T CARE ABOUT.
REMEMBER, KEEP YOUR
HEAD STILL.
[ GLASS BREAKS ]
OH BOY.
THAT WAS A BEAUTY.
OH GOOD.
I GOT ALL THAT ONE.
AND THE BEAUTY
OF THIS SYSTEM IS
THE ELASTIC BRINGS THE BALL
RIGHT BACK TO YOU.
AND YOU GET A CHANCE
TO REST BETWEEN SHOTS.
SO REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
Red: STAY TUNED.
GLEN IS GOING TO STAND THERE,
AND I'M GOING TO DO STUFF,
AND HAROLD IS HEARING VOICES
AGAIN, EXCEPT FOR MINE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
I WANT TO TALK TO ALL
YOU MIDDLE AGE GUYS OUT THERE
BECAUSE I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE GOING THROUGH.
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE TO
WAKE UP TWO HOURS BEFORE
YOUR BODY DOES
OR TO WATCH A FULL HEAD
OF OLD HAIR SWIRL DOWN
THE SHOWER DRAIN,
WHILE A BUSHEL OF NEW HAIR
SPURTS OUT OF YOUR NOSE
AND YOUR EARS.
AND AT OUR AGE YOU NEVER KNOW
IF THE CALL OF NATURE
IS GOING TO BE A SHOUT,
A WHINE OR A WHISPER.
GOING TO THE WASHROOM
IS LIKE GOING TO A
FIREWORKS DISPLAY.
YOU STAND THERE FOR AN HOUR
AND A HALF WAITING FOR
SOMETHING TO START,
AND THEN ONCE SHE GETS GOING,
THERE'S A LOT OF OOHS AND AHS,
BUT YOU'RE NEVER REALLY
COMPLETELY SURE WHEN
IT'S OVER.
AND HAVING A BIG HEARTY
MEAL OF SPICY FOOD
IS EITHER GOING TO BE A SUICIDE
ATTEMPT OR MURDER/SUICIDE
DEPENDING ON WHETHER OR NOT
YOU'RE ALONE IN THE CAR.
BUT THAT'S ALL JUST PART
OF GETTING OLDER.
I THINK IT WAS OSCAR WILDE
SAID, YOUTH IS WASTED
ON THE YOUNG.
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU,
PRIT'NEAR EVERYTHING
IS WASTED ON ME.
BUT I'M GOING TO BE
HANGING IN THERE.
I DON'T LIKE GETTING OLD
BUT IT'S A LOT BETTER
THAN THE ALTERNATIVE.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU,
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, MOOSE THOMPSON WON
THE SETTLEMENT,
AND NOW HE'S THE RICHEST
GUY IN THE AREA,
AT LEAST ON PAPER.
OH, HE'S A MILLIONAIRE!
OH, THIS IS GREAT!
DO YOU THINK HE'D LIKE TO
FINANCE MY FIRST FEATURE
FILM, BIKINI MADNESS?
[ HUMMING SURFER MUSIC ]
CALM DOWN, FELLINI.
THE JUDGE AWARDED
MOOSE $72,
PLUS AN ADDITIONAL
$1000 IN SUFFERING,
BUT THAT WENT TO
MOOSE'S PARENTS.
NOW, UNFORTUNATELY THE
POSSUM PRECIPICE SKI
AND GOLF CLUB
COULDN'T PAY UP, SO THEY
HAD TO DECLARE BANKRUPTCY,
AND NOW MOOSE GETS
ALL THEIR SKI EQUIPMENT
AND ALL THEIR
GOLF EQUIPMENT.
SO HE'S GOT HIMSELF A CHAIR
LIFT, A SKI JUMP,
AN ELECTRIC GOLF CART THAT
DOUBLES AS A SNOW MAKING
MACHINE,
A COMBINATION
LAWN MOWER/SNOW PLOW,
80 POUNDS OF SKI WAX
AND A BALL WASHER.
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE
FOR ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
REMEMBER WE'LL TAKE
THAT SMELL OFF YOUR HANDS.
HERE WE ARE AT
BRAXTON'S MARINA
WITH GLEN BRAXTON.
HOW ARE YOU
TODAY, GLEN?
NOT BAD AT ALL, RED.
GOOD.
YOU KNOW, CONSIDERING I'M
THE VICTIM OF TWO RECENT
HEART ATTACKS.
THAT'S TRUE.
GLEN IS ALSO THE
VICTIM OF 4,000 DONUTS
AND A PREDISPOSITION
TOWARDS WORK AVOIDANCE.
I THINK THAT'S ALL
BEHIND ME NOW, RED.
NO, THERE'S A FAIR
BIT OUT FRONT THERE
AND SOME HUGE
CHUNKS ON THE SIDE.
WELL, RED,
YOU'RE NOT EXACTLY A
GOSSAMER PRINCESS YOURSELF.
NO, I THINK YOUR COMPUTER
HAS GOT A FAIR SIZE
INPUT/OUTPUT ERROR,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT MEAN.
I'M JUST SAYING YOU ARE
ONE LAZY GUY, GLEN.
NO. NO.
SEE, NO.
I USED TO BE LAZY,
NOW I HAVE
TO BE LAZY.
OH YEAH,
THE SLIGHTEST STRAIN
AND, OH MAN, BOOM,
MY HEART WILL BLOW
JUST LIKE AN OVERLOADED
BILGE PUMP.
BUT THAT'S MY
RESPONSIBILITY.
ALL RIGHT.
AND I'LL TAKE IT.
OKAY.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE LIKE
MOOSE THOMPSON, NO,
SUE EVERYBODY IN THE WORLD
JUST BECAUSE THEY LET
ME OVEREAT.
NO. NO.
NO, JUST HAVE TO LIVE
WITH THAT, RED.
ANYWAY, FOR TODAY'S
BOATING TIP.
WE DON'T EVEN HAVE A
COURTHOUSE THAT BIG,
DO WE?
JUST DROP IT,
ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT.
FAIR ENOUGH.
AS I WAS SAYING,
TODAY'S BOATING TIP.
WHAT WE'RE GOING
TO DO TODAY IS
WE'RE GOING TO BUILD A FRAME
FOR THE BOAT TARP
SO YOU CAN STORE
YOUR BOAT PROPERLY.
ALRIGHTY.
WHAT WE NEED.
A PIECE OF WOOD.
THAT'S A BOARD.
NOW, AS YOU CAN SEE,
WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO IS
YOU HAVE TO DRILL
BOTH ENDS OF THIS.
AND I'VE DRILLED ONE
END ALREADY.
RIGHT HERE, YEAH.
AND, RED, MAYBE YOU
COULD DRILL THE OTHER
END FOR ME.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
NOW, WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO,
THIS BOARD ACTS AS
CENTERPIECE FOR THE
TARP, THE FRAME,
AND IT KEEPS THE TARP
UP OFF THE BOAT
SO THE TARP DOESN'T GET
ALL GUNGY AND GOOPY
AND MESSY LIKE,
YOU KNOW, AN OLD PAIR
OF GYM SOCKS OR SOMETHING.
NOW, THE TWO HOLES ARE SO
THAT YOU CAN TIE IT TO
THE FRAME --
OR TO THE BOAT,
EXCUSE ME.
THERE WE GO.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU
THINK OF THAT?
THAT'S A BEAUTY, RED.
THAT'S A NICE --
OH THAT'S A PERFECT CUT.
LOOK AT THOSE
EDGES NICE AND --
OH MY GOSH!
THAT'S A NICE ONE.
OH BOY.
YEAH, THAT'S A BEAUTY.
NOW, DO YOU THINK ANY
WATER'LL GET IN THERE
AT ALL?
NOPE.
YOU KNOW, RED,
IF I DO SUE EVERYBODY,
YOU'RE MY LAWYER.
Red: NICE SAFE SPORT TODAY
ON ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
WE'RE GOING
TO DO SOME GOLF.
YEAH.
THANK YOU, BILL,
AND GOOD MORNING.
DON'T YELL FORE NOW,
YOU'RE WAY TOO LATE.
TAKE THAT BALL AND -- WHAT?
OH, A LITTLE CONTEST,
A DRIVING CONTEST,
SEE WHO CAN HIT THE
BALL THE FARTHEST.
WELL, LET'S MAKE IT
INTERESTING, BILL.
LET'S PUT SOME MONEY ON THIS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
GET YOUR WALLET OUT.
THAT'S YOUR WALLET?
OH MY GOSH.
ALL RIGHT.
SO I'LL GO FIRST.
I FEEL PRETTY
GOOD ABOUT THIS.
JUST REAR BACK
AND LET 'ER RIP.
I DIDN'T GET ALL OF IT.
NO. NO. NO.
IT'S NOT BAD,
THOUGH, I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, SO I GO UP
TO THE LITTLE FLAG
AND I STICK THE FLAG
IN WHERE MY BALL IS.
AND NOW BILL HAS TO HIT HIS
BALL EITHER FARTHER
OR THE SAME DISTANCE
OR NOT AS FAR.
[ FARTING SOUND ]
THAT WAS THE FLAG.
I'M GUESSING NOT AS FAR.
OH, LOOK OUT, BILL.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
NOT BAD. NOT BAD.
NICE TRY, BILL.
I WILL JUST GRAB MYSELF --
WHAT? WHAT?
I WON -- WHAT?
THAT WAS A PRACTICE SWING?
WHAT THE HECK IS THIS NOW?
OH, NO, BILL IS TRYING TO GET
THE PENDULUM THEORY WORKING
WITH THE BIGGER,
LONGER CLUB.
YOU MISSED IT.
OH, NO.
NICE TRY BUT NOT ENOUGH.
EVEN THAT LONGER
PENDULUM DIDN'T -- WHAT?
NO, BILL, YOU'VE ALREADY
HAD TWO SHOTS, WHAT'S GOING --
HE ASKED ME TO HELP HIM
PUT THIS LADDER UP HERE.
HE'S GOT
SOMETHING IN MIND.
I DON'T THINK HE
HAS A CHANCE THOUGH.
SO WHAT THE HECK?
WHAT'S HE GOT NOW?
OH MY GOSH.
YOU WANT TO SEE THE
GOLF BAG THAT CAME OUT OF.
AND UP HE
GOES UP THE LADDER
AND I'M KIND OF INTERESTED TO
SEE HOW THIS TURNS OUT
AT THIS POINT.
HE SWINGS HIS LEG OVER,
ASKS FOR THE CLUB.
THAT'S PROBABLY
AN 18-FOOTER NOW.
AND I GUESS
THAT'S THE DRIVER.
YOU DON'T HAVE SOMETHING
THAT LONG AND MAKE IT
A THREE WOOD.
CAN YOU SWING THAT, BILL?
THAT LOOKS KIND OF
HARD TO CONTROL.
WATCH YOUR AIM.
WATCH YOUR AIM, BILL.
TEE UP. TEE UP.
OH, HE HIT THE LADDER,
HIT THE LADDER.
OH, OH, THE HYDRO POLE!
AND THE PENDULUM!
HERE COMES THE PENDULUM!
OH MY GOSH HE WON.
OH MY GOSH.
BE A GOOD WINNER NOW, BILL.
HERE'S YOUR MONEY.
THAT SHOULD BE ABLE TO BUY
THE FINEST MEDICAL TREATMENT
MONEY CAN BUY.
BILL SEEMS SHORTER.
STAY TUNED AS DALTON GOES
TO THE EDGE OF BANKRUPTCY,
SHORT TRIP,
AND WINSTON TELLS US HOW
TO DO PUBLIC SPEAKING.
"PUTTING IN THE DOCK,"
BY ME.
"WE GATHER BY THE
WATER'S EDGE,
"AND EVERYONE GRABS A SIDE,
"WE LIFT THE DOCK UP
ON OUR BACKS
AND BRACE OUR
LEGS FOR THE RIDE.
"WE DASH DOWN TO
THE ROCKY SHORE
"AND THROW THE DOCK
IN END OVER END.
"IT'S AN AWFUL
WAY TO TREAT A DOCTOR,
"BUT WITH MEDICATION,
DOC WILL MEND.
"PHYSICIAN HEAL THYSELF."
WELL, WE WENT
OVER TO THE CLUB.
WE PICKED UP ALL
THE GOLF EQUIPMENT
AND ALL THE SKI EQUIPMENT
THAT MOOSE HAD WON,
AND WE BROUGHT 'ER
ALL BACK TO THE LODGE.
WE JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO DO WITH IT NEXT.
WELL, YOU'VE ALREADY
DRAGGED IT 5 MILES,
OH, NO, HAROLD,
OUR PROBLEM IS
WE GOT TOO MANY
GOOD IDEAS.
LIKE, WE WERE THINKING MAYBE
TAKE THE CHAIR LIFT,
HOOK 'ER UP, AND WE'LL RIDE
THE GUYS FROM POSSUM LODGE
ALL THE WAY DOWN INTO LAKE
POSSUM AND BACK UP AGAIN,
YOU KNOW, AND ON BATH NIGHT
WE'LL DO TWO CYCLES,
WASH AND RINSE.
THAT'S DUMB.
YOU GUYS ARE DUMB.
WHAT STUPID THING YOU GOING
TO DO NEXT WITH THE STUPID
SNOW MAKING MACHINE?
OH, THIS IS GREAT,
HAROLD,
SIX-FOOT-WIDE
SNOW CONES.
WHO'S GOING TO EAT A
SIX-FOOT-WIDE SNOW CONE?
SOMEBODY WITH A REALLY
BIG MOUTH, HAROLD.
WELL, WHAT IF THIS PERSON
DOESN'T WANNA TO EAT A
SIX-FOOT-WIDE SNOW CONE?
WE'LL DROP IT IN
HIS PANTS.
Glen: THIS BOAT'S FOR SALE.
IT'S ONLY 100 BUCKS,
BUT YOU SHOULD BE
A STRONG SWIMMER.
WE'RE OUT HERE BY THE MAIN
HIGHWAY AT HUMPHRIES'
EVERYTHING STORE
TO DO A LITTLE BUSINESS
TRANSACTION WITH THE OWNER,
NOW, DALTON, WE WERE CLEANING
OUT MOOSE'S SKI AND GOLF
CLUB THERE,
AND WE COME UP WITH THIS
LITTLE UNIT RIGHT HERE.
WHAT DO YOU SUPPOSE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT
IS WORTH?
WELL, YOU KNOW, BEFORE
MOOSE THOMPSON BOUGHT
THAT RESORT,
THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN
WORTH A PRETTY PENNY.
NOW IT'S NEXT
TO USELESS.
OH COME ON, NOW,
DALTON, YOU GOT TO
BE PULLING MY LEG.
I MEAN, THIS WAS USED
BY THE PIONEERS FOR --
WELL, FOR SOMETHING,
I WOULD THINK.
RED, THE ANTIQUE BUSINESS
IS BUILT ON TWO CORNERSTONES,
GOLFER AND SKIERS.
WITHOUT THEM, I'D BE
BANKRUPT IN A WEEK.
WHY?
WELL, THE MEN
GOLF TOGETHER
AND THEN THE WOMEN
DROP THEM OFF
AND THEN THEY DRIVE AROUND
KILLING TIME DOING
GUESS WHAT?
LOOKING FOR ANTIQUES?
BINGO!
AND SKIERS, WHAT'S THE
NUMBER ONE SOUVENIR
THEY TAKE HOME?
BROKEN LEGS?
ANTIQUES.
THEY BUY THEM
BY THE TRUCK LOAD.
IT'S MUST ALL THAT COLD
WIND IN THEIR FACE,
MAKES THEM IRRATIONAL.
WITH THE GOLF
AND SKI CLUB CLOSED,
THEY WON'T BE BACK,
AND I'M STUCK WITH THIS.
WELL, NOW, DON'T
GO CRAZY HERE, DALTON.
WE'LL GET SKIERS UP
IN THE WINTER.
WE'LL GET
CROSS-COUNTRY SKIERS.
CROSS-COUNTRY
SKIERS, HAH!
YOU KNOW WHY THEY'RE
CROSS-COUNTRY
SKIING, RED?
THEY'RE TOO CHEAP
TO BUY LIFT TICKETS.
SKINNY BANDY-LEGGED
VEGETARIANS,
SHUFFLING THEIR WAY
FOR FREE ACROSS THE SNOW.
CROSS-COUNTRY SKIERS
ARE TIGHT WADS!
WELL, HOW ABOUT
ICE FISHERMAN?
THEY COME UP
TO POSSUM LAKE,
HUNDREDS OF 'EM.
I TELL YOU,
THEY SPEND MONEY.
OH, YOU'VE BEEN INSIDE
A LOT OF ICE HUTS,
HAVE YOU, RED?
YEAH.
YEAH?
SEEN A LOT OF ANTIQUES
THERE, HAVE YOU, HUH?
ICE FISHERMEN SITTING
AROUND THE HOLE,
JIGGLING THEIR
LINE SAYING,
OH, BOY, WHEN I
CATCH A TROUT
I'M GOING TO GO DOWN
AND  BUY MYSELF A
NICE SPINDLE BED
WITH A BRASS
HEADBOARD, HUH?
WON'T THAT BE
A NICE ACCENT PIECE
FOR THE WALL WHERE
I STORE THE BEER CASES?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S NO USE,
I'M GETTING OUT OF
THE ANTIQUE BUSINESS.
I'M GOING TO TRY TO
MAKE A GO OF IT
IN THE JUNK AND
SCRAP BUSINESS.
WELL, HOW ARE YOU
GOING TO DO THAT?
I'M GOING TO CHANGE
THE SIGN ON MY STORE.
THAT WILL DO IT.
THIS WEEK ON EXPERTS,
WE'RE BEING JOINED BY
MR. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THE FIRST LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"I HAVE TO GIVE A SPEECH
AT OUR NEXT GENERAL MEETING,
AND I'M VERY NERVOUS ABOUT
TALKING TO A GROUP
OF PEOPLE.
"CAN YOU HELP ME?"
WELL, I ALWAYS FIND
EXCESSIVE ALCOHOL
CONSUMPTION
REALLY LOOSENS --
UNCLE RED, I DON'T
THINK THAT BEING DRUNK
IS GOING TO HELP
THIS LADY'S SPEECH.
I MEANT THE
AUDIENCE, HAROLD.
YOU GET THEM SO JUICED UP
THEY CAN'T HEAR YOU,
IT REALLY TAKES
THE PRESSURE OFF.
LOW IS SELF-ESTEEM,
THERE'S YOUR PROBLEM, EH?
OH, YEAH,
I'VE BEEN THERE.
YOU KNOW, BEFORE
THE SEPTIC BUSINESS
I WOULDN'T EVEN
HOLD MY HEAD UP.
AND NOW YOU HAVE TO,
I WOULD THINK.
WELL, ANYWAY, I LEARNED
THE THREE JUMP STARTS
OF SELF-POWER
AND BIGGER LUNGS
IN A BOOK, "IF YOU CAN
DO THAT, ANY IDIOT CAN,"
BY ANTHONY ANTHONY.
OH MAN, YOU DIDN'T TAKE
ANOTHER ONE OF THOSE
SELF-ISH HELP COURSE
THINGS, DID YOU?
WELL, I WASN'T GOING
TO AT FIRST,
BUT I WORKED UP THE COURAGE
AFTER WATCHING
"SEIZE THE SELF-HELP COURSE OF
THE DAY" BY WALTER MOLLUSK.
SO, WINSTON, WHAT ARE THE
THREE JUMP START POINTS
FOR BIGGER LUNGS THING,
YOU KNOW,
WITHOUT, YOU KNOW,
PUMPING SEWAGE?
WELL, NUMBER ONE,
DOMINATE YOUR AUDIENCE.
I LIKE TO DO IT
FROM A 15-FOOT STEP LADDER
AND JUST SORT OF
TALK DOWN TO 'EM, EH?
WELL, MA'AM, FOR THIS
SPEECH YOU MIGHT WANT
TO WEAR SLACKS.
YOU KNOW SOMETHING,
THERE'S REALLY NOTHING
LIKE SEEING AN AUDIENCE
LIKE THIS, EH?
PUTTY IN YOUR HAIR.
NUMBER TWO, HAVE A LITTLE
DYNAMICS TO YOUR VOICE, EH?
LIKE, FOR INSTANCE,
whisper the nouns
AND SHOUT THE VERBS!!!
I DON'T THINK THE
AUDIENCE WOULD
LIKE THAT.
IT'S HARDER TO
SLEEP THROUGH.
THE MOST IMPORTANT
ONE OF ALL, "C,"
HAVE SOMETHING TO SAY
WORTH LISTENING TO, EH?
YEAH, WELL, MY ADVICE
TO THIS PERSON IS
GET UP THERE AND JUST
TELL THE FILTHIEST
JOKE YOU KNOW.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHY
YOU WERE NEVER INVITED BACK
TO GIVE A GUEST SERMON
AT THAT CHURCH.
WELL, I HAD TO DO SOMETHING
TO BREAK THE ICE, HAROLD,
THEY WOULDN'T LET ME
BRING ANY BOOZE IN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WELL, WE FINALLY FIGURED OUT
WHAT TO DO WITH ALL THAT
GOLFING AND SKIING EQUIPMENT
THAT MOOSE THOMPSON HAD WON.
AND ON PAPER
IT LOOKED PERFECT
BUT IN REALITY THERE
WERE A FEW GLITCHES.
HA! GLITCHES?
GLITCHES IS A POLITE TERM
FOR NINE GUYS HOSPITALIZED.
TOO BAD.
WE HAD THAT CHAIR LIFT
HOOKED UP WITH THE
GOLFING EQUIPMENT.
WE HAD A GOLF DRIVING RANGE
WITH A BALL RETURN.
YOU'D STAND AT THE TOP
OF THE SKI RAMP,
YOU'D DRIVE YOUR BALL DOWN
INTO NETS THAT WERE HANGING
FROM THE CHAIR LIFT,
BRING THE BALL RIGHT
BACK UP TO YOU.
WOULD HAVE WORK TOO
IF YOU DIDN'T USE THAT
SNOW MAKING MACHINE.
WELL, THE GUYS GOT
AWFUL HOT STANDING
THERE IN THE SUN
HITTING GOLF BALLS,
HAROLD.
THE PROBLEM WAS THE
HILL GOT ALL ICED UP,
AND GUYS STARTED SLIPPING
AND SLIDING ALL THE WAY
DOWN THE HILL
RIGHT INTO THE
DARN CHAIR LIFTS.
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
GUYS HANGING BY
THEIR FEET UPSIDE DOWN
BEING DRAGGED ACROSS
THE DRIVING RANGE.
OF COURSE, THEY WOULD
HAVE BEEN ALL RIGHT
IF THE REST OF YOU GUYS HAD
STOPPED DRIVING GOLF
BALLS AT THEM.
IT WAS JUST TOO
TEMPTING, YOU KNOW,
18 GUYS HANGING UPSIDE
DOWN FROM A CABLE,
IT LOOKED LIKE A
GIANT CHARM BRACELET.
WELL, IT WASN'T FUNNY
WHEN PEOPLE STARTED
GETTING HURT.
THAT WASN'T FROM
THE GOLF BALLS, HAROLD,
THAT'S WHEN THE CABLE
SNAPPED, TWANG.
EVERYBODY WENT
EVERYWHERE.
NOW THEY'RE ALL SUING
MOOSE FOR A MILLION
DOLLARS EACH.
WELL, NOW, WAIT A
MINUTE, UNCLE RED.
TO BE FAIR, WHEN THE CABLE
SNAPPED MOOSE DID YELL,
FORE!
HE WAS ORDERING
BEER FOR HIMSELF.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
IT'S MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A WHILE.
AS SOON AS
I DEFOLIATE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'VE DECIDED TO GIVE UP GOLF
UNTIL THEY GET SAFER
CHAIR LIFTS.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
UNTIL NEXT TIME, ON BEHALF
OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Harold:
I GOT SOMETHING TO SHOW!
I GOT SOMETHING TO
SHOW EVERYBODY.
IT'S A NEW SEGMENT
FOR THE SHOW.
HAROLD, THE FRONTIER HERO!
I'LL BE A HERO,
A BACKWOODS HERO.
AND I'LL JUST RIDE MY
REINDEER IN AND GO,
YOU THERE, DON'T EVEN DO
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.