♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: HI THIS IS RED GREEN,
IN TODAY'S SHOW IT LOOKS
LIKE HAROLD HAS GAS PAINS,
BILL GETS HIS AXE TOGETHER,
AND I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO MAKE A BOAT TRAILER
OUT OF A COUPLE OF
STOLEN BICYCLES.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: AND NOW LET'S HEAR IT
FOR THE HOST WITH THE MOST,
WELL IN TERMS OF
FACIAL HAIR ANYWAY.
THE STAR OF THE RED GREEN SHOW,
MR RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
AND THANK YOU FOR MENTIONING
MY BEARD THERE HAROLD,
I TAKE IT THAT WAS JUST
JEALOUSY ON YOUR PART.
>>HAROLD: NO, NO, NO, NO, NO,
THE BEARD'S YOUR THING
I DON'T WANT ANY PART OF IT,
THIS IS MY THING.
>>RED: WELL I THINK
THAT MAKES US EVEN.
ANYWAY WE HAD A BIT OF
EXCITEMENT UP AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK, MOOSE THOMPSON
DECIDED HE WANTED
TO GO WATERSKIING,
THE ONLY PROBLEM BEING WE
DON'T REALLY HAVE A BOAT
POWERFUL ENOUGH TO GET MOOSE UP.
>>HAROLD: NEITHER DOES THE NAVY,
MOOSE IS BIGGER THAN AN OX.
>>RED: WELL PHYSICALLY YES,
MENTALLY IT'S TOO CLOSE TO CALL.
SO MOOSE FIGURED HE GOT TO FIND
ANOTHER WAY TO GO WATERSKIING,
SO HE DECIDED HE'D GO OUT
AND FIND A LAKE WITH
A HILL IN IT.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED,
EXCUSE ME BUT I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE GOING TO FIND A LAKE
WITH A HILL IN IT,
THERE'S NO SUCH THING.
>>RED: WELL WHAT IS
A WATERFALL HAROLD?
SO MOOSE WENT WATERSKIING
OVER ROCKY REEF FALLS.
>>HAROLD: OH THAT'S
AN EXCELLENT CHOICE
ROCKY REEF FALLS,
EXCELLENT CHOICE BECAUSE PEOPLE
SAY YOU KNOW THAT WHERE THE
WATER FALLS INTO THAT POND,
THEY SAY IT BOTTOMLESS SO.
>>RED: WELL ACCORDING TO MOOSE
THOSE REPORTS ARE EXAGGERATED,
IN FACT THE COLLISION ALMOST
MADE MOOSE BOTTOMLESS.
BUT WHEN HE REGAINED
CONSCIOUSNESS IN THE RECOVERY
ROOM HE SAW SOME OF THAT
SURGICAL TUBING HANGING ON
THE WALL THERE AND THAT
GAVE HIM AN IDEA.
>>HAROLD: 2 IDEAS IN ONE DAY,
THAT DON'T SOUND LIKE MOOSE
TO ME.
>>RED: WELL I BLAME
THE CONCUSSION.
SO WHAT HE DID WAS HE MANAGED
TO STEAL ABOUT 100 FEET
OF THAT TUBING AND HE HID
IT IN HIS BELLY BUTTON,
HE TOLD THEM HE WAS AN OUTIE.
♪ IT'S A BEAUTIFUL MORNING ♪
♪ OF A BEAUTIFUL DAY ♪
♪ THERE'S DEW IN THE MEADOW ♪
♪ WHILE OTHERS DO ON THE HAY ♪
♪ GOOD MORNING TO THE SPARROW ♪
♪ GOOD MORNING TO THE DOVE ♪
♪ GOOD MORNING TO THE MEN ♪
♪ AS WE SIT DOWN FOR SUPPER ♪
♪ OH FOR GOSH SAKE I SLEPT IN ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE
GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW YOU
COULD USE ONE TYPE OF
TRANSPORTATION TO TRANSPORT
ANOTHER TYPE OF TRANSPORTATION
WITHOUT ACTUALLY TRANSPOSING
THE ONE TRANS.
ALL RIGHT WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT HERE IS MOVING YOUR
BOAT YOU KNOW LIKE A TRAILER
TYPE OF THING,
BUT OF COURSE YOU DON'T
NECESSARILY NEED A TRAILER
BECAUSE THE EASIEST WAY TO LEAD
A BOAT TO WATER IS JUST TO
THROW THE PIG INTO YOUR VAN.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>RED: ALL RIGHT YOU MIGHT
WANT TO CHECK THAT THE VAN
IS EMPTY FIRST.
YOU MIGHT HAVE YOUR CAMPING
EQUIPMENT IN THERE OR IN
THIS CASE A CHANDELIER THAT
I PROMISED MY WIFE I'D
TAKE BACK TO THE STORE.
OKAY BOAT TRAILERS,
NOW BOAT TRAILERS COME
IN ALL SIZES, YOU MIGHT GET
A REAL SMALL BOAT TRAILER
OR YOU MIGHT HAVE A REAL
BIG BOAT TRAILER.
THIS ONE HERE, WE COULD JUST
FILL THIS UP WITH WATER
AND GO CANOEING RIGHT IN
THE TRAILER ITSELF, BUT MAYBE
SOME OF YOU DON'T HAVE $2,000
BUCKS TO SPEND ON A TRAILER,
SO WHAT I SUGGEST IS YOU GET
ONE OF THEM TRAILER SPARE TIRES
AND THEN YOU JUST CRUISE
THE HIGHWAYS LOOKING FOR AN
ABANDONED TRAILER WITH A FLAT.
YOU NOT ONLY GET A TRAILER
OUT OF THAT, YOU GET YOURSELF
USUALLY A HALF DECENT BOAT
AND MOTOR AND ONCE YOU FILE
OFF THE SERIAL NUMBERS YOU CAN
HAVE YOURSELF A NICE SUMMER.
BUT FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO DON'T
ENJOY PRISON FOOD WE'RE GOING
TO SHOW YOU HOW YOU CAN MAKE
YOUR OWN BOAT TRAILER TRANSPORT.
THE FORM OF TRANSPORTATION
YOU KNOW AND USING ANOTHER,
BUT FOR THAT YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED ANOTHER FORM
OF TRANSPORTATION.
GET YOURSELF A COUPLE
OF OLD BIKES,
I GOT THESE HERE FROM THE
POLICE AUCTION, THE COPS
STOLE THEM FROM HAROLD.
OH YEAH DON'T USE GOOD BIKES.
OKAY NOW THIS HERE IS YOUR
GALVANIZED STEEL PIPE AND YOU'RE
GOING TO NEED THAT FOR THE
FRAMEWORK FOR YOUR BOAT TRAILER,
AND I GOT A BUNCH OF
JOINTS HERE.
I GOT T-JOINTS AND
I GOT THE L-JOINTS AND
I GOT X-JOINTS AND I GOT
Q-JOINTS AND I GOT PRETTY
WELL THE WHOLE ALPHABET HERE
BUT JUST THE CONSONANTS
NOT THE VOWELS.
DON'T, I MEAN LIKE AN O-JOINT
IS OF NO USE TO YOU AT ALL
AND OF COURSE A BEER JOINT
THAT'S A DIFFERENT STORY.
OKAY NOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED IS A HACKSAW TO CUT
THE GALVANIZED PIPING.
WELL YOU NEED A HACKSAW,
I USE POWER TOOLS.
>>HAROLD: AND NOW MY
FAVOURITE PART OF THE SHOW,
THE PART WE EXPOSE
THOSE 3 LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN
FIND SO DIFFICULT TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW.'
AND HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT
IS MY UNCLE RED AND HIS BEST
FRIEND IN THE WHOLE WIDE WORLD,
TODAY IT'S MR. GLEN BRAXTON.
'DEAR EXPERTS, FOR YEARS
WE HAVE BEEN TOLD THAT THE
COMMUNISTS WANTED TO CONTROL
THE WHOLE WORLD BUT IT
TURNED OUT THEY COULDN'T
EVEN CONTROL BULGARIA.
WHY DID THE ENTIRE COMMUNIST
SYSTEM COLLAPSE AND COULD
THE SAME THING HAPPEN
TO CAPITALISM?
>>GLEN: I DON'T KNOW,
I THINK THE REASON THE COMMUNIST
SYSTEM COLLAPSED WAS ONE WORD
RECREATIONAL VEHICLES.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN A RUSKY R.V?
HAVE YOU EVER SEE KARL MARX
DRIVING AROUND IN
A MOTORHOME?
>>HAROLD: OH NO,
NO IT WASN'T HIM.
>>GLEN: AND WHY NOT?
REMEMBER MAYDAY, YOU SEE I WAS
ON THE NEWS, THEY GOT THOSE
GUYS UP THERE WAVING AS ALL
THE MISSILES GO BY AND ALL
THE TANKS GO BY BUT NOT ONE R.V.
DO YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE THEY DIDN'T WANT PEOPLE
TO ROAM AROUND IN
THE SOVIET UNION, NO,
THEY DIDN'T WANT TO GIVE THEM
THEIR 4 TONS OF FREEDOM,
THAT'S WHAT IT WAS.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>GLEN: YOU GOT THE K.G.B.
YOU GOT THE U.S.S.R.
YOU GOT R.V.
COMMUNISM FELL AT THE KNEES
OF THE R.V.
>>HAROLD: WELL THANK YOU
MR. BRAXTON FOR THAT INTERESTING
INSIGHT INTO GLOBAL POLITICS.
>>GLEN: YOU SHOW ME A SOCIETY
THAT DOESN'T HAVE R.V.'S HAROLD
AND I'LL SHOW YOU A SOCIETY
THAT'S POLITICALLY AND MORALLY
AND SPIRITUALLY CORRUPT.
>>RED: THE WINNEBAGO
DOMINO THEORY.
>>RED: IT IS WINTER,
THE SNOW ON THE MOUNTAIN
REMINDS ME OF UNCLE LARRY.
UNCLE LARRY WAS NOT EDUCATED
BUT HE KNEW THE WOODS,
CONIFEROUS HE WOULD SAY,
WHAT THE HECK DOES
CONIFEROUS MEAN?
OR ECOLOGY, HE WOULD SAY,
WHAT THE HECK DOES ECOLOGY MEAN?
I REMEMBER THAT LAST TIME
WE WERE HIKING ON THE SNOWY
MOUNTAIN AND UNCLE LARRY
SAID HIS LAST WORDS TO ME,
AVALANCHE HE SAID TO ME,
WHAT THE HECK DOES AVA?
>>RED: ALL RIGHT, OH I FORGOT,
YOU MIGHT WANT TO MEASURE
THE WIDTH OF THE CANOE FIRST
TO MAKE SURE THAT IT'S
WIDE ENOUGH.
I GOT LUCKY THERE...
OKAY NOW WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS CHECK THE CUT END OF THE PIPE
TO SEE IF THERE'S ANY METAL
SPURS OR SLIPPERS
OR WHAT HAVE YOU.
YEAH, SHE'S LOADED WITH THEM.
ALL RIGHT NOW WE TAKE A FEW
OF THESE L-JOINTS AND T-JOINTS
AND WHAT HAVE YOU AND YOU
GOT TO CONNECT THEM TO THE
BIKES SO THAT WE CAN THEN
CONNECT THE RODS ACROSS TO THE
BIKES AND MAKE OUR FRAMEWORK.
SO WE'LL TAKE ONE OF THESE
T-JOINTS HERE AND JUST
STICK THAT DOWN RIGHT
ON THE HANDLEBAR.
NOW HOW'S THAT GOING TO HOOK
ON THERE IF IT'S SO SOLID?
MAYBE ONE OF THESE...
WELL I THINK WHAT WE'LL
HAVE TO USE HERE IS THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT,
AND YOU JUST SAVED YOURSELF
A $1,000 BUCKS.
YOU KNOW WHEN YOU'RE NOT
USING IT AS A BOAT TRAILER
YOU CAN USE IT AS A BICYCLE
BUILT FOR 2 AND IT'S ACTUALLY
BETTER THAN THE REAL BICYCLE
BUILT FOR 2 BECAUSE ON THEM
THE GUY ON THE BACK GETS
KIND OF A SCARY VIEW.
OKAY SO OUR TRAILER'S READY
FOR OUR LOAD,
SO LET'S GET OUR LOAD AND
PUT HER ON THE TRAILER.
HOOK THE BOTTOM UP, UP SHE GOES,
OKAY JUST PUT HER ON THERE
STRAIGHTEN HER UP.
A LITTLE BIT OF DUCT TAPE,
LOTS OF DUCT TAPE
THERE SHE GOES.
NOW WE JUST TAKE OUR TONGUE
AND WELL NOT OUR TONGUE,
THE TONGUE OF THE TRAILER
AND HOOK HER ONTO
THE HITCH HERE,
OKAY AND THEN ANOTHER LITTLE
PIECE OF DUCT TAPE,
SAFETY FIRST.
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT,
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME REMEMBER
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST FIND
YOU HANDY...
I'M GOING BOATING.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>BOB: OH! (GASPING)
IT WENT IN THE HOLE!
I SANK IT IN THE HOLE!
I PUT IT IN THE HOLE, ANYBODY,
I PUT THE BALL IN THE HOLE!
>>RED: BOB?
>>BOB: RIGHT IN THE HOLE.
>>RED: BOB, BOB, BOB, BOB.
>>BOB: RED.
>>RED: NO, NO, NO.
>>BOB: I PUT THE BALL
IN THE HOLE, IN THE HOLE.
>>RED: NO, NO, NO, NO BOB, BOB,
BOB, YOUR BALL'S BACK THERE,
IT'S IN A GROUNDHOG'S HOLE,
I JUST PUT THAT ONE IN THERE
YOU KNOW LIKE A LITTLE JOKE.
>>BOB: OH, OH A JOKE.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>BOB: WELL THAT WAS
A VERY GOOD JOKE.
>>RED: THANK YOU, YEAH.
>>BOB: ESPECIALLY THE PART
ABOUT THE BALL IN
THE GROUNDHOG HOLE.
>>RED: OH NO, NO, NO, NO, NO,
I'M SERIOUS ABOUT THAT PART.
>>BOB: NO, RED NO,
IT'S EITHER ALL A JOKE
OR IT'S ALL SERIOUS,
THAT'S THE WAY IT WORKS.
>>RED: OH.
>>BOB: AND SINCE THE BALL
IN THE CUP WAS A JOKE,
WELL I'M GOING TO HAVE
TO TAKE A FREE DROP, SORRY.
>>RED: BUSTER SAID YOU
WANTED TO SEE ME ABOUT
SOMETHING BOB.
>>BOB: OH YEAH THAT'S RIGHT RED,
I HEAR THAT MOOSE HAS MADE
A SLINGSHOT OUT OF
SURGICAL TUBING.
AND HE'S PLANNING TO WATER-SKI
WITH IT BY SLING SHOOTING
HIMSELF ACROSS THE LAKE.
>>RED: WELL I DIDN'T KNOW THAT
BUT IT CERTAINLY FITS HIS
PERSONALITY PROFILE.
>>BOB: ANOTHER JOKE.
>>RED: OH YEAH.
>>BOB: WELL RED DOESN'T IT
SEEM LIKE A TRIVIAL USE OF
A HIGH-TECH PIECE OF MEDICAL
EQUIPMENT TO YOU?
SLINGSHOT WATERSKIING, COME ON!
>>RED: WELL I'M SURPRISINGLY
UNCONCERNED ABOUT IT BOB.
>>BOB: MAYBE YOU SHOULD BE
CONCERNED ABOUT IT RED,
I MEAN IT COULD BE
ENVIRONMENTALLY HAZARDOUS,
I DON'T WANT PEOPLE FLYING
HEADFIRST INTO TREES AND
DENTING THEM, I MIGHT HAVE
TO CONFISCATE THAT HOSE FROM
MOOSE AND COULD YOU IMAGINE
HOW FAR THAT BABY COULD
FIRE A GOLF BALL?
IT COULD PUT ME ON THE PRO TOUR.
>>RED: WELL MOOSE THOMPSON'S
SLINGSHOT WATERSKIING UNIT
WAS A BIT OF A BUST.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
>>RED: NOTHING GOOD HAROLD.
HAVE YOU TRIED THE SLINGSHOT
WATER-SKI THING YET?
>>HAROLD: WELL I WANTED TO
BUT JUST EVERY TIME I GOT UP
TO THE FRONT OF THE LINE MOOSE
KEPT SLING SHOOTING ME TO
THE BACK.
ONCE WAS FUNNY BUT AFTER 6 TIMES
I GIVE UP YOU KNOW.
>>RED: WELL THE PROBLEM IS
THEY GOT THE THING WORKING
REAL GREAT,
BUT YOU KNOW ONCE MEN GET
SOMETHING WORKING THEY'RE
IMMEDIATELY BORED WITH IT,
SO THEY WANTED TO TRY SOMETHING
CALLED THE DOUBLE SHOOTER,
SO INSTEAD OF ONE GUY,
JUNIOR AND MOOSE BOTH HOPPED
UP INTO THE SLING THERE
AND THEN ALL THE OTHER GUYS
GOT TOGETHER AND PULLED
THE TUBING BACK AND THEY PULLED
IT SO HARD THAT THE TREES THAT
IT WAS TIED TO RIPPED RIGHT
OUT OF THE GROUND AND
SHOT PAST THEM.
>>HAROLD: THE SLINGSHOT
WASN'T MADE BY ACME COMPANY
BY ANY CHANCE WAS IT?
>>RED: NO WHY?
>>HAROLD: JUST ASKING,
BEEP! BEEP!
>>RED: ANYWAY IT'S NOT VERY
OFTEN YOU SEE A BIRCH TREE AND
ITS ENTIRE ROOT SYSTEM DOING
900 MILES AN HOUR EVEN UP HERE.
AND WHEN THE TREES ZIPPED PAST
THE GUYS IT ACTUALLY LIFTED
THEM RIGHT OFF THEIR FEET,
SO WE HAD A WHOLE BALL OF KIND
OF PLANT AND ANIMAL LIFE
HURTLING TOWARD THE 2-HOLER
WHICH I WAS COMING OUT OF.
>>HAROLD: WOO, HOLY!
>>RED: WELL THEY YELLED TO
WARN ME BUT THEY WERE TRAVELLING
FASTER THAN THE SPEED OF SOUND,
SO I DIDN'T ACTUALLY HEAR THEM
UNTIL 4 MINUTES AFTER THEY HIT
ME WHICH REALLY WASN'T ALL
THAT HELPFUL.
>>HAROLD: WELL I GUESS THAT'S
THE END OF THE SLINGSHOT THING
AND THE OUTHOUSE TOO.
>>RED: NO, NOW EVERYBODY WANTS
TO TRY THE DOUBLE SHOT THING,
I MEAN THESE GUYS NEVER HEARD
OF LIVE AND LEARN.
>>HAROLD: NO AROUND HERE
IT'S MONKEY SEE, MONKEY DO.
>>RED: I THINK I JUST
SPOTTED ONE.
♪ THERE'S A BIG RIG ♪
♪ SITTING IN THE PARKING LOT ♪
♪ AN 18-WHEELER ♪
♪ WHICH IS USUALLY ♪
♪ 9 ON EACH SIDE ♪
♪ THE DRIVER SQUEEZES ♪
♪ HIS BIG, FAT, TATTOO BELLY ♪
♪ IN BEHIND THE WHEEL ♪
♪ AND YOU CAN HEAR THE ROAR ♪
♪ OF THE DIESEL SQUEAL ♪
♪ HE DROPS HER INTO ♪
♪ ONE OF 32 GEARS ♪
♪ OH FOR GOSH SAKES ♪
♪ HE STALLED IT ♪
>>RED: EVERY WEEK WE DO
SOMETHING FOR THE YOUNG PEOPLE
AND UNFORTUNATELY THIS WEEK
IS NO EXCEPTION.
>>HAROLD: WELL HI,
I'M HAROLD GREEN AND WELCOME
ALL YOU YOUNG VIEWERS TO
'POSTURING FOR POPULARITY'.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
I FOUND THE SECRET TO IMPRESSING
THE OPPOSITE SEX,
I'M GOING TO SHARE IT WITH YOU
DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
THE SECRET OF IMPRESSING
THE OPPOSITE SEX IS LOOK SHARP.
IT'S TRUE, ALL RIGHTY,
SO NEXT TIME YOU'RE OUT IN
FRONT OF THE CAFETERIA
WAITING FOR ALL THE TOUGH
GUYS TO LEAVE, YOU SHOULD TIME
WISELY TO IMPRESS THE BABES
DON'T JUST STAND THERE,
STAND COOL, WATCH AND LEARN
MY FRIENDS, LET THEM THINK
THAT YOU'RE AN ATHLETE,
YOU'RE FRIENDLY BUT JOCULAR,
OR MYSTERIOUS.
WHO IS THAT GUY?
HE'S INTROVERTED ISN'T HE?
OH MY WHO IS THE SEXY DUDE?
I BET YOU THAT GUY IS A THINKER.
>>BILL: OH!
>>RED: I REALLY WISH BILL GAVE
US A LITTLE MORE WARNING
YOU KNOW WHEN HE'S COMING OVER,
2 OR 3 YEARS.
YEAH THANK YOU BILL.
DON'T TOUCH IT, DON'T TOUCH IT,
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THE HAT!
TIME NOW FOR
'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'
STARRING BILL.
OW! NOW THE IDEA HERE WAS,
OH GOD.
>>BILL: WHOA!
>>RED: THIS MAY NOT
LAST TOO LONG.
ALL RIGHT HE'S GOING TO,
THE IDEA BEING WE'RE TRYING
TO RAKE UP THE LEAVES,
IT'S THAT TIME OF YEAR WHEN
THE LEAVES FALL DOWN IN
THE FOREST AND SO ON AND
I WAS TRYING TO, BUT BILL SAYS
NO, NO, THERE'S A BETTER WAY,
HE STOLE THAT DUCT TAPE
RIGHT OFF MY WORKBENCH
I'LL BET YOU.
SO THE TROUBLE WITH BILL IS,
WELL I WAS GOING TO SAY HE'S
ALWAYS THINKING BUT HE'S
NOT ALWAYS THINKING,
HE'S ALWAYS DOING STUFF
AND THEN THINKING LATER.
BUT THE IDEA HERE WAS HE THOUGHT
IF HE TAPED A COUPLE OF THOSE
RAKES TO HIS BELT LOOPS
AND WE GOT THEM,
THEY'RE ON THERE REAL SECURE,
THEN HE HOLDS THE ONE RAKE
IN EACH HAND, HE'S REALLY,
HE CAN DO THE WORK OF
4 PEOPLE ALL AT ONE TIME
JUST RUNNING AROUND.
BUT HE WENT OVER THE BIKE AND
IT CAUGHT THERE AND THEN BILL,
BOY THAT DUCT TAPE REALLY
HANGS IN DOESN'T IT?
YOU COULD USE A BIT OF
DUCT TAPE WITH SOME OF THOSE
AND THEN HE GOT ONE OF THESE
LEAF BLOWERS WHICH YOU KNOW,
BILL, BILL, BILL, BILL, OH GOD!
YOU KNOW THE TROUBLE IS WHEN
A LOT OF TIMES WHEN YOU RENT
EQUIPMENT YOU DON'T GET
THE INSTRUCTIONS WITH IT.
(BILL SCREAMING)
>>RED: AND I'M NOT SURE IF BILL
WAS COMPLETELY SURE WHAT HE WAS
DOING THERE, ANYWAY THIS IS IT.
NOW THIS ONE I FOUND WAS VERY
INTRIGUING, HE HAD ONE OF THEM
PLASTIC GARBAGE CANS AND HE
SAYS THE IMPORTANT THING HERE
IS YOU GOT TO SEAL THIS INTO
IT IS COMPLETELY AIR TIGHT,
GET THAT LID ON THERE RIGHT
PROPERLY, THEN HE TAKES A HUGE
THING OUT OF HIS PANTS,
IT SCARED MOST OF US...
BUT HE FIRES THAT THROUGH
THE LID OF THE GARBAGE CAN,
NOW THE IDEA IS THAT APPARENTLY
THAT PICKAXE MAKES, OKAY.
>>BILL: OH, WHOA!
>>RED: IT MAKES A HOLE EXACTLY
THE SAME SIZE AS THE HOSE,
SO WANT HE WANTED ME TO DO WAS
TO TAKE THE END OF THE HOSE,
STICK IT IN THE HOLE THEN
IT'S LIKE AN AIRTIGHT SEAL
IN THERE AND THEN HE'S GOING
TO GET THE OTHER END OF THE HOSE
AND I THOUGHT HE WAS GOING
TO BLOW IN THIS BUT NO HE'S
GOING TO SUCK ON IT,
HE'S GOING TO SUCK ALL
THE AIR OF IT THERE,
BUT I THINK THE PROBLEM HERE
WAS WITH IT BEING PLASTIC
AND SO ON.
BASICALLY ALL HE DID WAS
COLLAPSE THE CAN AT THIS POINT
SO IT REALLY WASN'T MUCH OF
A USE SO, WE GOT TO RETHINK
THIS YOU KNOW, YOU GOT TO,
THIS IS SPEED.
>>GUY: HEY!
>>RED: OOPS, THIS WAS PLAN 'A'.
>>BILL: OH!
>>RED: OH, OH, OH, OH.
PLAN 'B' WAS HE WANTED ME TO
GET A METAL GARBAGE CAN,
THIS WAS HEAVY BOY I'M
TELLING YOU, IT DOESN'T LOOK
THAT HEAVY BUT IT, NO, NO,
NO, BILL, HE TRIED TO PICK
THESE UP AND BOY GOLLY WE WERE.
(AXE WHIZZING THROUGH THE AIR)
>>RED: OH WELL I DON'T
STAY IN THAT CABIN ANY MORE
BECAUSE THERE IS A PEEPHOLE
IN THERE NOW.
NOW HE SUCKS ALL THE AIR OUT,
THE TROUBLE WAS HE'S BRINGING
UP A LOT OF STUFF.
YOU KNOW HINDSIGHT IS A
GREAT THING, I THINK WE SHOULD
OF EMPTIED IT OUT, A LOT OF OLD,
ROTTEN LEAVES AND ACTUALLY
I'M NOT QUITE SURE WHAT THAT WAS
WE HAVEN'T HAD A PONY AT
THE LODGE FOR YEARS.
ANYWAY WE GOT THAT OUT OF THERE
AND WE GET THE LID ON THERE
AND NOW HE'S GOT IT AIRTIGHT,
YEAH IT'S WORKING AND YOU
CAN SEE IT JUST STARTING,
IT COMPRESSES A LITTLE
BUT NOT TOO MUCH.
THE IDEA BEING HERE WHAT YOU'RE
TRYING TO DO IS CREATE
A VACUUM INSIDE THE CAN.
THERE WE GO AND I KEEP MY THUMB
OVER SO WE GOT THAT CONTAINED
AND WHEN HE TAKES THE TOP OFF
IT'S JUST LIKE OPENING THE DOORS
FROM STAR TREK, YOU GET THAT,
IT'S LIKE A COMPLETE VACUUM,
I THINK THE SAME THING
IS UNDER BILL'S TOQUE.
ANYWAY HE'S GOT ALL THE LEAVES
IN THERE AND HE'S AS HAPPY
AS HECK BUT I JUST DIDN'T
GET TO HURT HIM AS MUCH
AS I WANTED TO.
>>BILL: OW!
>>RED: HERE'S RANGER GORD TO
TELL US ALL WHAT HE DOES WHEN
HE SPOTS A FOREST FIRE.
>>GORD: SURE WELL THE FIRST
THING I'LL DO IS I'LL DETERMINE
THE EXACT LOCATION USING
MY COMPASS AND MY BINOC...
(BINOCULARS GLASS SMASHING)
>>RED: OH BOY.
>>GORD: WELL USUALLY I
CAN JUST USE MY COMPASS.
BOY I HOPE THOSE DON'T RUST
OUT IN THE RAIN LIKE THIS.
ANYWAY, I'LL DETERMINE
THE EXACT, WHOA!
THAT LIGHTNING STRIKE WAS CLOSE.
MR. GREEN I'LL DETERMINE
THE EXACT LOCATION USING MY
COMPASS AND THEN I'LL CALL
IT INTO HEADQUARTERS,
ROBINSON CRUSOE TO MY MAN FRIDAY
THAT'S MY CODE NAME.
REPORT FOR DECEMBER 29TH.
>>RED: IT'S NOT DECEMBER GORD.
>>GORD: WEATHER, SEVERE
THUNDERSTORMS, FIRE DANGER LOW,
BOWELS REGULAR, I HAVE MY BEST
FRIEND MR. RED GREEN HERE
WHO'D LIKE TO SAY HELLO,
STAND BY, JUST SAY HELLO,
I'LL GET THE HEADPHONES
SO YOU CAN HEAR THEM.
>>RED: WELL THAT STUPID
SURGICAL TUBING WATERSKIING
SLINGSHOT THING HAS BEEN
DECLARED OFF LIMITS FOREVER.
FOR NOW ALL THE WATER-SKIERS
UP HERE CAN USE THOSE HUGE,
OVERPOWERED BOATS
LIKE NORMAL PEOPLE DO.
>>HAROLD: WHAT HAPPENED
UNCLE RED, DID THE GUYS RUN OUT
OF BIRCH TREES TO RIP OUT
OF THE GROUND?
>>RED: NO THEY GOT BORED AGAIN
HAROLD WITH THE DOUBLE SHOT
THING SO THEY ALL CLIMBED INTO
THE SLING THERE, WENT FOR WHAT
THEY CALLED A GANG SHOOT.
STINKY PETERSON HOOKED HIS DUMP
TRUCK UP TO IT AND STARTED
DRIVING DOWN THE DRIVEWAY.
HE GOT WAY DOWN ALMOST TO
THE ROAD THERE AND HE HAD HER
SO TIGHT, AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
SHE STARTED TO FRAY AND RUPTURE
AND RIP AND SPRUNG,
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN FLICKED
WITH A WET TOWEL HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: CONSTANTLY,
MY MOM CAN BE SO IMMATURE.
>>RED: WELL TRY MULTIPLYING
THAT BY 500.
>>HAROLD: WOO!
WHAT A BUNCH OF LOSERS!
>>RED: SORE LOSERS,
IT WAS A SNAP HEARD
AROUND THE WORLD.
SOME OF THE GUYS HAVE WELTS
YOU COULD FRY AN EGG ON.
NO REAL DAMAGE DONE BUT I DON'T
THINK THEY'LL BE WEARING
WOOL PANTS FOR A FEW WEEKS.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RIGHT,
WE GOT TO GO TO THE MEETING
NOW UNCLE RED.
>>RED: YEAH YOU GO AHEAD
HAROLD, I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
>>RED: WELL THAT'S ABOUT IT,
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING AND I WOULD
APPRECIATE IT IF YOU DON'T SAY
ANYTHING WHEN I TAKE MY
CLOTHES OFF TONIGHT,
JUST KIND OF LIMIT YOURSELF
TO THE USUAL SUBDUED LAUGHTER
AS YOU RUN TO KILL THE LIGHTS.
AND TO EVERYBODY ELSE,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING
AND KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
♪ ♪ ♪
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUONDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: SIT DOWN GUYS.
(GUYS MOANING & GROANING)
>>RED: SIT DOWN, SIT DOWN.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca