IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
WHAT'S RED AND GREEN
AND PLAID ALL OVER?
I'LL GIVE YOU A HINT.
YOUR!
WHOO!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
BY GOLLY -- OK, BEAUTIFUL.
THIS IS A BIG DAY,
PROBABLY MY FAVOURITE DAY,
NEXT TO CHRISTMAS
AND PANCAKE TUESDAY.
IT'S THE BEST DAY,
THE MOST FANTASTIC DAY.
IT'S NOT JUST THE GIFTS.
IT'S PEOPLE'S THOUGHTFULNESS,
THE APPRECIATION OF PEOPLE.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
THE BALLOONS AND THE FANCY CAKE
DON'T HURT AT ALL, EITHER.
WE'RE NOT TALKING ABOUT
THE SAME SPECIAL DAY, HAROLD.
WHAT SPECIAL DAY
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
ASPHALT DAY.
NO, I'M TALKING ABOUT
AUNT BERNICE'S BIRTHDAY.
WHAT?
AUNT BERNICE.
BERNICE? MY WIFE?
BINGO!
WHAT DID
YOU GET HER?
(Laughing)
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MAIN MESSAGE BEING,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
MAN! IT REALLY IS
BERNICE'S BIRTHDAY.
HER BIRTHDAY FALLS A WEEK
THAT'S HOW I REMEMBER IT.
WHAT IS ASPHALT DAY?
ASPHALT DAY,
HAROLD.
YOU KNOW,
ASPHALT DAY.
EVERY SPRING, THE HIGHWAY CREWS
FIX THE CRACKS
AND POT-HOLES IN THE ROAD.
THEY HEAD TO THE MAIN HIGHWAY,
BUT BEFORE THE ASPHALT COOLS,
WE DRIVE THROUGH THE HOLES,
UNDERCOAT ALL OUR VEHICLES.
THEN WE SCOOP UP
THE LOOSE ASPHALT,
TAKE IT HOME, AND
FIX OUR OWN DRIVEWAYS.
(Audience laughing)
WOW... UM...
I COULD SEE WHY
THAT'S EXCITING, IN YOUR MIND,
BUT I'M THINKING, YOU KNYOY,
MAYBE IT'S JUST SLIGHTLY
MORE IMPORTANT
E E BUCKET OF PAVEMENT.
I KNOW, HAROLD, BUT ALL
THE STORES WILL BE CLOSED.
IT'S NOT EVEN NOON YET.
IT'S ASPHALT DAY --
NOTHING'S OPEN.
OH, WAIT A MINUTE.
PORT ASBESTOS --
I'LL GO UP THERE.
IT'S NOT ASPHALT DAY THERE
TILL TOMORROW.
THAT'S 125 MILES AWAY.
BY THE TIME YOU ARRIVE,
EVERYTHING
WILL
BE CLOSED.
THEY'RE MORE COSMOPOLITAN
UP THERE.
THE GAS STATION'S OPEN
TILL 7:00.
(Audience laughing)
(Red): IN THE "ADVENTURES
WITH BILL" SEGMENT,
WE'RE GONNA BE
COOKING SOME HOT--
WELL, WE'RE STARTING
TO COOK THEM NOW,
BUT, YOU KNOW, BY GOLLY, JUST
TAKES YOU BACK, DOESN'T IT?
AND MY LUCKY CAMPING JACKET,
WHEN I WAS A KID --
I DON'T KNOW WHY BILL
FELT HE HAD TO WAVE
WITH HIS WIENIE BUT...
EVE WHEN YOUSTSTERSCK
WOULD BE MAYBE 9, 10...
SOME OF US WERE 17,
D DIDN'T MATTER.
WE WERE IN THEE E GRADE.
WE'D BE SITTING AROUND,
AND GET DOWN BY THE CAMP-FIRE
AND JUST...
WE WOULD USE THE STICKS,
YOU KNOW --
STICKS ON THE HOT DOGS,
AND EVERYTHING,
BUT BY GOLLY,
IT'S JUST KINDA NICE...
BILL SEEMS TO CARRY HOT DOGS
IN HIS POCKET.
I DON'T KNOW -- I GUESS
HE'S USING IT AS GRATUITIES
AT THE VARIOUS HOTELS
HE STAYS AT, I SUPPOSE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, BILL?
HE NEEDS THE COAT HANGER.
WHOA!
UH-OH!
OHHHH
DON'T EVER GET
A SNAKE BITE
DON'T EVER DARE ONE
TO STRIKE
DON'T TAKE A SNAKE AND
WRAP IT AROUND YOUR HEAD
ESPECIALLY WHEN
YOU'RE RIDING YOUR BIKE
ON THE HIGHWAY
OHH, DON'T EVER GET
A SNAKE BITE
'CAUSE, BELIEVE ME,
THAT HURTS PLENTY
AND DON'T DROP A RATTLER
INTO YOUR SHORTS
BUT THEN, HINDSIGHT IS
ALWAYS 20-20
OH, YEAH.
THIS IS FOR THE GRAND PRIZE
URURE SOUNDS,
RECORDED AT POSSUM LODGE,
WHEN STINKY PETERSON
ACCIDENTALLY HIT
THE RECORD BUTTON ON A DATE.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO MAKE MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSY
SAY THIS WORD...
"ALIEN".
NA-NA-NA-NA!
OK, GO.
ALL RIGHT,
IN THE MOVIE "E.T.",
E.T. WAS...
... MY IDEA.
(Audience laughing)
OF COURSE, SPIELBERG NEVER
GAVE ME ANY CREDIT... AGAIN.
YEAH, OK,
OK, FINE.
ALL RIGH
SAY ANXTXTRATERRESTRIAL
IN A SPACESHIP--
I CAN'T TALK ABOUT
THAT INCIDENT., NO.
NATIONAL SECURITY.
NO, HAP, A CREATURE
FROM ANOTHER PLANET.
VOLDAR.
PARDON ME?
THAT'S WHAT HE SAID
HIS NAME WAS.
I CAN'T DIVULGE MORE.
NO, HAP, I'M TALKING ABOUT
LITTLE GREEN MEN FROM MARS.
THAT'S A...
... A MYTH -- THEY'RE BLUE.
OH...
OH, BOY.
I MAY HAVE SAID TOO MUCH.
WELL, WE'RE
USED TO THAT.
I BETTER GET OUT OF HERE.
NATIONAL SECURITY.
"X-FILES" AND ALL THAT,
YOU KNOW.
THE TRUTH IS OUT THERE.
WAY OUT THERE.
(Laughing)
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
THOUGHT I'D GIVE
THE POSSUM VAN A PAINT JOB.
YOU'RE PROBABLY ASKING,
"HOW COME, RED?
"SHE LOOKS OK TO ME."
OR "DON'T YOU NEED
ONE OF THEM AIR COMPRESSORS?"
OR "WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS SHOW?"
LET ME ANSWER THAT
BY TELLING YOU,
NO, SIR, I DON'T NEED
ONE OF THEM AIR COMPRESSORS...
NOT WH G GOT 60 POUNDS
PER SQUARE INCH IN EACTITIRE.
GET YOURSELF A FUNNEL.
PUT YOUR FINGER OVER THE END.
PUT PAINT IN 'ER,
AND THEN WHAT YOU DO IS
YOU USE THE FUNNEL
TO PUT THE PAINT INTO THE TIRE.
OK, APPARENTLY THE AIR
DOES GET IN THE WAY OF THAT.
I'VE FLATTENED ALL FOUR TIRES.
FOR ONCE, I DID IT ON PURPOSE.
I NEEDED ALL FOUR BECAUSE I GOT
FOUR DIFFERENT KINDS OF PAINT.
I HAVE GREY AND BLACK
AND BLUE
AND THE LITTLE WHITE HIGHLIGHTS
ON HERE.
OUT OF MY FOUR TIRES,
LET'S SEE.
ONE IS OLD, ONE IS NEW,
ONE IS BORROWED...
SO THIS ONE, I'LL MAKE BLUE.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT PAINT
IN ALL FOUR TIRES.
NOW ALL'S I HAVE TO DO
IS JUST... PUMP 'EM UP.
(Grunting)
ALL RIGHT, NOW, YOU...
WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOU'RE IN PRETTY DECENT
PHYSICAL CONDITION
BEFORE YOU... PUMP UP
FOUR TIRES LIKE THAT.
JUST BECAUSE YOU SEE...
YOU SEE ME DO IT
DOESN'T MEAN IT'S SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD JUST
AUTOMATICALLY JUMP INTO.
I GOT THE PAINT
IN ALL FOUR TIRES.
NOW I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
THE PAINT IS WELL MIXED
ALL THE WAY THROUGH
ON THEM...
(Coughing)
IF YOU HAD A LEAKY VALVE,
YOU COULD PAINT THE TOWN RED.
THAT CAME OUT WRONG.
TO GET THE PAINT ONTO THE VAN,
YOU NEED THESE AIR HOSES, HERE.
YOU GET THEM
FROM YOUR LOCAL GAS STATION
AFTER THEY CLOSE AND MAYBE
THEY FORGOT TO BRING THEM IN.
SO I'VE GOT FOUR OF THEM,
ONE FROM EACH TIRE,
OR, I SHOULD SAY,
ONE FROM EACH COLOUR.
THEN, TO DISTRIBUTE
ALL THE PAINT,
I RUN 'ER THROUGH
ONE OF THESE SOFT-DRINK
DISPENSER NOZZLE UNITS.
I'M GONNA USE MAINLY BLUE,
SO I MADE THAT "COLA".
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I GOT SOME
VAN CUSTOMIZING TO DO.
(Clicking)
OHHH!
UH, ALL RIGHT,
I SHOULDN'T HAVE USED
THE QUICK-DRYING PAINT
ON THERE.
I'LL TELL YOU ONE THING.
I'LL NEVER HAVE A FLAT TIRE.
WAIT, NOW, WAIT, NOW.
NO, I THINK THE NOZZLE'S
JUST CLOGGED.
I'M GLAD THIS IS
A PLAID SHIRT.
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
WANT TO TALK TO YOU GUYS
WHO ARE THINKING
ABOUT GETTING MARRIED... AGAIN.
BEFORE YOU MAKE THE LIFE-LONG
TILL-DEATH-DO-US-PART
COMMITMENT THING
FOR THE SECOND OR THIRD TIME,
CAN I JUST ASK YOU
ONE SIMPLE QUESTION?
WHAT ARE YOU, NUTS?
WHY WOULD YOU GIVE UP THE ONE
THING THAT ALL MEN WANT?
FREEDOM.
I'M NOT JUST TALKING ABOUT
FREEDOM TO DRIVE ANYWHERE.
I'M TALKING ABOUT FREEDOM
TO DRIVE ANYWHERE...
THE WAY YOU WANT.
(Audience laughing)
FREEDOM TO STOP AT THE BATHROOM
WHEN
YOU
WANT TO.
FREEDOM TO GO TO THE
DRIVE-THROUGH WHEN YOU WANT TO.
THE FREEDOM TO BE ABLE
TO HOLD ON TO YOUR LOW-BROWED,
NARROW-MINDED,
SHORT-SIGHTED OPINIONS
WITHOUT EVER HAVING
TO DEFEND THEM.
(Audience laughing)
WHY WOULD YOU WANT
TO GIVE THAT UP?
BECAUSE YOU'LL HAVE TO.
OH, YEAH, OH, FOR SURE.
OH, YEAH.
SHE'S MARRYING YOU
FOR THE EXACT OPPOSITE REASON
THAT YOU'RE MARRYING HER.
SHE THINKS YOU'LL CHANGE.
(Laughing)
SHE THINKS YOU'LL CHANGE
FOR THE BETTER...
... IMPROVE WITH AGE.
HEY, THINGS DON'T IMPROVE
WITH AGE.
LOOK AT YOUR TRUCK!
(Laughing)
LOOK AT YOUR ROOF!
LOOK IN THE MIRROR!
SO FOR GOSH SAKE,
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE,
DON'T GET MARRIED AGAIN!
AND DON'T FEEL GUILTY.
I'M SURE SOMEONE ON
HER SIDE OF THE FAMILY
IS GIVING HER THE SAME ADVICE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Laughing and applause)
EVER GET THE FEELING
THAT CRUEL FATE IS
PLAYING YOU OUT LIKE A BASS?
WOULD THAT BE
A LARGE-MOUTH?
(Laughing)
WOULD THAT BE
A SUICIDE ATTEMPT?
(Audience laughing)
I'M HEADING OUT TO THE HIGHWAY
IN THE VAN.
SOME MORON TOOK ALL THE ASPHALT
OUT OF THE BIG POT-HOLE
BY PIE PEAK TURN-OFF.
MAN, I NAILED 'ER.
BENT A STRUT, BROKE A TIE ROD,
TOOK A GOOD SHOT
IN ONE OF MY BALL JOINTS.
I DIDN'T GET TO PORT ASBESTOS
AND COULDN'T GET BERNICE
A BIRTHDAY GIFT
AT THE GAS STATION.
A VERY NOVEL CONCEPT.
INTERESTING SHOPPING VENUE,
UNCLE RED --
A GAS STATION.
YOU KNOW, I GUESS YOU'RE AFTER
THAT HIGH-END STUFF --
THE FUZZY DICE, THE ROAD MAPS,
KEY CHAINS, THINGS LIKE THAT.
I WAS GETTING HER GLASSWARE.
IT'S FREE WITH A FILL-UP, OK?
THERE'S 12-OUNCE GLASSES.
THEY'RE UNBREAKABLE, AND
THE SUNOCO LOGO
MATCHES OUR KITCHEN.
OH! WELL, THEN,
YES, OF COURSE.
WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO NOW?
PLAN "B", HAROLD.
SELL ME YOUR GIFT.
I'D LOVE TO.
THANKS A LOT.
BUT I CAN'T.
THAT WOULD
BE WRONG.
AW, COME ON, HAROLD.
IT'S IMPORTANT,
WHAT I GIVE HER.
YOU'RE JUST A NEPHEW.
SHE COULDN'T CARE LESS
ABOUT YOU.
(Audience): AWWW!
THAT'S NOT EVEN TRUE!
I KNOW SHE LIKES ME!
I LIKE HER AND
SHE KNOWS I LIKE HER
BECAUSE I HAVE NEVER FORGOTTEN
HER BIRTHDAY.
WAHHH.
(Audience laughing)
TELL YOU WHAT YOU COULD DO.
ASK YOUR FRIENDS IF THEY HAVE
ANY USELESS GIFTS
THEY GAVE THEIR WIVES
BUT THE WIVES KNEW
IT WAS USELESS,
SO IT'S LAYING AROUND.
SO YOU'RE SUGGESTING I GET
A USELESS GIFT FOR BERNICE?
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'LL BREAK
TRADITION HERE, UNCLE RED.
(Audience laughing)
UH, HELLO, MY NAME'S DALTON.
I AM A MAN.
(All): HI, DALTON!
HELLO, MEN.
THE OTHER NIGHT,
I WAS WATCHING T.V.
I HAD THE REMOTE CONTROL
IN MY HAND.
MY WIFE WAS THERE
AND MY DAUGHTER WAS THERE
AND I WAS FLIPPIN' THROUGH
THE CHANNELS LIKE ALWAYS,
'CAUSE THERE WAS NOTHING ON,
WHICH IS SO DAMN TYPICAL!
ANYWAY, I WAS FLIPPIN'
AND FLIPPIN'
AND FLIPPIN' AND FLIPPIN'
AND, UH, YOU KNOW...
I KNEW I WAS DOING WRONG
BECAUSE THE T.V. GUIDE
WAS THERE.
THE T.V. GUIDE, YOU CAN NEVER
TRUST WHAT IT SAYS
BECAUSE THE DESCRIPTIONS
ARE NEVER VERY HELPFUL!
THE OTHER NIGHT, THEY HAD
THIS SHOW CALLED "FRIENDS".
I TURNED IT ON AND THERE WAS
NONE OF MY FRIENDS ON THEN.
ANYWAY, I WAS FLIPPIN'
AND FLIPPIN'
AND FLIPPIN' AND FLIPPIN'
AND SUDDENLY I HEAR THIS VOICE.
IT'S RIGHT IN MY HEAD.
IT WAS RIGHT THERE!
TURNED OUT IT WAS MY WIFE
BESIDE ME ON THE COUCH.
SCARED ME ANYWAY, THOUGH!
SHE SAID, "DALTON,
GIVE ME THAT REMOTE!"
YOU KNOW WHAT?
RIGHT THEN AND THERE...
I STOPPED FLIPPIN'...
AND I TURNED OVER
AND I HANDED THE REMOTE TO HER
AND I SAID, "HONEY...
"YOU... CHOOSE."
(Gasping)
WOW!
BIG STUFF!
THAT MADE ME FEEL
SO SICK TO MY STOMACH,
BUT I DID IT!
I LET MY WIFE CHOOSE
THE PROGRAMME SHE WANTED.
SHE WANTED TO SEE
"MARTHA STEWART LIVING".
WE WATCHED IT
FOR QUITE A WHILE.
I DON'T THINK
MARTHA STEWART IS LIVING.
I THINK THAT WAS SOME KIND OF
ROBOT THING ON THERE.
WE WATCHED IT FOR HOURS.
IT WAS THE WORST NIGHT
OF MY LIFE.
WE MUST HAVE WATCHED
FOUR OR FIVE SHOWS
ON HOME DECORATING,
ALL OF THEM FILLED
WITH IDEAS AND INFORMATION.
I DIDN'T WANT TO SEE
IDEAS AND INFORMATION.
I WANTED TO WATCH TELEVISION!
(Red): MEANWHILE, BACK AT
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL",
WE GOT ALL...
GOT THE WIENERS COOKED
AND THEY'RE READY TO PUT...
GOTTA BACK UP A LITTLE.
DROP THE WIENERS INTO THE BUNS.
THIS BRINGS ME BACK.
REMEMBER "THE ED SULLIVAN SHOW"
WHERE THE GUYS SPIN PLATES?
GET ONE GOING, THEN THE OTHER
WOULD ALMOST FALL...
THEN THE OTHER ONE,
THEN THEY GET--
THEN HE'D ADD ANOTHER ONE
AND THEN, ALL OF A SUDDEN...
THEY'RE GONE.
WHERE'S-- WHAT ARE YOU
DOING, BILL?
THEY GOTTA GO INTO THE BUNS.
HOLD THEM THERE?
UH-OH, BILL HAS A PLAN.
ON THE HAT, DOWN THE SHOULDERS,
AND...
OH, BY GOLLY.
PERFECT! OH, BY GOSH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE READY--
THEY'RE WARM, THEY SMELL GREAT.
JUST GONNA-- WHAT?
NO?
OH, BILL'S GOTTA PUT THE...
OH, MAN.
JUST A BIT OF THAT, BILL.
I'M NOT THAT FUSSY
ON THE...
OHHH...
YEAH, JUST PUT
A LITTLE BIT ON THERE.
I'LL SAY WHEN.
OK, WHEN.
WHEN.
OHHHHH!
WHEN!
THANK YOU, BILL.
WANT TO CHECK THE HEARING AID.
A LITTLE BIT OF RELISH.
NEED SOMETHING TO KILL
THE TASTE OF THE KETCHUP.
JUST A LITTLE BIT.
WHEN.
WHOA! WHOA!
YEAH, THAT SHOULD DO IT.
BOY, OH, BOY.
OOOH!
BILL'S JUST GONNA PUT
SOME MUSTARD ON HIS.
I DECIDED NOT TO HAVE
THE MUSTARD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HE COULDN'T GET 'ER OUT.
OK, ALL RIGHT, YEAH, OK.
YOU WANT ME TO HOLD--
YOU DID THE KETCHUP,
THE RELISH.
YOU WANT ME TO HOLD
THE HOT DOG--
NO, NO, NO!
UH-UH, MM-MMM.
LET'S TRY A SWITCH.... OHHH!
OHHH!
A THOUGHT WENT THROUGH
MY MIND, BUT... NO.
WE HAVE TO DO ANOTHER SHOW
NEXT WEEK... SO, UH,
STAND BACK, BILL.
THERE YOU GO.
JEEZ, I MAY HAVE MISSED THAT.
I COULD GO AGAIN, I SUPPOSE.
BILL, I COULD GO AGAIN,
IF YOU WANT.
HUH?
THERE'S SOMETHING YOU DON'T SEE
VERY OFTEN...
AN ARM WITH A HOT DOG
ON EACH END.
NO, THANKS, BILL.
MMM!
(Red): HERE'S A COMBINATION
FISHING ROD AND BAIT PAIL,
SENT BY A VIEWER.
I GOTTA GO HOME SOON.
I HAVE NOTHING FOR BERNICE.
YOU WERE RIGHT
ABOUT LODGE MEMBERS
AND STUFF THEY'VE BOUGHT
FOR
THEIR
WIVES.
THE SELECTION WAS THERE,
WASN'T IT?
YOU SHOULD HAVE
SEEN THE STUFF.
CREPE MAKERS,
HOT-AIR POPCORN POPPERS,
INDIVIDUAL GRILLED-CHEESE
SANDWICH WAFFLE-IRON THINGS,
A BREAD MAKER, ELECTRIC WIENER
WARMER... UNBELIEVABLE.
WHY DIDN'T YOU
BUY HER ONE?
BERNICE ALREADY
HAS ALL THOSE.
RIGHT, OK, YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU COULD DO?
GET HER A ROMANTIC INTANGIBLE.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA --
ARE THEY ELECTRIC?
(Audience laughing)
NO... NO, NO, NO.
IT'S LIKE, ONE TIME...
ONE TIME, RIGHT?
I HAD THIS CRUSH ON A GIRL
SO I GAVE HER A POEM.
WELL, I WROTE ONE.
WHEN IT CAME TIME
TO GIVE IT TO HER,
I PANICKED AND SWALLOWED IT.
I DIDN'T THINK SHE WANTED IT
AFTER THAT.
A POEM WON'T WORK, HAROLD.
NOTHING RHYMES WITH "BERNICE".
I KNOW WHAT I'LL DO.
I'LL BUILD HER SOMETHING,
ALL BY MYSELF,
RIGHT IN THE WORKSHOP.
YEAH, MM-HMM, YEAH.
NOTHING SAYS "I LIKE YOU"
LIKE GOOD ONE-SIDE PLYWOOD.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION,
WHERE WE EXPLORE
THOSE THREE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO DIFFICULT TO SAY.
(Audience):
"I DON'T KNOW!"
NOW, JOINING MY UNCLE RED IS
THE NEW PERSON
TO THE POSSUM LAKE AREA,
MR. KEVIN BLACK!
(Applause and cheering)
THE LETTER GOES AS FOLLOWS --
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"LAST YEAR, MY WIFE AND I
"HEATED OUR COTTAGE
WITH ELECTRICITY.
"WHEN THE BILL CAME,
"I HAD TO CASH IN
A SAVINGS BOND
"AND GET A SECOND JOB.
"IS THERE A CHEAPER WAY
TO HEAT A COUNTRY HOME?"
YEAH, THERE IS.
IT'S A SPECIAL SUBSTANCE
WE HAVE UP HERE
IN THE NON-CITY AREAS.
IT'S CALLED WOOD, ALL RIGHT?
IT GROWS ON TREES UP HERE.
(Audience laughing)
(Laughing)
NO,
HE'S KIDDING.
GO WITH GAS.
I'M BUILDING A PLACE HERE AND
I'M PUTTING IN A GAS FURNACE.
IT IS CLEAN AND INEXPENSIVE.
THIS WILL BE INTERESTING.
I THOUGHT YOU HAD TO HOOK
A GAS FURNACE UP
TO
SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, UH...
I BELIEVE THEY CALL THEM
GAS PIPELINES.
NOBODY HAS GAS
UP HERE.
OK.
OK, WELL, THEN, THE...
UH, THAT...
... TREE THING WOULD BE
THE WAY TO GO.
ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
IT MIGHT BE KIND OF FUN,
ROLLING UP THE SLEEVES,
SWINGING AN AXE.
NO, WE USE CHAINSAWS UP HERE.
I CAME HERE FOR THE QUIET.
CHAINSAWS ARE AWFUL NOISY.
I THINK YOU'D RATHER LISTEN
TO A CHAINSAW FOR A WEEK
THAN LISTEN TO AN AXE
FOR FIVE MONTHS.
ALL RIGHT,
WELL,
I'LL HIRE A LOCAL.
THERE MUST BE GUYS
WILLING TO WORK
FOR 80, 90 CENTS AN HOUR.
WHAT ABOUT
YOU, RED?
YOU NEED SOME
EXTRA PIN MONEY?
NO, THANKS, I HAVE ENOUGH PINS.
DON'T THINK YOU WANT ME
SWINGING AN AXE
UP AT BLOOD POINT.
IT'S CALLED BLUFF POINT.
NOT WHEN UNCLE RED'S THROUGH
WITH IT.
NO, THANK YOU,
I GOT MY OWN WOOD TO CHOP.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T MEAN
TO BE RUDE,
BUT I DON'T THINK YOU GRASP THE
CONCEPT OF BUSINESS MANAGEMENT.
WE DON'T, AND WE REALLY
APPRECIATE THE COMPLIMENT.
SEE, UH,
HOW IT WORKS IS
IF I CHOP YOUR FIREWOOD,
I GOTTA HIRE SOMEBODY
TO CHOP MINE.
HE'S GOTTA HIRE SOMEBODY,
AND SO ON.
WE THINK IT'S EASIER IF
EVERYBODY DOES THEIR OWN WORK
AND NOBODY HAS TO SPEND MONEY
THEY DON'T HAVE.
THEN YOU HAVE NO LOCAL ECONOMY.
NO, BUT WE HAVE THIS THING
CALLED A LOCAL REALITY.
WELL, THAT MAY...
THAT MAY BE ALL RIGHT
FOR THE BOONIES,
BUT I WOULD HATE TO SEE
WHAT THE CITY WOULD LOOK LIKE
IF WE OPERATED THAT WAY.
YOU'D HAVE MORE TREES
AND LESS GAS.
(Laughing and applause)
THIS IS THE ONE, HAROLD.
GET OFF THERE, YOU GOL-DARNED
SON OF A GUN.
I GOT 'ER THIS TIME!
CAN YOU IMAGINE
WHAT BERNICE IS--
I COME HOME -- LOOK AT THIS!
WHAT DO YOU THINK, HUH?
A DESK SET, HAROLD.
THAT'S A GAS-POWERED
PENCIL SHARPENER.
WE GOT A ONE-TON HOLE PUNCH.
HUH? EH? HUH?
WHAT DO
YOU THINK?
AHHH!
OHHHH! ASH TRAY.
SHE DON'T
SMOKE.
I'LL BUY HER CIGARETTES.
(Audience laughing)
COME ON, SELL ME YOUR PRESENT.
NO CAN DO,
NO CAN DO.
I WORKED HARD
ON IT.
IT'S SENTIMENTAL.
IT MEANS
SO MUCH.
FIFTY BUCKS.
SOLD.
ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
LET'S GET THIS
FROU-FROU STUFF OFF
SO SHE KNOWS IT'S FROM ME.
WHAT IS THIS, A CUSHION?
IT'S NEEDLEPOINT!
I WORKED REALLY HARD ON THAT.
"TO AUNT BERNICE.
"WITH LOVE,
YOUR NEPHEW HAROLD."
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
I'LL SEE YOU THERE IN A MINUTE.
YOU'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE?
ACTUALLY, YOU LOOK DOWN
ALREADY.
(Laughing)
WELL... IF MY WIFE IS...
OH, MY GOSH.
ARE YOU WATCHING, BERNICE?
WELL, UH...
I GUESS I'LL BE SLEEPING
ON THE PORCH TONIGHT
BUT DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'LL HAVE THIS CUSHION AND...
HEY, HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
AND REMEMBER,
YOU'RE NOT GETTING OLDER.
YOU'RE GETTING...
... MORE FORGIVING, I'M HOPING.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND THE NEEDLEPOINT MANIAC,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN.
IF ANYBODY'S TALKING
TO BUSTER HADFIELD, I WANT