IT'S THE "NEW RED GREEN SHOW!"
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
AND NOW HERE HE IS
THE LION IN WINTER,
MORE LIKELY LYING ON
THE LIVING ROOM
COUCH ACTUALLY.
YOUR HOST,
YOUR HERO,
MY UNCLE,
RED GR-E-E-E-N.
(APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
OH, BOY.
ALL RIGHT, APPRECIATE IT.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
POSSUM LAKE IS FINALLY
FROZEN RIGHT OVER.
NO, NO, IT DOESN'T
REALLY FREEZE,
IT CONGEALS.
HEY, WELL
WHATEVER, HAROLD,
THE THING IS WE CAN
SKATE ON IT NOW, MAN.
OF COURSE, THE PROBLEM NOW
IS WE'VE GOT THESE YUPPIE
COTTAGERS UP HERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY WANT
TO DO ON THE LAKE?
THEY WANT TO GO CURLING.
NO, NO, THAT'S EXCELLENT!
OH, NO, CURLING'S EXCELLENT!
IT'S A GREAT SPORT.
OH, YEAH, YOU SHOULD TRY
CURLING, UNCLE RED, YEAH.
HAROLD, IF BERNICE SEES ME
WITH A BROOM IN MY HAND,
IT'S ALL OVER, BUDDY.
SO WE GOT THE CLASSIC ARGUMENT
GOING ON NOW, YOU KNOW.
'CAUSE WE WANT TO
BE PLAYING HOCKEY,
AND THEY WANT
TO BE CURLING.
SO IT'S LIKE THE CATTLE RANCHERS
AGAINST THE SHEEP FARMERS.
WELL, DON'T LET THEM PULL
THE WOOL OVER YOUR ICE.
WOOL OVER YOUR ICE,
I SAID TO HIM.
BECAUSE IT'S LIKE WOOL OVER
YOUR EYES BUT IT'S DIFFERENT.
I SAID THAT.
IT'S EASY FOR YOU,
YOU CAN CHANGE CHANNELS.
(APPLAUSE)
[♪♪♪]
Red Green:
HERE'S A FEW SCENES
FROM THIS WEEK'S SHOW.
AS YOU CAN SEE
WE'RE GOING WITH...
KIND OF A WINTER THEME
FROM BEGINNING TO END,
GETTIN' INTO ALL
DIFFERENT TYPES OF SPORTS.
HERE'S ONE TYPE OF
SPORT RIGHT THERE.
BUT DON'T WORRY, WE'RE STILL
GOING DOWNHILL FAST.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
YOU KNOW,
UNCLE RED --
UNCLE RED, I DIDN'T THINK
YOU HAD TO BE SO RUDE
TO THOSE CURLERS.
OH, HAROLD, THEY WERE
ASKING FOR IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY
WERE WEARING?
MATCHING SWEATERS.
I THOUGHT THEY LOOKED SHARP.
YEAH, YEAH, YOU THINK
ACNE LOOKS SHARP.
ANYWAY, HAROLD,
I WAS MORE THAN FAIR.
I OFFERED THEM
A FAIR COMPROMISE.
YEAH, YOU SAID THEY
COULD USE THE RINK FROM
MIDNIGHT UNTIL DAWN.
THAT'S WHEN THE ICE
IS THE BEST.
HOW ABOUT THE FACT THAT IT'S
PITCH BLACK AND THERE'S NO
LIGHTS OUT THERE?
YOU DON'T NEED
TO SEE TO CURL, HAROLD.
ALL YOU NEED IS A
HIGH BOREDOM TOLERANCE,
AND MATCHING SWEATERS.
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
ANYWAY, WE CAME UP
WITH A PRETTY GOOD
SOLUTION I THINK.
OH, YEAH.
OKAY, OKAY.
KNOW WHAT THEIR
SOLUTION WAS?
I'LL TELL YOU
BECAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
ALL THE GUYS FROM POSSUM LODGE
CHALLENGED THE CURLERS
TO A HOCKEY GAME,
AND WHOEVER WINS GETS
FIRST DIBS ON THE ICE.
YEAH, WE'RE GONNA
BEAT THEM SO BAD
THEY'RE GONNA HAVE TO
FLY HOME ON THEIR BROOMS.
YEAH, YEAH, WENT UP
TO THE ATTIC THERE,
GOT OUT ALL MY
OLD HOCKEY EQUIPMENT.
I USED TO PLAY FOR THE POSSUM
LAKE INDUSTRIAL LEAGUE.
(APPLAUSE)
DON'T!
DO NOT
ENCOURAGE HIM!
DO NOT DO THAT.
HAROLD,
HAROLD.
THIS IS DISGUSTING.
DO NOT.
HAROLD.
WE WERE SPONSORED
BY A BREWERY,
THAT'S ALL, OKAY?
IT SURE CAME IN HANDY WHEN WE
HAD TO FLOOD THE RINK.
I STILL THINK
IT'S DISGUSTING.
WHAT ELSE YOU
GOT IN THERE?
LIKE, GUNS AND
KNIVES AND MACE
AND BRASS KNUCKLES?
JUST MY JOCK,
I THINK.
♪♪ OH, A HORSE WITH A HORN
IS CALLED A UNICORN ♪
♪ AND A HORSE WITH STRIPES
IS CALLED A ZEBRA ♪
♪ AND A HORSE WITH WINGS
IS CALLED PEGASUS ♪
♪ AND A HORSE WITH A
BROKEN LEG IS CALLED GLUE ♪♪
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
Mr. DALTON HUMPHREY OF THE
HUMPHREY'S EVERYTHING STORE
IS PLAYING FOR
THE GRAND PRIZE OF...
THIS WHISTLE.
WHISTLE SUPPLIED BY
MURRAY'S OUTDOOR STORE.
SPAT!
(BLOWING)
NO WONDER HE DONATED IT.
THE THING'S BROKE.
UNLESS, OF COURSE, I JUST GOT
SOME CORN CHIPS STUCK IN THERE
FROM MY RETAINER AGAIN.
(BLOWING)
(DOG BARKING)
UNCLE RED.
YEAH.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS TO GET
Mr. DALTON HUMPHREY TO
SAY THIS WORD...
COMPROMISE.
AND GO.
ALL RIGHT, DALTON,
A HAPPY MEDIUM...
THE AMAZING KRESKIN!
WHEN SOMETHING
IS 50/50...
100!
OKAY, OKAY.
LET'S SAY YOU AND YOUR WIFE
HAVE AN ARGUMENT...
NORMAL.
OKAY, OKAY, BUT YOU COME
TO AN AGREEMENT AFTER A
DISCUSSION, OKAY?
THERE'S BEEN A...
MIRACLE.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
YOU DECIDE TO DO
WHATEVER SHE SAYS, OKAY?
BECAUSE YOU...
MISUNDERSTOOD.
OKAY, THE SECRET TO GETTING THE
TWO OF YOU TO GET ALONG IS TO...
THREATEN TO CUT OFF BEDROOM
FAVOURS FOR AN ENTIRE YEAR.
YOU KNOW SHE HATES IT
WHEN I THREATEN THAT.
WE'RE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME, UNCLE RED.
ALL RIGHT.
DALTON,
YOU AND YOUR WIFE
GO INTO A FURNITURE STORE,
AND SHE LIKES ONE COUCH BUT YOU
LIKE ANOTHER COUCH, OKAY?
SO YOU MAKE A...
SCENE!
SPECTACLE!
A HUGE PRODUCTION.
NO, LET'S GO
ANOTHER WAY.
YOU DEMAND
TO BUY YOUR COUCH.
THEN YOUR WIFE SAYS,
"DALTON, YOU'LL HAVE
TO LEARN TO..."
SLEEP ON YOUR
STUPID COUCH.
AND I SAY, "FINE,"
AND SHE SAYS, "FINE,"
AND THEN WE GET
INTO AN ARGUMENT,
AND I POINT OUT
HOW SHE'S WRONG,
AND THEN SHE POINTS OUT
HOW I'M WRONG,
AND WE JUST
GET STEAMED,
AND FINALLY WE JUST
BUY BOTH DAMN COUCHES,
AND PUT AN END TO IT.
YOU'D BUY
BOTH COUCHES?
WELL, YOU GOTTA
COMPROMISE.
(FRANTIC BELL RINGING)
RIGHT HERE IS THE SECOND
BEST WAY TO SHOVEL SNOW.
YOU'VE SEEN THE DEAL.
OH,
GOSH, I'VE LOST MY SHOVEL.
BUT IF YOU'RE
MARRIED LIKE I AM,
YOU KNOW THE CHEESEY
EXCUSES ONLY WORK ONCE,
SO THIS WEEK ON
HANDYMAN CORNER.
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU A BETTER
WAY TO PLOUGH SNOW,
BY MAKING
A SNOWPLOUGH.
WE ARE GOING TO ACTUALLY USE
THIS DOOR AS OUR PLOUGH
BECAUSE SO FAR AT THE LODGE
WE'RE NOT USING IT AS A DOOR.
ALL RIGHTY, YOU SEE WE HAVE
A BIT OF A PROBLEM.
THE DOOR IS KIND OF SITTING
LOW ON THE GROUND THERE,
SO WE NEED SOMETHING
FOR IT TO SLIDE ON.
NOW, I COULD PUT
A TOBOGGAN UNDER THERE
OR MAYBE ONE OF
THOSE FLYING SAUCERS.
THEN I REMEMBERED THE
HANDYMAN CODE, HUH?
PUT SOMETHING YOU
DON'T USE TO GOOD USE.
SO I'M GOING TO USE THESE
CROSS-COUNTRY SKIS
THAT BERNICE GAVE ME FOR MY
BIRTHDAY AFTER THE CHECK-UP.
THEY ARE A LITTLE
BIT TOO LONG,
SO WHAT I WOULD DO IS JUST
TRIM THEM DOWN AND JUST
USE THE TIPS ON THOSE.
THAT WOULD PROBABLY
WORK PRETTY GOOD.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE
A PAIR OF THESE,
YOU CAN PICK THEM UP REAL CHEAP
AT A GARAGE SALE ANY TIME
A FAT GUY HAS ONE.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S GOT IT.
BUT YOU KNOW ME, I LIKE TO BE
DOING TWO THINGS AT ONCE,
THAT WAY I CAN MOVE SLOWER.
SO I CAN ALSO BE SALTING AND
SANDING WHILE I'M PLOUGHING.
THAT WILL REALLY GET THE
NEIGHBOURS TALKING.
SO WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS GET
YOURSELF A COUPLE OF SALT
SHAKERS FROM YOUR LOCAL
RESTAURANT.
YOU'RE THINKING TO YOURSELF, HOW
THE HECK AM I GOING TO GET SALT
SHAKERS FROM THE RESTAURANT?
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING...
DEEP POCKETS HELP.
ALL RIGHT, TAKE THE SALT SHAKERS
AND ATTACH THEM TO YOUR TIRES
WITH THE HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON.
THESE UNITS LOOK
PRETTY SHARP DON'T THEY?
OF COURSE, THE KEY TO ANY
KIND OF A SNOWPLOUGH IS,
YOU HAVE GOTTA HAVE SOME WEIGHT
IN THE BACK TO MAKE HER WORK.
SO I'M GOING TO THROW A FEW
YARDS OF SAND IN THE BACK
OF THE VAN THERE
NOT ONLY WILL IT
GIVE ME THE WEIGHT,
THE SAND WILL SIFT DOWN
THROUGH THE RUST HOLES
IN THE FLOOR THERE
AND SAND THE ROAD.
AND RUST THE ROAD.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, THAT FLOOR
DOESN'T LOOK TOO BAD.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO PUNCH
SOME HOLES IN THAT MYSELF.
(GUNSHOTS)
YOU MIGHT WANT TO WEAR
EAR PROTECTORS IF YOU --
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
DO YOU SMELL GAS?
EVERYBODY HEAR ME?
AM I TALKING?
HELLO.
OH, GEEZ, MY VOICE IS GONE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, YOU WANT A WAY
THAT EVERYBODY IS GOING TO BE
ABLE TO SEE YOU COMING,
SO I WENT DOWN TO ONE
OF THEM GARAGE SALES,
GOT MYSELF A COUPLE OF
TURNTABLES HERE.
AND THESE GO REAL FAST IF
YOU SET THEM ON 78 R.P.M.;
AT LEAST, THAT'S WHAT MY
GRANDFATHER TOLD ME.
SO REMEMBER...
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
(ENGINE REVVING)
LET ME TAKE A SECOND AND TALK TO
YOU OLDER FELLOWS ABOUT ANGER.
NOW, I DON'T MEAN
YOUR OWN ANGER
BECAUSE THAT, OF COURSE,
IS PERFECTLY HEALTHY AND NATURAL
AND REALLY NEEDS
TO BE EXPRESSED.
OH, YEAH.
IF YOU DIDN'T
EXPRESS YOUR ANGER,
HOW WOULD THE REST OF
THE WORLD LEARN ANYTHING?
NO, NO, I'M TALKING ABOUT
OTHER PEOPLE'S ANGER, YOU KNOW?
NOW, THE FIRST QUESTION THAT
GOES THROUGH YOUR MIND IS,
WHAT CAN I DO TO
PLEASE THIS PERSON?
THE ANSWER, OF COURSE, IS...
NOTHING.
NO, YOU ASSUME THAT BECAUSE
THEY'RE ANGRY AT YOU,
THEY'RE ANGRY AT YOU.
OTHER PEOPLE AREN'T ANGRY
AT YOU OR WHAT YOU DO,
OR HOW YOU DO IT.
THEY'RE JUST ANGRY.
YEAH, YOU HAPPEN TO BE HANDY
FOR THEM TO BE ANGRY AT.
SO DON'T TAKE IT PERSONALLY.
LET ME EXPLAIN IT
ANOTHER WAY.
MY WIFE BERNICE
IS ALWAYS CHILLY,
ALWAYS GOT THE
EXTRA SWEATER ON.
NOW, JUST BECAUSE SHE'S CHILLY
DOESN'T MEAN SHE'S CHILLY AT ME.
SHE'S JUST CHILLY.
SO SOME PEOPLE ARE JUST TALL;
SOME PEOPLE ARE JUST HAPPY;
SOME PEOPLE ARE JUST ANGRY.
AND THE BEST WAY TO DEAL WITH
ANGER IS THE POSSUM WAY...
ROLL OVER AND PLAY DEAD.
OH, YEAH.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
IT'S VERY HARD TO BE ANGRY
AT A DEAD THING.
JUST ASK MY WIFE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
HA HA HA.
WELL, I HAD A BIT OF A SETBACK
AT OUR HOCKEY PRACTICE TODAY.
THAT'S THE WORST TEAM
UNIFORM I'VE EVER SEEN.
WELL, WE USED TO HAVE THE
SPONSOR'S LOGO ON THERE,
BUT THEY FOUND IT WAS
HURTING THEIR BUSINESS,
SO THEY RIPPED
THEM ALL OFF.
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW,
EVERYBODY'S UNIFORM
LOOKS LIKE THIS.
OH,
MATCHING SWEATERS.
LIKE I SAY, WE WERE AT
THE PRACTICE THERE,
AND BUSTER HADFIELD
IS IN GOAL,
AND MOOSE THOMPSON COMES
STREAKING DOWN THE
LEFT WING THERE,
AND HE LETS
A SLAPPER GO.
HOLY MACKEREL!
IT HITS BUSTER ABOUT FOUR
INCHES ABOVE THE FIVE HOLE.
WHOA, RIGHT --
WHERE IS THAT?
YOU KNOW HOW BUSTER HAS
A FALSE SET OF TEETH?
WELL, NOW HE HAS
A FALSETTO VOICE.
(play on "false set of")
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
DID HE HIT, LIKE,
A HIGH "C"?
MORE LIKE A
HIGH "F", HAROLD.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
ACTUALLY HE SAID
THE WHOLE WORD.
BUT THE POINT IS WE'RE
LOOKING FOR A NEW GOALIE,
AND I'LL TELL
YOU SOMETHING, HAROLD,
YOU WERE OUR
UNANIMOUS CHOICE.
ME?!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
THERE WE GO.
NO, NO, NO.
COME ON, HAROLD.
YOU CAN WEAR AS MUCH
PADDING AS YOU WANT.
NO, NO.
IT WON'T BE US
SHOOTING AT YOU, HAROLD,
IT WILL BE
THE CURLERS.
HAROLD.
THERE'LL BE
GIRLS WATCHING.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
BUT YOU OWE
ME BIG TIME.
OKAY.
GET YOUR COAT ON.
LET'S GO.
HOW COME BUSTER WASN'T WEARING
ANY PADDING, YOU KNOW,
BETWEEN THE PIPES?
WELL, NO POINT IN PROTECTING
A PART OF HIS ANATOMY
HE NEVER USES, EH?
I GUESS THAT'S WHY YOU
DON'T WEAR A HELMET, HUH?
(APPLAUSE)
AND NOW WELCOME TO THE
EXPERT PORTION OF THE SHOW,
THAT PORTION OF THE SHOW WHERE
WE EXAMINE THOSE THREE LITTLE
WORDS THAT MEN FIND SO
HARD TO SAY...
Audience:
I DON'T KNOW.
IMAGINE IF THEY SAID THAT.
ANYWAY, JOINING MY UNCLE RED
ON THIS PART OF THE SHOW
IS HIS BEST FRIEND
Mr. MIKE HAMAR.
WELCOME MIKE.
(APPLAUSE)
OKAY, THE LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"I FIND IT IMPOSSIBLE TO GET
MY HUSBAND AND TWO TEENAGERS
"AWAY FROM THE
TELEVISION FOR SUPPER.
"I WOULD BE OVERJOYED IF THEY
COULD JUST SKIP ONE HALF HOUR
"SO THEY COULD ALL SIT DOWN
AT THE TABLE AND TALK AND EAT
TOGETHER LIKE A REAL FAMILY.
"WHAT SHALL I DO?
"WHATEVER HAPPENED TO THE
LOST ART OF CONVERSATION?"
WELL, I DON'T THINK ANY
CONVERSATION THAT WENT
ON AT MY HOUSE
COULD BE CONSIDERED ART.
IT'S MORE LIKE SPORT,
CONTACT SPORT.
THINGS GET A LITTLE
OUT OF HAND, DID THEY, MIKE?
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
A LOT OF HUBBUB.
MY UNCLE WOULD BE HIDING
UNDER THE COUCH,
AND SOMEBODY WOULD
BE IN THE CORNER BLEEDING.
MY DAD WAS ALWAYS IN A BAD MOOD
BECAUSE HE WAS BEING ARRESTED.
YOU KNOW,
THE USUAL STUFF.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THIS
PARTICULAR VIEWER
JUST WANTS TO TURN THE T.V.
OFF AND HAVE A SIMPLE
DINNER CONVERSATION
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, IT MAY
NOT BE THAT SIMPLE.
THIS IS A WOMAN,
SHE SAYS SHE'S
GOT A HUSBAND.
SHE'S GOT A COUPLE
OF TEENAGERS.
I'D SAY SHE'S BEEN MARRIED FOR
QUITE A WHILE NOW, YOU KNOW.
WELL, NOT NECESSARILY.
MY PARENTS HAD THEIR
8th ANNIVERSARY
WHEN MY YOUNGEST
BROTHER WAS 23.
OKAY, BUT THEY'VE BEEN LIVING
TOGETHER FOR A WHILE,
AND WHEN PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
LIVING TOGETHER FOR
A LONG TIME,
SOMETIMES THEY DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO SAY TO EACH OTHER.
OR YOU DO TRY TO SAY SOMETHING
CASUALLY AT DINNER
AND, LIKE, THE NEXT THING
YOU KNOW, YOUR SISTER'S
BEING SUBPOENA'D.
I THINK THAT'S
THE WORD FOR IT.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW --
AND THERE'S ANOTHER DANGEROUS
SIDE TO THIS, HAROLD.
WHEN PEOPLE DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO SAY TO EACH OTHER,
THEY END UP
CRITICIZING EACH OTHER.
YEAH, YEAH, AND YOU DON'T WANT
THAT AT THE DINNER TABLE
BECAUSE THESE FOLKS ARE
PACKING CUTLERY, RIGHT?
YOU GET SOMEBODY WAVING
A STEAK KNIFE AROUND,
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
YOU'VE GOT AN EXTRA EAR
ON THE CORN PLATTER.
WELL, HERE'S MY ADVICE
TO THAT LADY.
JUST TURN THE T.V. OFF
'CAUSE THERE'S NO PROGRAM
AS GOOD AS TIME SPENT
WITH YOUR FAMILY.
EXCEPT FOR
"AMERICA'S MOST WANTED."
THAT'S THE SAME AS SPENDING
TIME WITH MY FAMILY.
Red Green"
HERE'S SOMETHING
YOUNG PEOPLE DO.
IT'S CALLED SNOWBOARDING.
WE'RE GONNA TRY IT.
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
TOO MUCH FUN TO ME.
I DON'T KNOW --
NO THANKS BILL.
DON'T NEED THE
ICE RIGHT NOW.
SO THE IDEA IS YOU GO DOWN --
BILL, UH, THE BOARD...
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO BE
SOMEHOW ATTACHED TO THAT?
I DON'T KNOW, I'VE NEVER
DONE IT, BUT IS THIS RIGHT?
DOES THIS SEEM RIGHT TO YOU?
DOESN'T SEEM RIGHT TO ME.
WHAT?
OH, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
GOT TWO MORE BOARDS.
ALL RIGHT, BILL, I THINK
I UNDERSTAND THE THEORY.
WE'RE NOT DOING
THIS AGAIN, ARE WE?
THERE WE GO.
OH, THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
OH, I SEE, SO I'LL
NEED TWO BOARDS.
IT LOOKS AWKWARD TO ME.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I GUESS THAT'S
THE RIGHT WAY.
WATCH OUT FOR
THE VAN, BILL.
OH, NO, HE'S GOT IT.
FENCE!
OH, YOU GOT IT.
THERE.
STOP.
OH, OH, YOU DON'T EVEN
NEED A SNOWBOARD.
JUST USE A 4x8
SHEET OF PLYWOOD.
JUST LIKE BILL:
GOOD ONE SIDE.
SHE DUG IN.
SHE'S GOING OVER, BILL.
SHE'S GOING OVER.
NO, NO, I'LL HELP HIM.
OKAY, I'LL HELP HIM.
YEAH, I'LL HELP HIM.
OH, LOOK, STILL GOT A PULSE.
GET THAT BOARD OFF HIM THERE,
AND HE'S PROBABLY ALL RIGHT.
BILL, ARE YOU OKAY?
BILL?
GREAT.
I HOPE HIS FACE
IS AT THIS END.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
HAROLD, YOU COMING?
Harold:
YEAH, I'LL BE
RIGHT THERE.
WELL, THE BIG HOCKEY GAME TO
FIND OUT WHETHER POSSUM LAKE
IS FOR CURLING OR FOR HOCKEY
TAKES PLACE IN
ABOUT AN HOUR.
THE REST OF THE GUYS ARE ALREADY
UP THERE HAVING A COUPLE OF
BRACERS FOR WARMTH.
SOMETIMES THEY GET SO WARM
THEY CAN HARDLY MOVE.
(APPLAUSE)
HOW DO I LOOK?
WOW, HAROLD!
THAT BUBBLE WRAP?
YOU KNOW IT.
IF YOU GET INJURED WHERE
WOULD YOU LIKE TO BE SHIPPED?
I DON'T PLAN ON
GETTING INJURED.
NO, I THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO BE OKAY, HAROLD.
I SEE YOU'VE GOT
THE MAJOR ITEMS --
OH, THE FRY PAN'S
A NICE TOUCH.
HOW DO YOU WANT 'EM?
SUNNY-SIDE UP?
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
ANYWAY BUT SCRAMBLED
IS OKAY BY ME.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, JUST A
LITTLE WORD OF ADVICE.
YOU MAY WANT TO FLIP THAT
FACE MASK DOWN ONCE THE
HOCKEY GAME GETS STARTED.
OH, YEAH.
OH, MAN.
BOY, IF THERE WAS EVER ANYTHING
SCREAMING FOR A SLAP SHOT,
THAT'S GOTTA BE IT.
COME ON, HAROLD.
THIS IS THE REPAIR PART
OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
"IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYIN'."
WE'VE GOT OUR WATER TAXI
CAPTAIN, HAP SHAUGNESSY HERE.
HOW YOU DOIN' HAP?
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
FOR US TODAY?
I'VE GOT A FIREPLACE
GRATE HERE, RED.
OH, BOY, THERE'S BEEN
SOME WEIGHT ON THERE.
YOU MAY BE NOT DRYING YOUR
FIREWOOD ENOUGH THERE.
WELL, IT'S SOLID STEEL.
LOOK AT IT.
THEY DON'T MAKE STEEL
LIKE THEY USED TO.
NO, BUT THE BEAUTY HERE IS YOU
PUT A LITTLE HEAT ON THAT,
AND WE CAN BEND
THAT RIGHT BACK.
WHAT HAPPENED ANYWAY?
YOUR SISTER FALL INTO
THE FIREPLACE AGAIN?
NO, NO, NO, A BURGLAR
STEPPED ON IT.
WELL, THAT'S GOTTA BE SOME
FAT BURGLAR, I TELL YOU.
YEAH, NO KIDDING.
BROKE INTO MY HOUSE
OVER THE HOLIDAYS.
MUST HAVE SLID
DOWN THE CHIMNEY.
KIDS TODAY, EH?
CAN'T THROW THE ROCK THROUGH
THE WINDOW OR ANYTHING.
GOT TO GO THEIR
OWN WAY ON IT.
DID THEY TAKE ANYTHING?
NOTHING.
JUST ATE SOME
COOKIES AND MILK,
AND LEFT US
SOME PACKAGES.
OKAY, SO YOU'RE SAYIN' SOMEBODY
CAME DOWN YOUR CHIMNEY
DURING THE HOLIDAYS,
ATE COOKIES AND MILK
AND LEFT YOU SOME PRESENTS?
WAS HE WEARING RED WITH
WHITE TRIM ON IT, HAP?
DIDN'T SEE HIM, RED.
THE WIFE AND I HAD SETTLED IN
FOR A LONG WINTER'S NAP.
(APPLAUSE)
I HEARD A CLATTER ARISE,
BUT I DIDN'T GET UP TO LOOK.
I SUPPOSE I SHOULD HAVE
OPENED THE WINDOW AND
Both:
THROWN UP THE SASH.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
SO, OKAY, SO YOU'RE SAYING
SANTA CAME TO YOUR HOUSE
OVER THE HOLIDAYS.
SANTA?
YEAH, SANTA, YEAH!
NEVER THOUGHT
OF THAT,
BUT YOU COULD
BE RIGHT.
IF PEOPLE FIND OUT SANTA IS
REAL AND HE CAME TO MY HOUSE,
I BET PEOPLE WOULD
PROBABLY PAY TO SEE THAT.
RED, RED, FORGET ABOUT
STRAIGHTENING THAT.
I NEED THAT BENT
JUST THE WAY IT IS.
THAT'S MY PROOF.
ALL RIGHT, YOU TELL THE STORY
EXACTLY THE WAY YOU TOLD ME.
THAT WILL BE MY PROOF.
(APPLAUSE)
NOW, I TELL YOU THAT HAS
TO BE THE LOW POINT,
GETTING BEAT AT OUR NATIONAL
GAME BY A BUNCH OF CURLERS.
37-NOTHING.
NICE GOAL TENDING, HAROLD.
(MUMBLING)
I MADE SOME STOPS.
THAT WAS ONE OUT
OF YOUR MOUTH.
TWO, THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX,
SEVEN, EIGHT.
NINE.
OH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
BUT HAROLD,
YOU LET IN 37 GOALS.
HOW DOES THAT HAPPEN?
WELL, THEY WERE
CURLING THEM AT ME.
YOU KNOW,
"SWEEP! SWEEP!"
THAT'S SCARY
WHEN THEY DO THAT.
I GOT NERVOUS.
IT WOULD HAVE HELPED IF
I HAD HAD A LITTLE
OFFENCE, YOU KNOW.
MAYBE IF YOU GOT
JUST ONE GOAL.
EVEN IF YOU GOT
ONE SHOT ON GOAL.
WELL, HAROLD, THEY MADE THE
RINK THE SAME SIZE AS
THEY DO FOR CURLING.
YOU KNOW WE CAN'T
SKATE THAT FAR.
(POSSUM CALL)
MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO
AHEAD, GUMP.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
TAKE IT EASY.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I HOPE YOU'RE IN
A ROMANTIC MOOD,
I'VE ALREADY SUFFERED
ONE SHUTOUT TODAY.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND ALL THE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTER]
Harold:
HERE HE COMES!
SIT DOWN!
HE LIKES IT WHEN
EVERYBODY SITS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
OKAY, ALL RISE.
Everyone:
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red:
SIT DOWN.
Harold:
OKAY, WE'VE JUST GOT
ONE QUICK ANNOUNCEMENT.
THERE'S GONNA BE A MEETING
OF MEN AGAINST MALLS,
MAM, AS THEY LIKE
TO BE KNOWN AS.
THEY ARE GOING TO BE FILING A
GRIEVANCE AGAINST BACHELORS
AGAINST MARRIAGE,
OR BAM, AS THEY LIKE
TO BE KNOWN.
Red:
SOUNDS LIKE IT'S
GOING TO BE
SLAM, BAM, THANK YOU, MAM