You ever notice how
you always lose more
than one thing
at a time?
Like, say, your car keys
and your temper?
Well, I got this
neat trick.
I duct tape my car keys
to a cell phone.
Now, when I need
to find them,
I just dial
the cell phone
and look around the house
for where the ringin's
coming from.
[ PHONE VIBRATING ]
Man, I hope I didn't
set it on vibrate.
[ PHONE VIBRATING ]
See, now, that's why
I hate technology.
Harold's going
to need a new phone.
And I'm going
to need a new car.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Thank you very much.
All right.
Thanks very much!
I appreciate that.
Big, big week up
at the lodge this week.
Harold has broken up with
his girlfriend, Bonnie.
AUDIENCE: Awww!
Yep, all the guys
feel pretty sorry for him,
trying to cheer him up.
Some of them are even
talking to him.
Oh, hey,
Harold.
Did you want
to see me?
Yeah, notice anything
different, Harold?
You're gonna
do the laundry?
No, no, no.
No, I've got a little
surprise for you.
You doing the laundry
would be a surprise.
Now, Harold,
you don't know this,
but I feel
sorry for ya.
Well, right
back at ya'.
No, no, no,
Harold,
I know you're upset about
breaking up with Bonnie.
I'm fine.
No, you're not.
You know what
you need, Harold?
Yes, I do actually.
No, you don't, no.
You need to be my partner
in a two-man kayak race.
Wow!
What a compliment!
What a potentially
life-threatening
compliment,
but still...
Do we even have
a two-man kayak?
We will.
Here,
you go practice.
I never worked
one before...
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
And tonight, Mike Hamar
is playing for
a free gourmet meal and
toenail clipping
at Marjorie's Epicure
and Pedicure.
For meals and heels
just pull up a chair
and pull off your socks.
Okay, Mike,
cover your ears.
Red, you've got 30 seconds
to get Mike to say
this word...
Yeah, all right,
Dalton.
And Go!
Okay, Mike, over the years
in your dealings with the law
you've made a few...
Plea bargains?
Yeah, no.
Okay, in your criminal
activities in the past,
they were all...
Lifestyle choices.
Okay, okay.
But looking back
at those now,
you can see you
made a lot of...
Money.
Yeah, but you don't
do that anymore
because you
learned from your...
Parole Officer.
Okay, Mike,
if you made a bunch
of faux pas, those are...
Desserts?
They're delicious.
The cream, the caramel
are just so fantastic.
I really like them.
Okay, Mike,
we say, We're all human,
nobody's perfect.
We all make...
Gas.
Almost
out of time, Red.
Okay, Mike, you've given up
being a criminal
because you got
tired of making...
Bail.
No, I'm talking about all
the crimes you committed.
Those were the biggest
what of your life?
Oh, thrills.
Except for the times
I got caught.
Those are mistakes.
There we go!
Yeah! Yeah!
MIKE: How do you know
if you have body odour?
When you say "you"
do you mean me,
specifically,
or people in general?
I think he means
you specifically.
No, I mean people
in general,
present company
included.
How can you tell if
you have a bad case
of body odour?
You sure you don't mean
Winston, specifically?
I think the bigger
question is
who is going
to tell you
if you have some
offensive problem
like b.o.?
Or bad breath.
Or feet.
Because you've got
to hear it, you know.
You know,
as Anthony Anthony says,
"When we listen,
"truly listen,
"we can hear...."
ah, something or other,
I can't remember
what it was.
It's really -- I mean,
who is going to tell you
if you suffer from
something offensive
and embarrassing,
like some kind
of personal problem?
Is your friend going
to tell you that
you smell?
No, 'cause then you
don't want him as
a friend, right?
RED: All right, Winston,
you have b.o.
That's the thing,
because who don't
like you
are not going to tell
you stuff to your face.
They're going to do it
behind your back, right?
And if they really
don't like you,
they're not going
to tell you anything at all
ever, at all, ever.
Like my dad.
RED: And Mike, you smell
like an ashtray.
So no one's going
to give you the
bad news.
No one.
Nope.
And if you did get
the bad news,
would you be
willing to hear it?
Well, sure.
I would.
How else are you going
to improve, Red?
[ APPLAUSE ]
Man, the roads
around here
are in terrible shape.
It wrecks your car,
and it limits your speed.
It's almost enough
to make you pay your taxes.
But rather than do something
I know I'll regret later,
I've been trying to find
a way to smooth out the ride.
Now, this one
worked great
the odd time the helmet
actually lined up with
the pothole.
Other than that, it felt
like you were walking
with one high-heeled
shoe on...
not that
I've done that.
Now, this one wasn't
totally successful
because I forgot that
Bernice is allergic
to feathers.
I even tried filling up
the potholes.
Everybody at Bernice's
work gets one of these
totally uneatable
Christmas cakes
every year for
the last 35 years,
so we've got a
fair whack of them.
And if you
flip them over,
they're the same size
and shape as the pothole.
The trouble is,
after 35 years,
the Christmas cakes are in
about the same condition
as the road.
But then, in today's paper,
something caught my eye,
right about there.
No, no, I was looking
through the personals
to see if any of my old
girlfriends have come
to their senses,
when I saw some guy's
trying to unload
an above-ground pool.
And I'm thinking, hey,
that could be just the ticket.
Now, I don't have any
money to give him,
but maybe we can work out
a trade of some kind.
We'll see.
Okay, that was
a mistake.
I should have
emptied it first.
The only thing I need
from the pool is the side.
Cutting it in half
so I get two wide rings
of sheet metal.
It's light,
it's durable
and it's smooth,
a lot smoother than
the roads around here.
But I'm not going to be
driving on the roads anymore.
I'm going to be driving
on these babies.
Maybe I'm getting
a little ahead of myself,
but I'm just trying
to keep up with you guys.
I'm using these
lawn mower handles
as guides
for my pool sides.
Of course, taking the
handles off the lawn mowers
means I can't
cut the grass,
so it's a win-win.
The idea here
is to put something
between your
tires and the road,
something that will
smooth out the bumps...
kinda like your
what wife does
between you and
the neighbours.
Funny how slipping a ring on
can change your life forever.
Now, I'll just glide
over the potholes.
And here's
another bonus...
real easy to find this car
in the parking lot.
So remember, if the women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
And if the cops
pull you over
and ask you what
the heck it is,
tell them
it's a car pool.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I know it took a while,
but I've finally,
mostly, pretty much,
begun to embrace
the Internet,
especially the stuff
on used-crap.com.
The problem is
just as I was getting
comfortable with this
technology,
they went ahead
and invented the blog.
This is the place
in cyberspace
where any person whose
brain is half the size
of their leisure time
can spout off about what they
think of what they do
or who they feel should be
running the country.
It used to be called,
Talking to Dad.
But of course
now it's gone global.
A lot of you older guys
are logging on.
Well, here's my advice:
log off.
Your own wife doesn't
particularly care
that you're getting close
to patenting your idea
for the T-shirt with the
deodorant built right
into the armpits.
What makes you think
they're dying
for this information
in Finland?
My advice is
to relax
and go back to annoying
your immediate family.
And if at the end of the day,
you really feel
like you just got
to share your opinions
and petty complaints
with the whole world,
do it the
old-fashioned way...
get your
own TV show.
Remember,
I'm pulling for you.
We're all
in this together.
Don't play Texas Hold 'Em
with your septics.
If you see one,
and it raises you
two on the river,
call me before you
go all in.
C'mon, Harold,
we're good to go.
Okay, I'll
be right there!
Two-man kayak
trials are today.
You know, I think Harold
and I can win this thing,
if we can figure
out how to cheat.
You know, Uncle Red,
I don't know about this.
We're going
to be fine, Harold.
Here, put your
number on.
I'm a zero?
This is supposed
to cheer me up?
Well,
look at this way,
if the boats finish
in numerical order,
you'll be ahead
of number one.
See, I went
with number nine,
that's Bobby Hull's
number.
Because we're going to be
in a bobbing hull?!
Right, we're going
to be in bobbing hull.
You know Harold,
I can't wait for your
first Eskimo roll.
Well, me either,
me either.
I hear they're
delicious.
Yeah.
Well, the kayak's
all ready, Harold.
We're going
to clean up.
Wow, I never thought
I'd be going down
the river
in a 12-foot Maytag.
You'll be going
down the river just
fine, Harold.
Or up the creek.
Why do you always have
to be so negative,
Harold, eh?
She's light.
She's strong.
She's seaworthy.
And the galvanized
metal is perfect
for the toxins
in our fresh water.
It doesn't look
very comfortable.
No, no, it's fine.
I took the agitator out.
But you just
put him back in.
Right?
Bobbing hull,
bobbing hull!
RED: Bill and Winston went
down to the batting cage
we have just outside
Possum Lake there.
And Bill's in a hurry
but Winston says,
Don't forget your helmet.
You need the batting helmet.
There you go -- Oh!
Just a little outside.
That's a little small.
No, you got to get
that on there, Bill.
Get it on there.
Get it on -- no!
Look out, look out,
look out... oh!
Look at the bright side,
the hat fits now.
and they've
got all the gear.
Actually, Bill was going
to do the batting
and Winston was going
to do the catching.
Ooh, oh it's --
Oh, safety --
safety is an important.
I think that's supposed
to go under the --
All right,
all right, okay.
I hope the Ride Program's
not out today.
And so, as I was saying,
Winston was going to
do the catching,
and Bill was going to --
easy, ohh --
Look out, look out,
look out.
Okay. Okay.
Wow.
No kids, eh?
All right, so you've seen
these batting cages deal.
You get in, you pick
your favourite bat
and you get ready.
Bill's got quite
a wind up going there.
I think you missed --
No, no, let --
leave well enough alone.
I think you missed
an important step here.
You've got to --
It involves --
Bill, Bill, Bill, Bill.
Money, quarter.
Money, quarter,
in the box,
Quarter in --
quarter --
Yup, yup,
quarter in, quarter.
Then you can pick what kind
of pitch you want there.
You got slow ball,
slow pitch.
He goes for the fast ball,
and that's all ego.
All ego right now.
So he gets ready.
Here comes the fast ball.
And...
So Bill's still
watching.
Reaction time
a little slower.
You know, yeah...
So maybe
let's re-think that.
Go with the slow pitch.
He's going to be able
to hit this one.
So he gets back
and in she comes.
He just drills it,
and it goes right down
the throat of the machine,
jams all the machinery.
Now they got no more
balls coming,
so they decide to approach
the machine with caution
and see if they can --
I think if you just touch it
you may be able to
free that up,
but just be careful.
You might want
to shut that off first
before you actually --
Oh! Oh!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh!
All right,
later that day
he decided to try
the knuckle ball.
Nobody ever got hurt
with a knuckle ball.
No, no, you got
to wait for it.
You got to --
patience is a big --
No, no,
that won't help.
Get back in
the batter's box.
Just wait --
wait for it!
You're at strike three
and the ball's
not even there yet.
All right, yeah, bunt,
bunt, that's a good idea.
Oh... oh!
So Bill abandons the bat,
picks up the plate and...
Oh!
Okay, you know what,
Bill, you're out,
and I believe
so is Winston.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Sometimes, when men look
like they're goofing around,
we're actually
thinking.
And the opposite happens
even more often.
So you probably figure
I'm just playing
with this radio-controlled toy,
but I'm actually working on
one of the biggest unsolved
dilemmas facing
modern man.
How to drive while
you're eating...
without spilling
stuff on yourself.
Let's say you need
a little snack
to tide you over.
Triple cheeseburger
in one hand,
extra large pop
in the other,
half a pound a fries
on your lap.
Get yourself an extra-grip
cover for your stirring wheel,
make sure it's got
the big bumps on it.
That's for traction.
Okay, you secure the
toy truck to the dashboard,
using the handyman's
secret weapon.
Then you mount the controller
under the steering column
so you can steer
with your leg.
Kind of
like a dog does.
Problem solved.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I've got some
arteries to clog.
Okay, you might to check
the batteries in the toy,
before heading out.
[ APPLAUSE ]
We lost.
I little tip for you
kayakers out there...
if you're in a boat made
from washing machines,
they have a tendency
to go into the spin cycle.
Harold and I spun
into a rock.
Kayak broke in half,
so instead of having
a two-man kayak,
we had two
one-man kayaks.
I'm sure I'll be able
to get this off
once the swelling
goes down.
Uncle Red,
Uncle Red...
I know, I know,
Harold, I know --
Uncle Red.
I know.
No, you don't know.
You don't know
anything, ever.
Yes, I do,
Harold.
I know the two-man
kayak was a mistake.
I should have thought
it through --
Yeah, Uncle Red,
Uncle Red,
I was talking
to Bonnie.
Well, that's good,
I'm glad you were
talking to Bonnie
because you shouldn't
be unfriendly to her
because --
Uncle Red, she gave me
a ride home in her car!
How did you get to
sit in her car with
a thing on like that?
I stood on the tailgate.
Would you let me finish,
please?
Well, pick it up
a little bit, Harold!
I want to get out
of this kayak.
I asked Bonnie
to marry me!
AUDIENCE: Ohhhhh!
[ APPLAUSE ]
I couldn't have
heard that right.
I must still have
some water in my ear.
No, you heard me
absolutely correct.
I have asked Bonnie
to be my wife.
Wow!
You know what,
that's the dumbest
thing I ever heard of.
Well, she said yes.
I stand corrected.
No, you don't get it,
Uncle Red.
This is like one of
those weird life moments.
You know,
where I realize,
that Bonnie and I,
we need to be together.
You know, Harold,
wait a second.
You had a
rough day, okay.
You went down the river
in a washing machine kayak.
You banged your head
on at least seven rocks.
And your paddle.
Oh yeah!
[CHUCKLING]
But you need to
just slow down a bit.
Bonnie's not the
right girl for you.
Come on, you may be
half cra --
Hi Bonnie, just
talking about you.
Yes, Mr. Green, I need
a little favour from you.
Oh,
here we go.
Harold looks
up to you.
He respects you
very much.
And now that he is
going to be my husband,
I would appreciate it
if you didn't, like,
accidentally kill him
before the wedding!
I think she's got a point.
I have to agree with that.
That's reasonable.
Well, okay.
I'll stop trying
to turn Harold
into a man
because it's
probably hazardous
to his health,
how's that?
Thank you, Mr. Green.
All right,
you're welcome.
I'll see you
later, Pookie.
Awww.
See you later,
Mrs. Pookie.
Pookie or spooky,
you tell me.
AUDIENCE: Oooooooh!
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
What was that?
That's the meeting,
Harold.
Oh, right.
You go ahead,
I'll be right down.
Right.
Harold, we have
the meeting downstairs.
Oh yeah, right.
That's a big load.
So if my wife
is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting.
Harold asked Bonnie
to marry him,
and she felt so sorry
for him, she said yes.
Sound familiar?
And the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself
and Harold
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge,
keep your stick
on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Okay, guys.
Everybody,
sit down.
Everybody sit down.
All rise.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
RED: Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the Man's Prayer.
I'm a man,
but I can change,
if I have to...
I guess.
All right men, big news,
Harold and Bonnie
are getting married.
[ CHEERS ]
See, they're really
happy about it.
Misery loves
company.