You know, the problem with
making a man-sized
submarine sandwich
is the mess you make
trying to eat it.
You bite into this baby
and you're going
to have more spillage
than the Exxon Valdez.
But as always,
where there's a will,
there's a handyman.
Get yourself an
old caulking tube.
Empty it first.
Okay, now instead of putting
the goodies into the sandwich,
you put them in here.
Okay, we're ready
for the next step.
Get yourself a drill bit
that's the same size
as the widest part
of the nozzle.
It doesn't matter what
kind of bit it is.
Wood, metal, even concrete,
this won't be hard to drill
and if you don't
have a vice,
just hold the bun
between your legs
and you'll find out how
a submarine sandwich
got it's name.
[ DRILLING SOUND ]
Okay, make sure you don't
drill all the way through.
Anybody who's had the flu
knows it's impossible
to control both ends
at the same time.
And we're good to go.
Okay, we got her
all filled up.
Now comes the tricky part.
Getting the tube out
and plugging the hole
with a gherkin.
And it's just that easy.
No muss, no fuss and
she's real good eating.
[ SOUND OF GLASS BREAKING ]
Next time I'll
hold the pickle.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Thank you very much.
Appreciate it.
Well big, big week
up at the lodge this week.
Harold's been asked over
to his fiancee's house
to meet everybody
in the family.
So I made him a little
gift to take along
and help make a good
first impression.
Normally, the only
people that like Harold
at first sight
are dentists.
You know Uncle Red --
Yeah?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I don't think I
should take a gift.
What?
I don't think I
should take a gift.
I think they should
accept me just as I am.
Well that's a lot
to ask, Harold.
And you know, I've put a
lot of work into this gift.
I've wrapped it
and everything.
Oh my.
I wonder what it could be?
Well you know when
Bonnie's family sees you
they'll probably say
exactly the same thing.
Why I'm just sure they already
have a barbeque, Uncle Red.
Oh no, not like
this one, Harold.
It's remote controlled.
Oh, how does that work?
Pretty well.
So are you going to
take the gift or not?
Well I guess so.
Yeah, I mean, it's
certainly different.
You should talk.
I mean, I really like
the safety aspect of it.
I'm just worried they
may not get it to work.
I don't suppose
you wrote a manual?
Well Harold, it's just
like unlocking your car.
Oh hey look,
it's suppertime.
Let's fire
up the barbeque.
[ EXPLOSION ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Today's winner
receives this coupon
for one free anger
management class
at Big Bob's Institute
of Tough Love.
You've tried the rest,
now sit down and shut up.
All right, cover your
ears there, Mike.
Red, you've got 30 seconds
to get Mike Hammer
to say this word...
All right Winston.
And go!
Okay, Mike,
your father is?
One of three guys.
Okay, this is a person
who raises children.
Oh, detentions officer.
Okay, um, let's say
you're a kid
who wants to
go to a movie
that has sex and
violence in it.
You need to
bring along a?
Fake I.D.
No, okay, okay.
When some woman is
about to have your baby
that means soon you'll be?
Hiding out in Mexico?
All right,
remember last year,
you were dating that woman
and you were nervous
about meeting her?
Husband.
No, uh, okay, okay.
Let's try this.
These are older people
that you loved when you
were growing up
but they're gone now.
Grand?
Oh, Funk Railroad.
Almost out of time, Red.
Yeah, uh...
Okay Mike, when you
think of your mother,
you think of a single?
Stuffed into
her G-string.
You know, everybody in
the world has two of these
and you can't come
up with the word?
Apparently not.
There we go!
[ BELL RINGING ]
Yeah!
Well, I'm not getting any.
You know, there are so
many ways to take that.
And all of
them are correct.
You know what I'm
going to do?
What?
I'm going to read
the newspaper.
You know, I never get
to do it at home
because I'm always getting
interrupted by the wife
or the daughter
or the phone
or the crap
on television.
Hey, I catch
one lousy fish
and you go and
throw it back in.
Well, it's floating
there, scoop it up.
Fine.
There you go, Mike.
Now you've
caught two fish.
Oh wow.
A woman in Ohio gave
birth to a 90-pound dwarf
who brings a message
of world peace.
Really?
Yeah, it says
so right here.
Wow, no kidding, eh?
Yeah, here's a
political article too,
it says,
Alabama town sheriff
is actually a beagle.
No kidding, eh?
I wondered what Huckleberry
Hound was doing.
It's true, Red,
look, look.
They've got a
picture of the dog
in uniform right there.
That's fake, Dalton.
What?
They'd never let
the ears stick out
through the
hat like that.
Every police dog I ever met
was always plainclothed.
Well it says here, the beagle
has a specially-adapted
squad car that
doesn't have a siren
because he can stick his
head out the window
and go arrooooo.
Dalton, you don't
believe that.
Why not?
It's in the paper.
Yeah, well instead of
looking at a tabloid,
try a real newspaper.
Okay, ambassador predicts
Middle East peace.
The Mayor promises
no new taxes.
Hollywood wants to make some
more family-friendly movies.
Here.
[ CRASH ]
You know, there are two things
every man finds hard to do.
Number one is parallel park.
Number two is explain to your
wife why you watch this show.
Now, I can only deal with
one problem at a time
so I'm going to focus
on the parallel parking.
The problem is pretty simple.
You need the car
to move sideways
but the wheels
don't point that way.
What if you add
a set of wheels?
Smaller wheels?
These are brand
new caster wheels.
They're too pricey for me
so Dalton just
loaned me a bunch.
Or, at least, I'm sure
he would've if he was home.
Now I'm going to
mount those casters
on this heavy-duty
piece of marine plywood.
Okay, I'm not good with metric.
This is one-inch ply
but if you were buying it
from a Canadian lumber store,
you got to switch
over to celsius
which I believe is
nine deca-heca-liter.
Okay, this first
thing you want to do
is you got to cut this thing
so it's the same length
as the distance between
the front and back wheels.
For once in my life,
everything's working
out perfect.
Okay, I got the board
mounted on there
with a jack in each corner.
Got the casters underneath
pointing sideways.
This looks like
a winner to me.
How can you lose
with four jacks?
The jacks are activated
by what were cordless drills
but I've got them running
off the cigarette lighter.
They're nine-volt drills
and the car is 12-volt
so that should save
me a lot of time.
And the beauty of DC is that
you can reverse the drills
by just switching the wires.
So I got one cigarette lighter
for lowering the unit
and I got another
one for raising it.
I'm done with
parallel parking.
I'm into
perpendicular parking.
[ SOUND OF CORDLESS DRILL ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
Then when I'm ready to go,
just roll the car out,
and drop the tires
back on to the road.
So remember, if the women
don't find you hand --
hand --
oh...
They should at least
find you creative.
[ CAR STARTING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
You know, a lot
of guys my age get upset
because they can't seem
to find a decent conversation.
They say nobody wants
to talk to me anymore.
When the truth is nobody wants
to listen to you anymore.
Conversation is an art
not an outlet, okay.
It's not a sporting event
where your goal is to dominate.
Think of the last conversation
you had with a friend.
Oh, I know, you rattled on for
15 minutes without breathing.
But what did they say?
What did you hear from them?
Was it phrases
like, oh really?
Well, well...
and I got to go?
Then no wonder you can't
find a conversation.
You don't need a friend,
you need a podium.
Try being on the receiving
end a little more often.
You know, even a sewage plant
has to take something in
before it spews anything out.
And you might want to
think before you talk.
Don't walk up to
the new neighbour
and start ragging on
about all the problems
with organized religion
only to find out
he's a Lutheran minister.
And don't say
the word porker
until you've seen
the size of his wife.
Every time you shoot
your mouth off
you hit yourself
in the foot.
Try listening.
You've got one mouth
and two ears.
There's a reason for that.
I, on the other hand,
have a hat over mine.
Remember, I'm
pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
There's a famous quote
that says,
you can never go home.
Well if this applies
to your house,
maybe it's time you
get your septics pumped.
Oh, there we go.
Yeah, Dalton asked me
to find this bottle
of animal musk.
There's a female scent
in there that attracts
the male animals
when you spread it out
on bushes or whatever.
It's kind of like
sex appeal in a bottle.
It scares me to think
what Dalton wants it for.
Oh boy.
How do I look?
Oh Harold, don't
ask me that.
I'm not a good liar.
You see, I'm a
little bit nervous.
You know, I want Bonnie's
parents to really like me.
I mean, I am marrying
their daughter.
Yeah, well, I'm thinking
they waited a while
so they probably lowered
their standards a bit.
Seriously, I look okay?
No, you look fine.
I smell okay?
You look fine.
This is that aftershave
they advertise on T.V.
It smells a lot
better on T.V.
Well I'm going to go
meet my new family.
I sure hope they're
not a bunch of dorks
or something
like that, eh?
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red, did you find
that bottle of musk?
Yeah, it's right here.
What do you want
it for, Dalton?
Well you know, I
spread it around
the parking
lot of my store.
Customers see the animals
and they don't look
so closely at my prices.
Oh, that's good.
This isn't right.
This smells
like aftershave.
No, this is
aftershave, here.
No, no, Red,
that is animal musk.
Harold!
[ APPLAUSE ]
Bill and I are going to
spend the day on the lake
and he wanted to
use the canoe
but I just didn't feel
like going in the canoe.
Bill had a little more
sanding to do so I --
Bill, no, do
something else.
I have a boat --
I had left a boat
up there in the woods
a couple of years back
and I knew exactly
where it was.
Sorry Bill.
Yeah, she's down
in here somewhere.
Yeah, here we go.
The boat right here,
oh, oh, oh.
Watch out for the tongue
of the trailer there, Bill.
Yeah so I figured I'd
go get the possum van,
clear some bush
out of there
and we'll just
haul her out.
It's got the hitch on
the back and everything.
So as I was going
back to the van
I noticed there was a
bit of the broken --
I thought maybe I'll
just cover that up.
It's kind of
a little recycling
and I don't want
Bill to see that.
You know, that was a
complete accident
as far as I'm concerned.
So we get the possum van
hooked up to the boat trailer
and attached her real good
is that the trees had kind of
grown up around the boat
there was no way I could get it
cleared out of there, so...
There was no way of
getting the boat out
unless we knock
some of those --
Do we need to take
some of those trees down?
That's the only way --
Bill's got an idea.
He's got an axe.
Oh... okay.
That's not really what
I had in mind, Bill.
I noticed that the head
is now missing on his axe
and we're looking
around for that.
Can't figure out
quite where that went.
So I got a hole
in my boat now
and there's only one thing
worse than a hole in your boat
and that would be two
holes in your boat.
Now where's the
head of the axe?
There it is,
yeah, okay.
All right, so, yeah.
Luckily Bill gets back
working on the boat.
You know, I'll tell
you one thing,
the trees are safe.
I take the --
Okay, let's
get the axe --
Now let's try something
a little safer than that.
All right, this is --
Same problem.
All right, think of
something else, Bill.
Must be something else.
Bill?
Okay, got an idea.
Okay, now do not ever fill
your chainsaw up like --
I'm thinking to myself,
this is going to be interesting.
and it is.
Get the --
No, no, no, no.
So he gets her going and I
think he had the mix off
on the oil and gas
cause she was
smoking real good.
It got the point like I
couldn't see what he was doing.
That didn't matter.
The big problem was he couldn't
see what he was doing
but the trees
were coming down.
So I thought okay,
benefit of the doubt,
we'll get the boat out
but I'm not sure it was
technically even a boat
any more at this point.
Okay, Bill, now what?
Well good ol' Bill always
has another plan.
So he starts pulling
the logs together
and I realize
what he's up to.
Down to the boat ramp.
We got the outboard mounted
on the back of a log ramp
with the boat windshield
and the canoe front.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Remember when you used to
have these electric blankets
with the dual controls
so your wife could simmer
on her own side of the bed.
Then, once the
hot flashes started,
you replaced this baby with
a 40-horsepower ceiling fan.
Well today, we're going
to turn this unit into
something useful.
Okay, first you want to cut --
No, first... unplug it.
Second, cut the one side
into strips about a foot wide.
Now you're probably
going to snip through
a few wires as you go
but just reconnect them later
with the handyman's
secret solder.
Okay now you just attach
those strips to the edge
of the other half
of the blanket
and that way the dual
controls will allow us
to set one temperature
for the centre
and a different temperature
for the outside.
Have you figured out where
I'm going with this?
Me neither.
Oh yeah, I know.
Now I never have to worry
about dinner getting cold again
because on the outside edge
I've got her set on warm
because that's where
my dinner plates are
and then for the serving
dishes in the middle,
I've got her cranked
to the max.
Now, if you're serving
something cold like salad,
well... don't.
Nobody likes salad,
serve hot dishes.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I see by my electric blanket
that it's time
for me to tuck in.
[ ELECTRICAL ARCING ]
Wow, Harold's been over at
Bonnie's place for a while
and I haven't heard
any emergencies
on the police band radio.
So... I guess
everything's okay.
It was an accident that
he covered himself
with animal musk.
It's probably
worn off by now.
[ HAROLD SCREAMING ]
There's a wolf!
A wolf!
He chased me all
the way home.
What does he want?
Probably just
your phone number.
I got an idea.
Take the jacket off
and we'll splash some
animal musk on it.
I thought that
was aftershave.
Yeah, I made a mistake.
It turns out Old Spice
is young moose.
Oh, but I
like this jacket.
Not as much as
mister wolf does.
Get it off there.
Why can't I have
a normal life?
You don't want
to know, Harold.
Okay, give me the jacket.
Take this.
On boy.
We shouldn't be
watching this.
No.
They're in love!
Oh, I know, I know.
Boy this is all happening
on the first date, huh?
Do you know what,
I'm going to give
him a little privacy.
What should I do.
Wait a couple of minutes
and then toss the
wolf a cigarette.
Boy, this musk stuff
is pretty powerful.
Well you know
it's nature.
Nature's the
powerful stuff.
Oh, I know.
So how'd it go over
at Bonnie's place?
Was the musk a problem?
No not really.
Her mother was a
little threatened
but her father kept
putting his arm around me.
The dog really liked me.
He proposed to my leg.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Oh, meeting time.
Yeah, you go
ahead, Harold.
I'll be right down.
Okay.
Be careful with that.
Oh boy.
So if my wife is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting
and I hope you're going
to put on that scent
that drives me crazy...
honey-garlic.
And the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself and
Harold and the wolf
and everybody else up
here at Possum Lodge...
Keep your stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Sit down!
Sit down, now.
Sit down.
Come on, sit down.
You guys in the back there.
Sit down.
All rise.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
Sit down.
Bow your heads for
the man's prayer.
I'm a man
but I can change
if I have to
I guess.
Okay men, we had a bit
of a labelling mix up
on the musk that
you've been using.
So, we need you
to stop spreading that
over all the trees
and bushes and everything
'cause the whole forest