(Baby crying)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE MAN VOTED
MOST LIKELY TO HAVE A T.V. SHOW
BASED IN A LODGE
NAMED AFTER A POSSUM,
YOUR HOST, MY UNCLE,
RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I GOT NO TIME FOR YACKING.
WE'VE GOT TO GET BUSY
ON OUR ANNUAL POSSUM LODGE
FATHER AND SON BANQUET.
EXCUSE ME --
TIMES HAVE CHANGED.
THE BANQUET SHOULD INCLUDE
MOMS AND SONS,
AND FATHERS AND DAUGHTERS.
FAIR ENOUGH, HAROLD.
WE'RE HAVING THE FATHER AND SON,
FATHER AND DAUGHTER,
MOM AND SON,
MOM AND DAUGHTER BANQUET.
EVERYTHING EXCEPT
UNCLES AND NEPHEWS.
SORRY, HAROLD.
THAT'S OK,
'CAUSE MY DAD'S COMING.
BUT THANKS FOR ASKING.
I WASN'T ASKING.
YEAH, YOU WERE.
I KNOW YOU WERE.
I WOULD GO IF I COULD,
BUT I CAN'T!
STOP ASKING!
I'M NOT ASKING!
THAT'S AN ASK.
ARE YOU GETTING MAD?
I AM.
(Horns honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): TODAY,
I GET A LITTLE TIRED,
SO I MAKE A BED OUT OF TIRES.
SEGUE IS MY MIDDLE NAME.
MIKE GETS OUT OF PRISON
LONG ENOUGH
TO PLAY TWO ON A MATCH.
EDGAR MONTROSE SHOWS YOU
THE QUICK WAY TO BARBECUE.
YOUR FATHER'S COMING
TO THE BANQUET?
WON'T THAT BE GREAT? --
WE'LL ENTER RACES
AND WALK AROUND,
DO FATHER AND SON STUFF.
MAYBE HE'LL FLASH
HIS IDENTIFICATION,
AND THEY'LL STOP CALLING YOU
THAT NAME.
HERE'S HOPING.
WHAT'S THIS YEAR'S THEME?
THE COMMITTEE HAD A MEETING
LAST NIGHT.
WHO'S ON THAT?
ME.
YOU'RE NOT
A FATHER.
I'M A SON.
AROUND HERE 50% IS A QUORUM.
SO WE DECIDED TO MAKE
THIS YEAR'S THEME TIRES,
ALL KINDS OF TIRES, HAROLD.
STEEL BELTED,
ALL-WEATHER RADIALS,
BIAS PLY, OFF-ROAD.
WHAT CAN YOU DO WITH TIRES
AT A FATHER AND SON BANQUET?
WAIT AND SEE.
IT WILL BE BETTER THAN
LAST YEAR'S THEME.
OH YEAH, BIG WHOOP.
SALUTE TO ENGINE COOLANT.
THAT WAS GROSS.
WE WERE DOING OK TILL WE
USED IT FOR BOBBING FOR APPLES.
(Red): BILL'S WAY AHEAD OF US
ON THE TIRE THEME.
HE'S GOING TO MAKE A SWING
OUT OF TIRES.
HE PICKED A TIRE
OUT OF THE PILE.
OH, OH, OH, OH.
HE WANTED ME TO PICK ONE OUT,
BUT I THOUGHT HE'D MADE
A HASTY DECISION.
I DECIDED HE'D MAKE
A BETTER DECISION IF HE HAD
MORE TIRES TO CHOOSE FROM.
SO, BILL, HOW 'BOUT THAT ONE
OR THESE OR THAT?
HOW ABOUT THIS ONE?
HOW ABOUT THIS HERE?
HERE'S ONE.
HOW 'BOUT THIS?
OH, EXCELLENT CHOICE.
THIS IS THE BIG ONE!
THIS WEEK'S PRIZE WAS DONATED
BY JUNIOR SINGLETON.
A PROMISE TO RETURN
HALF THE TOOLS HE'S BORROWED.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO MAKE MR. HAMMER
SAY THIS WORD.
THIRTY SECONDS, AND BEGIN.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE, UH... BUDDY.
GANG MEMBER?
CLOSE BUDDY.
CELL MATE.
UH, SOMEONE WHO
TALKS ABOUT STUFF.
UH, INFORMER, STOOLEY, SQUEALY,
UH... DEAD MEAT.
NO, NO,
NO.
SOMEONE YOU CAN TRUST.
OH BOY, UM...
PRISON CHAPLAIN.
AND YOU CAN TRUST HIM
BECAUSE HE'S...
AN EX-CON HIMSELF.
(Audience laughing)
LET ME GO ANOTHER WAY.
I'M NOT JUST A GUY
WHO SIGNED YOU OUT
ON A PAROLE THING,
I'M ALSO YOUR BUDDY, YOUR...
WARDEN.
YOU'RE RUNNIN'
OUT OF TIME
MIKE, THERE MUST BE SOMEBODY
YOU CAN TRUST.
UM... BAMBI BAZOOMS,
THE FEATHER DANCER.
FAIR ENOUGH --
SO BAMBI IS YOUR...
MOM.
(Audience laughing)
(Strums acoustic guitar)
PEOPLE THOUGHT I WAS
LINE DANCING
WHEN I JUMPED UP
AND SPUN ON THE CHAIR
SO THEY JOINED IN
AND DID WHAT I DID
KICKING ONE FOOT
IN THE AIR
WE DANCED IN A LINE
OUT THE FRONT DOOR
AND DOWN BY
THE CEDAR GROVE
IT TURNED OUT I WASN'T
LINE DANCING AT ALL
I HAD JUST STUBBED MY TOE
ON THE STOVE
OW!
IT'S TIME FOR THIS WEEK'S
SEGMENT OF
"THE FRIENDLY SIDE
OF DYNAMITE".
THIS WEEK WE'LL SHOW YOU
HOW TO USE DYNAMITE
FOR HOME RENOVATIONS.
THE TRICK IS TO GET
THE DYNAMITE
INTO THE SHAPE
THAT WILL FIT THE JOB.
LOTS OF GUYS USE
EXPENSIVE PLASTIC EXPLOSIVES,
BUT THEY GOT MORE MONEY
THAN ME,
PLUS THEY GOT
THE PROPER LICENCE AND PERMITS.
WHAT I DO IS JUST
CRACK A STICK OPEN,
MIX IT WITH
SOME HAMBURGER MEAT...
THAT'S T.N.T. INSTEAD OF
M.S.G., RED.
YOU KNOW, THE ENGLISH
GOT THEIR BANGERS AND MASH.
THISS BOTH.
I GOT THIS DOOR
THAT'S BEEN STICKING.
I NEED TO GIVE IT
A LITTLE ATTENTION.
COME ON WITH ME, RED.
ALL RIGHT.
COULDN'T YOU JUST PLANE
A BIT OFF THE DOOR,
OR SAND SOME OFF THE FRAME?
I KNOW I COULD.
BUT I PREFER TO BLOW IT
TO KINGDOM-COME
AND START OVER AGAIN.
I'M FUSSY THAT WAY.
NOW, YOU LAY YOUR BURGER
INTO THE HINGE.
AND THAT SHOULD BE ENOUGH
TO BLOW HER HALFWAY
ACROSS THE LAKE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO USE
TO SET OFF THE CHARGE?
BARBECUE STARTER?
ULTRASONIC WAVES, RED.
THIS BABY SENDS THEM OUT
AND TOUCHES OFF THE DYNAMITE.
LOOKS LIKE YOUR
GARAGE DOOR OPENER, EDGAR.
WELL, TODAY IT'S
A SHED DOOR OPENER.
(Zapping)
HMM.
(Coughing)
THIS WEEK I THOUGHT
I'D CARRY ON WITH THE THEME OF
OUR FATHER-SON,
FATHER-DAUGHTER,
MOTHER-SON,
MOTHER-DAUGHTER BANQUET,
NAMELY, TIRES.
GIRLS TODAY,
THEY'RE CONCERNED WITH ECOLOGY.
THEY WANT TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY WE MAKE
AN ENTIRE GIRL'S BEDROOM SUITE
OUT OF RECYCLED TIRES?
GIRLS LIKE PRETTY THINGS.
I SUGGEST YOU GO WITH
THE WHITEWALL ON THAT.
THE FIRST THING WE COULD BUILD
IS A VANITY MIRROR.
YOU ALREADY GOT
THE FRAME ON THERE
WITH THE WHITE ACCENT.
FOR YOUR MIRROR, I SUGGEST
YOU GO WITH A MOON DISC.
IT'S GOT THE CURVE ON HER.
IT MAKES WOMEN LOOK SLIM.
THEY APPRECIATE THAT,
ESPECIALLY 13-YEAR-OLD GIRLS
GOING THROUGH
THAT CHUNKY STAGE.
WHY DON'T WE BUILD A DRESSER?
FOR THAT, ALL YOU DO IS
STACK UP A BUNCH OF TIRES,
AND CUT A FOUR-INCH HOLE
IN EACH ONE
USING A CARPET KNIFE.
PERFECT.
ONCE YOU GOT THE HOLES CUT,
STICK PATCHES ON
TO COVER THE HOLES.
I PUT A WHEEL DISK
BETWEEN EVERY TIRE,
SO YOU GOT SHELVING IN THERE.
YOU NEED SOME KIND OF A HINGE.
YOU COULD GLUE SOME FABRIC
ON THERE.
OR, IF YOU LIKE THE LOOK
OF SILVER,
I SUGGEST THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
ONCE YOU'VE GOT
ALL YOUR FLAPS ON THERE,
YOU CAN REACH IN,
GET YOUR VARIOUS ARTICLES
OF CLOTHING.
MAYBE YOU KEEP T-SHIRTS THERE,
AND...
NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
AND YOU GOT YOUR SOCKS.
LOOK AT HOW NEAT AND TIDY
THAT IS.
YOU CAN ALSO BUILD
AN ATTRACTIVE AND USEFUL
GIRL'S DESK.
ISN'T THAT A BEAUTY?
THIS IS A NICE TOUCH.
A BEAUTIFUL DESK LAMP.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE THIS,
BUT THIS IS MADE OUT OF TIRES.
WE CAN ALSO MAKE
A DANDY LITTLE GIRL'S BED.
WHAT DO WE USE
FOR A MATTRESS?
INNER TUBES MAKE SENSE.
WHY DON'T WE ADD
A BIT OF ROMANCE?
HOW ABOUT ONE OF THOSE
VICTORIAN FOUR-POSTER BEDS?
GIRLS LOVE THAT KIND OF STUFF.
WHAT CAN WE USE
FOR THE POSTS?
(Screeching)
HOW ABOUT ONE OF THESE
REAR END UNITS
WHICH YOU CAN GET FROM
PASSING VEHICLES
IF YOU DIG
A BIG ENOUGH POTHOLE.
THERE WE GO.
SO NOW WHEN YOUR TEENAGER
GETS TIRED,
SHE CAN JUST RETIRE
TO HER TIRES.
LET'S SEE IF IT'S COMFORTABLE.
FOOLS RUSH IN
WHERE ANGELS FEAR THE TREAD.
OH BOY, OH.
GOSH.
NOW THAT IBEAUTIFUL.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
AND TO THINK WE MADE THIS
OUT OF OLD REAR ENDS.
ACTUALLY, YOU CAN TELL.
EDGAR SHOWS THAT
THE EXPLOSIVES BUSINESS
HAS ITS UPS AND DOWNS.
I KNOW WHAT YOU GUYS
ARE GOING THROUGH.
YOU GET UP ON
A SATURDAY MORNING,
SWING OPEN THE CLOSET DOOR
AND YOU'RE FACE TO FACE
WITH CLOTHES
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE
IN YOUR LIFE.
MEN'S CLOTHES.
YOU RUN OVER TO THE BED
TO SEE IF YOUR WIFE'S
HAVING AN AFFAIR.
BUT NO, IT'S WORSE THAN THAT.
SHE HAS BOUGHT YOU NEW CLOTHES.
(Audience laughing)
COLOURED GOLF SHIRTS,
AND THOSE JEANS FOR FAT GUYS
SO YOU CAN'T TELL HOW BIG
THEIR BUTT IS.
(Audience laughing)
ORDINARILY, YOU'D NEVER
WEAR CLOTHES LIKE THAT,
BUT SHE'S THROWN OUT
YOUR OLD CLOTHES.
YOU KNOW THAT SWEATSHIRT YOU GOT
WHEN YOU WERE 14
AT CAMP KAPPAWIGGAMOGGAWEDGIE?
AND THOSE JEANS YOU'VE WORN
FOR 10 YEARS
EVEN THOUGH YOU'VE GOT TO
HANG FROM THE CEILING
TO GET YOUR GUT INTO THEM.
DON'T FIGHT IT --
USE YOUR HEAD.
A GUY WEARING NEW CLOTHES
CAN'T CUT THE GRASS,
WASH THE CAR OR
TAKE OUT THE GARBAGE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
YOU'LL NEVER GUESS
WHAT WE FOUND, HAROLD,
BEHIND LUCKY BALDERSON'S PLACE.
TIRE DUMP.
MUST BE FIVE ACRES OF TIRES.
NO WONDER THEY CALL HIM LUCKY.
GOT ENOUGH TIRES
TO MAKE A GLOBAL VILLAGE.
WE'LL HAVE THE YOKAHAMAS
FROM JAPAN,
PIRELLIS FROM ITALY AND
FRISK TIRES FROM K-MART.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU
THERE, HAROLD?
MY DAD CALLED.
CAN'T COME TO
THE FATHER-SON BANQUET.
OH BOY.
(Audience): AWW.
I'M GONNA CANCEL, UNCLE RED.
CAN'T GO, I GUESS,
OR SOMETHING.
HAVE TO FIND SOMEONE ELSE...
UNCLE... RED.
YOU KNOW, SOMEONE IN MY FAMILY,
SOME OTHER RELATIVE.
I DON'T KNOW... UNCLE... RED.
SOMEONE.
YOU KNOW, AS YOU'RE TALKING,
IT STRIKES ME FUNNY THAT
DADS ARE SO MUCH LIKE TIRES.
EVEN WHEN THEY GET OLD AND BALD
AND GOT BULGES IN THE SIDE,
THEY'RE STILL GOOD
FOR SOMETHING.
AT THE FATHER-SON BANQUET.
SOUNDS GREAT, YEAH, GOOD,
SURE, GREAT.
TELL YOU WHAT,
I'LL THINK IT OVER.
EXCELLENT, GOOD,
EXCELLENT, OK, GOOD!
THAT'S GREAT!
THAT WOULD BE PERFECT.
I'LL MAKE SURE THAT
I'M A GOOD GUY.
I'LL MAKE YOU PROUD
TO BE WITH ME.
I'LL BE CALM, SO CALM.
HA-HA HA!
I'LL DRINK MY POP REALLY SLOW
BECAUSE LAST YEAR
I HAD THIS REALLY BIG BELCH.
THIS YEAR I WON'T DO THAT.
I WON'T TALK A LOT.
WHEN I TALK, I'LL MAKE SURE
IT'S SPECIFIC TOPICS
OF INTEREST TO EVERYBODY,
NOT JUST MYSELF.
NOT TOPICS LIKE GIRLS,
OR HOW MUCH CANDY FLOSS
I CAN GET IN MY MOUTH
BEFORE IT COMES OUT MY NOSE.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT IT YET?
OH, AH.
(Coughing)
HI, THIS IS EDGAR MONTROSE
WITH A SAFETY TIP.
WHENEVER YOU'RE SETTING UP
EXPLOSIVE CHARGES
WITH YOUR PARTNER,
ALWAYS WORK OUT
YOUR HAND SIGNALS
BEFORE YOU LIGHT THE FUSE.
(Coughing)
WHAT?
I TOLD YOU "FIVE," NOT--
MY MISTAKE.
THIS IS FIVE.
THAT'S FOUR.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S SET IT UP AGAIN.
AH.
NOW WHAT DID YOU GO
AND DO THAT FOR?
OF ALL THE INSENSITIVE THINGS
YOU'VE EVER DONE.
SHE'S DISCUSSING
THE RELATIONSHIP.
SHE'S TALKING ABOUT THE FUTURE,
ABOUT BEING TOGETHER,
BUT BEING SCARED.
SHE'S POURING HER HEART OUT
TO YOU.
AND YOU HAD TO GO AND YAWN.
THE WORST THING
YOU COULD EVER DO.
NEVER, EVER, EVER YAWN
AT YOUR WIFE.
AS IN NEVER.
COULDN'T YOU HAVE
LEFT THE ROOM?
ONE OF
THE MOST PERSONAL MOMENTS
IN YOUR RELATIONSHIP,
AND YOU YAWN?
THIS IS A BIGGIE.
WE'LL SHOW YOU A COUPLE OF WAYS
YOU CAN UNDO THE DAMAGE.
FIRST, TELL HER
IT WASN'T A YAWN AT ALL.
IT WAS HER REVELATIONS
THAT LEFT YOU SLACK-JAWED
AND AMAZED,
SORT OF LIKE...
OR GO TO THE DOCTOR.
CONVINCE HIM YOU'VE GOT
A SLEEPING DISORDER.
ONCE SHE HEARS THAT,
SHE'LL BE FORGIVING.
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE
A LITTLE NEUROLOGICAL BLACKMAIL
TO GET YOU BACK IN
THE GOOD BOOKS.
THEN YOU NEED A LITTLE PLAN.
WE SAVED THE BEST ONE
FOR LAST.
TELL THEM.
ME?
YOU WAIT TILL
SHE'S REALLY TIRED.
I MEAN ZONKED,
AND READY TO GO TO BED,
AND THEN YOU CALL HER ASIDE.
YOU SAY, "HONEY, I HAVE
SOME VERY IMPORTANT THINGS
"TO DISCUSS WITH YOU."
THEN SIT HER DOWN
AND JUST START SPIELING.
YOU JUST SHOOT THE BREEZE
ABOUT ANYTHING.
TALK ABOUT YOUR WRENCHES,
THE DOG, DOESN'T MATTER.
JUST KEEP YACKING.
EVENTUALLY SHE'S GONNA YAWN.
(Audience laughing)
EVENTUALLY?
WITH YOU GOING,
SHE'LL BE YAWNING IN SECONDS.
SO MUCH THE BETTER.
AS SOON AS SHE YAWNS,
BLURT OUT SOMETHING PERSONAL.
THEN YOU CAN TURN THE TABLES
ON HER.
BUT DON'T BLOW IT.
REMEMBER, THIS IS
THE MOST IMPORTANT MOMENT
OF THE REST OF
YOUR MARRIED--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I WAS DOING THE THING HERE.
IT WAS A COMPLETE YAWN.
NO, NO, I WASN'T YAWNING.
WELL, HAROLD,
I'LL PROBABLY REGRET THIS,
BUT I'VE THOUGHT IT OVER.
YEAH, OK, YES, YES.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU ARE SORT OF FLESH AND BLOOD.
GO AHEAD,
GO AHEAD.
SEEING HOW YOUR DAD
CAN'T REALLY MAKE IT...
MM-HMM,
MM-HMM.
WELL, ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME
TO THE BANQUET WITH ME?
NO, I CAN'T,
SORRY.
(Audience laughing)
I'M GOING WITH SOMEBODY ELSE.
WHAT?
A COUPLE OF KIDS WERE LOOKING
FOR A FATHER FIGURE, NAMELY ME.
I'M GOING WITH THEM.
YOU KNOW RICKY AND RONNIE.
THE RYTALIN BROTHERS?
RITTLING, THE NAME'S RITTLING.
YOU KNOW WHAT
THEY'D PROBABLY ENJOY?
THE AIR DARE.
IT'S SORT OF LIKE THAT GAME
KA-BOOM,
ONLY INSTEAD OF WITH
A WHIMPY BALLOON,
WE BLOW UP AN INNER TUBE
FROM AN EARTH MOVER.
YOU SEE HOW FAR YOU CAN
TAKE HER BEFORE SHE BLOWS.
IT GETS AROUND 200 POUNDS,
IT STARTS TO CRACKLE AND POP.
GONNA TAKE A REAL MAN
TO TAKE HER OVER 210.
BUT
UNCLE RED,
THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
KIDS DON'T WANT TO WATCH
SOMEBODY BLOW THEIR ARMS OFF.
KIDS WANT TO DO SOMETHING
WITH THEIR FATHERS.
YOU SHOULD FIND GAMES THAT
KIDS WILL BE INTERESTED IN.
CANCEL THE AIR DARE?
WHAT ABOUT WRENCH JUGGLING?
NOT A GOOD IDEA.
AND YOU WONDER WHY
I DON'T HAVE KIDS.
HERE'S A TIP FOR HANDYMEN
WHO KEEP LOSING TOOLS.
TAKE THE TOOLS YOU NEED
MOST OFTEN
AND TIE THEM WITH STRINGS
TO YOUR BELT.
TODAY I'LL BE DOING
SOME PLUMBING,
SO I GOT MY SOLDER.
I GOT MY PIPE TAPE.
I GOT MY PIPE WRENCH.
MY BAND-AIDS.
(Red): MEANWHILE,
BACK AT THE TIRE SWING...
(Explosion)
BILL WANTED TO TRY
THAT LITTLE TIRE.
HE NEEDS TO THROW A ROPE
UP OVER...
WELL, THAT'S HANDY.
HE'S GOING TO THROW THAT UP
OVER THE BRANCH.
GET THAT OUT OF THERE.
YOU DON'T WANT THAT TO BE
SNUGGED UP AROUND...
GIVE IT A GOOD YANK.
I REALLY CAN'T...
I REALLY CAN'T EXPLAIN THAT.
ANYWAY, HE GOT MY PIPE WRENCH
WHICH I HAD FINISHED WITH,
AS YOU KNOW.
THAT GIVES IT A LITTLE WEIGHT.
THIS IS KIND OF SMART,
AT LEAST IT SEEMED SMART.
BUT YOU KNOW,
IT WASN'T REALLY THAT SMART.
BOY, I WONDER WHAT HAPPENED.
HEY, BILL, WHAT DO YOU SUPPOSE
HAPPENED?
DO YOU SUPPOSE IT WENT
OVER THE TREE?
I THINK IT WENT SOMEWHERE
IT SHOULDN'T HAVE GONE.
WHAT'S THAT WE HAVE HERE?
MY, MY, MY.
LET'S SEE.
IS THAT SOMETHING
THAT BELONGS TO BILL?
I DON'T THINK SO, NO.
I THINK THAT'S MY DOOR.
HA!
WE'LL FIND OUT WHY HAROLD
LOOKS ODDER THAN USUAL.
OH, UNCLE RED, ENOUGH
WITH THE TIRES ALREADY.
CAN'T HELP MYSELF, HAROLD.
IT'S LIKE A CARNIVAL OUT THERE.
WE GOT TIRE-TOSS GAMES,
TIRE OBSTACLE COURSES,
TIRE SWINGS.
WE BUILT A WHOLE BARBECUE
OUT OF WHITEWALLS.
I GOT MOOSE THOMPSON
DRESSED IN TIRES.
HE'S ROLLO, THE RADIAL CLOWN.
(Audience laughing)
I'M ALMOST SORRY I HAVE TO
GO ON MY OWN.
I'M GLAD TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT THE FACT
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE KIDS.
THAT PROBABLY MAKES YOU,
YOU KNOW, THE WAY YOU ARE.
AN OLD CHUBBY GUY
WITH A BEARD,
THAT'S PRETTY PATHETIC.
IS GOOD NEWS COMING SOON
IN THIS SPEECH?
I FOUND SOMEBODY FOR YOU
TO TAKE.
A FAKE SON?
A FAKE DAD.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK.
I TOLD HIM YOU WERE HIS SON!
WELL, THAT WOULD BE ALL RIGHT,
AS LONG AS WE TELL EVERYBODY
THAT I'M ADOPTED.
OH YEAH.
HE INSISTED.
(Red): HERE WE ARE
AT THE TIRE SWING.
HE GOT THE ROPE OVER.
OH!
THIS IS MORE FUN NOW.
(Laughing)
NOW HE'S GOT THE ROPE OVER.
OH, YOU'RE FINE.
HE'S STILL INSISTING ON
GOING WITH THAT LITTLE TIRE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, BILL?
HE'S GOING TO TRY
AND CUT A HOLE
WITH
AN EXACTO-KNIFE-TYPE THING.
OH, OH, OH!
OH!
OHH!
THERE ARE TIMES YOU WISH
THIS SHOW WAS ON RADIO.
ANYWAY, HE'S FINE.
GET RID OF THAT.
WHY DON'T WE GO
THROUGH THE HOLE.
THERE'S A NOVEL APPROACH.
YEAH, YEAH, WE KNOW.
HE GETS THAT UP.
IMAGINE YOU'RE WALKING
DOWN THE STREET.
YOU GO BY THE PLAYGROUND.
YOU LOOK IN AND YOU SEE
SOMETHING OF THIS NATURE.
WOULD YOU PERHAPS CALL 9-1-1,
OR AN AMBULANCE OF SOME KIND,
OR WOULD YOU JUST
START SHOOTING?
OH, NO, NO, LOOK OUT, BILL.
THAT KNIFE, THE KNIFE,
BILL, THE KNIFE.
WELL, HE'S MOVING.
OH, I SEE.
THE ROPE'S WINDING AROUND...
YOU MIGHT BE...
THIS MIGHT NOT WORK.
(Crashing)
THERE, HE STOPPED.
OH, HERE HE COMES.
AHHH!
WELL, THAT WAS A FUN RIDE,
WASN'T IT, BILL?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH.
WANT TO GO AGAIN?
AND TO THINK, A FEW HOURS AGO
I WAS ACTUALLY WISHING
I HAD A SON OF MY OWN.
COURSE, THAT WAS BEFORE
THE BIG TIRE FIRE.
IT STARTED WHEN SOME PARENT
GAVE THEIR KID MATCHES.
NOT ALWAYS THE KID'S FAULT,
YOU KNOW.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK TOLD ME
TO START THE BARBECUE.
(Audience laughing
and applauding)
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
OK, BUT SHOULDN'T YOU
BE CALLING HIM DAD?
A LOT OF THINGS
I SHOULD BE CALLING HIM.
TO BE FAIR,
I THINK WE HAD MAYBE
TOO MANY TIRES PILED UP
AGAINST THE LODGE.
BOY, CAN THOSE WHITEWALLS
BURN.
I THOUGHT WE HAD HER
UNDER CONTROL,
BUT THEN THE FIRE HIT
THE TIRE HIDE-AND-SEEK VILLAGE.
NEXT YEAR WE OUGHT TO
PICK A THEME
THAT'S NOT SO...
F-F-FLAMMABLE.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW FUN WORKS, DO YA?
A WALL OF BURNING TIRES,
AND BEING SURROUNDED
BY FLAMES,
AND RISKING LIFE AND LIMB
IS JUST NOT MY IDEA OF FUN.
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
(Possum
squeal)
I GIVE UP.
MEETING TIME.
GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I ACTUALLY KNOW THAT
A TIRE FIRE'S NOT FUN,
BUT WINDING HIM UP SURE IS.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
IT'S BEEN QUITE A DAY.
I SMELL LIKE BURNT RUBBER.
YOU'VE GOT A NEW FATHER-IN-LAW.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF, HAROLD,
AND THE GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): NO THROWING PLANES.
OH, ALL RISE, ALL RISE.
UP AND AT 'EM.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.