IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW!"
AND NOW PLEASE HELP WELCOME
THE MAN THAT KNOWS ALL
ABOUT NUTS AND BOLTS
BECAUSE HE'S A BIT
OF EACH HIMSELF,
YOUR HOST,
YOUR HERO,
MY UNCLE,
RED GRE-E-E-N!
(APPLAUSE)
AND THIS HERE IS HAROLD,
MY PRODUCER AND
DIRECTOR AND NEPHEW.
OH BOY.
I LIKE TO CUT, WIPE, DOLLY
AND ZOOM SQUEEZE FRAME.
LET'S HOPE HE'S TALKING ABOUT
TELEVISION TERMS THERE.
KIND OF A QUIET WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
NO, NO WAY, IT WASN'T.
THERE'S LOTS TO TALK
ABOUT, LIKE, CRIME.
AND PLENTY OF IT TOO.
WE GOT THIEVES
AMONG US, UNCLE RED,
AND BULLIES.
OH, HAROLD, SOMEBODY
STEAL YOUR LUNCH AGAIN?
YES.
AND I KNOW
WHO IT WAS TOO.
OH, I DO, I DO.
IT'S BUSTER HATFIELD'S
KID. WHAT A PUNK.
BUSTER HATFIELD'S KID?
YOU MEAN SUSIE?
YEAH, HER.
SHE'S A PUNK.
NOT FAIR AT ALL.
HAROLD, YOU DON'T
EVEN KNOW IT'S HER.
JUST BECAUSE YOUR LUNCH IS
MISSING OUT OF YOUR LOCKER
DOESN'T MEAN SUSIE TOOK IT.
WELL, I KNOW
IT WAS HER.
I'M WALKING THROUGH THE
CAFETERIA, RIGHT...
AND JUST WALKING ALONG,
AND I'M LOOKING FOR...
YOU KNOW, SOMEBODY TO
LET ME SIT WITH THEM.
AND, ALL OF A SUDDEN --
I GOT MY LUNCH HANGING
IN MY HANDS,
AND SHE WALKS RIGHT UP AND
GRABS IT AND KEEPS ON WALKING.
WHAT CAN YOU DO?
YOU CAN'T HIT HER.
NO, NO, NO, NO, HAROLD,
YOU DON'T EVER HIT ANYONE
BECAUSE THEY CAN HIT YOU
BACK, AND YOU'D FOLD UP
LIKE A DECK CHAIR.
I KNOW THAT.
PERSON'S GOT TO DO
SOMETHING, YOU KNOW?
'CAUSE IT'S EACH INDIVIDUAL'S
RESPONSIBILITY TO STOP CRIME.
THAT'S WHY I'M GOING
TO TELL THE PRINCIPAL.
OH, YEAH, GET AN ALL-POINTS
BULLETIN GOING THERE.
WHAT WAS IN THE
LUNCH ANYWAY?
THREE SARDINE SANDWICHES
AND A POMEGRANATE.
WELL, YOU BETTER TELL
THE COPS TO TREAT HER
AS ARMED AND DANGEROUS.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
GOT KIND OF AN APOCALYPTIC
SHOW FOR YOU THIS WEEK.
GOT A LITTLE BIT OF FIRE THERE.
THAT WOULD BE PESTILENCE,
I WOULD THINK.
AND WE HAVE AN ASSAULT WITH
A FRIENDLY WEAPON,
SO STAY TUNED.
WHERE EVERYBODY KNOWS EVERYBODY.
YOU DON'T GET A LOT OF ADULTERY
WHEN EVERYBODY IS YOUR COUSIN.
THERE'S NO
JUSTICE.
WHAT?
NO JUSTICE.
THE SYSTEM IS COMPLETELY
BREAKING DOWN.
THERE'S NO PROTECTION
OF INDIVIDUAL RIGHTS.
CRIME IS RUNNING RAMPANT.
O-O-W!
OKAY, YOU KNOW
WHAT HAPPENS?
I GO RIGHT INTO THE
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE TO
REPORT MY LUNCH THEFT.
WHILE I'M IN THERE, SOMEONE
STEALS MY RUNNING SHOES.
IT'S PROBABLY SUSIE.
YOU NEED RUNNING SHOES
WHEN THE SARDINES KICK IN.
UNCLE RED, YOU MOCK THIS, BUT
THIS IS JUST THE TIP OF THE
ICEBERG, I'M TELLING YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT? IN THE BIG
CITIES, RIGHT --
IN THE BIG CITIES, RIGHT --
THE BIG CITIES, RIGHT,
THEY'VE GOT, LIKE,
MURDERS EVERY TIME,
AND THEN THERE'S,
LIKE, FIRES AND ARSON
AND GANG WARS GOING
ON ALL OVER THE PLACE.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE IT'S HERE IN
POSSUM LAKE.
YEAH, YEAH.
IT'S A PRESSURE COOKER OUT
THERE, I'M TELLING YOU,
AND WHEN IT BLOWS... BOOM!
BEANS EVERYWHERE.
I WILL NOT STAND FOR IT,
UNCLE RED, I WILL NOT.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
YOU SHOULD JUST KIND
OF RELAX A LITTLE BIT.
THIS MIGHT JUST KIND OF BE
A HORMONE BUILD-UP
THAT TEENAGERS GET
WHEN THEY DON'T DATE.
YEAH?
BOY, YOU'VE GOT
A GOOD MEMORY.
YOU KNOW, THE SAD THING IS
YOUR GENERATION DOESN'T
HAVE A WAR
WHERE THEY CAN GO OFF TO A
FOREIGN COUNTRY AND BLOW
OFF SOME STEAM.
I'M TELLING YOU --
I AM TELLING YOU,
IT STARTS WITH STEALING
LUNCHES AND STEALING SHOES,
AND THEN THERE'S CAR STEALING
AND THE RUNNING NUMBERS.
WELL, WE'RE NOT GOING
TO TAKE IT ANYMORE.
WE'RE STARTING A
NEIGHBOURHOOD WATCH.
YEAH -- YEAH --
YEAH -- YEAH.
AND WE'RE SETTING UP
A SNITCH LINE,
SO YOU CAN PHONE IN,
AND YOU CAN SNITCH
ON PEOPLE.
YUP, WE'RE GOING TO MARCH
UP AND DOWN THE STREETS,
MAKING SURE THAT LAW AND ORDER
IS PRESERVED IN OUR COMMUNITY.
WHO IS THIS "WE"?
THE "WE."
WHO IS "WE"?
ME AND TOMMY DOUGAL.
YEAH, YOU KNOW TOMMY.
HE'S GOT THE BAD SKIN
AND THE MOTOR SCOOTER.
TOMMY.
AND CHUBBY DICKSON,
HIM TOO.
THE THREE OF US.
THERE'S SAFETY
IN NUMBERS.
THOSE ARE PRETTY
ODD NUMBERS.
WELCOME TO THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
AND WHAT'S THIS WEEK'S
GRAND PRIZE?
WELL, IF YOU'VE EVER THOUGHT OF
OWNING YOUR VERY OWN FORD
CONVERTIBLE MUSTANG,
WELL, THEN YOU PROBABLY HAVE A
LOT OF SALES BROCHURES,
AND NOW YOU CAN KEEP THOSE SALES
BROCHURES ORGANIZED IN THESE
FIVE FREE FILE FOLDERS.
FILE FOLDERS MADE AVAILABLE BY
THE HOME DEZPOT, YOUR HOME
AND OFFICE SUPPLIER.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET Mr. DALTON HUMPHREY TO
SAY THIS WORD... HAND.
HAND.
GO.
ALL RIGHT. DALTON, THIS IS
SOMETHING YOU HAVE TWO OF...
OKAY, NO, NO, ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, OKAY, YOU GO OUT FOR
A WALK WITH YOUR WIFE,
AND YOU HOLD...
MY TEMPER.
OKAY, OKAY, YOUR WIFE
IS FEELING AFFECTIONATE.
SHE REACHES OVER
AND TAKES YOUR...
WALLET.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SAY YOUR WIFE
IS PLANNING A FANCY DINNER...
K.F.C.
LET'S GO ANOTHER WAY.
WHEN SOMEBODY GETS
ANGRY WITH SOMEBODY,
THEY WILL HIT HIM
WITH A FIRM...
PATERNITY SUIT.
AND YOU'RE RUNNING
OUT OF TIME, UNCLE RED.
FIVE FINGERS...
FIVE ANGRY DRIVERS.
DALTON, WHAT'S THIS?
LIVER SPOTS.
COME ON.
HAMMER INJURY.
RIGHT. AND WHY DO I
HAVE A HAMMER INJURY?
ONE HAND DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT THE OTHER
ONE IS DOING.
THERE YOU GO.
(FRANTIC BELL RINGING)
THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I THOUGHT I'D SHOW YOU HOW YOUR
KITCHEN CAN ALMOST BE AS MUCH
FUN AS YOUR WORKSHOP.
YOU KNOW, A LOT OF THE
FAMOUS CHEFS ARE MEN.
YOU KNOW, YOU SEE THEM ON TV.
YOU KNOW THAT GUY?
WELL, THE FAT GUY.
AND THAT OTHER FELLA...
THE LOUD ONE, THE LOUD GUY.
AND THERE'S THE DRUNK GUY.
NOW, THINK OF ALL THE FAT,
LOUD, DRUNK GUYS YOU KNOW.
THEY COULD BE CHEFS.
AND IF YOU LIKE THE TOOLS,
WELL, THEY COULD DOUBLE
AS KITCHEN UTENSILS...
SPATULA,
GARLIC PRESS,
ELECTRIC FOOD SLICER,
WALNUT CRUSHER,
BOTTLE OPENER,
STUBBORN BOTTLE OPENER,
MEAT SKEWERS,
MEAT TENDERIZER,
AND SO ON.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO USE THE
SAME TOOLS IN THE KITCHEN
AS YOU DO IN THE GARAGE,
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
CLEAN THEM OFF FIRST.
YOU DON'T WANT
FOOD ON YOUR CAR.
AND IF YOU LIKE POWER TOOLS,
WHY NOT HAVE POWER
KITCHEN APPLIANCES?
LOOK WHAT I'VE DONE HERE.
SEE WHAT THIS IS?
THIS IS MY OLD BETA MAX.
NOW, I DIDN'T JUST THROW IT
IN THE GARBAGE OR GIVE IT TO MY
GRANDMA, LIKE MOST OF YOU DO.
NO, I HOOKED HER UP
TO THE MICROWAVE.
WHY?
WELL, I'LL SHOW YOU.
WHEN I WANT TO HEAT UP,
SAY, A BOWL OF MY SOUP HERE,
I JUST PUT HER
INTO THE MICROWAVE,
CLOSE HER UP,
AND I JUST PRESS "PLAY"
FOR A FEW SECONDS.
THAT SHOULD GET HER.
A NEW KIND OF TV DINNER
I'VE GOT GOING HERE.
THAT LOOKS GOOD, DOESN'T IT?
MAYBE SOME OF YOU LIKE TO HAVE
YOUR SOUP EVEN HOTTER THAN THAT.
PUT HER BACK IN,
CLOSE HER UP,
AND HIT THE "FAST
FORWARD" ON THAT.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU HAVE FOOD
ALLERGIES, YOU MIGHT WANT TO GET
A HEAD CLEANER TAPE IN THERE.
AND THAT SHOULD GET HER.
ALL RIGHT. OH, WHY,
THAT'S HOT!
WELL, NO PROBLEM.
WE'LL JUST LEAVE IT IN
THERE AND JUST HIT "REWIND,"
COOL HER DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
THAT SHOULD DO IT.
OH, ALL RIGHT, I MAY HAVE
COOLED THAT A LITTLE TOO MUCH.
BUT YOU GET THE
GENERAL IDEA.
TELL YOU ANOTHER BEAUTY
OF THIS UNIT HERE.
WHEN YOU WANT TO GET THE
STUFF OUT OF THE OVEN,
YOU JUST HIT THE
"EJECT" BUTTON.
SOUP'S ON, HAROLD.
ACTUALLY, SOUP IS ON HAROLD.
OKAY, THIS BRINGS ME TO
THE NEXT THING FOR THE
HANDYMAN'S KITCHEN.
YOUR OVEN CLEANER/FREEZER
DEFROSTER.
NOW, WHAT YOU NEED FOR THAT IS
A CAN OF OVEN CLEANER,
ROLL OF DUCT TAPE,
A DIRTY OVEN AND
A FROSTY FREEZER.
OKAY, FIRST THING, MAKE SURE
THEY'RE ALL FACING UP.
OKAY, NOW WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS PUT YOUR OVEN CLEANER
INTO THE FREEZER.
THAT'S RIGHT,
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
YOU HEARD ME RIGHT.
SOAK HER REAL GOOD.
NOW, WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS TO
GET YOUR FREEZER UP ON TOP
OF YOUR DIRTY OVEN.
(GRUNTING)
WHO MAKES THESE THINGS
SO DARN HEAVY?
HEY, THIS IS A VERY
IMPORTANT POINT,
MAKE SURE THAT THE DOOR IS OPEN
ON THE FREEZER AND ON THE OVEN.
MAN...
THERE WE GO.
IT KIND OF LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE MATING, DOESN'T IT?
I GUESS THAT'S WHERE
MICROWAVE OVENS COME FROM.
ALL RIGHT. THIS IS WHERE
THE DUCT TAPE COMES IN.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
DUCT TAPE THIS SIZE?
THAT'S THE RELAXED FIT.
OKAY, WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS MAKE THIS COMPLETELY
AIRTIGHT HERE.
YOU WANNA HAVE A PERFECT SEAL.
THAT'S WHY I PUT THE OVEN
CLEANER INSIDE THE FREEZER.
I DIDN'T WANT TO
HURT THE SEAL...
I'LL HAVE THE GREENPEACE
PEOPLE AFTER ME.
SEAL...  GREENPEACE...
WHO NEEDS WRITERS?
A CAUTIOUS HANDYMAN ALWAYS USES
TEN TIMES AS MUCH TAPE AS
HE THINKS IS NECESSARY.
THAT'S FUNNY, EH?
SOMETIMES YOU LOOK AT SOMETHING,
AND YOU CAN'T BELIEVE YOU BUILT
THAT WITH YOUR OWN HANDS.
YOUR PARENTS WILL KNOW
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS TURN
THE OVEN ON HIGH,
AND THAT'S ALL THERE
IS TO IT, REALLY.
NOW, THE WAY THE RIG WORKS IS
THE HEAT OF THE OVEN GOES UP AND
MELTS THE ICE IN THE FREEZER,
AND THEN THE MELTED ICE --
OR, WATER, AS I LIKE
TO CALL IT --
MIXES WITH THE OVEN CLEANER,
AND IT JUST FLOWS RIGHT
DOWN INTO THE OVEN.
OH!
OKAY, DUCT TAPE --
OKAY, DON'T PANIC.
JUST STAY CALM THERE.
JUST GET THE DUCT TAPE ON IT.
USUALLY I WOULD SAY "IF THE
WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD FIND AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY,"
BUT THIS WEEK I'M
GOING TO SAY,
IF YOU CAN'T STAND THE KITCHEN,
GET OUT OF THE HEAT.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU OLDER
TYPES ABOUT MODERN ART.
NOW, I KNOW THE ARTIST IS
SUPPOSED TO SUFFER FOR HIS ART,
BUT THERE'S GOTTA
BE A LIMIT HERE.
I GOT DRAGGED OUT TO ONE
OF THEM MODERN ART MUSEUMS.
I HUNG UP MY COAT,
AND TURNS OUT THE COAT RACK
WAS ACTUALLY A PIECE OF ART
SYMBOLIZING MAN'S
DYNAMIC SYMMETRY.
NOW, I DON'T KNOW HOW MAN'S
DYNAMIC SYMMETRY CAN BE
SYMBOLIZED BY A NAIL
IN A WALL,
BUT THAT APPARENTLY MEANS
I'M INSENSITIVE.
THEY HAD THIS OTHER THING, JUST
BLOTCHES OF PAINT ON CANVAS.
THAT WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE ART TOO.
THEY HAD A BIG STATUE
MADE OUT OF BIRD DROPPINGS,
AND THEY HAD A PICTURE
OF A CAN OF SOUP.
LIKE, HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED TO
KNOW IF IT'S GOOD ART
IF WE DON'T EVEN
KNOW IF IT'S ART?
HERE'S A SIMPLE
RULE I USE...
IF I CAN DO IT,
IT'S NOT ART.
OH, YEAH.
(APPLAUSE)
SEE, I CAN FINGER PAINT,
SO THAT'S NOT ART.
I CAN CHANT;
I CAN STAND STILL;
I CAN SNEEZE INTO
A PIECE OF PAPER.
NONE OF THAT STUFF IS ART.
SO I'M WARNING YOU MODERN
ARTISTS OUT THERE...
EITHER YOU STOP DOING
STUFF I CAN DO,
OR I'LL START DOING
STUFF YOU CAN DO.
AND THEN, BELIEVE ME, EVERYBODY
IS GOING TO SUFFER FROM MY ART.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
HELLO, POSSUM SNITCH LINE.
DO YOU WANT TO SNITCH
ON SOMEONE?
HA, EXCELLENT. EXCELLENT.
ALL RIGHT, WHO? WHO?
I DO NOT!
NO, I DO NOT.
NO, NO, NO, MY MOM SAYS I
HAVEN'T DONE THAT SINCE
I WAS NINE YEARS OLD.
WELL, SHE WOULD KNOW.
SHE DOES THE LAUNDRY.
OKAY, AND BY THE WAY,
IT'S NOT A CRIME,
IT'S A CONDITION.
WELL, HAROLD, I SEE YOUR
SNITCH LINE IS BRINGING
OUT THE BEST IN PEOPLE.
WE GOT SOME CALLS.
WE GOT ONE FROM OLD LADY
BANKMAN. HER CAT HAS
BEEN MISSING...
SINCE 1983.
MOOSE THOMPSON CALLED.
SOMEONE STOLE HIS GREMLIN.
YEAH, HE SAID IF
ANYONE RETURNS IT,
HE'LL HAVE THEM ARRESTED.
HERE'S AN INTERESTING ONE.
FLINTY McCLINTOCK CALLED.
SOMEONE STOLE
HIS TOOLBOX.
OH, REALLY?
OH, YEAH.
WOW.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, I THOUGHT YOU
WERE GOING TO BE WALKING THE
STREETS WITH THIS,
NOT BY THE PHONE HERE, LIKE
JO-JO'S SIDEKICK ALLIANCE
OR SOMETHING OR OTHER.
OH, YEAH,
WE ARE.
IT'S JUST THAT CHUBBY'S MOM
IS STILL WORKING ON OUR CRIME
FIGHTING OUTFITS, YOU KNOW.
I'M HOPING THEY'RE GOING TO
USE THOSE BIG DRAPES IN
THEIR FRONT WINDOW.
THEY'RE SO COOL.
IF SHE USES THE DRAPES, THEN
I CAN WALK UP AND USE OUR
SLOGAN AND SAY,
"IT'S CURTAINS
FOR CRIMINALS."
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
DON'T SAY IT OUT LOUD UNLESS
YOU'RE TIRED OF THOSE TEETH.
I WAS GOING TO GO OVER THERE
NOW FOR A FITTING, YOU KNOW.
WHILST I AM ON MY WAY OVER,
MAYBE I CAN RETURN THAT
TOOLBOX TO FLINTY FOR YOU.
OH, THIS?
OH, IS THIS FLINTY'S?
YOU KNOW,
I THINK SO.
OH.
YEAH, YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
APPRECIATE IT.
YOU SHOULD BE
ASHAMED OF YOURSELF.
WELL, I USED TO BE,
BUT SINCE I HAD YOU AS A
NEPHEW, NOTHING BOTHERS ME.
HELLO, FLINTY?
YEAH, I THINK HAROLD'S
GOT YOUR TOOLBOX.
I HEARD THAT.
NOW, THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
YOU CAN DO ON A SATURDAY,
AND I DON'T MEAN RUN OVER
A GUY YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, IT'S A LITTLE
SOMETHING YOU CAN DO
IF YOU'VE GOT A VEHICLE,
AND THIS IS SOMETHING NO ONE
EVER DOES ANYMORE.
IT'S ROTATING THE TIRES AND,
YOU KNOW, SWITCHING ONE FOR
THE OTHER, AND SO ON.
BILL HAD A PLAN HERE:
HE'S GOING TO NUMBER
ALL THE TIRES.
AND, YEAH, I THINK, YOU KNOW,
I THINK WE UNDERSTAND.
IT RUINS IT, YOU KNOW,
WHEN SOMEONE -- ANYWAY.
OKAY, LET'S JUST GET GOING.
FIRST THING YOU WANT TO DO
IS JACK UP THE ONE WHEEL.
AND WHICH WHEEL WILL THIS BE?
THIS WILL BE WHEEL NUMBER --
DON'T EXPLAIN IT, BILL.
BILL, LET'S MOVE ON.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS NUMBER
YOUR TIRES, SO YOU DON'T
CONFUSE --
BILL, CHALK IS NOT GOING TO
WORK ON A TIRE, ALL RIGHT?
HE'S GOT ANOTHER IDEA.
WHAT'S HE GOT THERE?
SILLY --
THAT'S FUNNY.
OH, NO -- OKAY, NO,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
I WAS WRONG.
IT'S NOT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ALL RIGHT, LET'S
GET ROTATING.
LET'S GET A NUMBER. MARK THAT
TIRE ANY WAY YOU CAN.
ANY NUMBER YOU WANT.
WELL, HE'S PRETTY GOOD
WITH THAT THING.
NOW, WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR IS A --
OH, BOY. HOLY SMOKE!
WELL, HE MUST HAVE INCREDIBLE
MEDICAL CONDITIONS.
WELL, HE'S GOT
ANOTHER ONE NOW.
ALL RIGHT, SO HE'S GOT
ALL THE NUTS OFF THERE.
ALL RIGHT, WATCH YOUR FOOT.
BILL, CAREFUL --
OH, THIS IS A --
OKAY, THIS IS WHAT WE CALL
A TIME FILLER.
WE'VE GOT TO GET ALL THESE --
THEY'RE ALL OVER
THE PLACE NOW.
WHO'S GOING TO
FIND THOSE?
WHY DID I ASK?
ACTUALLY, I DON'T MIND.
KEEP ME FARTHER AWAY
FROM BILL AND LESS CHANCE
OF BEING INJURED.
I WISH I COULD SAY
THE SAME FOR THE VAN.
TRY NOT TO GET REVENGE
RIGHT AWAY.
OH, WAIT A MINUTE.
NO IDEA.
NO IDEA --
I HAVE NO --
ALL RIGHT, SO HE'S GETTING --
THIS IS TIRE NUMBER THREE NOW.
AND JUST PULL THAT RIGHT OFF.
THE RIM IS KIND OF --
PULLED IT RIGHT OFF.
PULLED IT RIGHT OFF
THE RIM THERE, BILL.
WELL, WELL, YOU'RE
DOING A GOOD JOB.
OH, I WAS GOING TO SAY WE'VE
GOT ONE MORE TO GO, AND LOOKS
LIKE YOU'VE GOT IT.
I'M NOT HAVING THE BEST
TIME EVER AND I'M THINKING,
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO SPEND
THE REST OF THE DAY HERE.
I THINK I'LL HEAD OFF
TO THE RAILROAD TRACKS.
AMATEURS AND IMMATURES.
I CALL THEM THE
THREE DORKATEERS.
THEY GOT THE UNIFORMS
AND EVERYTHING.
IT'S PRETTY SAD,
I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU.
YOU'VE GOT TO SEE --
THAT'S -- THAT'S
QUITE A LOOK, HAROLD.
THE BIRD HEAD
IS A NICE TOUCH.
I'M GUESSING THAT'S THE ONLY
CHICK YOU'LL GET CLOSE TO.
IT'S NOT JUST ANY
BIRD EITHER.
IT'S A PIGEON.
WE CALL OUR CRIME FIGHTING
SQUADRON, "THE STOOL PIGEONS."
THE STOOL PIGEON, THAT'S A
MEDICAL TERM, ISN'T IT, HAROLD?
IT REMINDS PEOPLE TO PHONE
THE AUTHORITIES IN THE EVENT
OF A CRIMINAL ACT.
YEAH, WE'RE REALLY
REDUCING CRIME.
I DON'T KNOW, HAROLD.
I LOOK AT YOU, I WANT
TO COMMIT ONE.
DO YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE YOU WERE BROUGHT
UP IN A VIOLENT SOCIETY,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO LEARN TO FIGHT THAT.
AND THAT'S WHAT WE DO,
WE STOOL PIGEONS.
WE OFFER PEOPLE A REMEDY FOR,
YOU KNOW, FOR CHANGING THINGS
AND GETTING OUT THERE AND
HAVING A NON-VIOLENT WAY
OF REMEDYING
AND KEEPING PEACE
IN THE SOCIETY.
WOW, HAROLD, DO YOU
MIND A LITTLE ADVICE?
NOT AT ALL.
UNLIKE YOURSELF,
I EMBRACE CHANGE.
GOOD, GO CHANGE.
NO, I CAN'T BECAUSE ME AND THE
OTHER STOOL PIGEONS HAVE GOT
TO PATROL THE STREETS.
YEAH, WE'RE GOING TO SWOOP
DOWN FROM THE SKIES AND
GET A DROP ON CRIME.
DON'T GET ANY DROPPINGS
ON YOUR SHOES.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THAT PART OF THE SHOW THAT WE
EXAMINE THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY,
Audience:  "I DON'T KNOW."
WAY EXCELLENT!
OKAY, ALL RIGHT. JOINING ME AND
UNCLE RED ON THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW THIS WEEK IS
Mr. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD OF
THE ROTSHCHILD SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
WHERE ARE MOTTO IS:
"IF YOUR CUP OVERFLOWS,
"I'LL BE THERE
WITH MY HOSE."
OKEYDOKEY.
OKAY, THIS IS OUR
FIRST LETTER.
IT'S FROM EDNA KAY, AND
IT GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS: I WANT TO
GO ON A GRAND VACATION.
"SHOULD I TRAVEL ACROSS THE SEA
OR SOMEWHERE IN NORTH AMERICA?"
ALL RIGHT, EDNA, I WOULD SAY
STAY WITH NORTH AMERICA
BECAUSE YOU WANT TO
BE ABLE TO DRIVE HOME.
I'LL TELL YOU, GET INTO YOUR
THIRD WEEK OF CZECHOSLOVAKIAN
CHEESEBURGERS,
YOU'RE GOING TO WANT TO SLIDE
INTO THE VAN AND HEAD WEST.
OH, NO, I HAVE GOTTA
BEG TO DIFFERENTIATE
WITH YOU, RED.
EUROPE IS WHERE
YOU WANT TO GO.
THAT'S WHERE ALL
THE HISTORY IS.
THAT'S WHERE SHE
ALL BEGAN.
WHERE WHAT ALL BEGAN?
WESTERN CIVILIZATION.
OR, MORE SPECIFICALLY,
SEWAGE SYSTEMS.
OH, YEAH, YOU CAN STILL GO SEE
AND VISIT THE ANCIENT ROMAN
SEWAGE SYSTEM.
THE FAMOUS
'CLOACA MAXIMA'.
OH, YEAH, I'LL TELL YOU,
WHEN YOU'RE LOOKING DOWN
A TOILET DRAIN THAT WAS
BUILT IN 580 B.C.,
IT'S ALMOST LIKE YOU'RE LOOKING
UP THE BACK END OF YOUR
FAMILY TREE.
WELL, YOU KNOW, MAYBE OUR
VIEWER WOULD LIKE TO
GO TO EUROPE
TO VISIT MUSEUMS AND CASTLES AND
SEE THE SITES, YOU KNOW, WHERE
THE TURNING POINTS OF HISTORY
ACTUALLY OCCURRED.
WELL, YOU KNOW, IF THAT'S
YOUR THING, YOU KNOW.
BUT HOW DOES THAT COMPARE WITH
SEEING THE HOME OF ENGLISHMAN
SIR JOHN HERRINGTON,
WHO IN 1596 HAD THE ONLY WATER
CLOSET IN THE ENTIRE
BRITISH EMPIRE?
WELL, I BET HE HAD
A LINEUP, HUH?
WELL, EDNA, I ADVISE YOU GO TO
EUROPE AND GO OUT AND SEE THINGS
THAT AREN'T AROUND HERE.
OH, FOR SURE.
OH, FRANCE, YOU'VE GOT
TO GO TO FRANCE.
OH, YEAH, YOU'VE GOT TO SEE --
YOU'VE GOT TO SEE THE BATHROOM
GRAFFITI IN VERSAILLES.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S WHERE, IN MARIE
ANTOINETTE'S OWN HANDWRITING, IT
SAYS, "LET THEM EAT CAKE,
"BUT GO EASY ON
THE BRAN MUFFINS."
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, SOMETIMES YOUR
IDEAS BORDER ON A DEATH WISH.
YOU KNOW THAT, EH?
NO, NO, THOSE KIDS
DIDN'T MEAN ANY HARM.
THEY WERE JUST HAVING FUN.
WHAT WERE YOU STOOL PIGEONS
DOING UP BY THE MAIN
HIGHWAY ANYHOW?
WELL, WE GOT THIS PHONE CALL
THAT OLD MAN SEDGEWICK WAS UP
THERE KICKING STONES AT
PASSING CARS,
SO WE WENT TO
CHECK IT OUT.
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK WAS UP THERE
KICKING STONES AT PASSING CARS.
BUT THEN THESE TOUGH GUYS CAME
ALONG AND SAID THEY WERE GOING
TO BEAT US UP,
AND CHUBBY SPEAKS RIGHT UP AND
HE SAYS, "WELL, YEAH, WELL YOU
GUYS ARE JUST ALL TALK."
WHICH WE NOW KNOW
WAS A MISTAKE TO SAY.
YEAH. YEAH.
BUT THEN YOU KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED THEN?
SUSIE CAME BY AND SHE SAYS,
"YOU TOUGHS, DON'T BE HITTING
HAROLD AS HARD AS THE OTHERS."
I THINK SHE LOVES ME.
LOVE HURTS,
DOESN'T IT, HAROLD?
TODAY, YES.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT'S GREAT?
I THINK SHE JUST TOOK
MY LUNCH TO GET MY ATTENTION.
SHE STOLE IT TO
TAKE MY ATTENTION,
AND THEN SHE
STOLE MY HEART.
OH, BOY.
WELL, IF SHE LIKES SARDINES,
YOU MIGHT HAVE A CHANCE.
(POSSUM CALL)
IT'S MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
AWAY YOU GO.
TAKE IT EASY FOR NOW.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING, I'LL BE
COMING STRAIGHT HOME AFTER
THE MEETING.
IT LOOKS LIKE HAROLD MAY
HAVE FOUND A LITTLE BIT
OF PUPPY LOVE.
AND IF IT GOES ANY
FARTHER THAN THAT,
I'M GOING TO TELL
YOU RIGHT NOW,
I DON'T WANT ANY OF THE PUPS.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
AND ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
HAROLD AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTER]
Harold:  HERE HE COMES.
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
HE'S HERE.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red:  SIT DOWN.
Harold:  OKAY, WE JUST HAVE
ONE ANNOUNCEMENT TONIGHT.
ACTUALLY, IT'S A WARNING.
IF YOU'RE BOATING AT NIGHT,
WATCH OUT FOR THE
WATER SKI JUMP.
NO, SERIOUSLY, BECAUSE STINKY
PETERSON, HE'S GOING TO BE OKAY,
BUT HE'S GOING TO NEED HELP
GETTING HIS BOAT OFF THE
CHURCH STEEPLE.
SO ANY VOLUNTEERS? YOU'VE
GOT TO GO REALLY FAST...