IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
NOW, HERE'S THE MAJORDOMO
OF LIFE IN SLO-MO,
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
THINGS ARE OUT OF WHACK
AT MY PLACE THIS WEEK.
ONE OF BERNICE'S RELATIVES
IS STAYING WITH US.
BERNICE'S SISTER'S DAUGHTER.
SHE'S 16 YEARS OLD.
HELLO? HI? WHAT?
SIXTEEN?
LIKE, A FEMALE TYPE PERSON?
YOU MET HER, HAROLD,
AT THE CHURCH PICNIC.
SHE HAD THE TACO ON HER FACE --
WITH TEENAGERS,
IT'S HARD TO TELL.
I DON'T
REMEMBER HER.
WHAT'S HER NAME?
UM...
ALICE, OR... ALYSHA...
WE JUST CALL HER "HORSE".
HER?
OH, I REMEMBER HER.
SHE STILL WEARING THAT BIT?
I MEAN BRACES.
YEAH, SHE'S
GONNA
HAVE THEM
AWHILE.
IT WILL TAKE A WHILE
TO CORRAL THOSE TEETH.
SHE'S GOT A SMILE
LIKE STONEHENGE.
SAY HELLO FOR ME.
NO, NO, NO, HAROLD,
YOU SAY HELLO YOURSELF.
NO WAY!
COME ON.
AUNT BERNICE SAYS
YOU HAVE A LOT IN COMMON.
I DON'T EVEN FIND HER
ATTRACTIVE.
THERE'S ONE THING RIGHT THERE.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MAIN MESSAGE BEING,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
I INTRODUCED HAROLD
TO MY WIFE'S SISTER'S DAUGHTER.
HE DIDN'T SAY TWO WORDS.
NEVER SEEN HIM THAT QUIET,
WHICH MEANT HE HAD TO RELY
ON HIS LOOKS.
(Audience laughing)
TRY TO IMAGINE HOW THAT WENT.
MIND YOU, HORSE ISN'T SO EASY
ON THE EYES, HERSELF.
(Singing)
(Audience laughing)
(Giggling)
YOU OK,
HAROLD?
YEAH, OH, YEAH, OH, YEAH!
SORRY YOU TWO
DIDN'T HIT IT OFF.
ALYSHA
ASKED ABOUT ME?
DID SHE SAY SHE LIKES
STRONG, SILENT TYPES?
DID SHE SAY THAT?
I'M JUST SAYING, DON'T WORRY
THAT YOU TWO DIDN'T TALK.
MAYBE SHE DIDN'T WANT
TO FILL THE AIR
WITH MEANINGLESS CHATTER.
YEAH... I DON'T WANT YOU
TO TAKE IT PERSONALLY.
SHE PROBABLY HAD BROCCOLI
WEDGED INTO HER BRACES.
NO, NO, NO,
WE DID NOT HAVE TO SPEAK,
FOR OUR EYES SAID IT ALL.
(Audience laughing)
THAT WOULD BE
QUITE A CONVERSATION.
THEY EACH HAVE FOUR OF 'EM.
NOW... NOW...
ARE YOU SAYING
YOU ACTUALLY LIKED HER?
I'M GONNA MARRY HER!
FOR GOSH SAKES,
SHE'S ONLY 16 YEARS OLD!
WELL, WE'LL GO
TO MISSISSIPPI.
NO, COME ON, HAROLD.
SHE'S YOUR COUSIN, ALL RIGHT?
OH, RIGHT.
YEAH.
MAKE THAT ALABAMA.
(Laughing)
(Red): LATER ON, BILL'S
GONNA BE TRYING HIS HAND
AT A LITTLE TARZAN ACTION.
YOU KNOW, SWINGING
FROM TREE TO TREE.
RIGHT NOW,
HE'S GONNA DO A DRY RUN.
GONNA SWING FROM THAT LADDER
TO THE OTHER LADDER.
GONNA SWING...
SWING WITH THE ROPE.
HE'S GONNA THROW
THE ROPE UP -- OW!
THROW THE ROPE UP,
TRY TO GET THE TOP BRANCH --
NOT BAD!
THAT WILL PULL HIM...
I GUESS IT'S STRONG... OK.
UP HE GOES AND THEN
HE'S GONNA SHORTEN THE ROPE
AND SWING ACROSS.
I'M NOT SURE THAT TREE
IS AS STRONG
AS IT NEEDS TO BE TO HOLD
SOMEONE OF BILL'S, UH...
HOW CAN I PUT THIS DELICATELY?
FLAB?
YOU KNOW, WITH BILL,
SOMETIMES HE DOESN'T FOCUS
ON WHAT'S IMPORTANT,
LIKE, SAY, HIS BALANCE.
HE PULLS THE TREE DOWN,
HITS THE LADDER-- OHHH!
OH! OH! OH! AND...
THERE'S THE TREE.
YEAH, MM-HMM, YEAH.
BIT OF A DRY RUN.
A FEW WRINKLES IN IT, BILL.
AND I SEEM TO HAVE PICKED UP
A BIRD'S NEST.
NOW HE'S WANTING ME
TO EGG HIM ON
BUT I SAY, "HEY, BILL,
THE YOLK'S ON YOU."
OH, DON'T GO
IN THE BUSHES
THAT'S MY WARNING TO YOU
THERE ARE BETTER PLACES
THAN SHRUBS
TO DO WHAT YOU WANNA DO
OH, DON'T GO
IN THE BUSHES
THAT'S NOT
THE PLACE TO BE
AND IF YOU GET BITTEN
AND BADLY STUNG
DON'T NAME IT AFTER ME
(Laughing)
WELCOME TO THE POSSUM LODGE
WORD GAME!
TONIGHT'S PRIZE IS TWO DAYS
WITH A HOOKER,
FROM EDNA'S HOUSE OF RUGS!
(Audience laughing)
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MIKE HAMAR
TO SAY THIS WORD.
CRIMINAL.
AND GO, EH?
MIKE, SOMEONE
WHO BREAKS THE LAW.
COUSIN LARRY.
BANK ROBBER.
UNCLE EDGAR.
CAR THIEF.
AUNTIE THELMA.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE GENERAL TERM
FOR LAW-BREAKERS.
OHHH! FAMILY.
OK, OK.
SOMEONE GOES TO JAIL,
THEY ARE...
... RAILROADED.
BUT THEY ARE...
VICTIMS.
INNOCENT VICTIMS!
LET'S SAY YOU'RE ARRESTED.
I DIDN'T
DO IT.
NO, NO, NO,
THE COPS WOULD CALL YOU...
MIKE.
THEY ALL KNOW ME, RIGHT?
ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
HOW WOULD YOU DESCRIBE
THE COST
OF BAIL?
OH, CRIMINAL!
(Laughing and applause)
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
WE'RE GONNA DO A PROJECT
THAT COMBINES
TWO OF MY FAVOURITE
RECREATIONAL ACTIVITIES --
SITTING DOWN AND EATING.
THE OTHER DAY, I WAS WATCHING
T.V., WHICH PLACED THIRD
IN MY SITTING-DOWN-AND-EATING
SWEEPSTAKES.
ANYWAY, THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
I GOT HUNGRY AND I'M THINKING,
"WE GOT A KITCHEN
AND IN IT IS A FRIDGE.
"THAT FRIDGE IS ON WHEELS."
I'M THINKING, "BOY,
WHY CAN'T I GET THAT FRIDGE
"TO KINDA ROLL TOWARDS ME?"
MOOSE THOMPSON CAN DO IT
JUST BY WAITING,
'CAUSE HE TENDS TO BE
THE LOW POINT IN ANY ROOM...
AS HE IS IN ANY CONVERSATION.
FOR ME, I NEED
A MECHANICAL ADVANTAGE.
I'M THINKING, "WHY NOT USE
THE ONE THING
"THAT HAS ALWAYS PUT FOOD
ON MY TABLE?"
FISHING, HUH?
DEEP-SEA FISHING.
FIRST THING I GOTTA DO IS
ANCHOR THIS THING
ONTO THE CHAIR SOMEWHERE.
I'M THINKING RIGHT ABOUT...
... RIGHT ABOUT THERE,
ALL RIGHT?
NOW, TO DO THAT...
IF YOU'RE MADE OF MONEY,
YOU COULD GET
A PROPER DEEP-SEA
FISHING MOUNT THINGS
AND PUT THAT ON THERE,
OR YOU COULD USE ONE OF THESE
WALL-FLANGE MOUNTING UNITS,
BUT THAT'S GONNA CATCH
IN THE CUFF OF YOUR PANTS
AND SPOIL THE LOOK
OF THE CHAIR.
SO, INSTEAD...
KEEP IT SIMPLE.
OH...
HERE WE GO, HERE WE GO.
YOU CAN MOUNT THE FISHING ROD
IN THE CHAIR,
USING SOME KIND OF CLAMP
OR SHACKLE.
YOU COULD WELD THAT IN THERE.
I PREFER THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
I FEEL A SNACK COMIN' ON!
YOU DON'T WANT TO USE BIG HOOKS
INSIDE THE HOME.
EVEN INSIDE THE LODGE,
IT'S A BIT IFFY.
I'D RECOMMEND YOU GO
WITH THIS TYPE OF LURE.
THEY'RE LEFT OVER
FROM THAT TIME
I TRIED TO MAKE
THE HUMAN FLY OUTFIT
WHEN I WANTED TO CLIMB
THE OUTSIDE OF THE LODGE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE
IF THE FRIDGE ARE BITING.
(Thumping)
OH, THAT SOUNDED GOOD.
OH, YEAH, THINK WE GOT ONE.
YOU GOTTA PLAY THESE IN
JUST RIGHT.
IT'S AN APPLIANCE
YOU'RE DEALING WITH.
IF THEY WANT TO RUN,
LET THEM RUN!
GET 'ER IN HERE.
BY GOLLY, SHE'S A HUMMER!
OH, MY GOD!
OH, OH, OH, OH!
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I GUESS AIM IS IMPORTANT, TOO.
OK, SO, DON'T FORGET,
CATCH AND RELEASE.
(Audience laughing)
HERE WE GO!
OH, BOY!
(Grunting)
AHHHH!
THERE WE GO.
IT'S JUST THAT EASY,
JUST THAT DARN EASY.
GET US A DRINK... AHHH...
NEVER HAD TO... NEVER HAD TO
LEAVE MY CHAIR.
I THINK THIS PROJECT
IS REALLY GONNA CATCH ON.
(Thumping)
STINKY PETERSON
WANTS HIS RECLINING CHAIR BACK.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
IF YOU GOT ANOTHER LURE,
WE CAN HITCH IN TO TOWN!
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
WANT TO TALK
TO YOU MIDDLE-AGED GUYS
WHO ARE MAYBE CONTEMPLATING
SIGNING UP FOR BASEBALL.
IF YOU'RE ONE OF THESE GUYS
WHO THINKS
THEY CAN PICK UP A BAT
AFTER 25 YEARS
OF BASIC STILLNESS,
AND THEN SLAM A HIGH FASTBALL
OVER THE THIRD BASEMAN'S HEAD,
STRETCHING A DOUBLE
INTO A TRIPLE,
WELL, THINK AGAIN.
(Audience laughing)
DON'T BE SURPRISED IF A HIT
AND MAKING IT TO FIRST BASE
HAPPEN IN TWO DIFFERENT
AT-BATS...
MAYBE EVEN
IN TWO DIFFERENT GAMES.
YOU'LL BE LUCKY TO STRETCH
A TRIPLE INTO A SINGLE,
AND MORE LIKELY, YOU'LL STRETCH
YOUR HAMSTRING INTO A HOSPITAL.
THE ONLY THING IN YOUR FAVOUR
IS THAT THERE'S A GUY OUT THERE
WHO LOOKS LIKE YOU,
THE SAME WEIGHT AND AGE,
HE HAS TO RUN, BEND OVER,
PICK UP THE BALL,
AND THEN THROW IT IN.
HE PROBABLY SHOULDN'T
BE PLAYING, EITHER.
IT MIGHT BE TIME TO GIVE IT UP.
ONCE YOU HIT 40, THINK ABOUT
HANGING UP THE CLEATS.
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE ON A SLIDE
DOESN'T MEAN YOU SHOULD BE
PLAYING BASEBALL.
YOU'RE NOT ON DECK.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN
IN THE DAMN BOAT!
(Audience laughing)
SIT IN THE STANDS.
WATCH YOUR FRIENDS PLAY.
YOU'LL HAVE A BETTER VIEW,
FRESHER HOT DOGS,
AND YOU CAN DRIVE THEM TO
THE HOSPITAL BETWEEN INNINGS.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YA.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause)
WELL, HORSE -- SORRY --
ALYSHA IS STILL STAYING
WITH BERNICE AND I.
IT'S DIFFICULT GETTING USED TO
TWO WOMEN AROUND THE HOUSE.
GO IN THE BATHROOM,
YOU'VE GOT THEM WAFFLE IRONS
FOR YOUR HAIR.
WHEN WE WATCH T.V.
I'M ONLY ALLOWED TO FLICK
BETWEEN FOUR CHANNELS.
THAT'S ALL I GET.
UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED,
IS THIS TOO MUCH?!
NO, IT'S NOT ENOUGH.
I CAN STILL SEE YOUR FACE.
HA, HA, HA, HA.
IT'S NOT FOR ME.
IT'S FOR ALYSHA.
YOU KNOW
WHY?
NO.
NO REASON.
IT'S MY WAY OF SAYING,
"HERE'S SOME FLOWERS."
YOU'D BETTER SLOW DOWN.
YOU CAN SPEND TIME AND MONEY
AND THIS MIGHT NOT BE
GOING ANYWHERE.
SHE MIGHT BE ALLERGIC.
DON'T WORRY.
I MADE SURE THAT MY DEPOSIT ON
THE WEDDING RING IS REFUNDABLE.
OH, MAN, HAROLD, HAROLD, WHOA.
BEFORE YOU GET ENGAGED,
MAYBE YOU MIGHT WANT TO
GO OUT WITH HER ONE TIME.
YOU WANT TO FIND OUT
IF YOU LIKE HER?
TAKE HER TO SOMETHING
YOU DON'T WANT TO GO,
AN OPERA OR BALLET
OR ANYTHING WITH MIMES.
OH, I
HATE MIMES.
IF YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME,
YOU'LL KNOW
SHE'S THE WOMAN FOR YOU.
YOU'RE SAYING,
WHEN MEN AND WOMEN DATE,
YOU ONLY GO PLACES
THAT SHE ENJOYS.
YUP --
JUST TILL YOU'RE MARRIED.
(Audience laughing)
THEN YOU DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
UH, MY NAME IS DALTON HUMPHREY,
AND I'M A MAN.
(All): HI, DALTON.
HELLO, MEN.
IT'S BEEN LESS THAN 24 HOURS
SINCE I ACTED LIKE A GUY.
IT HAPPENED LIKE THIS.
I WAS, UM,
WELL, THE DISHWASHER
NEEDED A LITTLE REPAIRING.
YOU KNOW HOW THE FOOD TRAP
WILL NEED CLEANING OUT.
ALL I REALLY NEEDED
WAS A PHILLIPS SCREWDRIVER,
BUT I WENT TO THE BASEMENT
AND I GOT MY
BIG, BIG, BIG TOOL-BOX.
OH BOY.
AND IN FULL VIEW OF MY FAMILY...
I PULLED OUT
EVERY TOOL I HAD.
EVERY ONE.
I HAD THEM ON THE COUNTER,
THE FLOOR, ALL OVER THE PLACE.
AND I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU,
MEN, I HAD SO MANY TOOLS OUT,
I COULDN'T EVEN WORK.
AND THEN I LOOKED--
I LOOKED UP...
INTO THE FACES OF MY FAMILY,
MY WIFE AND MY DAUGHTER
STANDING THERE,
AND I WILL NEVER FORGET
THAT LOOK IN MY LIFE.
I WAS--
GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME, HAROLD.
I WAS SO ASHAMED...
TO BE SEEN THERE
SQUATTIN' AMONGST MY TOOLS.
I GUESS I MUST HAVE COME TO
MY SENSES AT SOME POINT.
I SAID TO MY WIFE,
"HONEY...
"I'VE GOT WAY
TOO MANY TOOLS OUT HERE.
"I ONLY REALLY NEEDED
A PHILLIPS SCREWDRIVER."
THEN I PUT ALL MY TOOLS...
BACK IN THE BOX.
ALL RIGHT!
YEAH!
(Sobbing)
WELL, I GUESS WE LEARNED
YOU ONLY CARRY THE TOOLS
THAT YOU NEED,
AND ONLY BUY THE TOOLS
THAT YOU CAN USE.
NO, WHAT WE LEARNED IS
YOU DON'T TRY FIXIN' STUFF
WHEN YOUR FAMILY
IS WATCHING YA.
(Applause)
ALL RIGHT, IT'S
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL".
THAT'S TARZAN BILL THERE.
THAT'S A LOIN CLOTH,
BUT HE'S GOT A LOT TO LOIN.
OH, THAT'S VERY TASTEFUL.
THANK YOU.
LOOK,
THERE'S ANOTHER ROPE THERE.
ANYWAY, HE'S GONNA
SWING OFF THE TOP OF THE VAN.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
ALL RIGHT, SHAKEY START,
BUT THERE HE GOES.
GRAB THE OTHER ROPE.
UH-OH.
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES.
ALL RIGHT, UH...
I'M THINKIN' THAT MAY NOT BE
WHAT HE HAD PLANNED.
MY MISTAKE.
WAY YOU GO --
GRAB THAT ROPE.
HE GRABBED IT HIGHER
SO HE COULD GET...
HE'S CLEARED THE VAN.
YOU'RE WAY UP THERE.
COME ON DOWN.
OH BOY.
HOT ON THE HANDS, BILL?
OH, THAT WOULD BURN
THE CALLOUSES OFF.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
I GOT A FAN IN THE TRUCK.
THERE YOU GO.
THAT FEEL BETTER?
HEY, TEMPER, TEMPER!
THAT'S MY FAN!
RIGHT OVER A TREE.
ALL RIGHT,
SO PRACTISE MAKES PAIN.
WE GOT THREE ROPES.
THAT'S THE EXTENSION CORD.
THAT'S THE EXTENSION CORD
FROM THE FAN.
GRAB THAT -- OH, NICE.
THAT'S THE EXTENSION CORD!
BILL, THAT'S THE--
OH, OH, OH!
HERE COMES ONE OF YOUR FANS,
BILL.
OH BOY.
HERE'S A QUILT OF POSSUM LODGE
MADE BY A NICE WOMAN
FROM WYOMING.
ALL THESE YEARS HAVING
HAROLD AROUND CONVINCED ME
THAT I DON'T REGRET
NOT HAVING A SON.
ALYSHA HAS ONLY BEEN WITH US
A WEEK,
AND I ALREADY FEEL THAT WAY
ABOUT NOT HAVING A DAUGHTER.
BERNICE HAS ME
ON MY BEST BEHAVIOUR.
GOT TO WEAR PANTS AT BREAKFAST,
CUTTING FOOD WITH A KNIFE
RATHER THAN MY THUMB NAIL.
OH, YES!
YES, YES, YES, YES!
WHO DE MAN? -- I'M DE MAN.
YOU DE MAN?
YOU CAN'T BE DE MAN
'CAUSE I'M DE MAN!
I'M SMOKIN'!
OW!
HA HA HA!
HOO HOO HA... HA.
GOT YOURSELF A DATE,
DO YOU, HAROLD?
YES, I DOES!
I TOOK YOUR ADVICE,
EXCEPT I WAS COOL.
I SAID "THE POSSUM LAKE PLAYERS
"ARE DOING
A DINNER THEATRE."
THAT'S WHERE YOU GET
A SHOW AND FOOD.
LAST WEEK THEY DID
"RIGOLETTO" AND RIGATONI.
THAT'S A GOOD SHOW RIGHT THERE.
SO, THIS WEEK THEY'RE DOING
"CARMEN" AND CRAB.
I THOUGHT "THAT'S GREAT."
I SAID "SINCE I HATE OPERA,
DO YOU WANNA GO?"
SHE WENT "UH-HUH."
(Giggling)
WELL, GOSH, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU CAN SIT THROUGH THAT,
THERE MAY BE
A TWINGE OF LOVE IN THE MIDST
OF THIS PATHETIC DESPERATION.
BUT THERE IS A BIT OF
A WRINKLE IN THE PLAN THOUGH.
SHE'S NOT ALLOWED TO GO ON
UNCHAPERONED DATES.
AUNT BERNICE SAID THAT
YOU AND HER WOULD BE HAPPY
TO JOIN US.
FORGET IT.
NO WAY, NO.
BERNICE DRAGGED ME TO
ONE OF THEM THINGS.
IT WAS "THE SOUND OF MUSIC"
WITH BAKED BEANS.
(Audience laughing)
YEAH, I HEARD THAT.
IT WAS ALL OVER TOWN.
BUT IT'S TOO LATE.
I GOT FOUR TICKETS
RIGHT UP FRONT.
YOU KNOW THE BEST PART?
AUNT BERNICE PAID FOR THEM.
AHHH, GEEZ!
WELCOME TO "AUTOBIOGRAPHY"
WHERE MEMBERS OF POSSUM LODGE
HAVE REMEMBRANCES
OF CARS GONE BY.
GOT ARNIE DOGAN HERE.
ARNIE, TELL US ABOUT
THE FIRST CAR YOU EVER HAD.
A VOLVO, '74.
VERY SAFE.
BUILT LIKE A TANK.
EXCELLENT FOR
THE ROOFIN' BUSINESS.
YOU COULD GET 10 CASES
OF SHINGLES IN THE TRUNK.
I GOT A CASE OF SHINGLES
IN A HOT TUB ONCE.
BOY, A VOLVO, ARNIE.
I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
YOU'D HAVE SOMETHING SPORTIER.
WHEN YOU'RE FALLIN'
OFF A ROOF THREE TIMES A DAY,
YOU'RE NOT LOOKING FOR
EXCITEMENT.
NO, NO.
WHAT WOULD IT BE LIKE, ARNIE,
A TEENAGER IN A VOLVO?
I'M THINKIN' DATES.
OH, A LOT OF DATES.
NO KIDDIN', HUH?
OH YEAH.
YEAH.
YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH, THEY'D CARRY MY CRUTCHES
AND CHANGE MY BANDAGES.
ON A CLEAR NIGHT, WE'D CRUISE
RIGHT ON UP TO ROCK REEF POINT
AND JUST GAZE OUT
OVER THOSE ROOF-TOPS
TRYIN' TO SPOT WHERE
DAD AND I LEFT THE LADDER.
SO YOU NEVER MARRIED THEN,
HUH, MR. DOGAN.
NO, NOT YET, HAROLD.
I'M MARRIED TO MY WORK.
JUST A CRUSTY ROOFER
IN A BEAT-UP VOLVO.
MORE LIKE A BEAT-UP ROOFER
IN A RUSTY VOLVO.
YEAH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW I WROTE A COUNTRY SONG
ABOUT THAT CAR.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO HEAR IT?
WE'RE A LITTLE
SHORT OF...
TOLERANCE.
GIMME THAT, HAROLD.
YOU BROUGHT
THE GUITAR.
GOOD MOVE,
HAROLD.
I WAS HIDING THE GUITAR.
THIS IS A SPECIAL ONE.
HERE WE GO.
SHE WAS MADE OF STEEL
AND NAUGAHYDE
WITH FIVE WHEELS
COUNTIN' THE SPARE
YOU NEVER KNEW
WHERE YOU WERE GOIN'
YOU WERE PRETTY SURE
YOU'D BE ABLE TO
THUMB A RIDE BACK
I REMEMBER THE NIGHT
OF THE ACCIDENT
NOTHIN' WAS LEFT
BUT THE RADIO AERIAL
THE DOCTORS
COULDN'T REMOVE IT
SO NOW I WALK
WITH A LIMP
BUT I GET
OVER 200 STATIONS
(Audience laughing)
(Applause)
WELL, I'M SORRY,
BUT THAT IS TOO MUCH TO ASK
OF ANY HUMAN BEING.
THE MOST EMBARRASSING NIGHT
OF MY LIFE.
"CARMEN" IS A FAMOUS OPERA.
IT WAS STUPID OF YOU TO GO
"WHICH ONE'S THE KARMANN GHIA?"
IT WAS A JOKE, FOR GOSH SAKE.
OPERA VIEWERS,
THEY'RE SUCH UPTIGHT PEOPLE.
THE WOMEN WITH
THE ZIRCONIUM HANGING OFF THEM,
THE GUYS IN THE SPORTS JACKETS,
ALL TO WATCH
A BUNCH OF FAT GUYS OVERACT.
HEY, HEY, HEY, EASY THERE.
IT SOUNDS A BIT LIKE OUR SHOW.
(Audience laughing)
I'M TELLING YOU,
THAT WHOLE EVENING
WAS A TOTAL DISASTER.
NOT FOR ME -- ESPECIALLY
AFTER YOU GOT THROWN OUT.
WHY WERE YOU SINGING
"THE TOREADOR SONG"?
THEY HAD THE WORDS ALL WRONG.
THEY LEFT OUT THE "DON'T SPIT
ON THE FLOORIE" PART.
HOW DID THE DATE TURN OUT
WITH HORSE?
STILL
IN LOVE?
DON'T CALL HER HORSE!
I WON'T TOLERATE
YOUR INSOLENCE ANY MORE.
DON'T EVEN DO IT.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
I WASN'T REALLY INSULTING HER
BY CALLING HER HORSE.
I JUST MEANT, UH...
SHE'S A STABLE GIRL.
(Audience laughing)
I REALLY LIKE HER.
BUT WE'VE DECIDED
WE'RE GONNA WAIT,
SEE WHAT WE FEEL LIKE
IN A FEW YEARS.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
YOU KISS HER GOOD NIGHT?
HA, HA.
GENTLEMEN DON'T TELL.
SO NO.
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
I THINK SHE WASN'T SURE
IF HER INSURANCE FOR HER BRACES
COVERED LIP PUNCTURES.
SO...
BUT I'M HOPEFUL --
IT'S LIKE THEY SAY IN OPERA.
"IT'S NOT OVER TILL THE FAT GUY
IN THE PLAID SHIRT
"GETS THROWN OUT BY THE USHERS."
(Squealing)
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
NOW THAT WE'VE HAD
OUR NIGHT AT THE OPERA
I WAS HOPING WE COULD HAVE
OUR DAY AT THE RACES.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): OK, HE'S HERE.
SIT DOWN.
OK, STAND UP.
(Red): ALL RIGHT.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Harold): THE PEOPLE WHO
ORGANIZE THE STRAWBERRY SOCIAL
WANT TO CHANGE
THE ORDER OF EVENTS THIS YEAR.
THEY'D LIKE TO HAVE THE DANCE
AND THEN THE STREET BRAWL.
SO, SOMETHING TO THINK ABOUT.