THE WORST THING
ABOUT APPLE TREES
IS THE APPLES.
THERE'S TOO MANY OF 'EM.
OH, SURE, I KNOW,
AN APPLE A DAY KEEPS
THE DOCTOR AWAY,
BUT 1,000 APPLES A DAY
KEEPS EVERYBODY AWAY.
SO WHAT ARE
YOU SUPPOSED TO DO
WITH ALL THE APPLES
THAT CLUTTER UP YOUR YARD?
OH, I SUPPOSE YOU COULD WING
ABOUT 500 OF 'EM AT YOUR
NEIGHBOURS' HOUSE.
BUT THAT'S PRETTY IMMATURE.
PLUS YOU END UP
WITH YOUR ARM IN A SLING.
WELL, I GOT A BETTER WAY.
THIS HERE'S A JAI ALAI BAT.
PEOPLE IN SPAIN USE THESE
TO THROW WOODEN BALLS
AT A 100 MILES AN HOUR.
DON'T EVER GET
A SPANISH GUY MAD AT YOU.
BUT INSTEAD OF WOODEN BALLS,
I HAVE GRANNY SMITHS.
[ RED CHUCKLING ]
NOW, SURE, I COULD SCOOP
THEM UP BY HAND
AND RISK MY OTHER ARM.
AM I GOING TO DO THAT?
IT'S "JAI ALAI"
[highly] UNLIKELY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
NO, NO.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
BEEN KIND OF A ROUGH WEEK
FOR THE POSSUM VAN.
I KNOW YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO CHANGE
THE OIL EVERY 3,000 MILES,
BUT I HAVE A PROBLEM WITH
THE METRIC CONVERSION.
I THOUGHT 3,000 MILES
WAS 450,000 KILOMETERS.
I GOT FRESH OIL NOW
'CAUSE IT CAME
WITH THE NEW ENGINE.
OH, UNCLE RED!
UNCLE RED!
[ APPLAUSE ]
MY $50,
WHERE'S MY $50?
WHAT?
MY $50!
THIS I.O.U.
IT EXPIRES TODAY.
IT'S YOUR I.O.U.,
SO YOU U.O.I,
50 BIG ONES.
IT'S NOT A GOOD WEEK,
HAROLD.
OKAY, TELL YOU WHAT,
GIVE ME THAT.
HERE YOU GO,
WE'RE FINE NOW.
"I.O.U. $50 BY NEXT
SATURDAY, RED."
NO!
NO, UNCLE RED,
C'MON, PLEASE.
I NEED THE MONEY.
I'M GOING ON A
DATE WITH BONNIE.
HAROLD, IF SHE CHARGES YOU,
IT'S NOT A DATE.
JUST HAND
OVER THE 50.
WHEN DO YOU
NEED THE MONEY?
ARE YOU NOT
LISTENING AT ALL?
TODAY! NOW!
I KNOW,
BUT WHEN TODAY?
WELL, OKAY, I'M GETTING
IN THE SHOWER AT 3:00,
GET OUT AT 5:00,
GOTTA DO MY HAIR.
THAT'S GONNA BE AN HOUR,
AND GET DRESSED -- 6:00.
ALL RIGHT, FINE,
BECAUSE AT 5:00,
THEY'RE DRAWING THE
WINNING LOTTERY NUMBER.
I GOT TWO TICKETS,
BUT HERE.
I'LL GIVE YOU ONE,
I'LL KEEP ONE FOR MYSELF,
AND AT 5:00, HAROLD,
THE WAY MY WEEK
IS GOING,
YOU'RE GONNA PROBABLY WIN
3 MILLION BUCKS.
YOU CAN TAKE BONNIE TO
YOUR OWN ISLAND IN FIJI.
A LOTTERY TICKET!
YOU KNOW WHAT
LOTTERY TICKETS ARE?
A TAX ON THE STUPID.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA,
THE VAGUEST NOTION AT ALL,
OF WHAT THE ODDS ARE
OF ME WINNING $3 MILLION?
HAROLD, YOU FOUND A GIRLFRIEND,
ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FOR ONE FREE NIGHT'S
ACCOMMODATION
AT POSSUM LAKE'S
HOLLYWOOD HOTEL.
CHECK OUT OUR NEWLY RENOVATED
BEVERLY HILLS COP SUITE,
FEATURING THE
EDDIE MURPHY BED.
ALL RIGHT THERE, MIKE,
COVER YOUR EARS.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET MIKE HAMAR TO
SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
UH, ALL RIGHT, MIKE,
THIS CREEPS IN THROUGH
AN OPEN WINDOW.
ME!
OKAY, NO, WE'LL GO
A DIFFERENT WAY.
LET'S SAY YOU WANNA TAKE
MONEY OUT OF SOMEBODY
ELSE'S ACCOUNT,
YOU NEED A BANK...
AND A GUN.
NO, OKAY.
IF A WRITER IS JUST
STARTING ON A SCRIPT,
HE'LL SAY,
THIS IS MY FIRST...
DRINK.
NO, OKAY, OKAY,
WHEN YOU WERE 18,
THIS WAS SOMETHING
THE AMERICAN ARMY HAD,
BUT OURS DIDN'T.
BULLETS.
UH, ALMOST
OUTTA TIME, RED.
UH, OKAY. OKAY.
OKAY, MIKE,
EVERY YOUNG ATHLETE
IS HOPING TO GET
PICKED UP IN THE...
SPORTS BAR.
NO, NO, NO,
NOT PICKED UP BY WOMEN.
OH, GAY BAR.
NO, UH --
YOU KNOW, MIKE, YOU'RE ENOUGH
TO DRIVE A MAN TO DRINK.
OH, OKAY, WELL,
I'LL HAVE A LARGE DRAUGHT.
THERE WE GO!
OKAY, FOR A WHILE NOW
WE'VE BEEN DOING
A FEATURE WITH
ED FRID
CALLED "TALKING ANIMALS."
UH, BUT,
APPARENTLY, UH --
WHY AREN'T WE
DOIN' IT ANYMORE?
UH, MEDICAL INSURANCE
COSTS WERE GETTING
PROHIBITIVE.
YEAH, RIGHT.
SO INSTEAD
WE'RE GONNA DO --
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
WILD BEAST ROUNDUP!
[ sarcastic ]
YEAH, WILD BEAST ROUNDUP.
OKAY, HERE WITH ME
IS ED FRID,
LOCAL DOG CATCHER
AND ROADKILL REMOVER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
ACTUALLY, MY OFFICIAL
TITLE IS
ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I KEEP FORGETTING THAT.
MAYBE IF EVER THERE WAS AN
ANIMAL THAT YOU ACTUALLY
CONTROLLED --
DO YOU WANT
THE JOB, RED, HUH?
DO YOU WANT THE JOB?
NO, NO, NO.
OKAY, I DIDN'T
THINK SO.
OKAY, BOYS AND GIRLS,
TODAY WE'RE GOING TO
LEARN ALL ABOUT
ANIMAL SAFETY,
BECAUSE,
AS I ALWAYS SAY,
ANIMALS CAN SMELL FEAR,
BUT THEY CAN
TASTE FINGERS.
THAT'S WHY I ALWAYS
WEAR SAFETY GLOVES.
AND RUNNING SHOES.
OKAY, BOYS AND GIRLS,
HERE IT IS...
THE KING OF THE JUNGLE,
THE SAVAGE MANEATER,
[ LAUGHTER ]
Red:
THE FURRY MITTEN.
THIS IS LEOPOLD THE LION.
UM, HI, LEOPOLD.
Ed as lion:
OH, HELLO THERE, EDWARD.
EDWARD?
OH, YEAH, LIONS ALWAYS
USE YOUR FULL NAME.
UH, LEOPOLD, THIS IS
MY FRIEND, RED.
Ed as Leopold:
OH, HELLO THERE,
REDWARD.
SO YOU FINALLY
FIGURED OUT A WAY
TO GET ON THE SHOW
WITHOUT HAVING
TO FACE A REAL ANIMAL.
Ed as Leopold:
WHAT'S HE TALKING
ABOUT, EDWARD?
Normal voice:
DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT HIM.
HERE, WHY DON'T YOU READ
THIS LETTER FROM A FAN?
HERE WE GO.
JUST GET THAT...
INTO --
LIONS CAN READ?
YEAH, THE TALKING
ONES CAN.
WHAT ARE
YOU DOING, ED?
HAVE YOU
CHANGED MEDICATION?
I JUST WANT TO TEACH
THE KIDS A BIT ABOUT
WHAT IT MEANS TO BE
AN ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER.
WELL, YOU DON'T NEED
A STUPID PUPPET
TO DO THAT.
HEY!
Red:
JUST STOP IT.
WE MIGHT HAVE
SOME KIDS OUT THERE
WHO ARE ACTUALLY INTERESTED
IN BECOMING ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICERS.
SO JUST TALK TO THEM,
STRAIGHT OUT.
DON'T!
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S FUNNY SOMETIMES HOW YOU
WANT SOMETHING UNTIL
YOU GET IT.
SOME OF YOU MARRIED GUYS
KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
AND IF YOU DON'T,
YOUR WIFE PROBABLY DOES.
LIKE MAYBE YOU THOUGHT YOU
WANTED FANCY AWNINGS
AND A CANOPY
ON YOUR HOUSE,
BUT AFTER YOU GOT 'EM
YOU NOTICED HOW THEY STOP
THE LIGHT FROM GETTING IN
AND HOW BIRDS NEST IN 'EM.
HOW MAYBE IT'S PRETENTIOUS
TO HAVE A CANOPY
ON A HOUSE THAT
HAS OUTDOOR PLUMBING.
SO NOW WHAT DO YOU DO?
YOU CAN'T LEAVE 'EM
ON THE HOUSE;
YOU CAN'T TAKE 'EM
BACK TO THE STORE.
I GUESS YOU COULD LIE DOWN
AND HAVE A GOOD CRY.
BUT I DON'T WATCH DR. PHIL.
SO INSTEAD, I'M GONNA
USE THOSE THINGS
TO CONVERT THIS
TOTALLY USELESS CAR
INTO AN OFF-ROAD READY,
HOMEMADE JEEP.
FIRST THING YOU WANNA DO,
TAKE OFF
ALL THE FENDERS.
YOU KNOW, I WAS HOPING
I MIGHT GET LUCKY
AND THE DOORS WOULD
FALL OFF AT THE SAME TIME.
I SHOULD'VE USED A PINTO.
MAN, THOSE BABIES ARE
REALLY RUSTED ON THERE.
EXCUSE ME, I'M GONNA
NEED A BIGGER WRENCH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, NEXT THING WE WANNA DO
IS RAISE THE BODY
UP A LITTLE BIT.
TO DO THAT, GONNA USE A FEW OF
THESE SCISSORS JACKS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY THEY
CALL THEM SCISSOR -- OW!
OKAY, JUST STICK THESE
THINGS BETWEEN THE AXLES
AND THE FRAME,
AND YOU CAN BE LIKE
AN OIL COMPANY...
JACK THINGS UP
AS HIGH AS YOU WANT.
DOES THIS SAY OUT
OF AFRICA TO YOU?
OR OUT OF RESOURCES,
OR JUST OUT OF
THE LOONY BIN.
BUT IT SURE DOESN'T SAY
OUT OF IMAGINATION.
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY TO
MAKE YOUR VERY OWN,
HOMEMADE JEEP.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OH, CHECK THIS OUT.
MY WINDSHIELD DOESN'T
JUST OPEN AND CLOSE,
IT LOCKS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
LOST MY CAR KEYS
LAST WEEK.
I DON'T MEAN MISPLACED;
I MEAN LOST.
LOST LOST.
LIKE YOU KNOW IN THOSE MOVIES
WHERE TEENAGERS FIND A DOOR
INTO ANOTHER DIMENSION
AND THEY THROW IN A NERDY KID,
AND HE NEVER COMES OUT?
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
THEN YESTERDAY I GO
LOOKING FOR THE TV REMOTE.
AND SHE'S GONE.
AGAIN, I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT
STUCK IN BETWEEN THE
COUCH CUSHIONS.
I MEAN VAPORIZED.
I STARTED TO WONDER
WHAT THIS WAS ABOUT.
SO I TALKED TO
OLD MAN SEDGWICK,
AND HE SAID, "BEEN THERE,
LOST THAT."
WELL, I THOUGHT
ABOUT ALL THIS STUFF,
AND EVENTUALLY
I HAD NO CHOICE
BUT TO ACCEPT A SIMPLE
YET TROUBLING TRUTH --
YOU PROBABLY ALREADY
GUESSED WHAT IT IS,
GOBLINS.
SOMETIME AFTER YOU
PASS THE AGE OF 40,
AND FOR NO GOOD REASON
OTHER THAN PURE SPITE,
GOBLINS START BREAKIN'
INTO YOUR HOUSE AND DOING STUFF
TO MAKE YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOIN' NUTS.
LIKE THE CUP OF COFFEE
ON THE COUNTER
THAT MAGICALLY
DRANK ITSELF.
OR THE CAP TO THE GAS TANK
THAT CAME OFF ON THE HIGHWAY,
EVEN THOUGH YOU
SCREWED IT ON TIGHT.
OR THE LIGHTS
THAT WENT OFF
IN SPITE OF THE FACT THAT YOU
ALMOST QUITE DEFINITELY
PAID THE ELECTRIC BILL.
THE GOOD NEWS IS
I CAME UP WITH A SOLUTION
TO TEACH THE
GOBLINS WHO'S BOSS.
THE BAD NEWS IS,
I WROTE IT DOWN
AND NOW CAN'T FIND IT.
AND I THINK WE ALL KNOW
WHO'S TO BLAME FOR THAT.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IF YOU'RE GETTING FLUSHED
BECAUSE YOUR TOILET ISN'T,
CALL ME.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, I WROTE DOWN
THE WINNING LOTTERY NUMBER,
AND I GOT MY
TICKET RIGHT HERE,
I DON'T LIKE
TO CHECK RIGHT AWAY.
I THINK IT MAKES
YOU LOOK GREEDY.
OH, UNCLE RED
YEAH. YEAH.
WOW.
I'M ALL SET FOR MY DATE.
WHERE IS MY $50?
WELL, I GAVE YOU A
LOTTERY TICKET, HAROLD.
I'LL GIVE IT BACK TO YOU.
I DON'T WANT THAT.
C'MON, JUST
GIVE ME THE $50.
JUST A MINUTE,
HAROLD, OKAY.
I'M ABOUT TO BECOME A
MULTI-MILLIONAIRE.
OH, BOY. OH, BOY!
OH, BOY... MAN!
I MISSED IT BY
ONE NUMBER!
YEAH, WELL,
THERE YOU GO.
TOO BAD YOU DIDN'T
BUY TWO TICKETS, HUH?
EXACTLY.
THAT'S MINE!
THAT'S ME!
I GOT THE TICKET!
WHOO! WHOO! WHOO!
[ APPLAUSE ]
IS THAT RIGHT,
WHAT HAROLD JUST SAID?
WHAT'D HE SAY?
imitating Harold:
I GOT THE TICKET!
YEAH. YEAH.
I GAVE HIM THE
LOTTERY TICKET
RIGHT NEXT TO MINE.
AND IT'S A WINNER.
I MEAN, HAROLD'S
A MILLIONAIRE.
THIS IS UNHEARD OF.
A MILLIONAIRE NERD
WHO DIDN'T START AN
INTERNET COMPANY.
CONGRATULATIONS,
HAROLD.
WELL, THANK YOU.
NOW, I KNOW YOU HAVEN'T
DECIDED WHAT TO DO
WITH THE MONEY,
BUT WHEN YOU DO,
YOU COME ON DOWN
TO MY STORE.
I WILL TAKE
GOOD CARE OF YOU.
WELL, THANK YOU,
DALTON.
I DON'T THINK I'LL
BE SHOPPING LOCALLY,
BUT THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW, I GAVE YOU
THAT TICKET TO COVER MY DEBT,
SO REALLY 50 BUCKS
OF IT IS YOURS,
AND THE REST
SHOULD REALLY BE...
YOU GAVE ME THAT TICKET,
AND POSSESSION IS 9/10
OF THE LAW.
WHERE IS THE TICKET?
YOU GOT IT?
YEAH, I GOT IT.
OH, I GOT IT.
I PUT IT ASIDE
BECAUSE --
OKAY, WHOEVER FINDS
THE TICKET, THOUGH,
THERE' S A REWARD.
WAIT A SECOND.
YOU JUST SAID POSSESSION
IS 9/10 OF THE LAW.
WHOEVER FINDS THE TICKET
GETS THE TICKET.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red: HAROLD ASKED US TO COME
DOWN TO THE USED OFFICE
FURNITURE PLACE
HE HAD BOUGHT A DESK AND A
CHAIR AND A BULLETIN BOARD
FOR HIS LITTLE
COMPUTER ROOM THERE.
WALTER WAS BACKIN' UP
THE POSSUM VAN
AND TO ME,
THE PERSON WHO'S WALKING
NEEDS TO WATCH
WHERE THEY'RE GOIN'.
THERE'S AN EXAMPLE
OF THAT RIGHT THERE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S
JUST A SMALL DESK,
BUT BOY, SHE HAD
SOME WEIGHT TO HER.
YOU KNOW, I WOULDN'T BE
SURPRISED IF THAT UNIT
WAS MAYBE 40 POUNDS,
YOU KNOW.
THEN I NOTICED
IT HAD THE WHEELS,
HAD THE CASTERS
ON THE BOTTOM.
WHY DON'T WE JUST --
I'LL USE THE BULLETIN
BOARD AS A RAMP,
AND THEN WE CAN JUST ROLL
HER UP RIGHT INTO THE VAN.
AND THAT MAKES
A LOT MORE SENSE.
BUT, UH -- SO WALTER
STARTED UP THERE,
BUT HE HAD THE HEAVY END.
SO HE GETS HER UP THERE,
BUT OF COURSE WHAT HAPPENS IS,
IT'S THE LAW OF THE LEVER,
THERE'S A FULCRUM EFFECT,
AND WHEN YOU GET THE
WEIGHT OVER THE EDGE THERE
SHE'S GONNA TEETER --
AND, UH, WELL, HAROLD LEARNED
SOMETHING THAT DAY,
EVENTUALLY.
SO I FIRED THE
CHAIR IN THERE,
AND WE'RE PRETTY
MUCH READY TO GO.
THANKS FOR
ALL YOUR HELP, HAROLD.
AND, UH, AWAY WE GO.
SO HAROLD CLOSES HER UP,
AND OF COURSE, BUT THE TIME
HE GETS UP TO THE FRONT,
WALTER'S LISTENING
TO HIS MUSIC.
HE'S IN THE
PASSENGER SEAT.
WE'RE A LITTLE
SHORT ON SEATING, HAROLD.
MAYBE IN THE --
JUST IN THE BACK THERE.
I'M SURE THERE'S
A CHAIR THERE SOMEWHERE.
HOW ABOUT THE CHAIR
YOU JUST BOUGHT?
THERE HE IS.
HE'S ALL SET UP.
LOOKIN' GOOD.
YOU'RE GOOD, HAROLD, EH?
OKAY, SO I PROBABLY PEELED
OUT A LITTLE FASTER THAN
I SHOULD HAVE.
THEN I SLOWED HER DOWN
PROBABLY A LITTLE FASTER.
HAROLD, THANKS FOR
DROPPING BY.
THEN I PEELED OUT AGAIN --
THIS TIME THE BACK DOOR IS --
AND OF COURSE
EVERYTHING'S ON CASTERS,
SO HE'S ROLLING ALONG THERE
AND A STOP SIGN GOES BY.
AND WALTER NOTICES
THAT HAROLD'S BACK THERE.
AND HAROLD'S
TAKING A NOTE.
WHAT'S HE SAYING?
STOP!!
OH, YEAH, I GET IT.
OKAY, I GOT YOU.
BUT THE RAMP,
THE BULLETIN BOARD COME OUT,
AND THEN I SLOWED DOWN,
AND OF COURSE HAROLD --
OKAY, THANK GOODNESS.
THEN HE REALISES THE RAMP IS
RIGHT IN FRONT OF HIM.
OF COURSE THE DESK GOES UP,
AND SO DOES HAROLD.
AND WE COME AROUND.
NOW, WHERE IS HE?
WHERE IS HE?
HE'S INSIDE
DOIN' A DONALD TRUMP.
I CAN'T BE FIRED.
I JUST QUIT.
YOU KNOW, WATCHING TV
USED TO BE EASY.
YOU JUST PLOPPED THE THING
DOWN ON ANY OLD CABINET
OR CRATE OR EMPTY TWO-FOUR
AND YOU'RE DONE.
BUT OF COURSE THESE DAYS
YOU CAN'T JUST HAVE A TV.
YOU'VE GOTTA HAVE AN
"ENTERTAINMENT CENTRE."
THAT'S BECAUSE NOW
YOU'VE GOT YOUR CABLE BOX,
YOU HOME THEATRE AMPLIFIER,
YOUR DESCRAMBLER,
YOUR DVDs, YOUR CDs,
YOUR VCRs.
NOT TO MENTION ALL
THE I.O.U.s AND C.O.D.s
THAT LEAVE YOU S.O.L.
MY WIFE WANTS ME
TO BUY ONE OF THOSE
EXPENSIVE WALL UNITS,
WITH ALL DOORS AND DRAWERS
THAT HIDE EVERYTHING AWAY.
BUT AT THIS POINT,
I'M LOOKIN' TO SAVE
A FEW BUCKS.
I CALL IT MY
REFRIGER-TAINMENT CENTRE.
IT GIVES COLD STORAGE
A WHOLE NEW MEANING.
STEP ONE: GIVE THE UNIT A NICE
WOODGRAIN MAHOGANY FINISH.
VERY NICE.
NOW, YOUR AVERAGE TV WILL FIT
NICELY INTO THE FREEZER
COMPARTMENT.
BUT HEY, THAT'S
JUST THE BEGINNING.
DOWN HERE IN
THE FRIDGE AREA,
I GOT PLENTY OF ROOM
FOR EVERYTHING.
VCR, DVD PLAYER.
AND I DON'T HAVE TO GO HUNTING
FOR MY VARIOUS REMOTES.
I KEEP 'EM ALL
IN THE DAIRY COMPARTMENT.
NOW, DOWN BELOW HERE,
WHERE I USUALLY HAVE
MY DRINKS AND SNACKS,
I HAVE MY DRINKS AND SNACKS.
HEY, IF IT
AIN'T BROKE...
OH, AND ANOTHER THING,
TO REALLY HELP
CLEAN UP THE MESS,
I PUT ALL MY MOVIES INTO
THESE CRISPER DRAWERS.
VHS ON THE LEFT,
DVD ON THE RIGHT.
BETA IN THE DEEP FREEZE.
[ sniffs ]
BOY, SOMETHING
STINKS IN HERE.
OH.
I WAS AFRAID IT WAS
DUCT TAPE FOREVER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
STILL LOOKIN' FOR HAROLD'S
WINNING LOTTERY TICKET.
NOT GOING TOO GOOD,
BUT FOUND A TV REMOTE
AND THIS PIECE OF PIZZA
FROM THE LODGE PICNIC.
NO, I THINK
THAT'S CHERRY PIE.
Harold:
I FOUND IT!
I GOT IT,
GOT IT, GOT IT!
COUPON FOR
PREPARATION H.
I'LL TAKE IT.
HAROLD, WHAT WERE YOU
DOING WHEN YOU HAD
THE TICKET LAST?
WELL, I WAS STANDING THERE
AND THINKING,
OKAY, I GOTTA GET
SOME FLOWERS FOR BONNIE.
AND I THOUGHT, WHAT KIND OF
FLOWERS WOULD SHE LIKE?
SHE LIKES FLOWERS.
I KNOW SHE LIKES FLOWERS.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S
INTERESTING THOUGH,
A LOT OF PEOPLE AREN'T
NAMED AFTER FLOWERS.
I THOUGHT
THAT TO MYSELF.
I SAID, HAROLD,
WHAT ABOUT PETE ROSE?
THAT'S TRUE, PETE ROSE
IS NAMED AFTER A FLOWER.
DAISY MAE IS.
YOU KNOW WHO ELSE IS?
FRED RHODODENDRON.
YOUR BACK POCKET!
YOUR BACK POCKET.
CHECK YOUR BACK POCKET!
OH! OH! OH!
THERE IT IS!
YOU GOT IT?
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
EIGHT.
TWO.
THREE.
FIVE.
SIX.
SEVEN.
NINE.
WHAT? NO! NO!
OH, HAROLD, YOU HAD
THE TICKET BEFORE ME,
NOT THE TICKET AFTER.
SEE, THIS IS WHY
I HATE LOTTERIES.
YOU CAN'T WIN
A LOTTERY!
BUT HAROLD, YOU HAD THE
FIRST SIX NUMBERS RIGHT.
THAT'S WORTH
50 BUCKS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
SEE, THAT WAS
REPAYING MY DEBT,
SO I GUESS WE'RE EVEN.
WELL, THAT'S NOT FAIR!
I MEAN, I DON'T MIND
LOSING $3 MILLION,
BUT REALLY NEED THAT 50.
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
I HAD THE FIRST SIX
NUMBERS RIGHT TOO.
HERE, YOU TAKE MY TICKET,
AND NOW WE'RE EVEN.
[ NO AUDIO ]
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU!
THAT'S FINE.
NO!
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
IT'S MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD,
HAROLD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
NO!
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I'M HOPING WE CAN
GO TO BED EARLY TONIGHT.
ALL DAY I'VE BEEN THIS
CLOSE TO GETTING LUCKY,
WHY STOP NOW?
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
HURRY UP AND SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN EVERYBODY.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
WELL, AS YOU MAY HAVE HEARD,
HAROLD DID NOT
WIN THE LOTTERY,
BUT ON THE PLUS SIDE,
HAROLD DID NOT WIN
THE LOTTERY.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY THAT YOUR
CHANCES OF WINNING A LOTTERY
ARE LESS THAN YOUR CHANCES OF
BEING HIT BY LIGHTNING.
HOW MANY OF YOU GUYS
BEEN HIT BY LIGHTNING?
SO THIS LODGE IS FULL
OF NOTHING BUT WINNERS.