♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: RED GREEN HERE,
IN THIS SHOW HAROLD STARTS
HIS OWN NEWS NETWORK
BILL GOES DOWNHILL SKIING.
AND I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW TO MAKE A
SUPER DUPER TOOL-A-RAMA.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: HERE'S A MAN
WHO HAS ALL THE FRIENDS
AND HE KNOWS HOW TO USE THEM.
HE'S SO DIPLOMATIC HIS
FAVOURITE COLOUR IS PLAID,
HERE'S MY UNCLE,
MR. RED GREEN!
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: BY GOLLY, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH AND THANK YOU
HAROLD FOR THAT INTRO.
THOSE WERE COMPLIMENTS
WERE THEY?
>>HAROLD: YOU GOT THAT
ONE RIGHT BIG FELLOW.
>>RED: WELL HE MEANS WELL.
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT IF
HE DID WELL OR WAS WELL.
ANYWAY WE'VE HAD A REAL
CATASTROPHE UP AT THE LODGE
WITH ONE OF THE ROCKS.
>>HAROLD: IT'S A ROCK UNCLE RED,
WHAT CAN GO WRONG WITH A ROCK?
IT'S A ROCK.
>>RED: WELL ACTUALLY IT
WASN'T SO MUCH THE ROCK,
IT WAS WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE BACKHOE AFTER
THE ROCK WAS MOVED.
>>HAROLD: OH IT
ROLLED INTO THE VAN?
>>RED: NO.
>>HAROLD: IT ROLLED
INTO A TREE?
>>RED: NO, NO, HAROLD,
THINK ABOUT A LARGE BODY
OF LUKEWARM FLUID.
>>HAROLD: IT ROLLED
INTO MOOSE THOMPSON?
>>RED: POSSUM LAKE HAROLD!
>>HAROLD: OH, OH THAT.
>>RED: IT ROLLED
INTO POSSUM LAKE.
>>HAROLD: YEAH I SHOULD OF,
THAT'S OH, THAT'S GREAT.
>>RED: BOY YOU MAKE
A LOT OF MISTAKES.
>>HAROLD: YES I DO,
BUT I DON'T BLAME THEM ON ROCKS.
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ THIS WAS MY GRANDDADDY'S FARM♪
♪ 100 YEARS AGO ♪
♪ HE WON IT IN A CARD GAME ♪
♪ EVERYONE ELSE HAD ♪
♪ THE SENSE TO FOLD ♪
♪ THE GROUND IS AS HARD ♪
♪ AS REALLY, REALLY ♪
♪ HARD MATERIAL ♪
♪ THE WATER TASTES LIKE EGGS ♪
♪ BUT LUCKILY THE ♪
♪ GOVERNMENT STEPPED IN ♪
♪ AND PAID HIM NOT ♪
♪ TO GROW STUFF ♪
♪ WHICH WAS MORE OR LESS ♪
♪ HIS SPECIALTY ♪
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER'
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW
TO BUILD SOMETHING THAT'LL
HELP YOU BUILD EVERYTHING
YOU'LL EVER BUILD,
BECAUSE THE ONE BIGGEST
DANGER THAT FACES EVERY HANDYMAN
IS NOT HITTING YOUR THUMB
WITH A HAMMER OR CUTTING OFF
YOUR FINGER AT THE KNUCKLE
OR EVEN CATCHING YOUR
NOSE HAIRS IN THE LATHE,
IT'S LOSING YOUR TOOLS.
IT JUST SEEMS THAT YOU KNOW,
YOU PUT A TOOL DOWN,
SAY A PAIR OF PLIERS YOU KNOW
OR A HAMMER AND 2 OR 3 SECONDS
LATER YOU GO AND LOOK FOR IT
AND YOU CAN'T FIND IT,
AND YOU END UP ROOTING
THROUGH EVERYTHING AND AFTER
A COUPLE OF HOURS YOU FIND
IT OUT IN THE TRUNK OF YOUR CAR
AND YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW IT
GOT THERE, THIS IS BECAUSE WHEN
YOU'RE NOT WATCHING TOOLS
THEY'LL GET UP AND THEY'LL
WALK AWAY ON YOU JUST LIKE KIDS.
SO ANYWAY I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT HAPPENED LAST WEEK
BILL DID SOME BUNGEE JUMPING OFF
THE ROOF OF THE LODGE AND
I GOT AN IDEA, ACTUALLY IT
GAVE ME 2 IDEAS,
THE FIRST ONE BEING DON'T EVER
BUNGEE JUMP BY TYING A BUNCH
OF OLD JOCK STRAPS TOGETHER,
ESPECIALLY WHEN SOMEBODY'S
GOING BY ON A LAWN TRACTOR
AND SECONDLY I GOT THE IDEA,
WHY DON'T WE MAKE A BUNGEE
BELT TO HOLD ALL OUR TOOLS.
OKAY, WELL THE FIRST THING
THAT YOU GOT TO DO IS
GATHER UP ALL YOUR TOOLS,
THESE ARE A FEW THAT I FOUND
AROUND THE BENCH AND ON
THE FLOOR, IN MY POCKETS
AND UP A CHIMNEY.
OKAY NOW YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
A BIG, WIDE BELT LIKE THE KIND
THE LUMBERJACKS USE OR THE
TELEPHONE REPAIRMEN OR ACTUALLY,
MAYBE YOU HAVE ONE OF THESE
YOURSELF IF YOU WENT TO
THE DISCO SAY 73, SATURDAY NIGHT
FEVER KIND OF A THING.
I USE THIS ONE TO HOLD THE
MUFFLER ONTO A POSSUM VAN.
OKAY NOW YOU NEED SOME STRETCHY
CORDS, ANYTHING WILL DO REALLY.
THESE ARE REAL GOOD,
THIS IS PHONE CABLE,
HARD TO COME BY THOUGH BECAUSE
THEY'VE SWITCHED TO THAT METAL,
FLEXIBLE STUFF IN THE PAYPHONES,
AND THEN OF COURSE YOU GOT
YOUR BUNGEE CORDS,
YOU GOT SOME LAMP CORD IN HERE,
THERE'S THE RUBBER HOSE
FROM THE LODGE SICK ROOM
AND WE GOT A SLINKY,
AN OLD SLINGSHOT.
STEP ONE, ATTACH ALL THIS
STUFF TO YOUR BELT
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT,
I'VE TURNED MYSELF INTO
A MORE EFFICIENT HANDYMAN
OR A HULA DANCER...
NOW ALL I GOT TO DO IS
ATTACH THE TOOLS TO THE END,
NOW I GO BACK, 2, 3, 4, 5.
♪ HUMMING HULA MUSIC ♪
OKAY NOW, SAY I HAVE TO INSTALL
A JACUZZI OR UNCLOG A DRAIN
AND ALL I NEED IS MY PIPE WRENCH
SO I JUST GRAB MY PIPE WRENCH.
ALL RIGHT I NEED TO ORGANIZE
THIS A LITTLE BIT, BUT WHAT
I NEED IS TO MARK EACH CORD
SO I KNOW WHAT'S ON IT,
SO I'LL JUST GET MY PENCIL,
MY PENCIL, MY PENCIL,
NOW THERE'S THE PIPE WRENCH.
OKAY, WELL THIS WHOLE THING
NEEDS TO BE ORGANIZED,
HANG ON, HANG ON A MINUTE.
OKAY NOW I GOT EVERYTHING
LABELLED IN ALPHABETICAL ORDER
FROM A.B.S. CEMENT RIGHT
AROUND TO ZINC SULFATE.
SO I WANT TO FIND MY
PIPE WRENCH, HERE WE ARE,
LEVEL, MALLET, NAILS,
OIL STONE, PAINTBRUSH,
PAINT SCRAPER, PIPE, HERE WE GO,
PIPE, PIPE CUTTER, PLIERS,
OH NO, NO, I LABELLED IT
UNDER WRENCH, 'W', WRENCH,
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT HERE WE ARE,
WRENCH ADJUSTABLE,
WRENCH MONKEY, WRENCH PIPE,
HERE WE ARE.
(LOUD SHATTERING OF GLASS)
>>RED: YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE
THOSE ARE REALLY SNUG DOWN
THERE AND MAYBE TO DO THAT
YOU CAN USE THE HANDYMAN
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
SO LET'S SEE, CALIPERS, CLEAVER,
DADOS, DRILL, DRILL BIT,
DUCT TAPE, YEAH THERE WE GO,
SO WE GOT THIS AND I GOT
ANOTHER IDEA, MY SCREWDRIVER
AND THE SMALLER TOOLS DON'T
FIT ON THE BELT REAL WELL,
I NEED A COUPLE OF BELTS OVER
THE SHOULDERS AND I'LL ATTACH
THAT WITH THIS STUFF.
AND THIS IS GOING TO
TAKE A LITTLE BIT OF TIME,
SO WHY DON'T WE GET ON WITH
THE SHOW AND I'LL GET HER
ALL BUILT AND WE'LL
COME RIGHT BACK.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S THAT
PART OF THE SHOW WHERE WE
EXPOSE THE 3 LITTLE WORDS THAT
MEN FIND SO DIFFICULT TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT
IS MY UNCLE RED AND OF COURSE
HIS BEST FRIEND,
MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
HERE'S TODAY'S LETTER,
'DEAR EXPERTS, LAST FALL
MY BROTHER WENT DEER HUNTING
AND GAVE ME SOME VENISON STEAKS
BUT I FORGOT TO REFRIGERATE
THEM, THIS SPRING AFTER THE
SNOW THAWED I NOTICED THE MEAT
WAS STILL SITTING ON THE BACK
PORCH RAIL WHERE I LEFT IT
LAST NOVEMBER, DO YOU THINK
THE MEAT IS STILL SAFE TO EAT?'
I DON'T THINK WE NEED AN
EXPERT TO ANSWER THIS ONE.
>>RED: WELL THAT'S
RIGHT HAROLD, THE MEAT
WILL BE JUST FINE,
ISN'T THAT RIGHT HAP?
>>HAP: YEAH, ONE WINTER
IS NOTHING, I REMEMBER WHEN
I LEAD A GROUP OF ARCHEOLOGISTS,
DIGGERS FROM THE UNIVERSITY OF
TEL AVIV ON AN EXPEDITION
TO GREENLAND AND WE CAME ACROSS
THIS DINOSAUR THAT WAS FROZEN
AND BURIED IN THE GLACIAL
TUNDRA AND I THAWED IT OUT
AND THE MEAT WAS DELICIOUS.
>>RED: SO YOU ATE
BRONTOSAURUS HAP?
>>HAP: NO NOT BRONTO,
NO THIS WAS STRATO,
STRATOCUMULUSAURUS,
HE HAD FALLEN INTO AN
ICE CREVICE AND IT WAS
PERFECTLY PRESERVED,
ALL EXCEPT THE TIP OF THE
TAIL THAT WAS A BIT RANCID.
>>RED: WOW, HE'S THE
EXPERT ON RANCID TALES...
SO TELL EVERYBODY HOW
DID THE DINOSAUR TASTE?
>>HAP: DINOSAUR IS A BIT GAMIER
THAN ANACONDA BUT NOT QUITE
AS FATTY AS SAY KILLER WHALE,
THERE'S A LOT MORE MEAT ON
THE STRATOCUMULUSAURUS,
YEAH IT WAS A BIG FELLOW.
>>HAROLD: RIGHT UP TO
THE CLOUDS I BET HUH?
>>HAP: YUP.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH.
>>HAP: YEAH I WAS GOING
TO BRING BACK ALL THE EXTRA
FLESH AND MAYBE TRY TO MARKET
MY OWN BRAND OF DINOSAUR MEAT
YOU KNOW BUT, I REGISTERED
MY OWN TRADEMARK, BRAND NAME.
>>RED: HAP'S DINO DOGS?
>>HAP: NOPE, JURASSIC PORK.
>>RED: IT IS WINTER,
THE ANIMALS ARE WARMLY
TUCKED AWAY IN THEIR DENS
WITH A CASE OF 24 AND
THE REMOTE CONTROLLER.
>>RED: OKAY THERE WE GO,
I CAN GO ANYWHERE AND FIX
ANYTHING AT ANY TIME.
I NEED A CURVED RASP PLANE,
GOT IT, COMPASS SAW, GOT IT,
SCREW-MATE DRILL BIT,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
NOW WHAT ELSE COULD I USE?
WELL IT'S ALWAYS NICE TO HAVE
A LITTLE EXTRA LIGHT ON A JOB
OR SAY A THIRD HAND WOULD
COME IN HANDY AND A LOT OF
THE GUYS AT THE LODGE SAY
THAT I COULD USE
A LITTLE HEAD PROTECTION,
WELL WHY NOT COMBINE ALL 3?
THAT'S HANDYMAN THINKING.
OKAY SO THERE IT IS,
I CAN NOW GO ANYWHERE AT
ANYTIME AND FIX ANYTHING,
ALTHOUGH I WOULDN'T ADVISE
GOING OUT INTO THE WOODS
WHEN THE MOOSE ARE IN HEAT.
NOW I HAVE ADDED ANOTHER
SAFETY ELEMENT HERE WITH
A LITTLE YOGURT TUB
FULL OF BAKING SODA.
SO IF I'M SOLDERING OR WELDING
OR WHAT HAVE YOU AND SUDDENLY
THE WHOLE WORKBENCH AND MOST
OF THE FURNITURE'S ON FIRE,
I CAN JUST LEAN FORWARD QUICKLY,
AND HOPEFULLY THE FIRE GOES OUT
FAST BECAUSE I ACTUALLY HAVE
MY FACE RIGHT INTO THE
FLAMES AT THAT POINT.
SO THIS REALLY IS
A WEARABLE WORKSHOP
KIND OF A NEAT LOOKING UNIT,
IT'S A FASHION STATEMENT
REALLY THAT SAYS,
HEY WORLD I'M A TOOL.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
I THINK I'LL JUST GO AND
CHANGE THE OIL ON THE FURNACE.
(JINGLING & CLANGING)
DON'T WORRY, I CAN FIX THAT!
>>RED: DOUGIE?
>>DOUGIE: YO.
>>RED: GETTING UP
IN THE WORLD ARE YOU?
>>DOUGIE: WELL ACTUALLY NOT
AS UP AS I MAY APPEAR TO BE RED
I'LL TELL YOU, IF YOU EVER IN
YOUR LIFE GET A CHANCE TO GRAB
OVER A TAXI, I WOULD SUGGEST
YOU REMOVE THAT LITTLE SIGN
FROM THE ROOF FIRST.
>>RED: IT COST YOU
SOME DAMAGE DID IT?
>>DOUGIE: WELL SIR,
I'LL TELL YOU, THOSE SUCKERS
ARE MADE OUT OF KRYPTONITE
OR SOMETHING, THAT RIPPED
RIGHT THROUGH MY OIL PAN
LIKE A BUMPER THROUGH
A BUS SHELTER.
>>RED: DOUGIE DO YOU THINK
THIS MONSTER TRUCK HERE
COULD PULL MY BACKHOE OUT
OF POSSUM LAKE?
>>DOUGIE: WELL NOT UNLESS
YOU SCAVENGE ME A NEW OIL PAN
IT WON'T, BESIDES YOU KNOW IF
I WERE YOU I'D RECOMMEND
THAT YOU CAN JUST LEAVE THAT
BACKHOE DOWN THERE IF
I WERE YOU.
>>RED: WELL THAT'D BE A LITTLE
HARD ON THE LAKE WOULDN'T IT?
MAKE THE WATER TASTE
LIKE BACKFILL.
>>DOUGIE: OH CONTRAIRE MON FERE
ACTUALLY IT'S QUITE GOOD
FOR THE LAKE, WELL HERE WE GO.
YEAH APPARENTLY THEM LITTLE
FISH, THEY NEED A PLACE TO GROW
IN YOU KNOW, A PLACE TO GROW UP,
THEY CALL THEM FINGERLINGS
I THINK AND YOU KNOW WITHOUT
THAT PLACE TO GROW THEM LITTLE
SUCKERS, WHOA! IF THEY DIDN'T
HAVE A PLACE TO HIDE THEY'D
STAND ABOUT AS MUCH CHANCE AS
A HONDA CIVIC IN ONE OF THEM
MONSTER TRUCK CRUSH-A-RAMAS.
>>RED: SO WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
IS THE BACKHOE SORT OF ACTS
LIKE A DAYCARE CENTRE
FOR THE LITTLE FISHES?
>>DOUGIE: OH WELL THAT'S IT,
THAT'S IT EXACTLY, I MEAN, EW!
OH JESUS, YOU HAVE TO WATCH
YOUR HEAD WITH THIS BABY.
I'LL TELL YOU, I HAD A FRIEND
OF MINE, HE ROLLED A SEMI RIGHT
OVER THE THIRD LINE BRIDGE
INTO MERCURY CREEK.
>>RED: WELL YOU KNOW I WOULD
HAVE THOUGHT THAT BRIDGE WAS
TOO NARROW FOR A BIG TRUCK.
>>DOUGIE: WELL IT IS,
BUT THAT'S WHY HE WAS UP
ON 2 WHEELS AND HE WOULD HAVE
MADE IT RIGHT ACROSS HERE TOO
IF THIS GUST OF WIND HADN'T COME
ALONG AND JUST DUMPED HIM RIGHT
OVER THERE LIKE A TURTLE ON
ITS BACK, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT,
HE LEFT THAT SUCKER THERE,
GETS A CHEQUE FROM THE
GOVERNMENT, SAID HE HAD CREATED
AN ARTIFICIAL REEF FOR
FINGERLING CONSERVATION.
IF YOU HAD HALF A BRAIN YOU
COULD CASH IN ON THAT
YOURSELF RED.
>>RED: GOLLY, IF THE GOVERNMENT
IS PAYING YOU TO THROW WRECKS
INTO THE LAKE, YOU'RE SITTING
ON A GOLDMINE HERE DOUG.
>>DOUGIE: RED, RED, RED,
I'M NOT IN THIS FOR THE MONEY
ALL THIS STUFF YOU'RE LOOKING
AT HERE, THIS IS MY JOIE DE VIVE
THIS IS MY HOBBY,
THIS IS FOR MY FRIENDS.
LISTEN, THIS AIN'T SOME
GET RICH QUICK SCHEME RED,
YOU'RE LOOKING AT MY LIFE HERE.
>>RED: I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY'S
LIFE RUST OUT QUITE
THIS BAD DOUG.
>>DOUGIE: BEAUTIFUL AIN'T IT?
AND GOD LOVE IT.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: WELL YOU CAN IMAGINE
THE EXCITEMENT AROUND HERE
WHEN THE WORD GOT OUT THAT
THE GOVERNMENT WAS PAYING
PEOPLE TO THROW CRAP IN
THE LAKE AND I'LL TELL YOU,
THEY PRETTY WELL EMPTIED
THE PARKING LOT OF
THE UGO DEALERSHIP.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED,
YOU KNOW I DON'T THINK
IT'S GOING TO WORK UNLESS
YOU ALTER THE 'PH'.
>>RED: WHAT'S THAT HAROLD,
YOU SOUND LIKE A
SHAMPOO COMMERCIAL.
>>HAROLD: NO, YOU HAVE TO
ALTER THE 'PH' YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN'T CATCH FISH IF
THE 'PH' IS TOO LOW,
SO YOU HAVE TO RAISE THE 'PH',
MAKE IT MORE ALKALINE.
>>RED: WHAT?
YOU GOT TO THROW
BATTERIES IN THERE?
THAT'S GOING TO COST
A LOT OF MONEY HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: NO, NO, LIMESTONE,
YOU HAVE TO DISSOLVE
LIMESTONE INTO THE LAKE.
>>RED: LIMESTONE?
LIMESTONE WON'T WORK,
LIMESTONE WILL KILL
ALL THE FISH.
>>HAROLD: NO IT HELPS,
IT'S LIMESTONE, REALLY THAT'S
WHAT YOU NEED, WATCH.
>>RED: WELL ALL RIGHT,
LET'S DO A LITTLE TEST HAROLD,
I'LL GET A LITTLE PIECE
OF LIMESTONE, I'LL PUT IT
IN YOUR EYE AND YOU TELL ME
IF IT HELPS OR HURTS.
>>HAROLD: I DON'T THINK THAT
THREATS ARE GOING TO SOLVE
ANYTHING HERE.
>>RED: WELL NEITHER
IS LIMESTONE.
>>HAROLD: OKAY, OKAY.
>>RED: SO WE'LL GET IN TOUCH
WITH THE RIGHT PEOPLE AND WE'LL
FIND OUT WHAT TO USE AND HOW
TO USE IT AND MORE IMPORTANTLY
HOW TO GET OUR HANDS ON THAT
GOVERNMENT MONEY OR AS WE
CALL IT, OUR CHANGE,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HAROLD?
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ WHEN IT COMES ♪
♪ TO THE MEN ♪
♪ THE MEN OF THE LODGE ♪
♪ OUR FRIENDSHIP LASTS LONGER ♪
♪ THAN THE WARRANTY ON A DODGE ♪
♪ I NEED THEM AND TRUST THEM ♪
♪ AND I'M ALWAYS ON THEIR SIDE ♪
♪ UNLESS THE SITUATION ♪
♪ INVOLVES MONEY OR ♪
♪ AN ATTRACTIVE WOMAN OR ♪
♪ PREFERABLY BOTH ♪
>>RED: KIND OF A WINTER
ADVENTURES WITH BILL TODAY,
SO I DROVE OVER THERE AND OOPS.
>>BILL: OW, OH.
>>RED: YEAH, NO, HE WAS GOING
TO DRIVE CLOSE TO THE CURB
I THOUGHT.
(HIGH PITCHED WHIRLING)
>>RED: WHAT IS THAT?
OH I THINK THERE'S ONE MORE,
LET'S SEE, ONE MORE
SKI TO COME YET.
>>BILL: AH!
>>RED: OH THERE IT IS, OKAY,
NOW BILL WANTED TO TRY SOME
DOWNHILL SKIING AND HE HAD
GOTTEN ALL THE EQUIPMENT
TOGETHER, AND ACTUALLY 2 OF
THE SKIS ARE MINE SO I PICKED
THEM UP AND HE HAD THE POLES
AND IT WAS A GOOD DAY TO
JUST GET, YOU KNOW THERE'S
SOMETHING ABOUT BILL THAT
YOU WANT TO GO HOME
AS SOON AS YOU GET THERE.
ANYWAY HE PICKED OUT A HECK
OF A HILL, THIS THING IS
PRACTICALLY STRAIGHT DOWN.
IT WAS SO STEEP I COULD
HARDLY KEEP MY PANTS UP.
BUT, WELL YOU KNOW I DON'T
ENJOY THIS PART OF SKIING,
YOU KNOW WHERE YOU GOT TO
WALK ALL THE WAY AND OF
COURSE WE DON'T HAVE THE TOW
ROPE THINGS AT POSSUM LODGE.
ANYWAY I'M UP THERE AND BILL,
HE'S PRETTY BAGGED YOU KNOW,
HE'S AN OLDER FELLOW YOU KNOW
OH, OH, OH, SO NOW I'M FEELING
ABOUT THE SAME AS HIM.
BUT HE JAMS HIS KEYS IN THERE
AND HE'S GOT THIS, APPARENTLY
THIS SKI WAX,
THIS REAL SLIPPERY STUFF
BUT IT GIVES YOU A LITTLE EXTRA,
EXTRA SPIN WHEN YOU'RE GOING SO,
OH, OH, OH THANKS BILL.
AND HE PUTS THAT ALL OVER THE
SKIS AND THEY'RE JUST, WELL
THERE YOU GO, YOU GOT THE IDEA,
SO HE PUTS MY SKIS DOWN TO SHOW
ME AND THEN WELL, BILL, BILL,
THE SKIS SEEM, YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH, GOOD BYE, OH MAN!
DOWN HE GOES,
I'M STARTING TO ENJOY THIS NOW.
OH NOT QUITE SO MUCH BUT
I ENJOYED THAT, SO I WALK
ALL THE WAY DOWN TO SEE
WHAT THE HECK'S GOING ON
BECAUSE THOSE ARE MY SKIS DOWN
THERE AND SO FAR I'M ENJOYING
MYSELF REAL WELL.
NOW BILL'S OKAY AND THAT'S
GOOD NEWS I GUESS.
MY SKIS DIDN'T FARE
QUITE SO WELL...
WHAT DO WE DO NOW BILL?
AND HE GOES BACK SKIING,
I'M FINISHED FOR THE DAY.
SO UP HE GOES AND BOREDOM
IS SITTING IN PRETTY DEEP FOR
ME NOW AND HE STICKS THE POLES
IN THERE, HE'S KIND OF FROZEN,
I THINK HE MELTED A BIT INTO
THE SNOW BUT THEN.
OH HE'S GOT NO POLES,
NO POLES, OH, OH, OH, OH,
THE HECK WITH THIS,
I'VE HAD ENOUGH!
SKIING WITH BILL IS
A TOTAL DRAG.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: AND NOW HERE'S SOMETHING
FOR YOU YOUNG PEOPLE BECAUSE
YOU'RE YOUNG AND YOU'RE STRONG
AND YOU'LL EVENTUALLY
RECOVER FROM THIS.
>>HAROLD: FOR THE FIRST TIME
ANYWHERE, HERE IS THE HAROLD
NEWS NETWORK WITH HAROLD GREEN
BRINGING YOU ALL THE NEWS
THAT WILL BE OF INTEREST
TO TEENAGERS.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT,
I'M HAROLD GREEN AND HERE'S
OUR TOPS STORIES FOR TONIGHT,
THE OLDER GENERATION CONTINUES
TO RULE THE WORLD AND DESTROY
THE EARTH'S ECOSYSTEM.
OLD PEOPLE STARTED 3 MORE
WORLD WARS THAT WE YOUNG PEOPLE
ARE GOING TO HAVE TO GO FIGHT IN
ON THE ECONOMIC FRONT,
OLD PEOPLE HOLD ALL THE JOBS
THAT WE YOUNG PEOPLE COULD
PROBABLY DO WAY MORE BETTER
IF WE WERE GIVEN LIKE HALF
A CHANCE MAYBE EVEN HUH?
NEW SCIENTIST EVIDENCE
HAVE JUST SHOWN THAT PEOPLE
OVER THE AGE OF 20 LOSE SOME
10,000 BRAIN CELLS A DAY.
SCIENTISTS BELIEVE THAT THIS
CAN ACCOUNT FOR THE WORLD
PROBLEMS FROM GLOBAL WARMING
TO CAFETERIA FOOD.
SPUNKY, OH, THIS JUST HANDED
INTO ME, THIS LATE BREAKING
NEWS, POLICE MAY SOON BE
INVESTIGATING THE MYSTERIOUS
DISAPPEARANCE OF A 17 YEAR
OLD BOY NAMED HAROLD.
AND THAT'S ALL THE NEWS THERE IS
FROM THE HAROLD NEWS NETWORK,
I'M HAROLD GREEN SAYING
GOODNIGHT AND GOOD BYE.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: NOW I KNOW A LOT OF
YOU TEENAGERS DON'T LIKE TO
HEAR ADVICE BUT COMMUNICATION
IS AN IMPORTANT PART OF LIFE
AND BESIDES WHO CARES
WHAT YOU THINK...
THERE'S A LOT OF STUFF
THAT YOU DON'T KNOW,
AND I'M GUESSING THAT THERE'S
ONE MAYBE EVEN 2 EXPERTS RIGHT
THERE IN YOUR OWN HOME,
THIS OF COURSE IS YOUR PARENTS.
SO IF YOU'RE WONDERING WHAT'S
IT LIKE TO BE REALLY, REALLY
INTOXICATED OR SAY CAUGHT
NAKED IN A PUBLIC PLACE,
WHY NOT ASK THE PEOPLE WHO'VE
BEEN THERE, MOM AND DAD,
ESPECIALLY MOM...
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: BOB WITH THESE
FISHING AND SO ON IS THERE SOME
KIND OF A CHEMICAL THAT WE CAN
ADD TO THE LAKE THAT'LL HELP
WITH THE ACIDITY AND SO ON?
>>BOB: LIMESTONE.
>>RED: LIMESTONE?
NO I KNEW THAT, WHAT I WANTED
TO KNOW WAS, WAS THERE SOME
OTHER CHEMICAL THAT WOULD WORK?
>>BOB: NO.
>>RED: OH, ALL RIGHT.
IS THERE ANOTHER NAME FOR
LIMESTONE THAT SAY SOMEBODY
LIKE HAROLD OR SOMEBODY
WOULDN'T KNOW?
>>BOB: CALCIUM CARBONATE.
>>RED: CALCIUM CARBONATE.
>>BOB: YES.
>>RED: GREAT.
>>BOB: CALCIUM CARBONATE.
>>RED: WELL ALL RIGHT,
THANKS BOB.
>>BOB: GOOD.
>>RED: I'LL GET BACK NOW AND
GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR LAND
SLOPE TEST THING.
>>BOB: ALL RIGHT, THANKS.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED
IS THAT YOU?
WHAT, I JUST SAID IS THAT YOU.
>>RED: NO I THOUGHT YOU
SAID STATUE.
ANYWAY THIS LIMESTONE MESS
TURNED OUT TO BE A
REAL DISASTER.
>>HAROLD: PARDON ME,
DID YOU SAY LIMESTONE?
>>RED: NO I MEANT
CALCIUM CARBONATE.
>>HAROLD: WHAT?
>>RED: CALCIUM CARBONATE
HAROLD, I ASKED AN EXPERT AND
I ASKED HIM ABOUT THE
LIMESTONE AND HE SAID USE
CALCIUM CARBONATE.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED,
CALCIUM CARBONATE IS LIMESTONE.
>>RED: DON'T PUSH IT HAROLD
ALL RIGHT, SO WE SOCKED 4 TONS
OF LIMESTONE INTO THE LAKE
WHICH COST US $280 BUCKS AND
THEN WE GOT A CHEQUE FROM
THE GOVERNMENT FOR $102
SO IT'S JUST LIKE INCOME TAX
TIME AGAIN AS FAR AS
I'M CONCERNED.
>>HAROLD: ALL RIGHT,
WELL THINK OF IT THIS WAY
YOU DID SOMETHING GOOD FOR
THE FISH AND WHO KNOWS,
MAYBE YOU'LL RETRIEVE
THE BACKHOE.
>>RED: OH NO, NO, WHEN THE LIME,
WHEN THE CALCIUM CARBONATE
HIT THE BACKHOE IT JUST
KIND OF DISINTEGRATED INTO
A CLOUD OF RUST,
KIND OF A LOW RUMBLE,
BAD SMELL AND THEN THE TIRES
POPPED TO THE SURFACE.
>>HAROLD: WELL THERE YOU GO,
THE TIRES, THE TIRES ARE
PROBABLY WORTH SOMETHING.
>>RED: THEY POPPED THROUGH
THE BOATHOUSE
THEN THEY JUST POPPED,
THEN THEY SANK TAKING
MY NEW CANOE WITH THEM.
>>HAROLD: WELL HEY,
YOU TRIED YOUR BEST YOUNG
FELLOW, DON'T BLAME YOURSELF.
>>RED: WELL I DON'T HAROLD,
I BLAME YOU.
>>HAROLD: WHY, WHAT DID I DO?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
>>RED: WELL YOU'RE THE GUY
THAT WAS USING THE ROCK
AS THE EMERGENCY BRAKE
FOR THE BACKHOE WEREN'T YOU?
>>HAROLD: I DIDN'T DO THAT,
AND ANYWAY LET'S JUST REMEMBER
WHO USED THE BACKHOE LAST.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT,
WELL I'LL BLAME THE ROCKS
WHAT I WANTED TO DO IN
THE FIRST PLACE ANYWAY.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH, OKAY, WELL,
ALL RIGHT FORGET THAT UNCLE RED
BECAUSE IT'S MEETING TIME,
THAT'S THE POSSUM SQUEAL.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT HAROLD YOU
GO AHEAD, I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
WELL THAT'S ABOUT IT FOR
THIS SHOW AND IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING, I'LL BE COMING
STRAIGHT HOME AFTER THE MEETING
UNLESS IT RAINS AND I HARDEN.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
ROCK HEAD AND THE WHOLE
BUNCH OF US HERE UP AT
THE POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORITATI.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca