IF YOU DO AN ANTHROPOLOGICAL
STUDY OF CIVILIZATIONS
THROUGH HISTORY,
YOU WILL FIND
THAT MEN HISTORICALLY
HAVE FIVE BASIC NEEDS:
FOOD, SHELTER, CLOTHING,
SEX AND ALCOHOLIC
BEVERAGES,
AND SOMETIMES THOSE
LAST TWO ARE REVERSED.
ALCOHOL IS VERY CEREMONIAL,
FOR TOASTING
AT DINNER PARTIES,
FOR COMMUNION AT CHURCH,
THEY EVEN DRINK BOOZE
AT TREATY SIGNINGS.
AND WHEN YOU SEE THE KIND
OF MESS THE WORLD IS IN,
IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS
THAT ALCOHOL WAS INVOLVED
SOMEWHERE IN
THE NEGOTIATIONS.
IT JUST SEEMS THAT
WHENEVER YOU GET
MEN TOGETHER,
YOU GET FERMENTATION.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT MAKES US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red Green:
ON TODAY'S SHOW,
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO BREW
YOUR OWN BEER,
AND WE GOT DOUGIE FRANKLIN
DRIVING HIS MONSTER
TRUCK AROUND,
WE GET UP CLOSE AND PERSONAL
WITH DALTON HUMPHREY
AND BILL IS GOING
TO TAKE A LOOK AT LACROSSE,
WHICH IS CANADA'S
NATIONAL SPORT,
WHICH I'M NOT.
AND HERE HE IS,
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE,
RED GREEN!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
AND NOW HERE IS
YOUR ANTI-HERO,
MR. ANTI-EVERYTHING,
WITH THE EXCEPTION
OF ANTE UP,
MY NEPHEW, HAROLD.
DON'T BE JEALOUS.
I'M AN ELECTRIC MAGICIAN.
GOOD.
SAW THAT THING
IN HALF, WILL YOU?
BIT OF A SETBACK
THIS WEEK,
THE BEER STORE CALLED
UP AND SAID
THAT IF WE WOULD
PAY OUR TAB,
THEY COULD RE-PAVE
THE PARKING LOT
AND BUY A NEW
FLEET OF TRUCKS.
AND WE KIND OF TWIGGED
ON TO THE IDEA
THAT PERHAPS WE'RE
SPENDING A LITTLE
TOO MUCH MONEY ON BEER.
YEAH, I AGREE.
I THINK EVERYONE
SHOULD JUST CUT BACK
ON THEIR CONSUMPTION
AROUND HERE.
CUT BACK?
OH, NO, NO, WE'RE
GOING TO BREW OUR
OWN BEER, HAROLD.
ALL WE NEED
IS PURE WATER,
BREWER'S YEAST,
HOPS, BARLEY, SUGAR,
AND CONTAINERS
TO PUT THE BEER IN.
WE GOT EVERYTHING
BUT THE PURE WATER.
WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
START BY BREWING
SMALL AMOUNTS.
THAT WOULD LIMIT
THE SIZE OF THE
POTENTIAL EXPLOSION.
WELL, HAROLD, THAT'S
JUST NOT THE WAY
WE DO THINGS AROUND
HERE, ALL RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, THE
ANCIENT ROMANS
BREWED BEER, HAROLD.
IN FACT, EVERY GREAT
WESTERN CIVILIZATION
BREWED BEER.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
YES I DID.
AND DID YOU KNOW
THAT AT SOME POINT
EVERY GREAT
CIVILIZATION COLLAPSED?
CONNECTION PERHAPS?
HAROLD, IF IT'S GOOD
ENOUGH FOR JULIUS CAESAR,
IT'S GOOD ENOUGH
FOR POSSUM LODGE.
BENE VIDE VOMITY.
I CAME, I SAW,
I RALPHED.
YOU'RE WATCHING
THE RED GREEN SHOW
AND NOBODY CAN STOP YOU.
OH, WE'RE OUT HERE
SQUASHING BEER CANS
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
THEY BLOW UP
LIKE TOMATOES
IF THE VAN JUST
HITS THEM RIGHT
YEAH, WE LOVE TO
SQUASH THOSE BEER CANS
DRIVE THEM
INTO THE GROUND
WE JUST SQUASHED
A CAN OF PERRIER
WE'RE OBVIOUSLY GETTING
TOO CLOSE TO TOWN.
TODAY ON MEET
YOUR MEMBER,
WE GOT THE OWNER OF
HUMPHREY'S EVERYTHING STORE,
DALTON HUMPHREY.
DALTON IS ACTUALLY
THE ONLY GUY AT
THE LODGE
WHO HAS A STEADY INCOME.
WELL, YOU KNOW, IT'S
NOT WHAT YOU MAKE,
IT'S WHAT YOU
SPEND THERE, RED.
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU
PAY, IT'S WHAT YOU BUY.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
MAYBE WE'LL JUST GET
AWAY FROM THAT STUFF
AND YOU CAN TELL US
A BIT ABOUT,
SAY, YOUR FAMILY
LIFE, YOUR BACKGROUND,
GROWING UP,
THAT KIND OF THING.
WELL, YEAH, I GREW
UP DIRT POOR.
YEAH, FIVE KIDS IN
A ONE ROOM SHACK.
AND NONE OF US HAD
A STITCH OF CLOTHING,
'CAUSE DRAPES
WERE CHEAPER.
SURE.
AND WELL THE
ELDEST FINALLY
GOT SOME CLOTHES
AND OF COURSE I
WAS THE YOUNGEST
SO ALL I GOT
WAS HAND-ME-DOWNS
AND I HATED THAT.
I HATED IT.
WELL, I HAD HAND-ME-DOWNS,
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
ALL I HAD WAS SISTERS.
MAKE IT TOUGH GETTING
A DATE I WOULD THINK.
SURE TAUGHT ME THE
VALUE OF A DOLLAR,
I'LL SAY THAT.
AND THEN OF COURSE
I LEARNED HOW TO SEW.
AND I MARRIED THE GIRL
WHO TAUGHT ME HOW TO SEW.
OH, YES.
YEAH.
OF COURSE THERE
WAS A NICER GIRL
WHO LIVED ACROSS TOWN
AND I LIKED HER A
LOT BETTER,
BUT, WELL, NOT ENOUGH
TO JUSTIFY THE BUS FARE.
NOW, YOUR DAUGHTER,
TELL US HOW
SHE FITS INTO
THE PICTURE HERE.
YOU HAVEN'T
MENTIONED HER YET.
WELL, SHE'S FINE.
OKAY.
SHE'S GROWN UP NOW.
OH, SHE SPENDS
MORE ON A DRESS THAN
I SPEND ON A CAR NOW.
$40 ON A DRESS.
SO SHE HAS MONEY THEN.
SHE HAS MY MONEY.
WELCOME TO HANDYMAN CORNER.
THIS WEEK WITH THE
BREW YOUR OWN BEER
PROJECT GOING ON,
I THOUGHT I'D SHOW
YOU HOW TO MAKE A
GREAT ADDITION
TO ANY BAR, WHETHER
THAT BAR BE IN YOUR
FAMILY ROOM,
YOUR OFFICE OR
YOUR GOLF CART.
YOU KNOW, TWO THINGS
THAT YOU NEED AT A BAR
IS ICE AND WATER.
WATER FOR MIXING DRINKS
AND ICE TO DROP INTO
PEOPLE'S SHORTS
OR INTO THEIR HATS,
DEPENDING ON WHERE
THEIR HANGOVER IS.
NOW, YOU CAN BUY ONE
OF THEM FANCY FRIDGES,
GOT THE ICE AND WATER
DISPENSER BUILT RIGHT IN,
BUT THOSE BABIES
ARE UP TO 200 BUCKS,
PLUS THEY MAY
NOT FIT INTO THE SAME
SPACE THAT YOU ALREADY GOT.
AND FOR ME I HAVE TO
CLEAN OUT MY FRIDGE
AND TAKE OFF ALL
MY MESSAGES,
THE PHONE NUMBERS,
THE MORTGAGE TO MY HOUSE,
MY WILL.
SO INSTEAD OF THAT,
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW YOU CAN TURN
THE FRIDGE YOU GOT NOW
INTO AN ICE AND WATER
DISPENSER MACHINE.
ALL RIGHT, FIRST THING
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
FOR ICE WATER
IS SOMETHING
FOR THE COLD
WATER TO FLOW THROUGH.
I'M THINKING GARDEN HOSE.
WHAT'S COLD ABOUT A
GARDEN HOSE YOU'RE SAYING
AS REACH FOR THE
CHANNEL CHANGER?
WELL NOTHING, UNTIL
YOU RUN IT THROUGH
THE FREEZER.
ALL RIGHT.
STEP ONE, DRILL A THREE
QUARTER INCH HOLE RIGHT
IN THE FREEZER
FOR THE HOSE
TO GO THROUGH.
PERFECT.
ALL RIGHT.
I DID THE SAME THING
IN THE BACK END THERE,
SO WE GOT THE GARDEN HOSE
GOING RIGHT THROUGH
THE FREEZER.
NOW, YOU'RE GOING
TO WANT TO CONTROL
THE FLOW
AND DIRECTION
OF YOUR ICE WATER,
SO I WOULD SAY PUT A
NOZZLE ON THERE LIKE THAT
OR IF YOU'RE
A REAL FUN GUY,
YOU CAN THROW A
SPRINKLER ON THERE,
YOU KNOW IF YOUR PARTY
GUESTS ARE GETTING
OUT OF HAND,
LIKE MAYBE THEY WANT
TO PLAY CHARADES
OR SOMETHING.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S
GIVE HER A TRY.
THAT'S ODD.
OH MY GOSH.
ALL RIGHT,
THERE'S THE PROBLEM,
SHE'S FROZEN
UP SOLID THERE.
SO WHAT WE GOT TO DO
IS WE GOT TO PUT
SOME INSULATION
I GUESS AROUND THAT
HOSE TO STOP IT FROM
FREEZING INSIDE THERE.
YOU COULD USE
STYROFOAM OR FIBERGLASS,
BUT I'M THINKING
WORK SOCKS.
ALL RIGHT.
LUCKILY I HAD
HOLES IN THE TOES
SO THEY JUST THREAD
RIGHT ON THERE.
NOW TO MAKE THE
ICE MAKER PART OF OUR
REFRIGERATOR RENOVATION,
YOU'RE GOING TO
NEED AN ICE CUBE TRAY
AND A CUPBOARD
DOOR HANDLE.
SO WHILE YOU GO
AND GET THOSE,
LET'S GET BACK TO
THE SHOW FOR A
FEW MINUTES.
MAN MY FEET ARE FREEZING.
Red Green:
COMING UP, WE GOT
RANGER GORD COMING DOWN
AND HAROLD IS
GOING TO TEACH ME
THE POLITICALLY CORRECT
WAY TO INVITE PEOPLE OVER.
LIKE THAT'S IMPORTANT.
TINY SHOOTS,
BY ME.
TINY SHOOTS COME
OUT OF THE GROUND.
CROCUS AND TULIPS
AND DAFFODILS RISE
TO A HEIGHT OF
TWO AND A HALF INCHES
AND ARE FROZEN IN TIME,
NOT BY A LATE FROST,
BUT BY AN
EARLY LAWN MOWER.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT WE DID WRONG
BUT OUR FIRST BATCH
OF HOMEMADE BEER
DID NOT TASTE
ALL THAT GREAT.
WELL, UNCLE RED,
DID YOU LIKE BOIL
AND STERILIZE
ALL THE BEER VATS
AND BEER BOTTLES?
HOW DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, YOU GOT TO
BOIL EVERYTHING
AND MAKE SURE ALL
THE GERMS HAVE
BEEN REMOVED.
WE WIPED THEM
ON OUR SHIRTS,
OUR SHIRTS ARE CLEAN.
I MEAN, YOU GOT TO MAKE
SURE THE CANISTER ARE
PERFECTLY STERILE.
HAROLD, THE ONLY
THING PERFECTLY STERILE
UP HERE IS OLD MAN SEDGWICK.
BESIDES, HOW CAN
YOU BOIL A HOT TUB?
OKAY, BUT YOU
KNOW WHAT HAPPENS
IF YOU GET ANY ONE
OF THOSE UNWANTED, NASTY,
LITTLE GERMS AND BACTERIA.
YEAH, THEY END UP
PRODUCING YOUR SHOW.
VERY SELDOM THAT
PEOPLE LIKE US
GET A CHANCE TO
DO A TELEVISION SHOW
AND WELL THANK YOU.
RANGER GORD?
WELL, WE'RE UP
HERE AT FIRE TOWER 13
BUT RANGER GORD IS
OBVIOUSLY NOT AROUND,
SO LET'S GO HAROLD.
RED!
RED, HI.
I THOUGHT I MISSED YOU.
OH, YEAH, WAIT.
HI, HAROLD.
TO ALL YOU YOUNG
PEOPLE OUT THERE,
LISTEN UP,
I'M GOING TO BE STARTING
A NATURE CLUB UP HERE
FOR ALL THE YOUNG
PEOPLE OF POSSUM LAKE.
IT'S GOING TO BE
CALLED THE POSSUM PACK.
SO EVERY WEEK YOU GUYS
ARE GOING TO COME UP HERE,
WE'RE GOING TO BE
LEARNING ABOUT NATURE
AND WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE SNACKS AND
JUICE, HUH?
AND I'M GOING TO TEACH
YOU ABOUT THE GREAT OUTDOORS
AND YOU'RE GOING TO
BE ABLE TO EARN BADGES
FOR PASSING CERTAIN TESTS.
I THINK THAT'S
A GREAT IDEA, GORD.
ANY TIME YOU CAN PASS
YOUR KID OFF ON
ANOTHER ADULT,
I SAY GO FOR IT.
BUT ACTUALLY, GORD,
I WANTED TO ASK YOU
SOME QUESTIONS HERE.
WHAT KIND OF A DEGREE
IS IT THAT YOU HAVE?
GENERAL ARTS.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WE'RE MAKING
OUR OWN BEER
AND WE NEED TO FIND
A SOURCE OF PURE
SPRING WATER.
SURE.
FINDING WATER,
THERE'S SOMETHING
THAT THE POSSUM PACK
COULD EARN
A BADGE FOR.
OH, YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE LOTS OF
BADGES, ARE YOU?
OH, YEAH.
THERE'S A
SOLITAIRE BADGE
IF YOU LEARN HOW
TO PLAY 5 DIFFERENT
GAMES OF SOLITAIRE.
THERE'S A BADGE FOR
TAKING A LONG HIKE ON
YOUR OWN AND REFLECTING.
THERE'S A BADGE
FOR COOKING FOR ONE.
SHADOW PUPPETS.
HUH?
AND THERE'S ONE FOR
LEARNING HOW TO HAVE
A MEANINGFUL
CONVERSATION
WITH YOUR ECHO.
WHAT ABOUT
FIRES, GORD?
THAT WOULD BE
A GOOD BADGE THERE
BECAUSE FIRES
IS GOING TO BE
A BIG PART OF THEIR
LIVES UP HERE AT
POSSUM LAKE.
GREAT IDEA.
YEAH.
YOU COULD
HAVE PUTTING
OUT FIRES IN CARS.
GOOD.
PUTTING OUT
FIRES IN BOATS.
RIGHT.
PUTTING OUT
FIRES ON RIVERS.
RIGHT.
ON RIVERS?
REMEMBER LAST YEAR,
STINKY PETERSON'S
LEAKY BOAT TANK,
GASOLINE ALL
OVER THE RIVER,
WALL OF FLAME A
HUNDRED FEET HIGH,
TWO MILES LONG.
YOU MUST HAVE SEEN THAT.
NO.
OH.
NO, I MISSED IT.
OF COURSE IT WASN'T
TECHNICALLY A FOREST FIRE.
IT WILL COME TO NO
SURPRISE TO MOST OF US
THAT MANY MEN IN THE
90S DO NOT KNOW HOW
TO COMMUNICATE.
OH, UNCLE RED,
OKAY, PLEASE COME IN.
WE'RE JUST ABOUT
TO DEMONSTRATE
THE CORRECT WAY TO
GRACIOUSLY INVITE
SOMEONE OVER
TO YOUR HOUSE
FOR DINNER.
WELL, HAROLD, WHEN A GUY
WANTS TO INVITE SOMEBODY
OVER GRACIOUSLY,
HE GETS HIS
WIFE TO DO IT.
YES, BUT WE'RE
GOING TO CHANGE
ALL THAT.
UNCLE RED, WOULD
YOU CALL ME
AND INVITE
ME OVER TO YOUR
HOUSE SATURDAY NIGHT?
NO.
WHY NOT?
WELL YOU MIGHT COME.
OKAY.
WE'RE PRETENDING.
WELL, AREN'T
YOU GOING TO
ANSWER IT?
I NEVER
ANSWER THE PHONE
ON THE FIRST RING.
OKAY, NOW I'M
GETTING UP AND
I'M WALKING ACROSS.
HELLO.
HAROLD, YOU
DOING ANYTHING
SATURDAY NIGHT?
SATURDAY NIGHT,
I DON'T THINK SO.
FINE.
COME ON OVER
FOR DINNER AROUND 7.
EXCELLENT.
CAN I BRING SOMETHING --
BYE.
AND REMEMBER WE'RE
JUST PRETENDING.
GOOD.
VERY GOOD.
THAT'S WHAT
WE'LL CALL THE
COMPLETELY WRONG WAY.
HE DIDN'T EVEN
SAY WHO WAS CALLING.
HE COULD SEE I
WAS TALKING TO HIM.
YOU STILL
HAVE TO TELL A
PERSON WHO'S CALLING.
AND HE DIDN'T SAY,
YOU KNOW, IS IT A
SPECIAL OCCASION.
IS IT A PARTY?
IS IT AN ANNIVERSARY?
IT'S SATURDAY NIGHT,
THE GAME WILL BE ON TV.
YOU DIDN'T MENTION
THAT TO ME.
THE GAME IS ALWAYS
ON TV SATURDAY NIGHT.
OKAY.
WELL HE DIDN'T SAY
IF I HAD TO BRING ANYTHING
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
DESSERT OR A GIFT
OR WHO'S GOING TO BE
THERE, CASUAL, FORMAL.
NOW I WILL DEMONSTRATE
THE CORRECT PROCEDURE
FOR PHONING SOMEONE.
[ DIALING PHONE ]
YEAH?
HELLO, UNCLE RED, IT
IS I YOUR NEPHEW,
HAROLD GREEN.
WHO GAVE YOU MY NUMBER?
VERY GOOD, THANK YOU.
AND HOW ARE YOU TODAY?
BUSY.
OH, ISN'T THAT
JUST WONDERFUL.
YES, IT IS A LOVELY
DAY, ISN'T IT?
NOT REALLY, NO.
THE REASON I'M
CALLING, UNCLE RED,
IS TO INVITE YOU
OVER TO DINNER.
WHEN?
WELL, I THOUGHT
I WOULD JUST HAVE
SOME MUTUAL FRIENDS.
WHEN?
NOTHING FANCY,
OF COURSE,
YOU KNOW JUST
LIKE SOME POT LUCK
DINNER KIND OF THING.
WHEN?
AND WE'LL ALL SIT
AROUND AND WE'LL WATCH,
YOU KNOW, SLIDES OF
MY BUS TRIP TO BRANTFORD.
WHEN?
WELL, HOW ABOUT
SATURDAY NIGHT?
OH, NO, CAN'T DO IT.
I JUST INVITED SOMEBODY
OVER FOR DINNER
SATURDAY NIGHT.
BYE.
Red Green:
TIME FOR
ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
ALL WE HAVE TO
DO IS FIND HIM.
BILL?
THERE HE IS.
A LOT OF TIMES WHEN
PEOPLE HAVE PADDING ON,
THEY DO STUFF THEY
WOULDN'T ORDINARILY DO.
AT LEAST I
HOPE HE WOULDN'T
ORDINARILY DO THAT.
YOU GUESSED ALREADY
THAT BILL IS GOING
TO DO A LITTLE BIT
OF LACROSSE HERE
FOR US TODAY.
HE GAVE ME THE
ONE BAT THERE.
HE WANTS ME TO --
YEAH, I UNDERSTAND, BILL,
YOU WANTS ME
TO STAND THERE.
HE'S GOING TO GO
AND PROBABLY PICK UP
A COUPLE OF LACROSSE BALLS
AND TRY TO THROW ONE AT ME,
BECAUSE APPARENTLY,
YOU KNOW, THERE'S SOME
TRICK TO CATCHING A
LACROSSE BALL
WITH THESE THINGS AND
HE WANTS TO I GUESS
MAKE ME LOOK STUPID.
AND WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
DID I MISS THAT?
WHERE DID IT GO?
I DIDN'T SEE THAT --
I DIDN'T EVEN SEE IT.
I DIDN'T EVEN SEE IT, BILL.
WELL, THAT'S
WHY I DIDN'T SEE
IT, IT'S RIGHT THERE.
THERE'S A TRICK
TO THROWING THE
BALL WITH THOSE THINGS.
NO.
THERE YOU GO.
NICE TOSS.
PUT HER IN THERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH PADDING ON THERE?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT.
OH, OH, OH.
OH, LOOK, THERE'S HAROLD.
HE MUST BE TIRED.
BILL'S NOT ALL THAT
CONCERNED WITH HAROLD.
YOU CAN'T BE
CONCERNED WITH PEOPLE
AND HAVE BILL'S
BEHAVIOUR PATTERNS.
THAT'S A BOY, BILL,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT HIM.
SO BILL IS GOING
TO TRY ANOTHER ONE.
TOSS HER IN HERE,
BILL, TOSS HER.
WAY HIGH.
OH.
BOY, WHEN I THINK
OF THE NUMBER OF TIMES
BILL HAS EITHER KNOCKED
MY MIRROR OFF
OR BROKEN MY WINDOW
OR PUT A DENT IN
THE SIDE OF THE VAN
OR STUCK A
KNIFE INTO A TIRE
OR BLOWN THE
WHOLE THING UP,
I CAN'T MANAGE
BEING SO STUPID -- OH.
MAYBE I SHOULDN'T
BE THINKING ABOUT
THAT RIGHT NOW.
OH, I'M FINE, BILL.
NEVER FELT
BETTER IN MY LIFE.
THANKS FOR ASKING.
NO I'M FINE.
DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT IT.
NO, NO, DON'T YOU
WORRY ABOUT IT.
YEAH.
I AM FINE.
TOLD YOU I WAS FINE.
ALL RIGHT.
TO MAKE IT SAFER NOW
I'M GOING TO KNOCK
A FEW BALLS DOWN.
BILL SAID TO
ME JUST KEEP
GRABBING THE BALLS
AND HITTING
THEM AT ME.
OKAY.
JUST THEM COMING.
THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
HE SAID KEEP THEM COMING.
NOW HE CAUGHT ONE.
HE GOT ALL EXCITED.
HE HAD SAID
KEEP THEM COMING.
THIS WAY WE'RE
A LITTLE SAFER.
BILL IS GOING TO
THROW THEM AT ME
AND I'M GOING
TO BAT THEM.
AND NOW NOBODY
IS IN DANGER.
WELL ALMOST NOBODY.
OH BOY.
STRIKE ONE.
STRIKE TWO.
OH BOY.
BALL.
STRIKE THREE.
HE'S OUT.
Red Green:
COMING UP WE
GOT DOUGIE FRANKLIN
WITH A PERSONAL QUESTION
AND BUZZ SHERWOOD
SAYS THE ANSWER IS
BLOWING IN THE WIND.
WELL, OUR SECOND
BATCH OF BEER
DIDN'T REALLY WORK OUT
ANY BETTER THAN THE FIRST.
I CAN'T UNDERSTAND HOW
THE ROMANS CAN BREW
BEER AND WE CAN'T.
MAYBE WE SHOULD
HAVE A TOGA PARTY.
DID YOU ADD
ENOUGH SUGAR?
I MEAN, DID YOU
LET THE BEER BREW AND
FERMENT FOR TWO WEEKS?
TWO WEEKS?
WHO HAS THAT
KIND OF TIME?
UNCLE RED, YOU
GOT TO DO IT.
WELL, DON'T
THEY HAVE LIKE
A MINUTE BEER?
I'M SORRY, YOU CANNOT
MAKE A FINE QUALITY LAGER
WITH LIKE, YOU KNOW,
KOOL-AID TECHNOLOGY.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL TRY IT AGAIN.
ACTUALLY, THIS TIME
WE HAVE A REAL PROPER VAT
TO BREW THE BEER IN.
A REAL BEER VAT?
ONE WHERE YOU CAN
LET THE BEER BREW
AND FERMENT
FOR TWO WEEKS?
OKAY, NOT A REAL
PROPER VAT, NO,
BUT THERE'S A STARCH
FACTORY UP ON BACK
BEND ROAD.
THEY GOT A WATER
TOWER THERE
FULL TO THE BRIM
WITH PURE RAIN WATER,
WE CAN MIX THE
BEER IN THERE.
AND TO HEAT IT UP?
WELL, THIS IS THE BEAUTY.
THE STARCH PLANT
HAS BEEN CONDEMNED,
SO WE CAN TORCH IT,
BOIL THE BEER.
I'LL TELL YOU
SOMETHING, IN TWO WEEKS
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
15,000 GALLONS OF BEER.
WE'RE GOING TO
CALL IT "ARSON ALE".
OH, UNCLE RED, THAT'S
A REALLY BIG FACTORY.
WHAT IF THE FIRE
GETS OUT OF CONTROL
AND STARTS TO SPREAD?
HOW YOU GOING TO
GET THE FIRE OUT?
WITH THE BEER.
OKAY.
WELL, HOW YOU GOING
TO GET THE BEER
FROM THE TOWER
TO WHERE THE
FIRE IS?
WE'LL DRINK
IT AND USE OUR
BODIES AS FIRE TRUCKS.
ALL RIGHT, BUT WATCH
OUT FOR BACKDRAFTS.
IF THERE'S ANY
ELIGIBLE WOMEN OUT
THERE, I'M AVAILABLE,
AND I'M HAPPY
TO ANNOUNCE I HAVE
THE ONLY MONSTER TRUCK
AND THE BIGGEST ONE
IN THE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
I PREFER WOMEN
WHO ARE PETITE, BLOND
AND KIND OF
ON THE SLIM SIDE
AND AREN'T AFRAID
OF LOUD NOISES.
WELCOME BACK.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOING
TO CONTINUE ON
WITH THE ICE MAKING PART
OF OUR REFRIGERATION
RENOVATION THING HERE.
AND LIKE I SAID
BEFORE, YOU NEED
AN ICE CUBE TRAY
AND A CUPBOARD
DOOR HANDLE.
NOW, YOU TAKE THE
CUPBOARD DOOR HANDLE
AND YOU MOUNT
THAT TO THE INSIDE
OF THE TOP OF THE FREEZER,
WAY AT THE BACK
THOUGH, ALL RIGHT?
THEN YOU HANG YOUR ICE
CUBE TRAY ONTO THE
DOOR HANDLE
WITH THE HOOK RIGHT
LIKE THAT, EXACTLY --
ABSOLUTELY EXACTLY LIKE THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
WE GOT THE DOOR
HANDLE MOUNTED IN THERE
AND NOW I'M GOING TO
HANG THE ICE CUBE
TRAY ON THAT.
AND I'VE PUT
SOME DUCT TAPE ON
HERE, STICKY SIDE UP,
SO THAT I CAN
ACTUALLY STICK THE TRAY
TO THE INSIDE OF THE
CEILING OF THE FREEZER.
YOU KNOW THE POSSUM
LODGE MEMBERS UP
AT RANKIN INLET
TELL ME THAT DUCT TAPE
WON'T STICK WHEN
IT'S FROZEN.
WELL THAT'S GOOD
BECAUSE WHAT IT MEANS
IS WHEN THE ICE
CUBES ARE ALL FROZEN,
THE DUCT TAPE IS
GOING TO LET GO
AND THE TRAY WILL FALL
BACK AND REST AGAINST
THE INSIDE OF THE
BACK OF THE FREEZER.
NOW ON THE OUTSIDE
OF THE BACK OF THE FREEZER,
RIGHT WHERE THAT TRAY
IS GOING TO BE,
WE MOUNT THIS PADDLE.
AND WE JUST MOUNT IT
AT THE BOTTOM SO IT'S
NICE AND SPRINGY
AND WHEN YOU
WANT AN ICE CUBE,
YOU JUST PULL
BACK ON THE PADDLE
AND LET HER GO, WHACK.
THERE WE ARE.
OF COURSE THE ICE
CUBE HAS GOT TO GET OUT
OF THE FREEZER SOMEHOW,
SO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO
IS PUT A HOLE IN
THE FRONT DOOR,
RIGHT DIRECTLY
IN FRONT OF WHERE
THAT TRAY IS HANGING.
YOU CAN CUT THAT
WITH TIN SNIPS, OF COURSE,
BUT, FIRST OF ALL
YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED A PILOT HOLE.
RIGHT TOOL FOR
THE RIGHT JOB.
THERE WE GO.
LET'S TEST
DRIVE A COCKTAIL.
I TOOK THE LIBERTY
OF FILLING THE ICE CUBE
TRAY UP WITH WATER THERE
AND I DUCT TAPED HER
TO THE INSIDE OF THE
CEILING OF THE FREEZER
SO ICE CUBES ARE
FORMING AS WE SPEAK.
ALRIGHTY.
NOW, ADD A LITTLE
BIT OF WATER.
DON'T WANT TO DROWN IT.
OKAY, THE ICE MAY TAKE
A FEW MINUTES HERE,
SO WHILE WE'RE WAITING
I WANT YOU TO REMEMBER,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
THERE WE GO.
THE ICEMAN COMETH.
[ ICE ROCOCHETING ]
PERFECT.
WELL, WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE TO SEE
BUZZ SHERWOOD
AND GET SOME AIR
SAFETY TIPS
BUT I HAVE NO
IDEA WHERE HE IS.
NO.
WOAH.
YO RED MAN, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WELL, BUZZ, YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO BE TALKING
TO THE VIEWERS
ABOUT AIR SAFETY.
OH, RELAX, RED,
YOU KNOW ME,
I ALWAYS FLY BY THE
SEAT OF MY PANTS.
THIS IS MY SCHEDULE.
I GUESS THAT'S
WHY I'M ALWAYS
A LITTLE BEHIND.
YEAH, I GOT NOTHING
ON HERE ABOUT
AIR SAFETY.
I GOT PLANE
MAINTENANCE
AND PEOPLE I
HAVE TO PICK UP
AND SUPPLIES I
GOT TO DELIVER.
OH, YEAH, GREAT.
I GOT NOTHING ON
HERE ABOUT AIR SAFETY.
I WOULD HAVE
WRITTEN IT DOWN.
WHAT'S THAT?
I CAN'T READ THAT.
HOLD THAT OUT FOR ME.
WHAT DOES THAT SAY?
I GOT BINOCULARS
IN THE VAN.
PICK UP GEOLOGISTS
ON FARFLUNG LAKE.
OH, I SHOULD HAVE
DONE THAT YESTERDAY.
FUEL UP THE PLANE,
YEAH, YEAH,
AND TALK TO RED
ABOUT AIR SAFETY.
I TOTALLY FORGOT.
WELL, YOU KNOW, YOU
GOT ME WORKING SO HARD
WATER BOMBING
THAT STARCH PLANT.
OH, YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
NOW, I DID THE HOPS.
I'VE DONE SOME HOPS
IN THE WATER TOWER
AND NOW I'M GONNA --
I'M GONNA DO THE YEAST.
YEAH.
SO WE'RE LAUGHING.
OKAY, NO, THAT'S FINE.
THAT'S FINE.
BUT BUZZ --
AIR SAFETY.
RIGHT.
OKAY.
AIR SAFETY.
RULE NUMBER
ONE ABOUT FLYING,
NEVER EVER FLY
INTO A TORNADO.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE YOU HAVE IT.
THANK YOU SO
MUCH, BUZZ,
FOR PUTTING
THE TIME AND EFFORT
INTO THAT PRESENTATION.
I VERY MUCH APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU.
HEY, NO SWEAT, RED.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
BYE.
THERE YOU HAVE IT,
BUZZ SHERWOOD, BUSH --
HEY, YOU
FORGOT YOUR PAPERS!
BUZZ YOU FORGOT YOUR --
AH, WELL
THE HOMEMADE BEER PROJECT
WAS I GUESS A BLOW OUT.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
TRYING TO MAKE
A DRY BEER.
I HEARD IT WAS RAINING
BEER FOAM ALL OVER
ROCK REEF POINT.
WELL, IT
STARTED OUT OKAY.
I MEAN, JUNIOR SINGLETON
MIXED EVERYTHING UP
IN A WHEELBARROW
AND THEN BUZZ FLEW
OVER IN A PLANE,
DROPPED HER DOWN INTO
THE WATER TOWER
AND THEN WE SEALED HER
UP TIGHT DOWN THERE,
WE SET THE STARCH
PLANT ON FIRE,
EVERYTHING WAS GOING
GREAT, AND THEN
SHE TURNED
INTO WHAT I BELIEVE
THEY CALL AN INFERNO.
I KNEW SOMETHING WAS
WRONG WHEN I SAW THE
SIDES OF THE TOWER
BULGING OUT
INTO A SPHERE.
AND THEN SHE
BLEW BIG TIME.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK WENT
KIND OF STRANGE ON US.
HE GOT UP AND HE
SAID, "I AM DEATH,
DESTROYER OF WORLDS".
AND THEN THERE WAS
A BIG SHOCKWAVE,
KNOCKED US ALL FLAT,
SHATTERED ALL THE EMPTIES.
WHEN WE WOKE UP,
IT WAS REAL STRANGE,
WE ALL STUNK LIKE BEER
BUT NOBODY WAS SINGING
IRISH SONGS.
TOO BAD YOU MISSED
IT, UNCLE RED.
THE BEST PART, THE
BEER ACTUALLY PUT
THE FIRE OUT.
IT WAS SO COOL.
YOU KNOW BUT THE LIQUID,
I MEAN IT INSTANTANEOUSLY
VAPORIZED, RIGHT,
BUT THERE WAS THIS
HUGE CLOUD OF BEER GAS
WAFTING OVER THE FOREST.
YEAH, BUSTER
SAID THE ANIMALS
WERE ACTING REAL WEIRD.
BIRDS WERE FALLING
OUT OF TREES,
RABBITS WERE
HAVING FIST FIGHTS,
BEARS WERE BELCHING
TREES FLAT.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, IT'S MEETING
TIME, UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO.
I'LL BE A LITTLE
WHILE, HAROLD.
MY UNDERWEAR WOULD SET OFF
A BREATHALYZER MACHINE.
ALL RIGHT.
IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I WILL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING
AND I'LL TELL YOU
SOMETHING, HONEY,
I AM OFF BEER UNTIL
PROBABLY THIS TIME
TOMORROW.
FOR THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO
MUCH FOR WATCHING.
UNTIL NEXT TIME, ON
BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.