Red: YOU EVER SEE
ONE OF THESE?
IT'S CALLED A LAZY SUSAN.
I DON'T KNOW
WHO IT'S NAMED AFTER,
BUT SHE SOUNDS
LIKE MY KINDA WOMAN.
NOW, THESE THINGS ARE GREAT
FOR REACHING STUFF AT
A ROUND TABLE --
I'M GONNA NEED
THIS TABLE CLOTH.
BUT IF YOU'VE GOT A NARROW
RECTANGULAR TABLE,
YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO DUMP SUSAN
AND GO WITH A
TALLER SKINNIER MODEL.
OKAY, FIRST THING YOU
WANNA DO IS LAY A LADDER
ALONG THE LENGTH
OF YOUR DINING ROOM TABLE.
IT'S ALWAYS HANDY
TO HAVE ONE ANYWAY,
IN CASE SOME OF YOUR
GUESTS ARE SOCIAL CLIMBERS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT
THE FIRST "STEP" IS?
THIS ONE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
HOW 'BOUT
THE SECOND "STEP"?
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD!
I'M GETTIN' TO IT.
OKAY, NOW, I CUT MY TABLECLOTH
INTO TWO NARROW STRIPS.
SAME LENGTH AS MY LADDER.
AND I ATTACHED
THE ENDS TOGETHER
USING THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON.
GOT THE ONE END AROUND THE
BOTTOM RUNG OF THE LADDER,
AND THE OTHER END GOES RIGHT
AROUND THIS CAR MUFFLER.
NOW, YOU CAN USE ANYTHING YOU
WANT, AS LONG AS IT'S
CYLINDRICAL,
BECAUSE WHEN YOU DUCT TAPE
IT TO A REVERSIBLE DRILL,
THE WHOLE UNIT BECOMES
MORE THAN A CENTERPIECE,
IT'S A CONVEYOR BELT.
THIS ISN'T JUST
A LAZY SUSAN,
IT'S AN EASY FLOW.
ACTUALLY GOT THE IDEA FROM
WATCHING ALL THOSE BEER CASES
ROLL ALONG THE METAL CYLINDERS
OVER AT THE BEER STORE.
AND THEY CALLED IT
A MISSPENT YOUTH.
SO IN KEEPING WITH
THE BEER STORE THEME,
I'VE PACKED ALL
MY FOOD AND CONDIMENTS
INTO THIS TWO-FOUR.
SO HEY,
PASS THE KETCHUP.
AND WHILE YOU'RE AT IT,
PASS THE MAYO, MUSTARD,
RELISH, SALAD DRESSING, SALT,
PEPPER, SALSA, JALAPEÑOS,
PEANUT BUTTER, OLIVES,
PAPRIKA, STEAK SAUCE,
CANNED GRAVY, LIQUID CHEESE
AND MALT VINEGAR.
AND WHEN YOU WANNA GET THOSE
CONDIMENTS FOR YOUR OWN FOOD,
JUST SWITCH THE
DRILL TO FULL-SPEED,
REVERSE,
AND YOU CAN GET THEM
BACK IN A HURRY.
OKAY, UH, IT'S ALSO
GREAT FOR PICNICS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
ALL RIGHT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
75th ANNIVERSARY
OF THE LODGE,
SO WE'RE HAVING KIND
OF A CARNIVAL THING.
STUFF LIKE BOAT RIDES --
OR SUBMARINE RIDES, IF YOU
GET ONE OF THE OLDER BOATS.
IT'S ALSO A
MAELSTROM YEAR.
EVERY 25 YEARS, WE HAVE THESE
THINGS CALLED A MAELSTROM.
IT'S WHEN LODGE MEMBERS ARE
ALLOWED TO CHALLENGE EACH OTHER
TO PROVE THEIR MANHOOD.
IN A MAELSTROM, YOU CAN EITHER
ACCEPT THE CHALLENGE,
OR YOU HAVE TO RESIGN
FROM THE LODGE.
PROBABLY WHY OUR
MEMBERSHIP NEVER GOES UP.
RED! RED!
YEAH?
WAIT'LL YOU SEE THIS!
IS IT A MAELSTROM THING?
SOMEBODY CHALLENGE
YOUR MANHOOD?
NO, BUT I HAVEN'T
BEEN HOME YET.
NO, NO, THIS IS OLD MAN
SEDGWICK'S MAELSTROM.
HE WAS DARED TO SELL ALL
HIS OLD ARMY MEMORABILIA.
THAT'S A PRETTY
SMALL CHALLENGE.
WELL... HE'S GOT A
PRETTY SMALL MANHOOD.
YOU KNOW WHAT, I GOT
SOME GREAT DEALS, RED.
I GOT A CANNON!
I GOT A REAL CANNON!
WOW!
YEAH, AND HIS
OLD HELMET.
YOU KNOW, I BET HE WORE
THIS ON HIS WAY TO BATTLE.
YEAH,
I BET HE DID.
I BET HE WORE THESE RUNNING
SHOES ON HIS WAY OUT
OF BATTLE!
UNCLE RED! UNCLE RED!
DALTON, HELLO.
I HAVE A
FANTASTIC IDEA.
HAROLD, YOU CAN'T
AFFORD A SEX CHANGE.
HA, HA, HA.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, IT'S A
FANTASTIC IDEA.
WHAT WE DO IS TAKE ALL THIS
STUFF FROM OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S
GARAGE SALE, RIGHT,
AND WE TAKE THAT AND WE
USE IT TO TURN OUR CARNIVAL
INTO A CIRCUS!
THAT'S A DUMB IDEA.
WELL, WE CAN CHARGE
PEOPLE MORE.
I LIKE IT.
THAT'S GOOD, DALTON,
BECAUSE EVERYONE
HAS TO PITCH IN TO HELP.
AND YOU CAN HELP
BY BEING THE CIRCUS CLOWN.
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S NOT A REQUEST...
IT'S A
MAELSTROM!
[ RED CHUCKLES ]
UNCLE RED,
YOUR MAELSTROM...
HUH?
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
EVERY CIRCUS NEEDS
A BEARDED LADY.
DID YOU KNOW WE
HAVE A CANNON, HAROLD?
YEAH, I HEARD.
YEAH, THAT'S GOOD.
WELL, YOUR MAELSTROM
IS TO BE THE HUMAN
CANNONBALL.
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WAHOO!
TODAY'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FOR A FREE SESSION
AT THE PORT ASBESTOS
RHINOPLASTY
AND HIGH COLONIC CENTRE,
WHERE YOU CAN
GET A NOSE JOB
AND A HOSE A JOB.
TRY IT.
YOU'LL BREATHE EASIER.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
THINGIES, ED.
UH, MR. GREEN,
YOU GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET ED FRID
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
MIKE.
OKAY, AND... GO!
OKAY, ED, UM, THIS IS
SOMETHING YOUR UNCLE SHEARS
TO MAKE SWEATERS.
HIS BACK.
NO, OKAY -- NO.
UH, ED, WHERE DOES
WOOL COME FROM?
WOOL-MART?
NO, NO, UH --
OKAY, WHEN YOU SEE A GUY
ON TV AND HE'S RUNNING
FROM THE LAW,
YOU KNOW HE'S ON THE...
BOARD OF DIRECTORS.
OKAY, OKAY,
THINK, ED.
MUTTON.
JEFF.
NO, OKAY, IN THE BIBLE IT
SAYS WHAT WILL LIE DOWN
WITH THE LION?
DEAD TOURISTS.
NO, OKAY, THIS IS A PERSON THAT
SOME FOLKS ACTUALLY WORSHIP.
IF YOU THINK OF THE MOUNTAINS,
YOU THINK OF THE DALAI...
PARTON.
YOU'RE ALMOST
OUTTA TIME, MR. GREEN.
YEAH, UH...
OKAY, ED,
THIS IS SOMETHING YOU'VE
HEARD MOST OF YOUR LIFE.
MARY HAD A LITTLE...
HEADACHE.
NO, NO, ED.
THIS IS A SONG.
OH, YOU MEAN LIKE,
WHO PUT THE BOP IN
THE BOP SHE-BOP SHE-BOP?
OR WHO PUT THE RAM IN
THE RAMA LAMA DING DONG?
THERE IT IS!
WHEN IT'S YOUR
40th BIRTHDAY,
YOU GET A HOUSE
FULL OF GIFTS.
WHEN IT'S YOUR
SEPTIC'S 40th BIRTHDAY,
YOU GET A WHOLE
YARD FULL OF 'EM.
CALL ME BEFORE YOU
HIT THE BIG 4-UH-OH.
MY WIFE WANTS ME
TO BE HEALTHIER.
SO SHE GAVE ME ONE
OF THESE WOKS TO COOK WITH.
A FEW YEARS AGO.
NOW, I KNOW THERE ARE A
LOT OF REALLY BAD WOK JOKES...
"WOK THIS WAY"
OR "IF I COULD WOK THAT WAY,
I WOULDN'T NEED THE FRYING PAN"
OR THE INCREDIBLY JUVENILE,
"YOU CAN TELL BY
THE WAY I USE MY WOK,
"I'M A LADIES MAN/
NO TIME TO TALK."
WELL, SEE, THOSE ARE JUST
THE KIND OF STUPID JOKES
THAT HAROLD WOULD DO.
I'M ABOVE THAT.
NOW, BERNICE SAYS
IF I CAN HEAT UP SOME OIL
AND SLICE A
FEW VEGETABLES,
I CAN MAKE A HEALTHY MEAL
IN ABOUT 10 MINUTES.
WELL, HECK, I CAN OPEN
A BAG OF PORK RINDS
IN A LOT LESS
THAN 10 MINUTES.
OKAY, THE POINT IS
MAYBE I SHOULD GIVE THIS
HEALTHY COOKING A TRY,
BUT I'M TELLIN' YOU,
COOKIN' ONE MEAL AT A TIME?
I DON'T THINK THAT'S
GONNA MAKE ME HEALTHY.
AND MY DOCTOR
AGREES WITH ME.
HE TOLD ME I COULD
USE A BIG WOK EVERY DAY!
SEE, WITH THIS BABY,
I CAN MAKE A WHOLE MONTH'S
WORTH OF MEALS AT ONE TIME.
IT'S ACTUALLY
JUNIOR SINGLETON'S
OLD SATELLITE DISH.
OR AS I CALL IT,
THE WOK OF LIFE.
OKAY, SHE'S GOOD AND HOT.
NOW, IT'S TIME
TO ADD THE OIL.
LOTS OF WAYS
WE CAN GO HERE...
CANOLA, OLIVE,
OR MY PERSONAL FAVOURITE,
10-W-30.
GOLLY, A MEAL THAT SMELLS
LIKE A STOCK CAR RACE.
[ CHUCKLING ]
THESE BEETS WERE
MADE FOR WOKKING.
[ CAT COMPLAINS ]
NOW, THE KEY TO STIR FRYING IS
TO STIR WHILE YOU'RE FRYING.
I FIGURED THAT OUT
MYSELF, ACTUALLY.
MAN, THIS IS GETTING
PRETTY HOT HERE.
OH YEAH, AND ALSO YOU DON'T
WANNA SCRATCH YOUR SUPER WOK,
SO MAKE SURE YOU
USE SOMETHING PLASTIC.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HEALTHY.
WHAT?
IF YOU SEE MY WIFE,
TELL HER
I WENT FOR A WOK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WANNA TALK TO
YOU OLDER GUYS OUT THERE
ABOUT YOUR
ATHLETIC ABILITY.
THIS WON'T TAKE LONG.
NOW, WE ALL KNOW THAT
WINE IMPROVES WITH AGE.
BUT WINE DOESN'T
PLAY HOCKEY.
YOU'RE NOT JUST
HURTING YOURSELF YOU KNOW.
EVERY TIME YOU
LACE UP YOUR SKATES,
YOU'RE INCREASING THE
COST OF
EVERYBODY'S
MEDICAL INSURANCE.
EVERYONE KNOWS YOU NAMED
YOURSELF CAPTAIN OF THE TEAM
SO YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT BEING PICKED LAST.
AND YOU HAD TO GET
THE BIGGEST LOCKER
SO YOU'D HAVE ROOM
FOR ALL YOUR ADVIL.
ARE YOU WONDERING
IF I'M TALKING TO YOU?
WELL, IF YOU'RE THE
OLDEST GUY IN THE ARENA,
INCLUDING
EVERYONE'S PARENTS,
THAT'S A CLUE.
IF THEY ASK YOU TO STAND STILL
DURING THE ANTHEM,
SO THE SOUND OF
YOUR JOINTS CRACKING
DOESN'T DROWN OUT THE P.A.,
THESE ARE ALL SIGNS
THAT IT MAY BE OVER.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO MOVE ON TO SPORTS
THAT ARE BETTER SUITED TO YOUR
CURRENT ATHLETIC ABILITY,
LIKE PICKING ONIONS
OUT OF YOUR SALAD
OR STAYING UP
UNTIL NINE.
BESIDES, YOU NEED
TO SAVE YOUR ENERGY
FOR THE ONE SPORT THAT
LASTS A LIFETIME FOR
MARRIED COUPLES...
ARGUING.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
IF YOU WAKE UP EVERY MORNING TO
THE SOUND OF BIRDS COUGHING,
IT'S TIME TO CALL
ROTHSCHILD'S.
WELL, THIS CARNIVAL THING IS A
BIG HIT WITH EVERYONE
EXCEPT THE PEOPLE
WHO ARE IN IT.
WE GOT A REGULAR
FOUR-RING CIRCUS GOING.
THREE IN THE TENT
AND ONE AROUND POSSUM LAKE.
AH, WE'RE GOOD TO GO,
MR. GREEN.
JUST WAITING FOR THE
PAINT TO DRY ON MY BOOTH.
YOU SELLI''
KISSES?
UH, NO, THE WARDEN
DOESN'T ALLOW THAT.
NO, I'M GUESSING PEOPLE'S
AGE AND WEIGHT.
WOULD YOU CARE
TO HAVE A GO?
OH, HE'S GOOD.
HE'S GOOD.
AND CONSIDERATE TOO.
HE WHISPERS THE
ANSWERS TO THE WOMEN.
WELL, ISN'T
WHISPERING TO WOMEN
WHAT GOT YOU INTO PRISON
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
JUST HOLD STILL, OKAY.
OKAY... HMM.
OKAY, I WOULD SAY
YOU ARE 58 YEARS OLD
AND YOU WEIGH
167 POUNDS.
WOW! HOW'D YOU
DO THAT?
IT'S ON YOUR
DRIVER'S LICENSE.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
HEY, HEY, HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOI''
IN THE CIRCUS?
OH, UH, I'M DOIN'
THE HIGH WIRE ACT.
ISN'T THAT A
LITTLE SCARY?
OH, NOT REALLY.
YOU LEARN THE SAME SKILL
AS YOU DO IN THE SEWAGE
BUSINESS...
NEVER LOOK DOWN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
UNCLE RED.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
WEARING YOUR DRESS?
NOW, THERE'S A QUESTION
EVERY MAN WANTS TO HEAR.
WELL, SINCE I'M ALL
READY TO BE SHOT OUT
OF THE CANNON,
I THINK YOU SHOULD
BE DRESSED LIKE THE
BEARDED LADY.
YOU KNOW, UNLESS YOU WANNA
JUST CALL THE WHOLE THING OFF.
NO, NO, NO.
I'M GOOD TO GO.
WHY, DO YOU WANNA
CHICKEN OUT?
NO!
NO, I DON'T.
I WAS JUST -- I WAS
THINKING OF CONVENIENCE.
THAT'S ALL,
JUST CONVENIENCE.
YOU KNOW, YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE TO LOOK SILLY.
I WOULDN'T HAVE TO DIE.
NO, I THINK WE SHOULD
FACE OUR FEARS.
YOU DO, HUH?
ALL RIGHT, THEN I WILL.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
I'LL DO!
HERE I GO.
WISH ME LUCK.
GOOD LUCK, HAROLD.
OKAY.
HAROLD, THE CANNON'S
THAT WAY.
[ whimpering ]
I KNOW.
Red: WE HAD PUT OUR LUNCH
IN A PICNIC BASKET
AND LEFT HER IN THE BARN
BECAUSE WE WERE DOING SOME
CLEAN-UP AROUND THE LODGE.
AND WALTER, APPARENTLY, HAD
GOTTEN THERE JUST A TAD EARLY.
AND, UH...
BILL AND I CAME IN.
WE WERE PRETTY HUNGRY.
WE WERE KINDA LOOKING FORWARD
TO THE LUNCH WE HAD PACKED.
WE GOT IN THERE
AND OPENED UP THE BASKET
AND WERE QUITE SURPRISED
TO SEE THAT IT WAS
MAINLY JUST SCRAPS
AND FLOTS AND BITS
AND WHAT HAVE YOU.
AND WE INQUIRED AS TO
WALTER WHAT HAD --
HE DIDN'T SEEM TO HAVE
A LOT OF INFORMATION
IN THAT AREA.
AND THEN, UH, HE FINALLY
SURMISED THAT HE KNOWS
WHAT IT IS.
RATS, LITTLE RATS
IN THE --
BILL GOES, NO PROBLEM.
I HAPPEN TO HAVE A COUPLE OF
TRAPS IN MY PANTS.
THERE WE GO.
WELL, THEY WEREN'T SET.
WASN'T DANGEROUS.
SO HE GRABS SOME
CHEESE OUT OF THE BASKET
AND SETS ONE DOWN OVER --
THEY'RE A GOOD SIZE --
THE RAT TRAP IS A
GOOD-SIZED TRAP.
IT'S GOT A REAL
GOOD SPRING ON IT.
OFF AN '82 RELIANT,
I BELIEVE.
THEN HE SETS THE OTHER --
CAREFUL.
OH! GOLLY THAT CAN STING.
AND THEN HE'S
DANCIN' AROUND A BIT,
AND WOULDN'T YOU KNOW,
HE CLIPS THE OTHER ONE
WITH HIS FOOT.
NOW THIS IS STARTIN'
TO HURT HIM.
AND THEN...
OH! OH!
WAIT, DON'T WE
HAVE TWO RAKES?
OH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT,
LATER THAT DAY...
I GOT THE IDEA
TO GO TO PLAN "B",
WHICH IS ONE OF THESE
STICKY RAT PADS THEY HAVE.
WE'VE HAD THIS
BABY A WHILE.
I FIGURE IT WORKS,
AND IT'S IT SAFER.
YOU JUST LEAVE
THE PAD LYING OUT,
AND THE RAT GETS KINDA --
HIS FEET GET STUCK IN THERE.
IT'S DRIED.
MOISTEN MAYBE IT'D BE OKAY.
I FIGURE OKAY,
THE TECHNOLOGY,
IT'S A GOOD IDEA, MAYBE WE'LL
JUST BUILD OUR OWN.
BUILD MAYBE
A BETTER MOUSETRAP --
OR RAT TRAP,
OR WHAT HAVE YOU,
BY JUST POURING
OUR OWN ADHESIVE,
GLUE, WHAT HAVE YOU,
INTO SOME GARBAGE CAN LIDS.
THIS IS THE STRONG STUFF.
AND YOU TAKE THAT,
LEAVE THOSE IN THE BARN
JUST STRATEGICALLY PLACED,
AND THEY'RE GONNA CATCH MAYBE
SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE,
MAYBE A THOUSAND RATS.
OH, WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
UH, THEY SEEM TO BE
PREOCCUPIED
WITH SOME SORT
OF NASAL ADJUSTMENT.
AND THEN OF COURSE THEY STEP
RIGHT INTO THE GLUE
AND FALL DOWN,
AND THE LIDS ARE
STUCK TO THEIR FEET.
NOW, WALTER DIDN'T
COME OFF TOO BAD,
'CAUSE I GOT HER
OFF RIGHT AWAY.
BUT YOU CAN SEE THE
ADHESION QUOTIENT THERE.
BUT JUST AN EXTRA
FEW SECONDS WAS ALL IT TOOK
FOR BILL'S
TO SET RIGHT IN.
SO I'M THINKIN', WALTER,
GO AND GET THE POSSUM VAN.
I GOT AN IDEA.
I FIGURE IF I COULD WEDGE THAT
LID RIGHT INTO THE FLOOR,
LIKE STRAIGHT
UP AND DOWN,
AND THEN GET WALTER
TO BACK OVER HIM,
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IS,
I FIGURED --
I DIDN'T REALISE HE HAD
SO MUCH GLUE ON HIS FEET.
BUT ANYWAY, HE DID
EVENTUALLY GET THERE.
AND I JUST FIGURE,
I'LL JUST CLEAR THE AREA.
SLOW DOWN! SLOW DOWN!
I DIDN'T REALISE WALTER'S FEET
AT THIS POINT WERE STUCK.
SO I JUST GOT
OUTTA THERE.
AND THEN HE WAS
RIGHT OVER BILL,
NAILS THE GARBAGE CAN LID,
AWAY SHE GOES.
AND, UH, YOU KNOW,
EVERYTHING'S AS GOOD AS NEW.
UH, BILL'S A LITTLE UPSET,
YOU KNOW, WITH THE TREATMENT.
AND, UH, HE GETS
INTO A LITTLE BIT OF
A SOMETHING WITH WALTER,
BUT WALTER JUST KEEPS
COMIN' BACK FOR MORE.
MEANWHILE, I WASN'T
HAVIN' MY BEST DAY.
WAIT A MINUTE!
DON'T WE HAVE TWO RAKES?
IF YOU'RE GETTING
BACK TO NATURE,
GOOD FOR YOU.
IF NATURE'S GETTING
BACK TO YOU,
GOOD FOR ME.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ WOLF WHISTLES
AND APPLAUSE ]
I CAN'T STAY.
THE CARNIVAL
STARTS ANY MINUTE,
AND WHEN YOU'RE
DRESSED LIKE THIS,
IT'S GOOD TO KEEP MOVING.
[ APPLAUSE ]
RED, DALTON AND I DON'T
WANNA GO THROUGH WITH THIS.
I MEAN, WHEN I AGREED
TO WALK THE HIGH WIRE,
I DIDN'T KNOW
IT WAS THE ONE THEY
RUN ELECTRICITY THROUGH!
WELL, I'M SURE THEY'LL
TURN THE POWER OFF.
AT LEAST DOWN.
WHAT'S YOUR
PROBLEM, DALTON?
I JUST DON'T
FEEL FUNNY.
I DON'T KNOW HOW WE
CAN GET OUT OF THIS.
I MEAN, IT'S THE
MAELSTROM.
WELL, IF ANY ONE
OF US RENEGES,
THAT MEANS WE'RE
NOT A MAN, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
WHICH IS BASICALLY LIKE
SAYING WE'RE DIFFERENT
FROM THE OTHERS.
BUT IF WE
ALL CHICKEN OUT --
I MEAN, UH --
UH, RETHINK THE PLAN --
RETHINK THE PLAN.
YEAH.
AND ALL OF US QUIT,
THEN NOBODY'S DIFFERENT,
AND NOBODY HAS
TO RESIGN FROM THE LODGE.
OH, I DUNNO,
WINSTON.
OH, MR. GREEN!
YOU'VE GOT
BEAUTIFUL LEGS.
OKAY, THAT'S IT.
THE DEAL'S OFF.
THE MAELSTROM
DOESN'T COUNT,
'CAUSE WE'RE ALL
QUITTIN' AT THE
SAME TIME.
THANK YOU, RED!
HADN'T SOMEBODY
BETTER TELL HAROLD?
HE'S ALREADY
IN THE CANNON.
HAROLD! HAROLD!
[ BLAST ]
[ CRASHING ON ROOF ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Dalton:
UH, MEETING TIME!
HAROLD? YOU OKAY?
YOU KNOW, I THINK
YOU'RE FINE.
JUST, UH, YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE UNCONSCIOUS.
YOUR BODY DOES THAT, EH,
SO IT CAN CONCENTRATE
ON THE HEALING.
BOY, WE LEARNED A LOT TODAY,
UH, DIDN'T WE, HAROLD?
LIKE I WAS WRONG ABOUT
THAT MAELSTROM THING,
UH, HAROLD, YOU KNOW.
YOU'RE ALREADY A MAN.
IN FACT, YOU'RE A
REAL GOOD MAN,
AND YOU DON'T NEED ME FORCIN'
YOU TO DO DUMB THINGS,
YOU KNOW, THAT REALLY DON'T
PROVE ANYTHING, SO --
UNCLE RED.
HAROLD?
YOU THOUGHT THAT
DUMMY WAS ME.
FORCE OF HABIT.
THOSE WERE
THE NICEST WORDS
YOU ALMOST
EVER SAID TO ME.
TAKE YOUR HANDS
OFF ME, HAROLD.
I'M A LADY.
I'M JUST GONNA GO.
PLEASE DO.
OKAY, UH, IF MY
WIFE IS WATCHIN',
I'LL BE COMIN' STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETIN'.
AND I'M HOPIN' TO PROVE THAT
I'M MORE OF A MAN THAN I LOOK.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHIN'.
ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN EVERYBODY.
SIT DOWN IN YOUR SEATS.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
OKAY, NOW, I'VE BEEN HEARING
SOME RUMOURS THAT MANY OF YOU
ARE DISSATISFIED WITH THE WAY
THE LODGE EXECUTIVE
HANDLED THE WHOLE
MAELSTROM SITUATION.
I TAKE GREAT
EXCEPTION TO THAT.
NOW, IF I COULD JUST
GET MY VICE PRESIDENT
AND MY SECRETARY TREASURER
TO STAND WITH ME,
I THINK IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS
THAT WE'VE GOT THE
RIGHT PEOPLE FOR THE JOB.