[breezy folk music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> OKAY, THIS IS IT.
WE'VE DONE ALL THE PREPARATION,
ALL THE PLANNING.
WE'VE WORKED REALLY,
REALLY HARD.
WELL, YOU KNOW, OKAY,
SOME PEOPLE DIDN'T WORK AS
HARD AS OTHERS.
THAT'S BECAUSE THEY DON'T CARE
AS MUCH AS I DO.
ANYWAY, WE'VE DONE ALL WE CAN
DO, BUT, YOU KNOW, OKAY,
NOT BECAUSE EVERYTHING IS
PERFECT OR ANYTHING,
JUST THAT WE PRETTY MUCH RAN
OUT OF TIME.
SO PLEASE WELCOME THE STAR
OF THE RED GREEN SHOW,
MR. RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
YEAH, WE HAD A HECK OF A LOT
OF FUN THIS WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE.
BUT, OH, HEY, BEFORE I GET
TO THE FUN ASPECT, HAROLD,
COME ON OVER HERE A MINUTE.
HAROLD IS THE PRODUCER AND
DIRECTOR OF THE SHOW,
AND HE HAS THIS FANCY LITTLE
GIZMO THAT ALLOWS HIM TO DO
ALL KINDS OF SPECIAL EFFECTS
THAT YOU'LL BE SUBJECTED TO
THROUGHOUT THE HALF HOUR.
>> YEAH, NEAT WEIRD STUFF
LIKE THIS.
WAH.
SEE, THAT WAY, I CAN GET
FROM A BORING SEGMENT
INTO A REAL INTERESTING ONE.
[buzzing]
FOR EXAMPLE, I CAN DO THAT.
>> YOU WOULDN'T EVEN NEEDED
THAT GIZMO UP HERE
YESTERDAY, HAROLD.
WE GOT INTO A CANOE JOUSTING
CONTEST.
THIS IS WHERE YOU TIE YOUR
LAUNDRY TO THE END OF A
CANOE PADDLE, AND THEN YOU
USE THAT AND TRY AND KNOCK
THE OTHER GUY, YOU KNOW,
OUT OF HIS CANOE.
>> THAT SOUNDS NEAT.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU GOT FOOTAGE OF THAT?
COULD I SEE FOOTAGE OF THAT?
IF YOU'VE GOT FOOTAGE OF THAT,
I'D LIKE TO SEE FOOTAGE OF IT
IF YOU GOT SOME.
YOU GOT FOOTAGE?
>> OH, NO, I HAVE THE MEMORY
OF IT, HAROLD.
I CAN JUST TELL A STORY
ABOUT IT.
THAT'S JUST AS GOOD.
>> OH, YEAH, THAT'S GREAT,
BUT FIRST JUST LET ME GO TO
THE NEXT SEGMENT.
I HAVE FOOTAGE OF THAT.
[acoustic guitar music]
>> BLOOD ON THE SADDLE
BLOOD ON THE GROUND
BLOOD ON THE TREETOPS
HALFWAY TO TOWN
I ADMIT I WAS CARELESS
BUT I'VE TAKEN THE PLEDGE
NEVER AGAIN WILL
I KILL A MOSQUITO
WITH A 16-POUND SLEDGE
[laughter]
THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA TAKE YOU OUTSIDE
AND SHOW YOU SOMETHING YOU
CAN DO WITH SOMETHING THAT
EVERYBODY HAS AT LEAST ONE OF
IN THEIR BACKYARD,
AN OLD JUNK CAR.
MAYBE YOU FOUND THE CAR,
OR IT COME WITH THE HOUSE,
OR YOU JUST GOT UP ONE
MORNING AND THERE IT WAS,
DROPPED OUT OF A PLANE OR
SOMETHING.
YOU CAN TELL A LOT ABOUT
PEOPLE HAVE--WHAT THE KIND
OF CAR THAT THEY HAVE.
AND MAYBE THEY JUST HANG ON
TO IT FOR SENTIMENTAL VALUE
OR MAYBE IT HAS NO WHEELS,
BUT WE WANT TO SHOW YOU
SOMETHING THAT YOU CAN DO
WITH THESE THINGS.
WITH A LITTLE BIT OF INNOVATION,
YOU MAYBE COULD MAKE A PLAY FORT
FOR THE KIDS, OR IN OUR CASE
TODAY, A FABULOUS, FABULOUS
GARDEN CENTER.
LET ME SHOW YOU HERE.
NOW, THIS IS THE GARDEN SHED,
AND IN HERE, I KEEP ALL MY--
ALL MY GARDENING TOOLS
AND MY WEED-WHACKER,
MY WEED-WHIPPER,
MY WEED
WHIP-WHACKER-WHACK-WHIPPER,
AND THE WHIPPIN' WHACKIN'
WEEDIN' THE WEEDIEST.
THEY'RE ALL IN HERE,
AND--WHAT IS THAT?
THAT LITTLE FELLOW SHOULDN'T
BE IN THERE.
NOW, THEN, THIS AREA IN THE CAR,
YOU'VE ALWAYS WANTED A
GREENHOUSE.
HOW ABOUT A GREENHOUSE WITH
A AM/FM RADIO, HEAT CONTROL,
DEFROST, SIDE VENTS,
TOP VENTS.
WE DON'T HAVE A SUNROOF ON THIS.
MAYBE YOU'D LIKE IT TO HAVE
A SUNROOF, AND YOU CAN
EVEN HAVE AN AIR CONDITIONER.
YOU CAN ADJUST THE AIR
TEMPERATURE JUST BY ROLLING UP
AND DOWN THE WINDOWS,
OR YOU WANT TO JUST BLOW ALL--
YOU WANT THE PLANTS TO ALL GROW
ONE WAY, YOU JUST OPEN
AND JUST BLOW.
FABULOUS, FABULOUS THING.
AND LET ME SHOW YOU SOMETHING
ELSE WE'VE GOT OVER HERE.
WAY OVER THE OTHER SIDE HERE.
THIS IS AN INTERESTING WAY
TO GROW TOMATOES.
YOU HOOK 'EM RIGHT ONTO THE
RADIO AERIAL, AND THEN AS THE
TOMATOES GROW UP, SO DOES
THE AERIAL.
THE RADIO WAVES WILL GIVE
YOU A VERY UNUSUAL TASTE.
KIND OF A--WELL, YOU CAN
SET THEM FOR HEAVY METAL,
OR MIDDLE OF THE ROAD TOMATOES,
WHATEVER IT IS THAT YOU WANT.
NOW, HERE, MAYBE YOU HAVE
SOME TROPICAL PLANTS THAT
REQUIRE A LITTLE MORE WARMTH,
A LITTLE MORE HUMIDITY.
HERE'S YOUR SPOT RIGHT HERE.
AND THESE THINGS WILL GROW--
YOU ONLY HAVE TO START HER UP
TWO OR THREE TIMES A DAY
AND THESE'LL JUST FLOURISH
IN HERE.
YOU KNOW YOU THINK ABOUT
WATERING YOUR PLANTS AND SO
FORTH, AND I SAY, YOU KNOW,
WHY RISK GETTING ANOTHER
HERNIA CARRYING A WATERING CAN
OR WHAT HAVE YOU, WHEN YOU GOT
THE RAD HOSE HERE.
YOU JUST--YOU MIGHT HAVE
TO PUT AN EXTENSION ON THAT.
PUT ANOTHER COUPLE EXTRA
FEET ON THAT.
BUT YOU TAKE HER RIGHT BACK
HERE.
I HAD THE GREENHOUSE LOCKED.
AND RIGHT IN THERE YOU'VE GOT--
THIS IS YOUR--YOU GOT SAFETY.
WE GOT SECURITY,
FULL SECURITY HERE.
GET IN HERE, AND THEN ALL YOU
GOT TO DO IS START UP YOUR
ENGINE.
[engine turning over]
AND SEE, THERE WE GO.
AND I CAN JUST HOSE HER
RIGHT DOWN THERE.
THING WITH THAT DEAL IS, YOU
WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU GOT
THE CAR RUST-PROOFED.
AND IF YOU WANT TO MAKE YOUR OWN
WEED-WHACKER
OR WHIP-WEEDER, WEEDY,
WEEPER, WEEDY, WEED...
[groans]
HOW ABOUT THIS?
[grunts]
IT'S THE FAN OUT OF THE HEATER.
OH, LET ME SHOW YOU SOMETHING
ELSE.
NOW, BACK HERE, ANOTHER THING
YOU CAN DO IS, YOU JUST LEAVE
THE CAR RUNNING, AND THE
EXHAUST GAS--'CAUSE PLANTS
WORK ON CARBON DIOXIDE.
WELL, THERE'S CARBON DIOXIDE
IN THERE, AND THERE'S SOMETHING
ELSE CALLED CARBON MONOXIDE,
WHICH I THINK IS EXACTLY
THE SAME THING.
AND THERE'S LEAD,
AND THERE'S PEWTER,
I BELIEVE,
AND I THINK THERE'S ALSO
OAT BRAN IN CAR EXHAUST.
I'M NOT SURE ABOUT THAT.
USUALLY MAKES ME HAVE TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
ANYWAY, ANOTHER THING
I WANTED TO SHOW YOU.
THIS IS FABULOUS,
FABULOUS INVENTION.
THIS IS A HOSE REEL.
I MEAN, HOW MANY TIMES DID
I RUN OVER THE HOSE WITH THE
LAWN MOWER BEFORE I GOT THIS
BEAUTY, EH?
17.
BUT I'VE GOT A BETTER WAY OF
MAKING A HOSE REEL OUT OF
THIS GARDEN CENTER,
WHICH YOU'LL SAVE A FEW BUCKS.
LET ME SHOW YOU HOW THAT WORKS.
ALL RIGHT.
[clears throat]
SO WHAT WE'RE LOOKING AT HERE
IS A 200-HORSEPOWER HOSE REEL.
THAT SAVES YOU A HECK OF A LOT
OF TIME AND A HECK OF A LOT
OF ENERGY AND ALL I GOT TO DO
IS START UP THE CAR AND DROP HER
INTO REVERSE.
BUT BEFORE I DO,
I JUST LIKE TO SAY,
UNTIL NEXT TIME,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST FIND
YOU HANDY.
[laughter]
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE
OF THE CANOE JOUSTING STORY.
>> AND SOON IT WILL BE SEARED
INTO YOUR MEMORY TOO.
[breezy folk music]
>> "IT IS SPRING.
YOUNG COUPLES RETURN FROM
THE WOODS WITH STARS IN
THEIR EYES AND LOVE
IN THEIR HEARTS
AND MOSQUITO BITES THAT CAN'T
BE SCRATCHED IN PUBLIC."
WELL, AS I WAS SAYING, WE GOT
INTO THIS CANOE JOUSTING THING,
AND THE GUYS ALL WENT DOWN
TO THE DOCK, AND WE BROUGHT
OUR LAUNDRY AND OUR CANOES
AND OUR PADDLES AND EVERYTHING.
BUT YOU KNOW, WE NEEDED SOME
KIND OF A HANDICAPPING SYSTEM,
AND IT DIDN'T SEEM FAIR THAT
STINKY PETERSON WOULD HAVE
TO GO HEAD-TO-HEAD AGAINST
MOOSE THOMPSON WHEN STINKY
WEIGHS ABOUT THE SAME AS
A MOOSE'S TONGUE.
SO TO GIVE STINKY A FAIR
ADVANTAGE THERE,
WE LET HIM USE THE PADDLE
THAT HAD OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S
LAUNDRY ON IT.
I MEAN, IT WASN'T EVEN TIED ON.
IT JUST STUCK.
THEN WE RAN A SAFETY WIRE
FROM THE LAUNDRY UP TO THE
ROOF OF THE BOATHOUSE SO
THAT IF THERE WAS A PROBLEM
AT ALL, IT WOULDN'T FALL
INTO THE LAKE AND KILL THE FISH.
WELL, THE FIGHT GOT GOING THERE,
AND STINKY WAS DOING PRETTY
WELL KEEPING HIS BALANCE AND
EVERYTHING, BUT JEEZ,
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
MOOSE THOMPSON BENDS WAY
OVER AND JUST BIT THE BOTTOM
RIGHT OUT OF STINKY'S CANOE,
YOU KNOW, WHICH--
THAT PUT STINKY INTO
THE SANDBAR AND PUT MOOSE
INTO THE SEMIFINALS.
>> EXCUSE ME, UNCLE RED.
I JUST GOT TO SAY,
THERE'S NOBODY IN TELEVISION
WHO TELLS A STORY LIKE YOU DO.
>> WELL, THANK YOU HAROLD.
>> I THINK THERE'S A REASON
FOR THAT.
>> GOOD MORNING, GLEN.
>> HI, RED.
HOW'D YOU LIKE TO GO FOR A
RIDE IN THE R.V.?
>> OH, WHERE TO?
>> OH, I DON'T KNOW.
HOW ABOUT THE GRAND CANYON?
>> WELL, GOLLY, GLEN,
THAT'S GOT TO BE 3,000 MILES
SOUTH OF HERE, ISN'T IT?
>> I CAN SHUT THE MARINA
DOWN, RED.
I'VE DONE IT BEFORE.
>> YEAH, BUT YOU'RE GONNA NEED
A LOT OF EXTRA FOOD AND CLOTHES
AND MAPS AND SO ON.
>> SHE'S ALL LOADED UP, RED.
I KEEP DELORES FULLY LOADED
FOR ALL TIMES.
>> WOW.
DELORES.
>> YEAH.
SHE'S MY FOUR-WHEEL FREEDOM
MACHINE HERE, RED.
YEP.
WITH AUTO CRUISE ON THIS BABY,
WE COULD GET DOWN TO THE
GRAND CANYON IN 83 HOURS.
>> WELL, ACTUALLY, GLEN,
I JUST NEED SOME OUTBOARD MOTOR
OIL FOR THE LODGE RUNABOUT.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
>> RED, WE COULD BE SITTING
IN THE GRAND CANYON
SUCKING ON MICROWAVE CHILI.
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
>> WELL, ACTUALLY, THE ECHO
WOULD SCARE ME TO DEATH.
NO, I JUST NEED
THREE QUARTS OF OIL
FOR THE 9 1/2 WE GOT UP
AT THE LODGE.
>> YEAH, SURE.
>> SO YOU HAVE ANY OIL, GLEN?
>> WHY SHOULD I HELP YOU?
>> WELL, YOU'RE THE ONLY MARINA
WITHIN 100 MILES.
YOU'RE A LODGE MEMBER.
I'M A LODGE OWNER.
YOU SOLD ME THE MOTOR.
STOP ME IF I MAKE A POINT HERE.
>> ALL RIGHT, OKAY, SURE,
HELP YOURSELF.
>> OH, ALL RIGHT.
WHERE DO YOU KEEP THE OIL?
>> UH...
[laughter]
>> GLEN?
>> I'M THINKING, RED.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE YOU COULD
MICROWAVE ME A CUP OF COFFEE.
I ALWAYS THINK BETTER WITH THAT.
>> WHY DON'T I JUST LOOK IN
THE--IN THE WORKSHOP HERE?
>> OH, I THINK THE COFFEE WOULD
BE FASTER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW, THERE'S SOME
FROZEN LAYER CAKES IN THERE.
>> YEAH?
>> YOU KNOW, THEY GOT TONS
OF LAYERS, JUST LIKE
THE GRAND CANYON.
>> PROBABLY THE SAME AGE.
TOUGHER THAN IRON
NOT ONE OUNCE OF FAT
ALL SINEW AND MUSCLE
AND BLACKER THAN BLACK
I GUESS I BURNED
THE STEAKS AGAIN
MMM
>> OH, GREAT.
UNCLE RED, COME ON IN.
GRAB A SEAT.
I DIPPED IN THE OLD MALE BAG,
GRABBED A COUPLE LETTERS,
AND THEY BOTH HAVE TO DEAL
WITH ETIQUETTE.
>> [coughs]
YEAH, WELL GO AHEAD.
>> OH, OKAY.
WELL, FIRST ONE SAYS,
"DEAR, RED,
WHAT DO YOU SERVE WITH RED WINE
AND WITH WHITE WINE?"
>> WELL, THAT'S A LITTLE OUTSIDE
MY AREA OF EXPERTISE, HAROLD,
BUT HERE'S WHAT I DO.
I SERVE RED WINE WITH
VINEGAR-FLAVORED CHIPS,
ONION RINGS,
THOSE LITTLE HICKORY STICKS,
AND LICORICE,
WHEREAS WHITE WINE, I CHILL
THAT FOR ALMOST A FULL MINUTE,
AND SERVE THAT WITH
KETCHUP-FLAVORED CHIPS,
CHEESE BALLS, PEANUTS, POPCORN,
AND THE PEPPERONI STICKS.
>> WOW, THAT SHOULD CERTAINLY
HELP OUR VIEWER PLAN THAT
WEDDING RECEPTION.
[laughs]
WELL, WE GOT ANOTHER LETTER
HERE, UNCLE RED, AND IT SAYS,
"DEAR, RED, RECENTLY I DINED
AT A REAL FANCY RESTAURANT
WHERE EVERYONE HAD, LIKE,
TWO OR THREE FORKS,
A COUPLE OF KNIVES,
AND MORE SPOONS THAN WE HAVE
IN OUR WHOLE HOUSE.
HA! WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA?"
>> WELL, THIS HAPPENS A LOT.
OKAY, YOU KNOW,
IT HAS TO DO WITH THE TYPE
OF RESTAURANT.
NOW, YOU MIGHT BE HAVING
A FANCY MEAL AT THE RESTAURANT.
YOU'LL BE HAVING, LET'S SAY,
CRAB, OR STEAK ALASKA,
OR "FILETT MAGNON"--
>> OH, NO, THAT'S FILET MIGNON.
>> FILLY?
WAS IT HORSE MEAT?
>> NO, IT'S FRENCH.
>> THE FRENCH EAT HORSE,
DON'T THEY?
>> NO.
THE FRENCH WORD FOR HORSE IS
CHAPEAU.
>> OH, WELL ANYWAY,
THEY GIVE YOU ALL OF THESE
CUTLERY THINGS BECAUSE THEY
HAVE A DIFFERENT PIECE OF
CUTLERY FOR EVERY DIFFERENT
COURSE, BECAUSE IN A FANCY
RESTAURANT, THE WAITER IS
NEVER GONNA SAY,
"SAVE YOUR FORKS,
'CAUSE THERE'S PIE."
IT'S TOO, UM...
>> GAUCHE.
>> WHAT?
>> IT'S FRENCH.
THOSE FANCY RESTAURANTS USE,
LIKE, A LOT OF FRENCH.
YOU KNOW, LIKE PIE A LA MODE,
AU GRATIN, MAITRE D'.
>> YEAH, OKAY,
SO LIKE WHEN YOU'RE IN A FRENCH
RESTAURANT AND YOU BELCH,
YOU DON'T SAY, "EXCUSE ME."
YOU SAY, "PARDON MY FRENCH."
>> AU GRATIN, MONSIEUR.
>> YOU'RE STARTING TO GET ON
MY NERVES, HAROLD.
>> WELL, LET'S GO TO THE NEXT
SEGMENT THEN, BY ALL MEANS.
>> WHERE'D ALL THIS FRENCH
STUFF COME FROM, ANYWAY?
>> SCHOOL.
>> YEAH, I MIGHT'VE KNOWN.
IT'S ANOTHER SEGMENT OF OUR
ADVENTURES WITH BILL,
WHERE WE KIND OF DEAL WITH
SURVIVALISM, SURVIVING,
SURVIVALISTS, STAYING ALIVE,
BASICALLY, AND I THINK YOU CAN
SEE WHERE WE'RE GOING WITH THIS.
HE'S OUT OF WATER,
AND WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
YOU CAN FIND WATER IN NATURE.
I DON'T MIND BILL DOING THESE.
I JUST--I JUST DON'T LIKE,
YOU KNOW, HAVING TO DO THEM
WITH HIM.
ANYWAY, OUT COMES HIS AX.
BILL'S GOT HIS AX.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT YOU
MAY NOT BE AWARE OF,
BUT IF YOU CAN CHOP A BRANCH
OFF A TREE,
SOMETIMES YOU CAN HOOK RIGHT
INTO THE SAP OR THE WATERY STUFF
THAT COMES OUT THERE.
NO, NO, NOTHING, NOTHING YET.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
"THIRD TIME LUCKY."
[water rushing]
>> [gurgling]
>> I DON'T KNOW QUITE WHAT
KIND OF A TREE THAT WAS THERE.
ANYWAY, ANOTHER THING YOU CAN DO
IS LOW-LYING BRANCHES,
GIVE 'EM A--AND THEY GOT--
WATER COMES FLYING OFF THOSE,
OR EVEN THE HIGHER BRANCH,
IF YOU CAN SEE,
YOU GET A BIG STICK NOW.
I DON'T THINK BILL REALIZED
THERE WAS A BEEHIVE UP THERE.
>> [yelling]
>> OH, BOY, OH, BOY, OH, BOY,
OH, BOY, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
OH, BOY.
[bees buzzing]
>> [yelling]
>> OH, YEAH.
THE GOOD THING WAS,
HE WAS KEEPING THE BEES OFF ME.
AND THEN HE MADE ONE OF
THESE LITTLE DIVINING RODS,
OR WITCHING RODS,
OR I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU
CALL THESE THINGS.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE FOLK ART
KIND OF THING.
THEY SAY THAT--I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S HAPPENING THERE EXACTLY,
BUT THEY SAY THEY CAN FIND
WATER, YOU KNOW, BY THE SPIRIT
OF THE TREE OR SOMETHING.
SO ANYWAYS, HE SAYS THERE'S
WATER RIGHT THERE,
SO I GRABBED THE SHOVEL,
AND WOW, I COULD HARDLY
BELIEVE IT.
I COULD HARDLY--I DON'T KNOW.
BUT WHAT HE'D DONE IS HIT
THE UNDERGROUND HOSE THERE.
BILL.
AH, WELL.
HE MEANT WELL, I'M SURE,
BUT WHO CARES.
NOW WE'RE JUST MOVING ALONG.
HE'S LOOKING FOR ANOTHER SPOT
WITH WATER, AND, YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU'RE WALKING ALONG
WITH BILL, IT SEEMS THAT
STRANGE THINGS HAPPEN.
ALL RIGHT, I DON'T ASK.
IN FACT, I'D RATHER NOT KNOW
MOST OF THE TIME.
HE WAS MOVING THROUGH,
AND HE WAS STARTING TO GET
SOMETHING.
HE WAS STARTING TO TWITCH
AND SO WAS THE ROD.
YOU KNOW, HE'S LOOKING BACK
AND FORTH, AND HE SAID,
"DO WHAT I DO."
SO I TRIED DOING IT THE BEST
I COULD, AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
HE SEEMED TO BE CENTERING IN,
AND, OF COURSE, GUESS WHERE
THE WATER WAS.
RIGHT UNDER THE ROCK.
HE WANTS ME TO MOVE THE ROCK
FOR HIM.
OH, YEAH, THAT COULD HAPPEN.
SO I DECIDED TO SMASH THE ROD.
[water rushing]
[laughter]
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT EITHER.
[water rushing]
WATER WOULD BE HARD,
WOULDN'T IT?
THIS IS ANOTHER TECHNIQUE.
THIS IS REALLY TO CATCH RAIN.
YEAH, YOU STRAP A TARPAULIN
BETWEEN A FEW TREES.
AND IT WASN'T RAINING THIS
PARTICULAR DAY, SO BILL
JUST WENT TO GET A HOSE,
AND HE'S NOT REAL GOOD WITH
THE HOSE, SO I DECIDED
TO KIND OF TAKE OVER,
AND WE JUST PRETEND THAT IT'S
LIKE IT'S RAINING IN THERE.
HE GETS HIS CANTEEN BACK, AND HE
GOES UNDERNEATH IT,
AND WHAT HE DOES IS, HE WAITS
FOR THE RAIN TO BUILD UP IN
THE TARP, WHICH WAS--
AND YOU KNOW WATER
IS QUITE HEAVY,
AND WE DIDN'T NOTICE THE
KNOT STARTING TO SLIP OFF
ONE CORNER.
SO THEN ALL HE HAS TO DO IS
TAKE A LITTLE KNIFE AND JAM IT
IN THE BOTTOM, AND THEN--
AND THEN HE GOT THE WATER.
HE EVEN MANAGED, EVENTUALLY,
TO GET THE CANTEEN FILLED UP.
"IT IS SUMMER.
THE DAYS ARE LONG.
RELATIVES ON VACATION COME
TO STAY WITH YOU.
THE DAYS GET LONGER.
THEY BROUGHT MOM.
INFINITY."
>> YOU SEE, UNCLE RED,
IT'S NOT THAT I HAVE ANYTHING
AGAINST HOCKEY, IT'S JUST THAT
SOCCER IS A BETTER SPORT.
I JUST HAPPEN TO PREFER SOCCER,
THAT'S ALL.
YOU KNOW, MORE KIDS ARE
ENROLLING IN SOCCER SCHOOL
THAN THEY ARE IN HOCKEY SCHOOL.
IT'S TRUE.
BECAUSE IT'S A BETTER SPORT.
IT'S A TREND.
IT'S A WAVE.
THAT'S ALL.
YOU KNOW, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
FOR INSTANCE, IN SOCCER,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BUY THOSE
GREAT BIG HARD PADS THAT
EVENTUALLY PINCH YOU, YOU KNOW?
AND THERE'S NO ICE TO FALL DOWN
AND CRACK YOUR SKULL ON.
THERE'S NO BOARDS TO RAM
YOUR FACE INTO.
I, FOR ONE, PREFER THAT.
>> SOCCER IS NOT A REAL SPORT,
HAROLD, OKAY?
FOR ME, FOR A REAL SPORT,
YOU GOT TO HAVE BLOODSHED,
YOU GOT TO HAVE SERIOUS
PHYSICAL INJURY.
>> SOCCER HAS ALL THAT.
UP IN THE STANDS.
>> FIGHTS?
>> OH, GANG WARS.
>> THAT BAD, EH?
>> OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT PARENTS
CAN BE LIKE.
>> ANY THOUGHTS COMING TO YOU,
GLEN, AT ALL?
>> YEP.
>> YOU REMEMBER WHERE YOU LEFT
THE OIL?
>> NO, I WAS THINKING ABOUT
THE GRAND CANYON, RED.
>> WELL, I THINK I'LL
JUST POKE AROUND.
SEE IF I CAN FIND IT MYSELF.
>> MAN, OH, MAN, RED.
JUST THINK OF IT.
THE GRAND CANYON.
WE COULD BE SITTING IN THE
BOTTOM OF THAT BABY LOOKING
RIGHT UP AT ALL THAT ROCK
AND SHALE AND STUFF.
EVERY SEDIMENT TELLS A STORY.
YEP.
YOU COULD LOOK AT ALL THAT
GRAY STUFF, THAT ROCK,
AND JUST THINK THAT THEY USED
TO BE DINOSAURS AND PREHISTORIC
TREES AND FOLIAGE AND STUFF.
YOU COULD REACH UP AND BUST
A PIECE OF THAT STUFF OFF.
MAN, WE COULD JUST HOLD IT
IN OUR HAND AND JUST LOOK AT IT
AND THEN THROW IT AT EACH OTHER.
THEN HUMMER IT INTO THE LAKE
OR THE RIVER OR WHATEVER'S
AT THE BOTTOM OF THAT CANYON.
>> OKAY, GLEN.
FOUND THE OIL I WAS LOOKING FOR,
SO THANKS A LOT.
JUST PUT IT ON MY BILL, HUH?
>> I KNOW WHY YOU CAN'T GO, RED.
IT'S YOUR WIFE, ISN'T IT?
SHE WON'T LET YOU GO.
YOU SEE, RED, I'M A FREE MAN.
>> YEAH, RIGHT, GLEN.
>> OH, YEAH,
I CAN DO ANYTHING I LIKE.
I CAN GO ANYWHERE AND COME
AS I PLEASE.
I'LL GO TO THE GRAND CANYON,
RED.
YOU JUST WAIT,
AND YOU JUST WATCH ME.
OH, BY THE WAY,
THAT'S THE WRONG OIL.
>> WE'LL BE BACK WITH LOTS
MORE STUFF,
AND LET'S NOT FORGET THE PHRASE
"CANOE JOUSTING."
>> LET'S NOT FORGET THE PHRASE
"BORED OUT OF OUR TREE."
LET'S NOT FORGET THAT EITHER.
>> THERE'S A GRASS FIRE
BLAZING IN THE BACK
OF THE HOUSE
THE BLACK SMOKE SMELLS LIKE
A TOASTED MOUSE
WE DO THIS EVERY YEAR
'CAUSE IT HELPS
WITH THE GROWING
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY
IT'S A HELL OF A LOT EASIER
THAN MOWING
[lively acoustic guitar music]
HI!
>> HI.
[laughter]
>> I KNOW A LOT OF YOU
TEENAGERS OUT THERE ARE
REBELLING, AND YOU DON'T
REALLY KNOW WHY.
MAYBE YOU'RE TORCHING SCHOOL
BUSES OR KNOCKING OVER
VARIETY STORES.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
WHAT DOES MATTER IS THAT
THIS IS JUST A NATURAL PART
OF THE MATURING PROCESS.
IT'S JUST YOUR WAY OF SAYING
"HEY, I AM NOT LIKE MY PARENTS.
I'M ME."
AND IF THAT MEANS TAKING A
FLAMETHROWER TO THE MALL,
THEN SO BE IT.
THE IMPORTANT THING TO REMEMBER
IS THAT IF YOU'RE GONNA BE
REBELLIOUS, HAVE SOME FUN
WITH IT.
YOU KNOW THEY SAY THE TEENAGE
YEARS ARE THE BEST YEARS,
AND YOU SHOULD REMEMBER THAT
AND ENJOY THEM,
BECAUSE YOU'RE PROBABLY
GONNA SPEND THE REST OF YOUR
LIFE BEHIND BARS.
SO WHEN WE GOT DOWN TO THE
ABSOLUTE FINAL MATCHUP IN
THE CANOE JOUSTING COMPETITION,
IT TURNED OUT TO BE
MOOSE THOMPSON AGAINST
BUSTER HATFIELD.
NOW, WHAT BUSTER LACKED
IN SIZE AND SPEED,
HE ALSO LACKED IN STRENGTH
AND CUNNING.
BUT YOU KNOW HE SURPRISED US.
BEFORE THE FIGHT BEGAN,
WHAT BUSTER DID WAS, HE SWUNG
HIS PADDLE RIGHT AROUND,
AND HE CATCHES MOOSE RIGHT
SQUARE BETWEEN THE EYES.
YOU KNOW, AND OF COURSE,
THIS GETS MOOSE LAUGHING,
YOU KNOW?
AND THEN BUSTER UNTIES THE
LAUNDRY AND LOOPS AN OLD PAIR
OF WORK PANTS UPSIDE DOWN
OVER MOOSE'S HEAD.
WELL, I MEAN, HOW IS MOOSE
SUPPOSED TO FIGHT LOOKING OUT
THE FLY OF A PAIR OF WORK PANTS
WHILE HE'S HAVING A MAJOR FIT
OF THE GIGGLES?
SO NATURALLY, IT ENDED
IN A DRAW.
BUT GOLLY, IT WAS A GREAT DAY,
AND YOU KNOW, AFTER
WE RETURNED THE BROKEN CANOES
TO THE SCOUT CAMP,
WE ALL HAD OUR PICTURE TAKEN
WITH MOOSE'S FOREHEAD LUMP.
AND, BOY, I'LL TELL YOU,
A GOOD TIME WAS HAD BY SOME.
SO ANYWAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING, I'LL BE COMING
STRAIGHT HOME, AND I'M BRINGING
EVERYBODY'S LAUNDRY.
I KNEW YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
OKAY.
SO THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
THE SHOW, AND ON BEHALF
OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE REST OF THE GANG
UP HERE AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[laughter, applause]