[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ GUNSHOTS ]
[ BIRD SQUAWKS ]
Harold: AND NOW IT'S TIME
FOR "THE RED GREEN SHOW,"
BEING BROADCAST TO YOU LIVE --
WELL, OKAY, NOT LIVE,
BUT, WELL, ALMOST LIVE.
WELL, NOT DEAD YET.
THAT'S THE IMPORTANT THING.
ANYWAY, WE'RE BROADCASTING
AND FLY CASTING
FROM POSSUM LODGE
HERE IN THE NORTHERN WILDERNESS
OF OUR GREAT COUNTRY --
OR YOUR COUNTRY,
OR THE BANKS' COUNTRY, ACTUALLY.
THEY PROBABLY OWN MOST OF IT.
ANYWAY, SPEAKING OF THINGS
THAT ARE OWNED BY THE BANK,
HERE'S THE STAR OF THE SHOW
AND MY UNCLE, MR. RED GREEN.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
THANK YOU.
WELCOME TO POSSUM LODGE.
UH, HAROLD HERE IS MY
PRODUCER/DIRECTOR/ANNOUNCER/
NUISANCE ON THE SHOW.
GIVE THEM A TASTE
OF YOUR MAGIC THERE, HAROLD.
IT'S HAMMER TIME!
[ KEYBOARD CLACKING ]
WA-A-A-A!
I DON'T GO TOO MUCH FOR
THAT ELECTRONIC CRAP MYSELF,
BUT, UH, ANYTHING
THAT EATS UP TIME FOR FREE
IS CERTAINLY A WELCOME ADDITION
TO THE SHOW.
ACTUALLY, THINGS HAVE BEEN
JUST A LITTLE BIT TENSE
UP AT THE LODGE,
UH, THIS WEEK.
UH, STUFF HAS GONE MISSING,
OR STUFF HAS BEEN MOVED
OR EVEN CHEWED.
GUYS ARE GETTING
A LITTLE BIT ANTSY, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, OLD MAN SEDGWICK SAID
THAT, UH, SOMEBODY ATE
ALL HIS PILLS.
HE COULDN'T REMEMBER
IF THEY WERE M&Ms OR SMARTIES.
I'D SAY THEY DEFINITELY
WERE NOT SMARTIES.
AND MOOSE THOMPSON
WAS TELLING ME
THAT SOMEBODY'S BEEN RUMMAGING,
UH, THROUGH HIS LAUNDRY HAMPER,
OR AS HE CALLS IT, HIS BED.
YOU KNOW, I-I'M WORKING
WITH NOEL ON THE INVESTIGATION.
WE'RE GATHERING CLUES.
OH.
SO YOU'RE NOT CLUELESS ANYMORE.
WELL, THAT'S A TREAT.
NOEL IS ACTUALLY THE, UH,
HEAD OF SECURITY
UP HERE AT THE LODGE.
IT'S KIND OF
A TOKEN APPOINTMENT THING.
IT BACKFIRES FROM TIME TO TIME,
AS DO MOST OF THE LODGE MEMBERS.
YOU KNOW, I'M HOPING
THAT IT'S NOT, LIKE --
LIKE, THIEVES OR VANDALS
OR PERVERTS THAT, LIKE --
THEY JUST COME IN
AND THEY TOUCH YOUR STUFF.
I HATE THAT WHEN PEOPLE
TOUCH MY STUFF!
I HATE THAT.
WELL, HOW DO YOU THINK
THE PEOPLE FEEL, HAROLD?
ANYWAY, WHAT DO YOU HAVE
OF VALUE? YOUR RETAINER?
WELL, SOMETIMES PEOPLE JUST
COME IN AND THEY STEAL STUFF.
AND MAYBE THEY -- YOU KNOW,
THEY THROW IT IN THE DUMP.
WHY?
THE CRIMINAL MIND, UNCLE RED.
IT WORKS IN MYSTERIOUS WAYS.
YEAH, BUT AT LEAST
IT WORKS, HAROLD.
GET ON WITH THE SHOW,
WILL YOU?
ALL -- ALL RIGHTY.
UH-HUH. UH-HUH.
OKAY, HAROLD, I THINK
I'VE SEEN ENOUGH EVIDENCE.
WHEW!
YOU KNOW, NOEL,
IF THEY'RE NOT CLUES
AND THEY ARE
JUST MOUSE DROPPINGS,
MAYBE WE SHOULD
CLEAN THEM UP.
HAROLD, YOU SHOULD NEVER DISTURB
A CRIME SCENE.
I MAY HAVE TO DUST THOSE
DROPPINGS FOR FINGERPRINTS.
YOU SURE HAVE
AN INTERESTING JOB, NOEL.
WELL, IF YOU'VE FINISHED
EXAMINING THOSE MOUSE DROPPINGS,
NOEL, MAYBE YOU'D LIKE
TO JOIN ME FOR A QUICK 18.
HE DOESN'T DRINK.
GOLF, HAROLD -- THE GREATEST
SPORT EVER INVENTED...
OTHER THAN SEX.
WA-A-A-A!
YOU SURE WOULDN'T WANT TO BE
BELOW PAR ON THAT ONE.
"BELOW PAR."
YOU HEAR WHAT I SAID, NOEL?
YOU GET THAT?
B-BELOW PAR?
I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR JOKES.
AND I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR GOLF.
I AM ON A CASE.
THAT'S MY JOB, OKAY?
I DON'T EXAMINE
ANIMAL DROPPINGS
JUST FOR THE FUN OF IT,
YOU KNOW.
NOT ANYMORE.
WELL, I'M WORKING
WHILE I PLAY, NOEL.
I WORK FOR THE DEPARTMENT
DOING NATURAL-RESOURCE WORK.
YOU KNOW, THE GOLF COURSE
IS A PERFECT PLACE TO, UH...
COLLECT INSECT SAMPLES.
WELL, IT'S FIVE MINUTES
TO TEE-OFF -- WORK.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
THERE GOES A MAN
WHO'S TAKEN A MUNDANE JOB
AND REALLY MADE IT
INTO SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, RED,
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
WE'VE HAD A MAJOR BREACH
OF SECURITY.
HAROLD, EXCUSE YOURSELF.
WA-A!
AN INDIVIDUAL
OR POSSIBLY A ROVING GANG
HAVE GAINED ACCESS
TO THE LODGE,
AND THEY'RE
MOVING THINGS AROUND.
IT IS A CLEVER RUSE.
THEY'RE JUST SETTING US UP
FOR SOMETHING TO STEAL.
MY RECOMMENDATION --
RED ALERT,
DEFCON 1, SITUATION 9.
YOU MEAN SOMEBODY'S
BREAKING INTO THE LODGE
AND NOT TAKING STUFF?
I CAN LIVE WITH THAT.
THOUGHT IT WAS JUST MICE.
ISN'T IT JUST MICE?
I THINK IT'S JUST MICE, 'CAUSE
THEY LEAVE LITTLE DROPPINGS
AND FUR ALL OVER THE PLACE,
AND THEN THEY GNAW
ON THE CORNER OF FURNITURE.
HAROLD?
HAROLD!
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO THINK.
IT'S A DIVERSIONARY THING.
OH, YEAH.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT'S REALLY HAPPENING HERE.
THE PERPETRATORS
ARE COMING IN,
AND THEY'RE GNAWING
ON THE FURNITURE.
THEN THEY THROW DOWN
A HANDFUL OF DROPPINGS
TO THROW US OFF THE TRACK.
EXCUSE ME.
ATTENTION, EVERYONE.
OKAY.
DID ANY OF YOU GUYS EAT THESE?
BILL? HUH?
I PUT A FULL PLATE OF THESE
ON THE COUNTER LAST NIGHT,
AND THIS MORNING,
HALF OF THEM HAVE BEEN EATEN.
WELL, THEY CAN'T HAVE
GOTTEN TOO FAR.
NOEL, CALL THE HOSPITAL.
SEE IF THEY'VE HAD A WHOLE RASH
OF STOMACH PUMPINGS.
WELL? WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO ABOUT THIS?
I MEAN, YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
HEAD OF SECURITY, NOEL,
AND I DON'T FEEL
VERY SECURE.
THE ONLY THING WE HAVE TO FEAR
IS FEAR ITSELF.
I DON'T THINK YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
I THINK WE NEED
A NEW HEAD OF SECURITY.
I GOT A MIND TO CITE YOU
FOR CONTEMPT, MISTER,
AND I CAN DO THAT.
OH!
IT'S IN THE LODGE CHARTER --
ARTICLE 55, AMENDMENT "B."
OH, COME ON. I-I THINK WE OUGHT
TO GIVE NOEL ANOTHER CHANCE.
OKAY, YES, EDDIE.
YES, HE'S SMALL, INSIGNIFICANT,
INCOMPETENT, EVEN.
BUT LET'S GIVE HIM
ANOTHER CHANCE,
'CAUSE THEN,
WHEN HE SCREWS UP,
WE CAN REALLY NAIL HIM
TO THE WALL, YOU KNOW?
AT LEAST THAT'S FAIR.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU HAVE 24 HOURS.
THE WAY I LOOK AT IT,
WE'RE LOOKING FOR ONE CRIMINAL.
COULD BE ARMED.
COULD BE DANGEROUS.
[ SNIFFS ]
AND WE CAN'T RULE OUT
INSANITY.
[ STRUMS ACOUSTIC GUITAR ]
THE KNEE BONE CONNECTED
TO THE HEAD BONE
THE ANKLE BONE CONNECTED
TO THE WRIST BONE
THE BUTT BONE CONNECTED
TO THE EAR BONE
IT WAS THE WORST SKATEBOARDING
ACCIDENT ON RECORD
Red: THIS WEEK
IN THE "HANDYMAN CORNER,"
WE'RE DOING ANOTHER INSTALLMENT
OF OUR SERIES
ON HOW TO BUILD FINE FURNITURE.
YOU KNOW, THERE IS
SOMETHING DARN WONDERFUL
ABOUT, UH, BEING ABLE TO TAKE
SOME STRIPS
OF UNBLEMISHED HARDWOOD
AND MAKE YOURSELF
A BEAUTIFUL TABLE
OR EVEN TAKE SOME WROUGHT IRON
AND WELD IT INTO SOME,
UH, LAWN FURNITURE.
OR, UH, GRAB A COUPLE
OF MILK CRATES...
AND TURN THEM INTO
A HANDY-DANDY LITTLE BOOKSHELF.
SUDDENLY, YOU'RE PART OF A LONG
TRADITION OF FINE CRAFTSMEN
WHO'VE TURNED, UH, WOODWORKING
OR WHAT HAVE YOU INTO AN ART.
BUT, YOU KNOW, AFTER YOUR
FIRST PROJECT WITH THIS, UH,
YOU MIGHT WANT TO TRY SOMETHING
A LITTLE MORE AMBITIOUS.
I MEAN, A BOOKSHELF
IS OKAY TO LOOK AT.
BUT NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
YOU HAVE TO BUY BOOKS,
AND, UH, THAT SEEMS A LITTLE
PRETENTIOUS FOR A LODGE MEMBER.
SO, THIS WEEK,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW YOU CAN DO SOMETHING
JUST A TAD MORE AMBITIOUS.
[ CLATTERING ]
WE'RE GONNA TAKE, UH,
THESE MILK CRATES HERE,
AND WE'RE GONNA MAKE
A FOLDAWAY COUCH BED.
ALL RIGHT. UH, YOU BUILD, UH,
TWO UNITS LIKE THIS,
3x3, FOR YOUR SIDES.
MIGHT WANT TO PUT SOME PADDING
ON TOP OF HERE AS AN ARMREST.
AND YOU GOT THE STORAGE BINS
IN HERE -- WINE RACK, BEER RACK,
EVEN A SOFT-DRINK RACK,
YOU KNOW,
IF YOU'RE ONE OF THOSE.
AND YOU PUT THESE THINGS,
UH, AROUND, UH...
EIGHT CRATES' WORTH APART.
GO GET YOUR TOP.
UH, IT'S BASICALLY THE, UH,
THE SAME TECHNIQUE.
UH, YOU KNOW,
WITH THE DUCT TAPE
AND A LOT -- LOT MORE RACKING,
SHELVING HERE.
YOU KNOW, THE DUCT TAPE
WITH THAT SILVER, CHROME LOOK,
YOU KNOW, KIND OF LOOKS LIKE
THE METAL FURNITURE
THAT'S SO POPULAR
WITH THE ART DECO.
AND THEN YOU...
PUT THAT UP ON TOP.
AND THERE'S YOUR SHAPE.
ALL YOUR TELEVISION, UH, REMOTE
CONTROLLERS CAN FIT INTO HERE.
AND, UH, THERE'S OUR FRAME DONE.
STARTING TO TAKE SHAPE,
ISN'T IT?
NOW WE'RE READY TO MAKE
THE, UH, FOLDAWAY SEAT BED.
OKAY. NOW, UH, WHAT I'VE DONE
IS I'VE, UH, MADE TWO UNITS,
3x5 CRATES EACH, AND
WRAPPED THEM ALL IN DUCT TAPE.
WHEN YOU DO THIS, THOUGH,
DON'T SKIMP ON THE DUCT TAPE.
WHENEVER I'VE DONE A PROJECT
AND USED LESS THAN A DOZEN ROLLS
OF DUCT TAPE,
I'VE NEVER BEEN REAL PROUD
OF THE RESULTS.
ANYWAY, YOU KNOW,
BEFORE YOU PUT THIS TOGETHER,
YOU'VE GOT ONE OF THOSE
EXERCISE THINGS.
YOU SEE THE -- THE FOOTBALL
PLAYERS DO THAT KIND OF --
DO THAT KIND OF STUFF.
I NEVER WANTED TO PLAY FOOTBALL.
UH, AND NOW WE JUST
FOLD HER UP TOGETHER.
[ GRUNTS ]
THERE'S OUR SEAT.
SO, YOU JUST, UH, UPHOLSTER THIS
NOW TO MATCH YOUR HOUSE.
OR IF YOU DON'T HAVE A HOUSE,
UH, GET IT TO MATCH YOUR PANTS.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE PANTS, WELL,
YOU HAVE A MORE INTERESTING LIFE
THAN I DO.
MILK BUILDS STRONG BONES
AND STRONG COUCHES, DOESN'T IT?
NOW, YOU KNOW, OF COURSE,
WHEN SOMEBODY DROPS OVER,
THEY GOT A -- THEY GOT A PLACE
TO SLEEP, YOU KNOW?
UH, YOU JUST GET UP,
AND, UH, YOU WHIP OFF THE --
WHIP OFF THE BLANKET HERE.
AND PULL OUT THE SEAT.
[ GRUNTS ]
I'M SURE THEY'D HELP YOU.
POP HER UP.
AND THEN,
WITH THE BEAUTY OF OUR HINGE...
[ HUMS ]
TELL THEM TO STAND WELL BACK.
AND SAY, "BEDTIME.
BED--"
HOP INTO BED.
AHH.
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT.
FANTASTIC.
SO REMEMBER -- IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
I DON'T THINK YOUR GUEST
WILL BE STAYING ANY MORE
THAN ONE NIGHT, EITHER,
SO THAT'S AN ADDED BONUS.
"IT IS SUMMER.
A SPEEDBOAT ZOOMS BY.
"THE HORSEPOWER IS 360,
"WHICH IS FOUR TIMES
THE RATING OF THE BOAT
AND 10 TIMES THE I.Q.
OF THE DRIVER."
SO, ANYWAY, NOEL'S BEEN
QUESTIONING ALL THE MEMBERS
ABOUT THEIR WHEREABOUTS,
WHICH IS KIND OF DUMB,
BECAUSE THESE GUYS
CAN'T REMEMBER
WHERE THEY WERE 10 MINUTES AGO.
AND THEN HE'S -- HE'S DUSTED THE
WHOLE PLACE FOR FINGERPRINTS.
AND, OF COURSE, THERE'S
FINGERPRINTS EVERYWHERE.
SO, UH, NOW NOEL WANTS TO ARREST
ANYONE WITH FINGERS.
SO FAR, MOST OF US
HAVE OFFERED HIM ONE FINGER,
SO THAT'S A START.
BUT ACTUALLY,
HIS INVESTIGATION IS HELPING,
BECAUSE WE KNOW THAT NOEL
IS ALWAYS WRONG,
SO WHOEVER HE SUSPECTS
WE CAN KIND OF ELIMINATE.
UNCLE RED, MAYBE HE'S
DOING IT ON PURPOSE.
YOU KNOW,
LIKE REVERSE PSYCHOLOGY?
'CAUSE NOEL --
I MEAN, HE'S TRAINED
IN INVESTIGATIONAL
CRIMINAL TECHNIQUES.
HAROLD, READING MAGAZINES
DOESN'T MAKE YOU AN EXPERT.
IF IT DID, OLD MAN SEDGWICK
WOULD BE A GYNECOLOGIST.
NOW, OBVIOUSLY, UH,
SOME ANIMAL OF SOME KIND HERE
IS JUST -- IS ROOTING AROUND.
AND WHEN IT CAN'T FIND FOOD,
IT -- IT EATS EDDIE'S COOKING.
NOBODY'S SEEN AN ANIMAL, BUT YOU
CAN TELL THEY'VE BEEN AROUND.
YEAH, BY ALL THE DROPPINGS
ON THE FLOOR.
THAT'S RIGHT, HAROLD.
YOU CAN GET A LOT OF INFORMATION
OUT OF A STOOLIE.
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW HOW LONG
THEY'VE BEEN THERE, EH?
I MEAN, DID ANY OF THEM
LOOK LIKE A DATE?
UH, NO.
[ LAUGHS ] NO!
HUH? HUH?
SO ANYWAY,
I-I BORROWED HAROLD'S CAMERA,
AND I KIND OF SNUCK AROUND,
AND I TOOK SOME PICTURES
THAT I THINK ARE GONNA SOLVE
THIS MYSTERY.
YOU TOOK MY CAMERA?
YOU BORROWED MY CAMERA?
YOU DIDN'T EVEN ASK ME
TO USE IT?
YOU CAME IN AND SWIPED
IT WHEN I WASN'T EVEN
LOOKING OR SOMETHING?
I TOLD NOEL IT WAS STOLEN.
ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS ASK.
YOU DON'T GOT TO
STEAL STUFF FROM ME.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW YOU DID THAT.
DON'T EVEN DO IT.
WELL, I'M SORRY, HAROLD.
I FORGOT WHAT A WHINER YOU ARE.
I JUST HATE WHEN PEOPLE
TOUCH MY STUFF. I...
SO, WHAT'S THE, UH --
WHAT'S THE BIG QUESTION?
WELL, WE'RE HAVING A PROBLEM
AT THE LODGE.
WE GOT A WILDLIFE, UH,
INFESTATION THERE.
YOU GOT A NEW MEMBER?
[ LAUGHING ]
NO. UH, ACTUALLY, UH,
I TOOK SOME PICTURES
OF THE ANIMAL DROPPINGS
TO SHOW YOU.
SCAT.
PARDON ME?
SCAT, RED.
OH. OKAY.
OH, NO.
NO, NO, RED. NO.
THAT'S THE SCIENTIFIC TERM
FOR ANIMAL DROPPINGS -- "SCAT."
YOU KNOW, LIKE WOLF SCAT,
DEER SCAT, SNAKE SCAT --
THAT SORT OF THING.
OH, OKAY.
MAKES SENSE.
WELL, I -- YOU KNOW,
I-I TOOK THIS PICTURE OF IT.
AHA! WOW.
SOME GREAT BACKLIGHTING
YOU GOT THERE.
BEAUTIFUL COMPOSITION.
THANK YOU.
UH, I REALLY LIKE THE CHOICE
OF THE BLACK-AND-WHITE FILM.
YEAH, WELL, I GUESS
I CAUGHT ITS GOOD SIDE.
YOU KNOW,
YOU REALLY HAVE A FLAIR
FOR STILL-LIFE
PHOTOGRAPHY.
YOU SHOULD, UH, DO THIS
FOR THE GOVERNMENT.
YOU COULD MAKE TOP DOLLAR
DOING THAT KIND OF THING.
WELL, UH, THANKS, BOB.
BUT, UH, I DON'T THINK
EXCREMENT PHOTOGRAPHY
WOULD BE A REAL BIG
CAREER MOVE FOR ME.
WELL, THINK ABOUT IT.
SO, WHAT --
WHAT TYPE OF ANIMAL
DO YOU THINK
WOULD LEAVE THE...
OH.
WELL, RACCOON.
OH, RACCOON. OH.
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
OH, YEAH. YEAH.
I MEAN, IT'S THE SAME SCAT
THAT WAS OVER, UH,
BY THE SAND TRAP ON THE, UH,
11th HOLE OVER THERE.
OKAY. SO, WHAT DO I DO TO
GET RID OF A RACCOON, UH, BOB?
DO YOU HAVE
A NUMBER-2 WOOD?
YOU WANT ME TO KILL A RACCOON
WITH A GOLF CLUB?
OH, NO. NO, YOU NEED
A NUMBER-2 WOOD ON THIS HOLE.
NO, IT'S ILLEGAL
TO KILL RACCOONS.
WELL, TELL THAT TO MY VAN.
I HAVE AN IDEA, THOUGH.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I'LL DO.
AFTER WE'VE PLAYED
OUR GAME OF GOLF HERE,
I'LL GO BACK
TO THE OFFICE.
I CAN LEND YOU
A RACCOON TRAP.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT THAT?
WELL, SOUNDS ALL RIGHT,
I GUESS.
WELL,
YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.
FORE!
[ WATER SPLASHES ]
[ FILM PROJECTOR CLICKING ]
Red: NOW IT'S TIME FOR ONE OF MY
FAVORITE THINGS -- FISHING.
NOT FISHING WITH BILL.
THERE'S A BIG DIFFERENCE.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
I'LL FISH WITH ANYBODY.
FIRST THING ABOUT BILL
YOU HAVE TO NOTICE
IS THE SIZE OF THE TACKLE BOX.
YOU CAN TELL A LOT ABOUT A MAN
BY THE SIZE OF HIS TACKLE BOX.
AND, OF COURSE,
BILL DOESN'T HAVE A BOX THAT BIG
TO KEEP IT EMPTY.
HE'S GOT HIS MOTORCYCLE HELMET.
HE'S GOT AN OLD PROPANE TANK.
YOU KNOW, THEY WON'T REFILL
THOSE AFTER 10 YEARS,
BUT I THINK BILL
JUST KEEPS IT AROUND.
KIND OF AN OLD MEMORY THERE
OF A BARBECUE.
AND HE --
AND HE DID FIND A LURE --
ONE OF THOSE LITTLE, UH...
MARITIME WIGGLER,
I THINK THAT THING'S CALLED.
AND, UH, I THINK I DATED
ONE OF THOSE, ACTUALLY.
HE'S GOT
A CHRISTMAS WREATH THERE
AND AN OLD LAWN SPRINKLER.
NO, THAT WAS AN ACTION FIGURE.
THAT'S WHAT THAT --
AND THERE'S A CROWBAR.
THAT'S MINE, ACTUALLY.
I USED THAT TO CHANGE
A HEADLIGHT A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
AND THEN HE'S GOT A BOBBER.
THIS IS A FLOATER.
THEY'RE A BOBBER, FLOATER,
FLOATER, BOBBER --
WHATEVER YOU LIKE.
AND, UH, THIS GOES
ON THE FISHING LINE
SO THAT, UH, YOUR LURE
AND WHAT HAVE YOU WON'T, UH --
WON'T SINK TOO FAR
INTO THE WATER.
JUST HOOKS ON LIKE THAT.
NO BIG DEAL, REALLY.
AND NOW WITH BILL, HE WANTED
TO USE NOT ONLY THE LURE,
BUT HE WANTED TO USE SOME, UH --
SOME BAIT AS WELL.
SO, BAIT AND LURE.
KIND OF A "BLURE."
OH, WHAT'S THAT?
I GOT A NICE LITTLE BIKE THERE.
YOU KNOW, THE DOCK WAS GETTING
A LITTLE FULL,
SO WHAT AM I GONNA DO WITH THIS?
AH, PROBLEM SOLVED.
SO HE GETS OUT
AN OLD PIECE OF HAM
FROM ONE OF OUR
POSSUM LODGE REUNIONS.
UH, LATE '70s,
I THINK THAT ONE WAS FROM.
AND HE HOOKS THE, UH --
HOOKS THE LURE RIGHT INTO THAT.
AND NOW HE'S OBVIOUSLY
GOING FOR THE BIG FISH HERE.
LOT OF WEIGHT.
LOT OF WEIGHT ON THE LINE THERE.
AND UNFORTUNATELY,
WHAT HAPPENED -- OH, GOSH.
THERE GOES HIS -- AND YANKS THE
FISHING ROD RIGHT OUT OF HIS --
AND THERE IT GOES, AND
EVERYTHING GONE TO THE BOTTOM.
SO, THAT SHOULD NOT --
NO, IT'S NOT THE END OF THE DAY,
'CAUSE HE'S GONNA USE MY STUFF.
TERRIFIC IDEA, BILL.
THANK YOU.
BACK INTO THE TACKLE BOX
FOR SOMETHING ELSE.
[ DOG WHIMPERING ]
WHAT? WHAT, WHAT, WHAT?
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES.
HELLO, THERE, LITTLE FELLA.
NICE HOCKEY STICK.
WHAT THE HECK
IS GOING ON IN HERE?
AND ANOTHER LURE.
OH, NICE ONE.
AND YOU'RE GONNA PUT HIM BACK?
HE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT
IN THERE, BILL?
GOT HIS OWN, UH --
HIS OWN LITTLE, UH --
LITTLE KENNEL IN THERE.
HE WASN'T...IN NO DANGER
AT ALL. NO, NO.
ANYWAY,
BILL PUTS THE OTHER LURE,
TIES HER ON THERE.
A LOT OF HOOKS.
LOOK AT THE HOOKS ON THAT THING.
HOLY MACKEREL. THAT'S
A MAJOR, MAJOR THING THERE.
AND THEN HE'S, UH --
LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT,
LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT.
AND HE'S GONNA CAST THAT.
AND, OF COURSE,
WITH ALL THOSE HOOKS,
IT GETS KIND OF --
TANGLES WITHIN ITSELF.
AND NOW HE'S GOT TO...
OH, BOY.
HE'S GOT SOMETHING
JUST FOR THAT.
UH, IT'S A RUBBER GLOVE.
HE ALWAYS HAS
A RUBBER GLOVE HANDY
FOR ANY OF THE EVENTS
THAT WE HAVE AT THE LODGE.
AND ANYWAY,
HE'S GONNA CAST HER OUT.
AND JUST -- I'M GETTING
THE HECK OUT OF THE WAY,
AND GET BILL DOWN THE --
THAT'S IT.
GET BILL DOWN THE END THERE.
I HAVEN'T GOTTEN TO FISH YET,
AND I'VE BEEN THERE
FOR SOME TIME NOW.
MIND YOU, BILL'S GOT MY ROD.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
OH, WELL, I'LL LET HIM HAVE
ONE MORE CAST,
AND THEN I THINK --
OH, GEEZ, HE GOT MY TACK--
BILL, MY TACKLE BOX!
OH, G-- OH! OH!
I WANT MY TACKLE BOX BACK, BILL.
GET ME THE -- GET --
BRING IT BACK.
THERE WE GO.
LOOK OUT. OW! OW!
GEEZ!
WHAT THE HECK?
OH!
AAH!
OH.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AND YOU BROKE THE ROD.
WELL, WHAT A TREAT.
[ DOG WHIMPERING ]
SO, BILL, YOU JUST PACK --
LOOK. WATCH.
BE CAREFUL, NOW.
CAREFUL, NOW. CAREFUL.
OH, HE'S FINE, HE'S FINE,
HE'S FINE. YEAH.
YEAH. HAS HIS OWN TACKLE BOX
WITH A GUARD DOG.
THANK YOU, BILL,
FOR A GREAT DAY OF FISHING.
WELL, WE, UH, RIGGED UP
THE RACCOON TRAP.
PUT A BIG WEDGE OF CHEESE
IN THERE
AND STUCK HER UP IN THE ATTIC.
AND IN ABOUT FIVE MINUTES,
WE CAUGHT BUSTER HADFIELD'S ARM.
IT WAS STILL ATTACHED,
BUT THE CHEESE WAS GONE,
SO WE DROVE HIM OUT TO THE DUMP
AND LET HIM GO.
JUNIOR SINGLETON SAYS
THAT RACCOONS SLEEP ALL DAY,
WHICH IS GONNA MAKE THEM,
YOU KNOW, REAL HARD TO CATCH
AND ALSO MAKES THEM
POTENTIAL LODGE MEMBERS.
SO I GUESS WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
WAIT UNTIL MORNING.
ACTUALLY, UNCLE RED,
WE CAUGHT ONE ABOUT AN HOUR AGO.
YEAH, HE GOT ALL TANGLED UP
IN OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S TRUSS.
YOU KNOW,
WHEN HE WAS TRYING IT ON,
HE THOUGHT IT WAS JUST, LIKE,
HIS CONDITION ACTING UP.
BUT, BOY, WHEN THAT TAIL
POPPED OUT -- WA-A! --
THAT SCARED HIM.
SO EDDIE GRABBED IT
AND TOOK IT BACK TO THE KITCHEN.
OH, BOY. THAT'S GONNA MAKE
A PRETTY SCARY ROAST.
I MEAN, THE GRAVY --
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
HE'S GONNA MAKE IT INTO A PET.
YOU SEE, IT SEEMS
IT'S THE ONLY LIVING CREATURE
THAT ENJOYS
EDDIE'S COOKING.
HE'S ALSO GONNA MENTION
TONIGHT AT THE LODGE MEETING
MAYBE WE CAN TURN HIM INTO,
LIKE, THE LODGE MASCOT.
[ SCREECHING ]
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
COME ON.
WE GOT TO GO DOWNSTAIRS.
HURRY UP, EH?
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
THIS'LL JUST, UH, TAKE ME ABOUT
A MINUTE TO STRAIGHTEN OUT.
MAYBE WHAT WE'LL DO IS MAKE
THE RACCOON HEAD OF SECURITY
AND TURN NOEL
INTO THE LODGE PET.
[ SCREECHING CONTINUES ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
OKAY. EVERYONE GET A SEAT.
HURRY UP.
ALL RISE.
All:
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS, MORITATI.
SO, UH, HOW WE DOING WITH THIS,
UH, RACCOON PROBLEM, GUYS?
ALL RIGHT. FLOOR RECOGNIZES
BOB STUYVESANT.
WELL, RED, I-I THINK
THAT WE SHOULD PROBABLY
SEND THE RACCOON
BACK INTO THE WILD.
IT'S, UH, AGAINST THE LAW
TO DESTROY A RACCOON, OF COURSE,
UNLESS IT'S RABID.
NO!
UH, D-DON'T LET IT GO!
IT LIKES IT HERE!
WE'RE FRIENDS.
IT -- IT EATS MY COOKING.
WELL, IT SOUNDS RABID
TO ME.
BOB, GO DO
WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO.
NO!
YOU CAN'T KILL NEDDY!
NEDDY?
WE WERE GONNA BECOME A TEAM --
NEDDY AND EDDIE.
ANIMAL ACTS ARE VERY BIG.
IT'S NOT THAT KIND
OF LODGE, EDDIE.
WE WERE GONNA PLAY THE PALACE
IN LAS VEGAS, LIKE --
LIKE SIEGFRIED & ROY.
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT, RED.
OH, NO!
[ SOBS ]
NOEL,
WE HAVE A TRESPASSER.
YEAH. SURE.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
I THRIVE
ON THIS SORT OF THING.
NOEL...
YOU DON'T HAVE TO KILL
THE RACCOON, OKAY?
AS LONG AS YOU GET IT
OUT OF THE LODGE.
RIGHT.
I'LL DO THAT.
W-WELL, THIS IS
HEARTLESS AND CRUEL.
I HAVE NEVER ONCE
ASKED FOR A PET.
AND NOW -- AND NOW
I'VE GOT SOMETHING TO LOVE,
THAT'LL EAT MY COOKING,
AND YOU WANT TO TAKE IT AWAY
FROM ME!
[ RATTLING ]
WA-A-A!
WATCH YOURSELF THERE,
HAROLD.
THANK YOU.
WELL, YOU KNOW, EDDIE, UH,
RACCOONS CARRY
A NUMBER OF PARASITES
THAT ARE HARMFUL TO HUMANS.
OH, YOU SOUND
JUST LIKE MY MOTHER!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
[ SOBS ]
WHAT HAPPENED, NOEL?
HE JUMPED ME.
THE RACCOON JUMPED ME.
MUST HAVE BEEN BEHIND THE DOOR
OR SOMETHING.
WRESTLED THE GUN
OUT OF MY HANDS.
FIRED A WARNING SHOT
BETWEEN MY LEGS AND RAN OUT.
GOOD FOR YOU, NEDDY!
RUN!
BE FREE!
OH, IT WAS AWFUL.
HE HAD THIS MANIACAL LOOK
IN HIS EYE...
BETWEEN THAT
LITTLE MASK OF HIS.
WHEN HE RAN OFF,
HE WAS THINKING, I'M SURE,
"I GOT TO GET BACK
TO THE FOREST.
I NEED REAL FOOD."
BOY, I DON'T LIKE THE IDEA
OF A RACCOON
RUNNING WILD OUT THERE
WITH A LOADED GUN.
WOULD YOU RATHER HAVE NOEL
RUNNING AROUND WITH ONE?
NO.
GOOD POINT.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
NOW THAT'S OUT OF THE WAY, I --
I THINK WE'LL CALL ON EDDIE
TO GIVE US
THE EVENING'S ENTERTAINMENT.
AND -- AND GO EASY ON HIM.
HE'S HAD KIND OF A ROUGH DAY.
[ MURMURING ]
THIS IS JUST A LITTLE SOMETHING
THAT I WROTE FOR -- FOR NEDDY,
THE KINDEST FUR-COVERED THING
I HAVE EVER KNOWN.
YOU KNOW, UH, ONE OF THE REASONS
I KEEP COMING BACK TO THE LODGE
IS THE FAITH I HAVE
THAT, UH, NATURE'S COURSE
IS THE BEST COURSE.
THAT WAS PROVED AGAIN TONIGHT.
WHEN NATURE CALLS,
YOU'D BETTER LISTEN.
ANYWAY, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I-I JUST DIDN'T
HAVE THE HEART
TO GET YOU THAT RACCOON COAT.
UH, BESIDES,
THE ARMS WERE TOO SHORT,
AND THERE WAS FOUR OF THEM.
SO, UNTIL NEXT TIME,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
FOR YOU AND YOUR
WHOLE FAMILY
HEY!
YOU KNOW, I'D LIKE
TO MEET YOUR MOM
AS FOR YOU, HELMUT,
YOU'RE LOVELY AND BEAUTIFUL
AND HEY!
I LOOKED AROUND MY KITCHEN
AND WHAT DO YOU THINK
I FIND?
HEY!
YOU MIGHT BE GONE, BUT YOU
LEFT A LOT OF YOURSELF BEHIND
HEY!
OKAY, IF YOU COULD ALL, LIKE --
LIKE, DO THIS?
EVERYBODY, COME ON, NOW.
DO THE CLEANING PAW.
CLEAN YOUR PAWS.
AND HEY!
YOU KNOW
WHO'S ALL WASHED UP?