Here’s a great idea for anyone
who lives in a small house.
It's a little
something I call
my spacesaver table.
First thing you do is attach
one edge of the table
to the wall
with a piano hinge.
Now, you can take a hinge
right off a piano,
but be sure you tell
the pianist first
or somebody could
lose a finger.
Next thing you want to do
is remove all the table legs
with either a screwdriver
or a fat person
falling over it.
Then you replace the
front legs with these
toilet plungers
and mount them right
up through the table
as I've done here.
And just like my own legs,
they're not only decorative,
they're also
fully functional
as coasters...
and as snack bowls.
But here's the best part
when you finish dinner
and you need room to
square dance or
gut a moose,
you can easily get
the table out of the way.
And in keeping with my
bathroom plunger motif,
I'm using toilet paper holders
as my handles.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
All right.
Thank you very much.
Appreciate it.
Thank you.
Big, big week up
at the lodge this week.
Thanks to a wave
of unbelievable luck
and my ability
to negotiate,
I am now the proud owner
of the Possum Lake Motel.
It's not just by the bay,
it's by the hour.
Uncle Red?
Yeah.
Have you been
borrowing my CDs?
Uh, not lately,
the skeet thrower's broken.
No, 'cause Bonnie
and I are trying
to pick out music
for our wedding.
Oh yeah, well,
I would suggest
Send In The Clowns
and Who's Sorry Now.
Ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha!
You know, I heard when
people have nothing
interesting to say
they make stupid jokes.
Well, that's what
your parents did.
You know, Harold, if you
and Bonnie are looking
for a place to have
your honeymoon,
you might want
to take a look at this.
A quaint little spot
I like to call the
Possum Lake Motel.
I can get you
a corporate rate.
I know the owner.
You bought that dump?
I think the correct term
is congratulations.
Congratulations,
mister dump owner.
I bought the motel
for 800 bucks, Harold.
800 bucks for
the entire motel,
lock, stock
and towels.
All the towels,
nobody's ever taken one.
They can't, they're
stuck to the rack.
Why do you want
to buy a motel?
800 bucks for a motel!
I mean, the land value
alone's got to be
50 grand.
That's called
business savvy,
Harold.
Yes, yes.
But you didn't buy the land,
just the motel.
What?
Yup.
Excluding all lands.
And it says you got 24 hours
to get rid of the motel
because the land owners
are actually going to build
a new resort.
So instead of them having
to pay thousands of dollars
to have the motel torn down,
they got you to do it for free
and you paid them
800 dollars to do it.
Yeah, that's
business savvy.
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Today's winner
receives this coupon
for a large section
of charred countertop
from what was formerly
Crazy Bob's House
of Fireworks...
in what was formerly
downtown Port Asbestos.
All right, cover your
ears there, Glen.
Red, you got 30 seconds
to get Glen Braxton
to say this word...
All right, Winston.
And go!
Okay, Glen, what do you
call it when people workout?
Stupid.
Okay, no, no.
This is a term for sit-ups,
push-ups, jogging...
Death wish.
No, no, no, okay, no.
Glen, what do you do
in a fitness centre?
I don't know.
All right, all right
all right, okay...
What do people do to get
their cardiovascular
system pumping?
Oh, watch the
Playboy channel.
Okay, no, okay, okay.
This is something
your doctor told you.
He told you, you need
to get a little more...
Oh, well,
tell my wife that!
Almost outta
time here, Red.
Okay, okay.
Glen, when you were a kid
what did you do in gym class?
Oh, I snapped my towel
at the geeks,
There we go!
Welcome to
Talking Animals
with local animal control
officer, Ed Frid.
What do you got
in the trap here, Ed?
Oh, it's not a
trap, Red.
It's a
beekeeper's box.
Oh boy.
There's about a billion
bees in there.
Oh...
So what you got
to ask yourself
is why would anybody
want to keep bees?
Well, for the honey.
For the honey?
Yeah, it's not worth
getting killed over a
waffle topping, Red.
Okay, there's two ways
you can deal with bees safely.
One, is kill them all
and push them around
with a long-handled broom.
Or you can smoke 'em
with a smoker.
Oh yeah, oh yeah,
the bees settle right down
with one of these,
don't they?
Yeah,
this is good.
Or better still,
one of these.
Oh boy.
Oh yeah,
oh yeah.
[ RED COUGHING ]
Okay, look in the box
and see how docile
the bees are.
Oooh...
[ BEE BUZZING ]
Oh God, he got me.
Whoa!!
Whoa!
Red, you got to get
the stinger out!
Yeah, yeah, all right,
all right.
Good thing he got you
in someplace I don't
mind touching.
Hurry up and get
the stinger out.
Oooowwww!
You know,
back when I was a kid,
long family car trips
were never a problem
for one simple reason...
we were all
afraid of Dad.
But times have changed.
Parents today give their kids
respect and freedom
and constant support.
And man, are they
paying the price.
So this time,
on Handyman Corner,
I'm going to show you
how you can enjoy
a pleasant family car trip
without reverting back
to the pattern
of parental discipline
and behavioral standards
that were apparently
ruining all
of our lives.
Okay, the first step in
giving kids their own space
is to divide up the space
so you can still have yours.
I've cut this cardboard
template in the exact
shape of the gap
between the driver and
passenger compartment
in my minivan.
Now, this is just a template
for something stronger.
But don't use plywood
or cinderblock,
you want something
you can see through.
Kids can do bad things
very quietly.
I'm going to use
this plexiglass,
just need a little paint
remover to get the
words off there.
I told Abe nobody around
here would pay extra
for a handwash.
I left this
on for the kids.
Now to cut the same shape
out of plexiglass.
Plexiglass
splinters real easy
so I've got a fine saw.
Well, it's not real fine,
but it's fine,
and I cut slowly.
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
Well, there's two weeks of my
life I'll never get back.
Now, I just put the plexiglass
in place and hold it there,
using the handyman's
secret weapon.
So I'm going
to have a divider,
you know, like they have
in limos or police cars.
I guess the same rules
apply to rich people
as it does
to criminals.
Don't want to treat
anybody unfairly.
Boy, this doesn't fit
as well as I had hoped.
I'll just use
more duct tape.
Oh, no, no.
Wait a minute.
Okay, we're good.
Okay, the next step
is to soundproof
the passenger compartment.
That way, your kids can
listen to their own music
without you constantly
hearing words
that need to be
explained to you.
So how do we get
that soundproof
recording studio décor?
Look what I found
in my shed.
You know, I should probably
get my cholesterol checked.
Okay, let's give it a try.
[ AIR HORN BLASTS ]
[ NO AUDIO ]
Hope the kids don't think
I'm egging them on.
[ ROOSTER CROWS ]
Maybe I should have said that
in the soundproof area.
But we're not done yet.
You really don't want
other motorists to see
your kids' faces
and hand gestures.
It's been my experience
that motorcycle gangs
have virtually no sense
of humour.
So to avoid those
confrontations,
we're going to
tint the windows.
Here again, cost is
a consideration,
but if you've got
an old movie theatre
in your town,
go into the storage room
and you'll probably find
3-D glasses.
How about that, huh?
It's functional
and it looks...
functional.
Your first trip should be
to the 3-D movie at the
drive-in theatre.
That way the kids get
the full effect
and you won't
hear a thing.
So remember,
if the women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
Oh, I must have hit
the childproof lock button.
Harold?
Harold!!
Har --
[ NO AUDIO ]
You know, sometimes people
will come up and ask me
why I got
into television.
My answer's
always the same...
to foster understanding
between the sexes.
We always get a good chuckle
out of that one.
The truth is I got
into television
because I'm just
like television.
TV and I were born
around the same time
and with the same
lousy reception.
When TV and I were young,
we were both small,
we saw everything
in black and white
and we spent most of the day
sitting quietly in the corner.
But it wasn't long
before TV hit the cable age
and I hit middle age,
and that's when we
started to grow apart.
We both got wider,
but my viewpoint
got narrower.
The TV got less static,
I got more.
The only thing we had in
common was you could
press our buttons
without even getting
up off the couch.
Now Harold tells me
that pretty soon the TV
will also be the computer,
the stereo and the phone,
the hardest working thing
in the house.
Needless to say,
this is where TV
and I part company.
Remember,
I'm pulling for you.
We're all
in this together.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Sewage is a
pattern of numbers.
Number one,
then number two,
then... number's up.
You do the math.
Well, I got the
motel problem all
worked out.
[SHOUTING]
I'm trying to pick out
a song for our first dance
for the wedding!
You think, "Like A Virgin"
is too on the nose?
How about two minutes
of silence, Harold?
You can't start a wedding
with two minutes of sil --
I meant right now.
Okay.
Hey Red, Red, Red?
Yeah?
Now that you bought
the Possum Lake Motel,
what happened to the
video surveillance tapes?
Oh no, I've got them all,
they're Beta.
Oh, perfect, perfect.
Now, look,
if you find one, um,
from room four
on July 23, 1967,
I'd be very interested
in buying it.
Trying to destroy
the evidence?
No, no.
No, no, no.
I was hoping it might jog
Anne-Marie's memory.
Well, you're going
to have to hurry
because Uncle Red
has to tear down that motel
in the next 12 hours.
Well Harold,
I have a plan.
Oh no.
Oh yes I do, Harold.
Take a look at this.
You've got a houseboat,
you got a house.
What's the difference?
Huh, huh?
You get it?
Get it?
No...
No, we don't.
You turn the house over,
you've got a houseboat.
I turn the motel over,
what have I got?
Shag carpet
on the ceiling?
No, sir.
I have a cruise ship.
Wow!
All I got to do is flip
the motel into the lake.
The roof becomes the hull,
the floor becomes
the flat roof,
I slap a 9.9
on the back there
for some decent
gas mileage.
I turn a motel
into a boat-el.
It's going to be huge!
It's going to be
gigantic!
It's going
to be Titanic!
RED:
Winston had got a couple
of those model airplanes
that you wind up,
and sometimes it's hard to
open the packaging on them.
And Bill was
going to join them
but Bill thought it was
a kayaking day and...
you know, communications is
a big part of Bill's stupidity
but he has a more aggressive
approach to opening a package.
Oh, oh, oh...
Never work with a guy
wearing a helmet,
that's the rule there.
So Winston hands him
all the parts,
and he's going to take a
look at the instructions,
try to get it right
and everything,
and Bill's got the A.D.D.
kicking in so he's --
He's just kind of doing
what he was to do
and funny how, you know, it's
an idiot-idiot with Bill.
There, he's fine so Winston
hands him the second --
Same approach basically.
Bill is so talented
that he can actually
put the plane together
without all the parts
which I find...
Now, he's looking at Winston
and that's too much work
winding up that elastic
so he's thinking,
wait a second,
is there some way
that I can do
a bit of a
shortcut here?
He gets an idea, why doesn't he
take Winston's work
and kind of borrow it
for a minute
and he hands it
back to Winston.
You can keep winding,
Winston.
Meanwhile, Bill's plane
is ready to go
so he fires it up there.
And the thing with
those planes is
they set the tail
on a bit of an angle
so they'll do
a big circle around,
and Bill probably
should have thought that...
Oh!
And unfortunately, Winston,
in his pain jumped up and down
on Bill's
airplane and so...
and Witon had let his
plane go and it was
going in a circle
the other way,
and you know, you wanna --
the heck with it...
Oh!
And it kind of jammed
right in there.
My golly.
Whoa!
That's two minutes
for slashing, right there.
So now they've got no planes
so Bill's got an idea.
He's got the kayak and he's got
the paddles and he thinks,
"Wait a sec., maybe we can
take this up a notch."
And they had found a small
tricycle they're using
as the landing gear
And now they just need
an elastic --
Oh, there's your elastic,
kind of like a wet suit --
a rubber deal.
And he takes
that onto the prop.,
and then Bill hooks
her on to the --
oh, boy!
All right, I don't know
about this.
So Bill gets in,
and I'm thinking you know,
you still don't have
any wings do you?
No, there's no wings.
Bill, there's no wings.
Bill... no wings.
Oh no, you're good.
You're good.
Okay, all right.
So Winston's wind -- really
putting the tension on there
and getting her done...
Okay, he's going
to let her go,
but he had wound it
the wrong way
which was unfortunate.
You know, it's human nature
to remember things
as being better
than they were,
like say,
your dating years
or this old jukebox.
Oh sure, it was kind of neat
to see the arm swing over,
pick up the record
and then swing across
so that the machine
could play it
and then put it away
when it was done.
Something you could never get
your kids to do.
But the problem was that all
the records everybody liked
got played to much
they got all scratchy.
The only ones that
sounded good were like,
The Hanky Panky
by Jim Nabors.
So what do you do when
an old entertainment centre
stops being entertaining?
You do what Jim Nabors
couldn't do,
you modernize.
All it takes is
a little imagination
and a B.B. gun,
and I can change this unit
from a jukebox into
a video game.
Actually, you can change
a lot of things
with imagination
and a B.B. gun,
like, where you'll be living
for the next six months.
Okay, let's see...
Elvis, The Beatles,
Barry Manilow.
Number one
with a bullet.
The bridge and groom
will now have the
first dance.
How did it go?
Did you manage to turn
that flea-bitten motel
of yours
into a cruise ship?
Uhh, pretty much, yeah.
So did you pick out
the songs for your wedding?
Oh yeah, pretty much.
You know,
I was hoping maybe
for a suggestion
maybe something like The Wreck
of the Edmund Fitzgerald?
Well, that's an
odd choice,
isn't it?
Yeah, I just grabbed it
out of the air, you know.
Yeah, you must have,
yeah.
So no problems
at all,
you know like nothing broke,
no personal injuries,
no massive
property damage
due to something happening
you hadn't anticipated
like, say... gravity?
No, no, no,
it went great.
Oh good.
So I can
go see it, then?
No, no, she's out
on sea trials now
and you know,
a test run.
You know, 'cause Bonnie
and I are really interested
in booking a honeymoon
aboard the ship.
Okay, well, okay.
Cruise ships are
really for an older
crowd, you know,
and I think the Boat-el
cruise ship is very nice,
but I think
you and Bonnie
might enjoy something
a little more exciting.
Like living?
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Meeting time,
Uncle Red.
Yeah, you go ahead.
I'll be down in a minute.
Okay, but everything
went well, though?
It went as well
as could be expected.
I'm sorry.
If my wife is watching,
I'll be coming straight home
after the meeting.
I learned a lot today.
Okay, maybe
I lost 800 bucks,
but when you flip over
a seedy motel
and you see the stuff
that falls out of that thing,
sure makes you feel a lot
better about your
relationship.
I'm glad the batteries
were all dead.
And to the rest of you,
thanks for watching
and on behalf of
myself and Harold
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge,
keep your
stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Guys, come on in,
everybody.
Everybody seated.
C'mon guys, sit down.
Everybody
sit down please.
All rise.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
RED: Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the man's prayer.
I'm a man,
but I can change,
if I have to...
I guess.
Okay men, good news.
I have a bunch of used beds,
bathtubs, sinks and toilets
at a very
reasonable price.
If you want to see them,
with the breeze and current,
they should wash onshore
around nine o'clock tomorrow.