IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE MAN WHO SAID
NO MAN'S AN ISLAND
IF HE HAS A BOAT...
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
(Applause and cheering)
HUH? HUH?
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
WELL, BIG NEWS THIS WEEK.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HEARD.
MOOSE THOMPSON'S
SELLING HIS HOUSE.
MOVING?
THAT'S USUALLY A CONDITION
WHEN YOU SELL YOUR HOUSE.
YEAH, MOOSE SAYS
HE NEEDS MORE SPACE,
APPARENTLY.
HE'S NOT MARRIED,
HE DOESN'T HAVE KIDS.
WHY DOES
HE NEED SPACE?
MAYBE HE'S GOING UP
ANOTHER PANTS SIZE.
MOOSE BETTER BE CAREFUL.
REAL ESTATE TRANSACTIONS
CAN BE COMPLICATED.
NOTHING AGAINST MOOSE, BUT
HE'S NOT THE SHARPEST KNIFE
IN THE DRAWER.
HE SHOULD GET HIMSELF
A REALLY GOOD
REAL ESTATE AGENT.
HE'S HIRED THE BEST AGENT
IN POSSUM LAKE.
WAHHHH! WHO?
(Audience laughing)
OH, YIKES.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MAIN MESSAGE BEING,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
HAVE YOU GOT AN AD
IN THE PAPER?
I'M WAY AHEAD OF YOU.
LOOKIT, CIRCLED 'ER
RIGHT THERE.
"HOUSE FOR SALE --
CALL RED GREEN."
(Audience laughing)
THAT'S IT?
YEAH.
A LITTLE VAGUE, ISN'T IT?
MIGHT WANT TO BE
DESCRIBE HOW IT LOOKS.
I DIDN'T WANT TO SCARE PEOPLE.
BESIDES, ANOTHER LINE
COST ANOTHER DOLLAR.
HOW MUCH ARE YOU CHARGING MOOSE
FOR THIS
PSEUDO-SEMI-PROFESSIONAL
SERVICE OF YOURS?
THE STANDARD RATE, HAROLD --
THE 6% COMMISSION.
IT'S THE EASIEST MONEY
YOU CAN MAKE.
THINK ABOUT THIS, OK?
I FIND A BUYER,
SELL THE HOUSE IN AN HOUR.
IT'S A $100,000 HOME
SO YOU MAKE SIX GRAND.
YOU WORK AN EIGHT-HOUR DAY...
THAT'S ALMOST $50,000.
THAT'S $250,000 A WEEK,
$1 MILLION A MONTH...
THAT'S $12 MILLION A YEAR
YOU'RE LOOKIN' AT, HAROLD!
YEAH, RIGHT, YOU'RE GONNA WORK
AN EIGHT-HOUR DAY.
(Audience laughing)
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
(Red): LATER ON, WE GOT
THE ADVENTURE WITH BILL.
WHAT ARE WE DOING, HAROLD?
HAROLD?
AH, IT'S PING-PONG!
YOU LOOKING FOR HAROLD?
THERE HE IS.
THE BOYS SET UP
THE PING-PONG TABLE.
HAROLD'S GOTTEN IT SET UP,
LEVEL AND EVERYTHING.
BILL'S GOT THE NET --
KEEPS IT IN HIS PANTS.
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU?
CATCHIN' ANY?
GOTTA THROW
THE SMALL ONES BACK, BILL.
THAT'S A BIT OF A NET...
MORE OF A COD NET, I THINK.
OOH! OOH! BY GOLLY!
YOU GOT ONE, HUH?
THEY BITING? THEY BITING?
(Laughing)
ALL RIGHT, HE'S GOT--
THAT MAY BE A LITTLE...
TOO MUCH "A NET"...
YOU KNOW, AS FRANKIE AVALON
USED TO SAY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU HAVE A PLAN?
HE
HAS A PLAN?
OH, THAT'S VERY RELAXING.
WHAT ARE WE DOING, BILL?
ANOTHER PING-PONG TABLE?
HOW MANY PING-PONG TABLES
DID YOU BRING?
RATHER THAN SHORTEN THE NET,
THEY'RE GONNA WIDEN THE TABLE.
THAT'S THE KIND OF THINKING
THAT GOT THEM WHERE THEY ARE...
OUT BEHIND THE LODGE.
START 'ER UP, BOYS!
THE COMPETITION IS-- HAROLD'S
GOT THE GOOD STUFF TODAY.
TAKE A POINT -- ONE-NOTHING.
OK, BILL,
I'D SAY MORE DEFENCE.
THERE WE GO -- THAT'S IT!
ONE MORE -- THERE WE ARE.
STAY TUNED.
OHHHHH
MY FAVOURITE TOOL
IS THE ADJUSTABLE WRENCH
IT'S ALWAYS
CLOSE AT HAND
MIND YOU, SCREWDRIVERS
AND CHISELS ARE OK, TOO
BUT THEY HURT A LOT MORE
WHEN YOU SIT ON 'EM
THIS IS THE BIG ONE!
FOR OUR GRAND PRIZE,
A BAG OF RAD-HOSES
FROM JULIO'S STEAM-ROOM
AND ENGINE FLUSH,
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET DOUGIE FRANKLIN
TO SAY THIS WORD.
"LOVE".
(Laughing)
AND GO!
DOUGIE, WHEN A MAN
MEETS A WOMAN,
AND THAT STARTS AN ATTRACTION
WHICH DEVELOPS INTO
AN AFFECTION AND THEN COMES...
... ANTIBIOTICS.
(Audience laughing)
I'M SORRY, RED,
DID YOU SAY "INFECTION"?
NO, NO, NO,
"AFFECTION".
I'M SORRY -- START OVER.
ALL RIGHT, WHEN A MAN
AND WOMAN FEEL STRONGLY
ABOUT EACH OTHER,
THEY FALL IN...
... BED.
NO, NO, BEFORE THAT.
UH... THE
BACK SEAT?
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE FEELING.
... OF TOUCHING... GROPING...
SMACKING THE HAND.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE EMOTION:
THIS IS THE PERSON FOR YOU.
OH, THAT'S DESPERATION.
NO, NO.
NO?
A MAN AND WOMAN GET MARRIED
AND HAVE KIDS.
THEY'RE DEEPLY
IN...
... DEBT.
NO, NO, WHEN A MAN AND WOMAN
STAY TOGETHER,
IT'S BECAUSE THEY'RE IN...
... A RUT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU CAN'T GUESS THIS WORD!
WELL, RED, NO WOMAN
HAS EVER MADE ME SAY IT,
AND EVEN THOUGH
YOU'RE MIGHTY GOOD-LOOKIN',
NEITHER WILL YOU!
(Laughing and applause)
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
WE'RE GONNA COMBINE TWO THINGS
THAT ALL MEN LOVE --
GASOLINE ENGINES
AND HITTING THINGS.
WE'RE GONNA BUILD
OUR VERY OWN BATTING CAGE.
GOTTA LOVE A BATTING CAGE...
ALL THE FUN OF BASEBALL
WITH NONE OF
THAT DARN RUNNING-AROUND.
WHAT DO WE NEED?
WE NEED SOMETHING
TO THROW THE BALLS AT US,
SO I'M THINKIN'... LAWN MOWER.
I'VE SEEN SOME ROCKS
COME OUT OF THIS BABY
THAT ANY MAN WOULD LOVE TO TAKE
INTO THE UPPER DECK.
ALL I GOTTA DO IS
MODIFY THIS PUPPY
TO CHUCK BASEBALLS.
I WANT TO DULL THE BLADES
ON THIS UNIT
BECAUSE WE ARE BUILDING
A BATTING CAGE,
NOT A CUISINART.
YOU COULD FILE THE EDGES
OR GRIND 'EM DOWN,
BUT I PREFER TO RUN OVER
SOME TIRE IRONS.
WHOA! THAT SOUNDED GOOD.
AHHH!
OH, BY GOLLY!
YEAH, OH, THAT'S TERRIFIC.
WAIT A MINUTE --
THAT'S NOT MY LAWN MOWER.
WELL, IT IS NOW, I GUESS.
YOU WANT TO HAVE THE BASEBALLS
COME OUT THIS HOLE.
YOU GOTTA SEAL THE BOTTOM
OF THE LAWN MOWER.
I SUGGEST YOU GRAB
THAT CHUNK OF KITCHEN COUNTER
FROM WHEN YOU PUT THE SINK IN.
THIS IS A GREAT OPPORTUNITY
TO TELL YOUR WIFE
HOW SMART YOU WERE
TO HANG ON TO IT.
SOMETHING YOU GOTTA BE
AWARE OF.
THE END OF THAT BLADE
WILL BE TRAVELLING
IN EXCESS OF 100 MILES AN HOUR,
SO REALLY SOCK
THE DUCT TAPE TO 'ER.
YOU KNOW ME -- SAFETY FORCED.
AS WITH MOST THINGS IN NATURE,
YOU HAVE AN INPUT
AND AN OUTPUT.
ON THIS UNIT, ALL I HAVE
IS THE OUTPUT,
FOR THE BALLS TO COME OUT.
WHAT I NEED IS AN INPUT,
A HOLE ON THE OTHER SIDE
FOR THE BALLS TO GO IN.
BEAUTY.
HERE'S AN EXTRA
ADDED FEATURE...
AUTOMATIC BALL RETURN,
SO YOU'RE NOT GRABBING BALLS
OUT OF SOUP BOWLS
AND EYE-SOCKETS.
I'VE ADDED THIS SHEET
ONTO THE GRASS-CATCHER
SO WHEN THE BALL GOES IN,
SHE FILTERS INTO
THE GRASS-CATCHER,
INTO THE INPUT,
AND BECOMES MY NEXT PITCH.
ALL RIGHT, JUST START 'ER UP.
(Grunting)
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
PLAY BALL!
(Glass breaking)
I'LL SLOW 'ER DOWN TO "MULCH".
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
HEY, PITCHER, COME ON!
OH, MAN!
THAT'S OUT OF HERE!
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
WANT TO TALK ABOUT SOMETHING
ALL OF US ARE LOOKING FOR
AS WE GO DOWN
THE HIGHWAY OF LIFE...
A HALF-DECENT PARKING SPOT.
I CALL IT "THE SEVEN STAGES
OF PARKING".
STAGE ONE, YOU'RE A KID.
ALL YOU HAVE TO PARK
IS YOUR BUTT.
THEN YOU HIT STAGE TWO --
YOU'RE A TEENAGER.
YOU'RE PARKING WITH A GIRL
WHO HAS A GOOD CHANCE
OF BEING YOUR FUTURE WIFE...
FOLLOWED BY STAGE THREE --
YOU'RE MARRIED WITH KIDS.
NOW YOU'RE PARKING
AT McDONALD'S...
THE ONE WITH THE PLAY AREA.
THEN WE HAVE STAGE FOUR --
KIDS ARE GROWN,
AND THEY'RE WORKING...
COINCIDENTALLY, AT McDONALD'S.
SO YOU'VE NOW GOT YOURSELF
A SPORTS CAR
AND YOU'RE CAUGHT PARKING
WITH A GIRL WHO HAS NO CHANCE
OF BEING YOUR FUTURE WIFE.
THIS LEADS IMMEDIATELY
TO STAGE FIVE --
NOW YOU'RE PARKING
IN THE GARAGE,
WHERE YOU'RE ALSO LIVING.
NOW COMES STAGE SIX --
YOU'RE OLD.
NO LICENCE, NO CAR,
NO PARKING SPOT.
THEN WE HAVE STAGE SEVEN...
YOU'RE PARKED.
(Audience laughing)
I'M TALKING PERMANENTLY.
YOU GOT YOUR OWN PARKING SPOT.
EVEN HAS YOUR NAME OVER IT.
SO THE LESSON HERE IS,
LIFE IS SHORT, ALL RIGHT?
GRAB YOUR SHIFTER,
MOVE IT OUT OF "PARK",
AND THROW IT INTO GEAR!
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YA.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause)
DID YOU GET A PICTURE
OF MOOSE'S HOUSE?
I WANT TO PUT IT
IN TOMORROW'S PAPER.
YEAH, SORT OF --
THIS IS
JUST THE FIRST ROLL.
I'M TESTING THE LENS,
THE APERTURE...
IT'S WHAT WE PHOTOGRAPHERS CALL
A TEST ROLL.
THIS IS 24 PICTURES
OF YOUR NOSE.
I GUESS THE LENS MUST BE
ON THE BACK ON THIS MODEL.
IT TOOK ME
A WHILE
BUT I GOT THE RIGHT ANGLE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET THOSE
45-GALLON DRUMS OF AXLE GREASE
AND THE THREE FRIDGES
ON HIS PORCH.
NO, THOSE AREN'T
REAL SELLING POINTS.
I ASKED MOOSE TO TAKE HIS
UNDERWEAR OFF THE CLOTHES-LINE.
THAT'S UNDERWEAR ON THERE?
I THOUGHT HE'D BOUGHT
A SAILBOAT.
(Siren)
POSSUM 911 -- STATE YOUR
CARD MEMBERSHIP NUMBER, PLEASE!
UH, 8-9, UH, 2-3-4.
OH, HI, TIMMY.
WHO THE HECK'S THAT?
MY FRIEND, TIMMY.
HOW DID ONE OF YOUR NERD
DORK-BALL FRIENDS
GET TO BE A MEMBER
OF POSSUM LODGE?
HE PAID
ALL HIS DUES.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
HOW CAN WE HELP YOU?
I'M STUCK IN A NEBULA ZONE.
MY SECTOR CHARGE IS AT 30%.
THE GALAXY BOMBERS ARE BLOCKING
ALL THE TELEPORTS
AND MY CRYSTAL'S ON SHORT-LIFE.
AW, COOL!
HE'S PLAYING
MY FAVOURITE
VIDEO GAME,
"GALAMAXIA."
DOESN'T SOUND LIKE A PROBLEM
WE HAVE A LOT OF
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE.
WHAT LEVEL
ARE YOU ON?
LEVEL 42-- OHHHH! HE JUST
PHASED MY NOVA FORCE.
AW, LEVEL 42!
WAHHAHHH!
HOW LONG
YOU BEEN PLAYING?
I STARTED TWO DAYS AGO --
I HAVEN'T STOPPED.
YOU EVER HEARD OF GIRLS, TIM?
DEATH TO YOU AND YOUR HAIRY
GORP-SUCKING SCUM ROCKETS!
HE'S TALKING
ABOUT THE GAME.
ONLY ONE SUPER-CHARGER LEFT,
AND I'LL HAVE ALL THE PIECES
TO THE ORACLE.
AW, YOU'RE
DOING GREAT.
YOU DON'T
NEED HELP.
I DO -- I'VE BEEN PLAYING
FOR TWO DAYS
AND I DON'T KNOW HOW TO PAUSE
AND I HAVE TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
TO PAUSE IT,
JUST PRESS "DELETE"--
OHHHHH!
NEVER MIND... TOO LATE.
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
TOO LATE FOR THE GAME, RIGHT?
YEAH, MY NEUTRO PACK WAS
AT THE DANGER LEVEL.
MY POWER CANNISTER
COULDN'T TAKE THE PRESSURE.
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
THE GAME, RIGHT?
IT'S... "MALE CALL"!
(Laughing)
THAT REALLY HURTS!
OK, OUR FIRST LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS...
UH... "DEAR RED,
"MY HUSBAND WHISTLES
ALL THE TIME, ON PURPOSE.
"HE CERTAINLY ENJOYS IT
BUT NOBODY ELSE DOES.
"I'VE EVEN NOTICED BIRDS
LAUGHING AT HIM.
"HOW CAN I GET HIM TO DESIST?
"IS THERE A POLITE WAY OF
SAYING, 'DEAR, STOP WHISTLING
"'OR I'LL HAVE TO STAPLE
YOUR LIPS TO YOUR EYEBROWS'?
"SIGNED,
ACHY-BREAKY EARS."
THIS IS A REAL ODDBALL ONE,
YOU KNOW,
'CAUSE WHISTLING'S USUALLY
A SIGN OF HAPPINESS.
BUT HE'S MAKING HER UNHAPPY.
YOU CAN'T MAKE YOURSELF HAPPY
IF YOU'RE MAKING
SOMEONE ELSE UNHAPPY.
YOU MANAGE TO DO IT
ON A REGULAR BASIS.
STOP A GUY FROM WHISTLING...
WELL, MAYBE CHANGE HIS DIET.
ONCE YOU STUFF HIS FACE
FULL OF CRACKERS,
THAT MIGHT SLOW HIM DOWN.
REMEMBER UNCLE JACK?
HIS NOSE WHISTLED.
HOW DID HE EVER STOP?
HE STARTED WEARING ONE OF THOSE
THINGS THAT SWIMMERS WEAR.
YEAH, A BIKINI.
(Audience laughing)
IT WORKED BUT COST HIM HIS JOB
AT THE POST OFFICE.
I'M THINKING IF YOU CAN'T STOP
THIS GUY FROM WHISTLING,
MAYBE SPEND TIME
AWAY FROM EACH OTHER.
MAYBE SEND YOUR HUSBAND
ON A HOLIDAY BY HIMSELF.
YEAH, WHISTLE HIM OFF
TO WHISTLER!
(Giggling)
HE COULD VISIT HIS MOTHER --
"WHISTLER'S MOTHER"!
(Laughing)
I SAID "WHISTLER'S MOTHER"
'CAUSE THAT'S WHERE...
HE COULD GO.
(Audience laughing)
WELL, ULTIMATELY, I THINK,
IF YOU CAN'T GET HIM
TO GO YOUR WAY, MAYBE YOU
GOTTA CHANGE YOUR ATTITUDE.
THINK ABOUT IT THIS WAY.
AS LONG AS HE'S WHISTLING, HE'S
NOT SMOKING, DRINKING, EATING,
AND YOU KNOW WHERE HE IS.
MAYBE THIS LADY'S BEHAVIOUR
IS THE PROBLEM.
MAYBE SHE'S GIVING HIM
TOO MUCH TO WHISTLE ABOUT.
(Laughing)
(Giggling)
NOT JUST WHISTLING DIXIE THERE!
CAN YOU WHISTLE THAT THEME
TO "ANDY OF MAYBERRY"?
NO, BUT I CAN WHISTLE
THIS ORANGE OFF YOUR FOREHEAD.
(Audience laughing)
(Red): MEANWHILE,
BACK AT THE-- OOOH!
OH, BOY! YOU ALL RIGHT, HAROLD?
SUCK IT UP -- THERE YOU GO.
YOU'RE FINE, YOU'RE FINE.
YOU'RE FINE -- YOU ALL RIGHT?
THEY'RE PLAYING PING-PONG,
AND, OH, BOY, CRAFTY TRICKS!
OH, GOLLY!
MAYBE TOO MUCH GREASE
ON THE HAIR, HAROLD?
THAT MAKES IT HARDER, EH?
BILL'S RACKING UP POINTS.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO HIT ONE
AT SOME POINT, HAROLD...
OH, THERE WE GO.
HIT YOUR OWN RACQUET, EH?
IT IS NOW -- OH, IT'S HANDBALL!
LOOK, HAROLD'S WINNING, 20-19.
ONE MORE POINT, HAROLD!
COME ON, SUCK IT UP, HAROLD.
I DIDN'T MEAN LITERALLY!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHOSE POINT IS THAT?
HOW DOES THAT WORK?
I THINK THE BALL
HAS TO TOUCH THE GROUND.
THAT MAY TAKE ANOTHER WEEK.
OH... UH, HAROLD,
ARE YOU ALL--
BILL, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO JUST GET OVER--
GO THAT WAY, GO THAT WAY.
THIS WAY, THIS WAY.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S GOOD-- NO, NO,
IT'S NOT DOWN THERE YET.
IT'S STILL UP IN HIS THROAT.
HERE WE GO -- DO WHAT YOU CAN.
THIS IS THE-- OHHHH!
OH, THE HEIM-PONG MANOEUVRE.
OH, BY GOLLY.
IS THAT EVER DISGUSTING
TO WATCH.
BY GOLLY-- OHHH!
OH, MY GOSH!
OHHH!
TAKE IT EASY --
THAT'S OUR LAST BALL.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
OH, BOY, THAT'S GOTTA GET 'ER.
YOU ALL RIGHT, HAROLD?
BALL COME OUT YET?
ALL RIGHT, ONE MORE COAT.
THAT OUGHT TO GET 'ER.
OH, BOY!
YEAH, YEAH, HERE, BILL.
YOU KNOW WHAT TO TRY? EXACTLY.
THERE WE GO!
HEY, THAT'S HAROLD'S POINT!
THAT'S YOUR GAME, HAROLD!
THAT'S YOUR GAME!
OH, MAN! HE'S A NATURAL,
ISN'T HE?
ADD YOUR OWN NOUN.
HERE'S A PUPPET OF ME
FROM A VIEWER IN NEW HAMPSHIRE.
HAROLD HAD A HAND IN THIS.
YOU ARE SURE POPULAR!
PHONE HASN'T STOPPED RINGING
ALL AFTERNOON!
MOOSE THOMPSON CALLED.
WHEN?
WHAT DID HE WANT?
10:30 -- "HAVE YOU SOLD
MY HOUSE YET?"
10:55 -- "HAVE YOU
SOLD MY HOUSE YET?"
11:15 -- "ANY OFFERS?"
11:20 -- "SO WHAT GOES?"
11:25 -- "SOLD MY HOUSE YET?"
11:45 -- "DO I STILL HAVE
A HOUSE OR WHAT?"
ALL RIGHT, I GET THE IDEA.
MOOSE THOMPSON'S
A PAIN IN THE NECK.
HE'S ONLY HAD HIS HOUSE
ON THE MARKET ONE DAY
AND HE'S PRESSURING ME BECAUSE
HE'S BOUGHT A NEW PLACE.
YOU BETTER SELL HIS PLACE.
YOU HAD AN OPEN HOUSE?
I HAD THE HOUSE OPEN
BUT NOBODY WOULD GO IN.
I THINK AN ONSHORE BREEZE
WOULD HAVE HELPED.
BUSTER HADFIELD WAS INTERESTED,
BUT WAS CONCERNED ABOUT
UREA FORMALDEHYDE IN THE WALLS.
I SAID, "NO, WHAT YOU SEE
IS DAYLIGHT."
YOU KNOW WHAT, THEN?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD FIX IT UP.
WAY AHEAD
OF YOU, HAROLD.
WE GOT IT
ALL PLANNED.
SOME PAINT, WALLPAPER,
CEILING JOISTS,
SOME I-BEAM, SUPPORTING WALL,
SOME ELECTRICITY...
WHAT WE REAL ESTATE PROS
CALL "T.L.C."
T.L.C. --
TORCH IT... LEVEL IT...
AND CART IT AWAY.
(Audience laughing)
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION,
WHERE WE EXPLORE
THOSE THREE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO DIFFICULT TO SAY...
(Audience):
"I DON'T KNOW!"
SO TRUE.
JOINING MY UNCLE RED
ON THE EXPERT PORTION
IS MY UNCLE RED, NATCH,
AND HIS BEST FRIEND,
DALTON HUMPHREY!
(Applause and cheering)
ALL RIGHT.
OUR VIEWER ASKS...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"SOMETIMES, WHEN MY HUSBAND
GOES OUT,
"I'LL ASK HIM TO PICK SOMETHING
UP FOR ME THAT I NEED.
"HE ALWAYS FORGETS --
WHY IS THAT?"
WELL, MAYBE HE'S GOT
ONE OF THOSE
EXTREMELY RELIABLE AND ACCURATE
ONE-ITEM MEMORIES.
YOU'VE MADE THE MISTAKE
OF GIVING HIM ITEM NUMBER TWO.
OR IT COULD BE THAT
THE ITEM IN QUESTION IS OF
A HIGHLY EMBARRASSING NATURE.
(Audience laughing)
LIKE WHAT? WHAT'S
AN EMBARRASSING NATURE?
WELL, SEE, UH,
SOMETHING THAT'S, UH,
OF A SO HIGHLY PERSONAL NATURE
THAT IT'S, UH...
BEST LEFT UNSPOKEN.
MAN, YOU GOT ME CURIOUS NOW.
WELL, ALL RIGHT, RED, OK!
ALL RIGHT,
I'M TALKING ABOUT, UM...
... A RECIPE MAGAZINE
OR A COMB.
(Audience laughing)
A COMB IS EMBARRASSING?
HOW DO YOU COMB YOURSELF,
DALTON?
LOOK, MAYBE IT'S NOT
EMBARRASSING ON THE SURFACE,
BUT IF THAT'S ALL
YOU'RE BUYING...
PEOPLE START
TO LOOK AT YOU FUNNY, YOU KNOW?
THEY THINK YOU'VE BEEN SENT
FOR SOMETHING PERSONAL
AND YOU CHICKENED OUT AND
BOUGHT A MAGAZINE OR A COMB!
YOU KNOW?
SO YOU'RE STANDING
IN THE CHECK-OUT LINE...
SWEAT'S POURING DOWN YOUR FACE
'CAUSE YOU KNOW EVERYBODY
IN THE STORE IS SMIRKING
AND TRYING TO IMAGINE WHAT
PERSONAL THING YOU GOT SENT FOR
THAT YOU DIDN'T HAVE
THE GUTS TO BUY!
(Audience laughing)
YOU MEAN LIKE PANTYHOSE?
OHHHH!
FOR HEAVEN'S SAKES, HAROLD!
HAVE YOU
NO SHAME?
OK, DALTON, BUT WHAT IF
YOU WENT FOR MILK?
OH, SURE, SURE!
ON YOUR WAY TO THE COOLER,
YOU HAVE TO GO PAST THAT RACK
FULL OF FILTHY MAGAZINES!
YEAH, THAT'S TRUE...
(Audience laughing)
... I WOULD IMAGINE.
BUT WHAT IF YOU WERE JUST
MAILING A LETTER?
OHHHH...
A LETTER.
YOU KNOW THE KIND OF SLEAZY
REPUTATION A LETTER HAS,
ESPECIALLY IF THAT LETTER
HAPPENS TO BE OF
PARTICULARLY EUROPEAN --
DARE I SAY FRENCH? --
PERSUASION.
(Audience laughing)
YOU ARE REALLY STEPPING
OFF THE DOCK ON THIS ONE.
BOY, OH, BOY,
MR. HUMPHREY!
WITH THAT ATTITUDE, YOUR WIFE
CAN'T SEND YOU FOR ANYTHING!
BINGO.
(Laughing)
OHHHHH!
(Applause)
I TELL YA, THERE IS NO FIGURING
SOME PEOPLE.
SO, THE
RENOVATION
OF MOOSE THOMPSON'S HOUSE
GO PER USUAL?
IT WAS A DISASTER.
THAT'S A "YES".
(Laughing)
I TOLD MOOSE,
"LET'S TAKE OUT THE ONE WALL."
THEY ALL COME DOWN.
THEY MUST HAVE BEEN CONNECTED.
THEY SURE DIDN'T LOOK IT.
NOW MOOSE HAS NO HOME AT ALL.
IT'S MORE OF A BASEMENT
WITH A ROOF ON IT.
IT WILL NEVER
SELL NOW.
OH, REALLY, HUH?
SOLD WITHIN THE HOUR, HAROLD.
APPARENTLY, THE LOT
WAS WORTH MORE
WITHOUT MOOSE'S HOUSE ON IT.
SAVES THE NEW OWNER
HAVING TO RENT A BULLDOZER.
SO IS THAT
A FAT COMMISSION CHEQUE
IN YOUR SHIRT?
NO.
NOTHING.
(Audience laughing)
JUNIOR SINGLETON
BOUGHT THE PLACE
SO IT WAS A NO-CASH DEAL.
GAVE HALF A SCHOOL BUS
AS A DOWN-PAYMENT
AND PAYS A "K"-CAR A MONTH
FOR FIVE YEARS.
SO MY COMMISSION WAS
A BROKEN SNOWMOBILE AND A GOAT.
THE GOAT ATE THE SNOWMOBILE
AND DROPPED DEAD.
(Laughing)
SO YOUR COMMISSION'S
OUT OF COMMISSION.
(Giggling)
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
AWAY YOU GO, HAROLD... GO NOW.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M GONNA GET OUT
OF THE REAL ESTATE BUSINESS.
ANYBODY WHO LOOKS LIKE I DO
AND THINKS LIKE I DO
WON'T GET MANY OFFERS.
IF YOU GIVE ME ONE, I THINK
WE CAN CLOSE THAT DEAL TONIGHT.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): ALL RIGHT!
STAND UP! STAND UP!
I DIDN'T SAY "SIMON SAYS".
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN, GUYS.
(Harold): THE LOCAL PIZZERIA
WILL NO LONGER HONOUR
THE 30-MINUTES-OR-FREE
IF YOU'RE PHONING
FROM MOBILE HOMES.