MOST MEN AND WOMEN
ARE IMPULSE BUYERS,
BUT THERE'S A
DIFFERENCE.
A WOMEN WILL ADMIT
SHE BOUGHT ON IMPULSE,
WHEREAS A MAN WILL
PRETEND HE RESEARCHED
THE WHOLE THING
FOR SIX MONTHS,
COMPARED ALL THE
DIFFERENT MAKES
AND THEN FINALLY JUST
COULDN'T RESIST
THIS PRICE.
AND WHEN IT TURNS
OUT TO BE A MISTAKE,
A WOMAN WILL JUST TAKE
IT BACK OR GIVE IT
TO A FRIEND OR
JUST THROW IT AWAY
AND THAT'S THE END OF IT.
BUT A MAN WILL
TRY TO COVER.
HE'LL ADAPT IT OR
HE'LL SAY IT WAS
FOR THE GARAGE
OR HE'LL BUY SOMETHING
ELSE TO STICK ON IT
OR HE'LL START USING
IT FOR SOMETHING
IT WASN'T EVER
INTENDED TO DO.
OF COURSE THEN IT
BREAKS AND IT
GETS ADDED
TO THAT PILE OF JUNK
HE'S GOT OUT IN
THE BACKYARD,
WHICH ONLY SERVES TO
HIGHLIGHT THE STUPIDITY
OF THE INITIAL PURCHASE.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT
BUT IT'S ONE OF
THE THINGS THAT
MAKES US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
I'LL TELL YOU, IF
YOU LIKE CONVEYERS BELTS,
YOU'RE GOING TO
LOVE TODAY'S SHOW.
PLUS WE GOT DOUGIE
FRANKLIN HERE
GIVING US ALL
KINDS OF ADVICE
ON NOTHING OF VALUE.
I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU THE WRONG WAY
TO MAKE AN ENTRANCE.
AND I GET TO GIVE
BILL THE RUNAROUND.
AND NOW HERE IS THE
MAN THAT TIME TRIED
TO FORGET
BUT HE EVENTUALLY
JUST IGNORED, MY
UNCLE RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU.
THAT'S VERY NICE.
I FEEL THAT I
KNOW YOU ALL NOW,
SO I WOULD LIKE TO
SHARE A FAMILY EMBARRASSMENT,
MY NEPHEW, HAROLD.
BIG WEEK UP AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK,
BUSTER HADFIELD'S
BROTHER,
WHO HAS HAD AN ONGOING
STRUGGLE TO FIND GAINFUL
EMPLOYMENT,
HEADED OUT WEST
'CAUSE HE HEARD
THERE WAS A BIG OIL
BOOM GOING ON OUT THERE.
JUST WHEN, NOW?
THE OIL BOOM HAS BEEN
OVER FOR 10 YEARS, HE
JUST WENT NOW?
NO, NO, HE WENT
12 YEARS AGO, HE
JUST GOT THERE NOW.
HE WALKED.
HE WALKED TO ALBERTA?
UNCLE RED, THAT'S LIKE
3000 MILES OR 4000
MILES OR --
HOW FAR IS IT?
TOO FAR TO WALK.
WELL, YEAH.
SEE, EXACTLY.
DID HE GET A JOB?
NO, NO, WAY BETTER,
HAROLD, HE WENT DOWN
TO THAT TARSAND PROJECT,
THINGS WERE SLOW,
YOU KNOW,
AND THEY WERE SELLING
EVERYTHING OFF,
INDUSTRIAL EQUIPMENT AND
CLOTHING, DIRT CHEAP.
HE DIDN'T BUY
ANYTHING, DID HE?
I MEAN IF HE DOESN'T
HAVE A JOB HE SHOULDN'T BE
THINKING OF BUYING THINGS.
OH, YEAH, WELL,
HE COULDN'T RESIST, EH?
HE GOT HIMSELF
A HARD HAT AND A
12-MILE CONVEYER BELT.
NOW HE'S GOING TO
BRING THAT BACK
WITH HIM
AND HE AND BUSTER
ARE GOING TO GO INTO
BUSINESS OF SOME KIND.
HE'S ASKED A BUNCH
OF US TO COME UP WITH
SOME IDEAS FOR IT.
WELL, I BET YOU'LL
HAVE LOTS OF IDEAS.
YEAH, YEAH,
SOMETHING GOOD, HAROLD.
WELL, THERE'S
A LONG SHOT.
SORRY, WE'RE CLOSED.
HE HAD CUTS ALL OVER
HIS CHIN AND HIS NECK
AND ALL THE WAY
DOWN TO HIS WAIST
THE DOCTOR WENT THROUGH
NINE SPOOLS OF THREAD
JUST TO PUT A SMILE
BACK ON HIS FACE
HE FOUGHT BACK THE PAIN,
PROPPED HIMSELF UP
AND PROMISED THE
DOCTOR NEVER AGAIN
WOULD HE TRY SHAVING
WITH A WEED WHACKER
TODAY ON MEET
YOUR MEMBER
I GOT MY GOOD FRIEND
DOUGIE FRANKLIN HERE
WHO'S GOING TO TELL
US A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT HIMSELF.
THANK YOU, RED.
WELL, I BUILT A MONSTER
TRUCK FROM THE FRAME UP
OUT OF AN OLD
K-CAR ACTUALLY.
AND NOW THERE'S A
BIT OF IRONY THERE,
YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU CONSIDER
THE NUMBER OF
THOSE BABIES
I'VE CRUSHED
OVER THE YEARS.
I THOUGHT K STOOD
FOR CRUSH ACTUALLY.
WELL, NO, I KINDA
MEANT MAYBE SOMETHING
A LITTLE MORE PERSONAL
ABOUT YOURSELF, YOU KNOW?
OKAY.
YEAH.
WELL, I GOT
THE BRAKES, I
GOT THE ASSEMBLY --
BRAKE ASSEMBLY
READY TO GO.
I GOT THE FOUR-WHEEL
DRIVE UNIT JUST PREPARED
TO DROP IN THERE AND...
YOU WANT MORE
PERSONAL STUFF?
OH ABSOLUTELY.
LIKE THE CAB, MAYBE
THE INTERIOR?
LET'S GO A DIFFERENT
WAY ON THIS.
MAYBE DOUG, MAYBE YOU
CAN TELL US A LITTLE
BIT ABOUT YOUR FAMILY,
YOUR FAMILY LIFE,
THAT KIND OF THING.
WELL, I DON'T
THINK THERE'S
A PERSON ALIVE
THAT COULD HAVE HAD
A BETTER HOME LIFE
THAN I DID, RED.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
MY DADDY USED TO DRIVE ME
TO SCHOOL EVERY
DAY IN HIS '57 CHEVY
LONG BOX PICK-UP TRUCK
WITH THE
TURBO-CHARGED 427,
PORTED AND RELIEF.
HE COULD LAY A PATCH
OF RUBBER THE ENTIRE LENGTH
OF THAT TEACHERS'
PARKING LOT.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT
YOUR MOTHER?
TELL US ABOUT YOUR MOTHER.
THAT'LL BE GOOD.
NOT REALLY MUCH
TO SAY THERE.
NOT MUCH TO TELL YOU.
I MEAN, SHE WAS
A LOVELY WOMAN.
YEAH.
BUT SHE DIDN'T DRIVE.
WELL, IF BUSTER HADFIELD'S
BROTHER IS MAKING THAT
BIG CONVEYER BELT,
I THOUGHT I WOULD TAKE
THE HANDYMAN CORNER
TO SHOW YOU HOW
TO MAKE A SMALL
CONVEYER BELT,
ONE THAT YOU CAN
USE RIGHT INSIDE
YOUR HOUSE.
WHETHER IT BE TO
BRING SNACKS FROM
THE KITCHEN
ALL THE WAY OVER TO
YOUR RECLINER/ROCKER
SO YOU DON'T HAVE TO
GET UP OFF YOUR DUFF
AND MISS YOUR FAVOURITE
COMMERCIALS
OR MAYBE TO USE TO BRING
LAUNDRY UP FROM
THE BASEMENT
OR EVEN TO HAUL YOURSELF
UP TO BED ON THOSE
ODD OCCASIONS
WHEN YOU'RE OVERSERVED IN
THE BREWED BEVERAGES
DEPARTMENT.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW THE FIRST THING
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
TO MAKE A CONVEYER BELT
IS A PIECE OF A
CONVEYER BELT.
AND WHERE YOU GET THAT
IS YOU CUT A PIECE
OFF A CONVEYER BELT.
NOW IF YOU DON'T HAPPEN
TO HAVE A CONVEYER BELT,
I TELL YOU WHAT, THEY
USE A LOT OF THESE AT
THE CONSTRUCTION SITES.
AND HERE'S ANOTHER CLUE,
THEY DON'T USUALLY
WORK ON A SUNDAY 'CAUSE
THERE'S NO TRAFFIC TO BLOCK.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
SOMETHING TO PUT THE
CONVEYER BELT ON,
IT'S GOTTA SLIDE
OVER SOMETHING.
SO YOU GET ONE OF
THESE OLD WOODEN LADDERS
WITH THE ROUND WRUNGS
SO THE BELT CAN
SLIDE OVER EASILY,
JUST LIKE YOU SLIDE 'ER
DOWN EASILY WHEN YOU
COME DOWN BY SURPRISE.
IT WILL WORK PERFECTLY.
NOW, YOU'LL
NEED SOMETHING TO
ACTUALLY DRIVE THE BELT.
I WOULD SUGGEST
YOU USE ONE OF
THE OLD WRINGERS.
REMEMBER THE OLD
WRINGER WASHER?
ON A SATURDAY MORNING,
MOM WOULD BE DOWN THE
BASEMENT THERE,
RUNNING YOUR DAD'S
SHIRT AND YOUR DAD'S
PERSONALITY
THROUGH THE WRINGER
ALL AT THE SAME TIME.
NOW, OF COURSE, YOU
GOT TO HAVE AN
ELECTRIC MOTOR
IN THERE TO DRIVE
THAT WHOLE RIG.
YOU COULD USE THE NORMAL
ELECTRIC MOTOR OFF THE
MACHINE ITSELF,
IF YOU'RE A WUSS.
BUT IF YOU'RE A REAL
MAN, HOW ABOUT ONE OF
THOSE BABIES, HUH?
THIS HERE IS THE
ELECTRIC MOTOR
OFF THE SWING
BRIDGE IN TOWN
OR AT LEAST IT USED
TO BE UNTIL, WELL,
UNTIL THEY
WEREN'T LOOKING.
SOMETIMES WHEN
YOU'RE A HANDYMAN,
YOU HAVE TO MAKE
EXECUTIVE DECISIONS.
ANYWAY, WITH THE SWING
BRIDGE NOT WORKING,
THAT JUST MEANS THERE'S
NO SAILBOATS ON
POSSUM LAKE,
SO IT'S GOOD FOR
THE COMMUNITY.
ALL RIGHT.
TALK IS CHEAP.
LET'S BUILD.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT
THE CONVEYER BELT
ALL LAID OUT AROUND
THE LADDER HERE
AND I GOT HER UP AND
THROUGH MY WRINGER
AND THEN I GOT THE
WRINGER HOOKED UP
WITH A DRIVE BELT
DOWN TO MY BIGGIE
SUPER DUPER HUNKIS
DORIS ELECTRIC MOTOR.
AND I WASN'T QUITE
SURE HOW FAST THIS
MOTOR WOULD GO
'CAUSE I KNOW
SHE DEVELOPS 20
HORSEPOWER AT 1750 RPM
AND THEN THE BELT, OF
COURSE, IS 18-FEET LONG,
SO IT TURNS OUT TO
BE PRETTY DARN FAST.
SO I THOUGHT I
WOULD HOOK HER UP
TO A 250 WATT
LIGHT DIMMER HERE.
SURE IT COSTS FIVE BUCKS
BUT I DON'T SCRIMP
ON SAFETY,
UNLESS IT'S
LIKE 10 BUCKS.
ANOTHER PROBLEM I HAD
IS THAT THE MOTOR
RUNS ON 550 VOLTS
WHEREAS AT THE LODGE
HERE WE ONLY HAVE 110
VOLTS ON THE GOOD DAYS,
WHICH IS ONLY
ONE-FIFTH.
I SOLVED THAT ONE EASY
ENOUGH, I JUST ADDED
FIVE PLUGS ON TO THE --
TWO, THREE --
ANYWAY THE FIFTH
PLUG HERE
AND FIVE PLUGS ONTO
THE MOTOR AND THAT
WAY SHE ALL WORKS OUT.
NOW, LET'S SAY I
WANTED TO TAKE
THIS BOX
OF CANDIES AND
JELLY DONUTS
AND ASSORTED THINGS
THAT I LIKE TO
SNACK ON
AND I WANTED TO MOVE
THIS INTO ANOTHER ROOM.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
STICK HER ON
MY CONVEYOR
AND GRAB MY DIMMER
AND JUST TURN HER
ON AND GIVE HER A SHOT.
I GUESS SHE NEEDS
A LITTLE MORE JUICE.
MAYBE THOSE JELLY DONUTS
ARE HEAVIER THAN I
THOUGHT THEY WERE.
WHY DON'T WE OPEN
HER WIDE OPEN?
OH, NO, WAIT A SEC,
THERE'S THE PROBLEM,
THE BELT IS CAUGHT
IN THE WRINGER, HERE.
WOAH!
WELL, THAT WORKED GREAT.
DID I SAY CONVEYER BELT?
I MEANT CATAPULT.
REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
I HOPE THE NEIGHBOURS
ENJOY THOSE TREATS.
RED GREEN:
STAY TUNED.
BILL IS GOING TO
STRETCH HIMSELF
TO THE LIMIT
AND GLEN AND I ARE
GOING TO SHOW YOU
WHY FAT GUYS
SHOULDN'T DO STUFF.
YOU KNOW A LOT
OF PEOPLE MY AGE
DON'T LIKE RAP MUSIC.
THEY SAY RAP MUSIC
ISN'T MUSIC
IT'S NOT EVEN POETRY.
IT'S JUST A BUNCH OF
PEOPLE TAKING REVENGE
ON THE ENGLISH LANGUAGE
BY TURNING IT
INTO A SET OF DRUMS.
AND THE RAPPERS HAVE
KIND OF STRANGE
NAMES, YOU KNOW,
LIKE ICE BUCKET
OR ZAP ZIPPER.
BUT I LIKE RAP
MUSIC BECAUSE YOU DON'T
NEED ANY TALENT, YOU SEE.
THIS IS SOMETHING
I CAN DO.
I COULD MAKE THOSE
FINGER MOTIONS AT
THE CAMERA
WHILE I'M CHANTING
DIRTY LIMERICKS TO
SOME METRONOME.
AND I CAN HIRE
UNDERDRESSED GROUPIES,
SLITHERING AWAY IN
THE BACKGROUND THERE,
FEELING THEIR BODIES
LIKE THEY'RE CHECKING
FOR MOLES.
I COULD EVEN
CHANGE MY NAME,
CALL MYSELF ICE GREEN
OR MASTER RED DEF
JAM OR EXCUSE-E-ME.
I COULD BE HUGE.
NOT GOOD, BUT HUGE.
WELL, WE GOT BUSTER'S
BIG CONVEYER BELT
ALL PUT TOGETHER.
AND YOU SHOULD HAVE
SEEN HOW DIRTY SOME
OF THE GUYS GOT.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE
NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YOU SHOULD NOT
BE PUTTING THAT
THING TOGETHER.
OH, HAROLD, IF YOUR
PARENTS HAD ANY IDEA
WHAT THEY WERE DOING,
THEY WOULDN'T HAVE PUT
YOU TOGETHER EITHER.
ANYWAY, BUSTER AND
HIS BROTHER HAVE NOW
ESTABLISHED A 12-MILE
STRIP OF MOVING RUBBER
RIGHT DOWN THE MIDDLE
OF POSSUM COUNTY.
WHAT AN EYE SORE.
AND AROUND HERE
THAT'S SAYING SOMETHING.
HAROLD, ONE MAN'S EYE
SORE IS ANOTHER
MAN'S MONORAIL.
MONORAIL?
THE HADFIELD
RUBBER ROCKET.
THEY'RE GOING TO USE
IT TO REPLACE THE
SCHOOL BUS.
EVERYBODY JUST THROWS
THEIR KIDS ON THE BELT
AND OFF THEY GO.
THE PROBLEM IS THERE'S
NO REVERSE ON
THE MOTOR,
SO THE KIDS WILL
HAVE TO WALK HOME.
UNLESS YOU MAKE
IT PART OF THE
PHYSICAL FITNESS TRAINING.
YOU KNOW BECAUSE I
BET IT WOULD BE
GOOD EXERCISE
FOR THE KIDS TO
TRY TO WALK HOME
AGAINST THE TREADMILL
GOING THE OTHER WAY,
BECAUSE THAT'S HOW
THEY TRAIN ASTRONAUTS
AND STUFF, YOU KNOW,
SO THEY'RE OKAY
IN MALLS AND THAT.
WELL, I SUPPOSE IF
THEY GOT THE MOTOR
GOING SLOW ENOUGH
SO THE KIDS COULD
MAKE HEADWAY WITHOUT
BURNING THE BOTTOMS
OUT OF THEIR
PF FLYERS.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW
IF THEY SLIP UP,
THEY'RE GOING
RIGHT BACK TO SCHOOL.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
I WAS IN GRADE FOUR
THREE YEARS IN A ROW.
AND HERE WE ARE AT
BRACKSTON'S MARINA
WITH GLEN BRACKSTON.
HOW ARE YOU TODAY, GLEN?
I'M FINE, RED.
GREAT.
THAT WAS JUST
A FALSE ALARM.
JUST A LITTLE
TOUCH OF ANGINA.
SO OFFICIALLY I'VE
STILL ONLY HAD TWO
HEART ATTACKS.
TODAY'S BOATING TIP:
TODAY WE'RE GOING
TO PRESERVE THE
FINISH ON A BOAT.
SO WHAT YOU NEED
IS A HIGH QUALITY
POLYMER RESIN WAX
AND A DAMP,
CLEAN CLOTH.
MORE DAMP
THAN CLEAN.
SO WE GOT TO --
HOP UP HERE RED.
NOW WHAT WE
GOT TO DO
IS GET A LITTLE OF THE
RESIN ON THE CLEAN
HERE -- WELL,
THERE YOU GO, RED,
MAYBE YOU'D LIKE
TO DO IT.
YOU CAN LEARN
BY DOING.
NO, IT'S OKAY.
I DON'T LEARN BY DOING.
YOU GO AHEAD, GLEN.
OKAY, SURE.
I GUESS I COULD DO IT.
MAYBE YOU
COULD RUN OUT
AND GRAB MY NITRO PILLS
FOR ME IN THE BOATHOUSE.
ALL RIGHT.
SO WHAT YOU NEED
TO DO IS SOME
NICE BIG
CIRCULAR MOTIONS.
AND WHEN IT DRIES THEN
YOU TAKE IT OFF WITH
A CLEAN RAG.
A CLEANER RAG.
HOW DID YOU LEARN
ABOUT THIS STUFF GLEN?
NOT BY DOING,
OBVIOUSLY.
OH, NO, BY
WATCHING RED.
I ONLY WISH I COULD
LEARN BY DOING BUT MY
HEALTH PREVENTS THAT.
I FIND MY LOT IN LIFE
IS JUST GIVING ADVICE,
YOU KNOW.
LIKE YOU GUYS WITH
YOUR CONVEYOR SCHOOL
BUS RIG THERE.
YOU KNOW, I THINK YOU GUYS
MIGHT WANT TO TRY THAT
OUT ON YOURSELVES
BEFORE YOU GET ANY OF
MY KIDS ON THERE.
OH, YEAH, WE DON'T
WANT ALL SEVEN OF
YOUR DAUGHTERS
ON THERE AT THE
ONE TIME ANYWAY,
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
IS THAT SOME SORT
OF FAT SHOT, RED,
THEY'RE HEAVY?
OH, NO, NO,
NO, NO.
WHAT I MEANT WAS
WE DON'T WANT YOU
ALL STRESSED OUT,
YOU KNOW, HAVING ALL
YOUR KIDS AT RISK.
OKAY.
I THINK THAT'S
PRETTY WELL GOT HER.
THAT WAS GREAT.
THAT'S A GREAT
DEMONSTRATION.
THANK YOU VERY
MUCH, GLEN.
OH, RED, YOU NEED
TO FINISH IT UP, RED.
I PROMISED A GUY
I WOULD HAVE IT
DONE BY TWO O'CLOCK.
YOU DON'T MIND,
DO YOU?
YEAH, I DO MIND.
I GOT THINGS TO DO.
SORRY, GLEN.
WELL, SURE, I GUESS
I CAN DO IT MYSELF.
I JUST HOPE
IT'S NOT THE LAST
THING I EVER DO.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
CAN I GET YOU A DONUT
OR SOMETHING RED?
IT'S MAIL CALL.
THIS WEEK WE GOT A
REALLY NEAT LETTER IN.
LOOK AT THIS ONE
UNCLE RED,
IT'S ALL ART
ON THERE AND SOME
DESIGNS AND STUFF.
IT'S NEAT.
OH BOY.
YOU KNOW HAROLD I WANTED
TO BE A STRUGGLING
ARTIST AT ONE TIME
BUT I JUST COULDN'T PUT
UP WITH THE BAHAMIAN
LIFESTYLE.
THAT'S BOHEMIAN
LIFESTYLE, UNCLE RED.
BOHEMIAN.
WHATEVER.
YOU KNOW I WANTED
TO DO THAT BUT BOY
I SEE THE WAY THEY
LIVE AND THE FILTH,
YOU KNOW,
AND THE BUGS
AND THE RATS
AND NOTHING TO WEAR,
PENNILESS, HUNGRY
ALL THE TIME.
NO THANK YOU.
WELL THAT'S HOW
YOU LIVE NOW.
NO, HAROLD, I'M NOT
HUNGRY ALL THE
TIME, YOU KNOW.
I WAS REAL SERIOUS
ABOUT BEING ARTIST.
I GOT A BERET
AND THE WHOLE --
BUT, AGAIN, AS I SAY,
I COULDN'T PUT UP WITH
THE BULGARIAN LIFESTYLE.
BOHEMIAN.
YEAH, WELL, WHATEVER.
I SETTLED DOWN AND GOT
MYSELF MARRIED, HAROLD.
WELL, I WAS GOING
TO BE AN ARTIST, TOO.
YEAH, I TOOK ONE OF
THOSE LIFE DRAWING
CLASSES,
YOU KNOW, WHERE
YOU DRAW LIFE,
YOU KNOW.
THERE'S JUST LIKE
LIFE FIGURES AND
YOU DRAW THEM.
NUDES, HAROLD?
EXACTLY.
THEY HAD A NUDE MODEL
COME IN ALL NAKED.
I GOT SO NERVOUS I
SHARPENED MY CRAYON
RIGHT DOWN TO A NUB
AND I SWALLOWED
MY ERASER.
THE MODEL HAD TO COME
RUNNING OVER AND GAVE
ME A HEIMLICH MANEUVER.
SAVED MY LIFE.
AND DID THIS NUDE MODEL
GIVE YOU MOUTH-TO-MOUTH
RESUSCITATION?
WELL, HE WANTED TO.
RED GREEN: IT'S TIME FOR
ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
BILL HAD SOMETHING
KIND OF MODERN ON
HIS MIND TODAY.
GOT TO GET
HIMSELF INTO SHAPE.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE
DOING THIS THESE DAYS.
AND WE'RE GOING TO
SHOW YOU IT DOESN'T
TAKE A THOUSAND DOLLARS
AND AN ARM
AND A LEG.
WELL, IT MIGHT TAKE
AN ARM AND A LEG.
HE WANTED ME TO
PUT THE GAS CANS A
CERTAIN WAY THERE.
AND THAT ONE WAS FULL
AND THIS ONE HAD VERY
LITTLE IN IT AT ALL,
WHICH SEEMED ODD TO ME,
BUT, YOU KNOW, I
DON'T QUESTION,
BILL'S THE EXPERT.
AND HE PUTS THE BAR
THROUGH THERE, A LITTLE
PIECE OF ANGLE IRON.
AND THEN HE'S GOING
TO CHALK DOWN.
THAT'S NOT CHALK, BILL.
BILL, THAT'S NOT --
BILL, THAT'S NOT CHALK.
THIS IS WHAT I
THOUGHT WOULD HAPPEN.
LOOKS LIKE HE --
GOOD THINKING, BILL.
YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH, GREAT.
BILL THAT'S NOT --
BILL THERE'S A FLAME.
BILL.
HE'LL BE BACK IN
A MINUTE I GUESS.
THERE HE IS.
THAT WILL BE QUITE
A BIT LATER NOW.
YEAH, HE'S FINE.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
GETTING ALL KINDS
OF EXERCISE TODAY.
NOW HE TAKES OUR
MANURE SPREADER, HERE.
HE'S GOT THE LITTLE
LIKE SURGICAL TUBING.
THE KIND OF SOMETHING
USED TO REPLACE
THINGS INSIDE YOUR BODY
THAT LOOK LIKE THAT.
AND HE -- OH, OH, OH.
YOU KNOW SOMETIMES
IN LIFE YOU CAN
LOOK AROUND
AND YOU CAN SEE AN
ACCIDENT ABOUT TO HAPPEN.
YOU JUST KNOW THERE'S
GOING TO BE TROUBLE,
YOU DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHEN,
BUT YOU CERTAINLY KNOW
WHAT IT'S GOING TO
BE, DON'T YOU?
YEAH, THAT'S THE
ONE I PICTURED.
AWAY YOU GO BILL.
EVERYTHING IS EXERCISE
WITH BILL.
LOOK WHERE HE'S
WEARING THE HARD HAT NOW.
AND HE'S GOTTEN EVERYTHING
EXERCISED ALL AT ONCE.
AND THEN HE'S GOT
THIS KIND OF A BOXING THING
WHICH I THOUGHT WAS
KIND OF NEAT,
KIND OF LIKE MOHAMMED
ALI, GEORGE FRASER-
TYPE OF THING.
HE'S GOING TO LEAN
AGAINST AND THROW
THE PUNCHES.
BUT THE DOORKNOB MAYBE
IS NOT AS ATTACHED
JUST QUITE AS WELL.
SOME OF THE THINGS AT
THE LODGE ARE REALLY
NOT UP TO SPEC.
I DON'T THINK COMPARED
TO WHAT -- UH-OH,
UH-OH, UH-OH, UH-OH, UH-OH,
UH-OH, UH-OH, UH-OH.
THAT'S MY VAN, BILL.
NOBODY MESSES
WITH MY VAN.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED
EXERCISE, RIGHT?
WELL I HAVE GOOD NEWS,
I CAN HELP YOU
WITH THAT.
WATCH YOURSELF ON
THE BUILDING THERE.
RED GREEN:
STAY TUNED.
HAROLD'S GOT A COUPLE
MORE STUPID THINGS
TO SAY
AND DALTON HUMPHREY
GETS EXCITED
SO YOU KNOW THERE'S
MONEY INVOLVED.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELL, WE HAD A LITTLE
TROUBLE WITH BUSTER
HADFIELD'S
MOVING CONVEYER
BELT THING.
OH REALLY?
EVERYTHING WAS
FINE, YOU KNOW,
THE BUNCH OF US WERE
SITTING ON THERE
READY TO GO
AND MOOSE THOMPSON
THROWS THE POWER SWITCH
AND THEN HE DECIDES
HE WANTS TO GET
ON IT TOO.
I'M GUESSING
BAD DECISION?
WELL, IT WOULDN'T HAVE
BEEN TOO BAD IF HE
JUST CLIMBED ON.
BUT, OH NO,
NOT MOOSE,
HE'S GOT TO DO ONE OF
THESE FLYING SUMMERSAULT
CANNONBALL THINGS.
A HALF GAINER.
A TOTAL LOSER.
THE WHOLE CONVEYER
BELT CRASHES TO
THE GROUND
AND CHANGES FROM A
MOVING CONVEYER
INTO KIND OF LIKE
A TANK TREAD.
BUT WITHOUT THE TANK.
WELL, WE HAD MOOSE.
SO NOW YOU GOT A 12-MILE
BLACK ELASTIC BAND,
COVERED WITH HUMANITY,
POWERED BY A DIESEL
ENGINE HEADING SOUTH.
SOUTH.
NOW, SOUTH, THAT --
I CAN'T PICTURE THAT.
WHAT IS THAT
TOWARDS?
WELL, THIS DOOR.
YEAH.
AND THE BARN AROUND IT.
THAT'S FARMER
ASHLEY'S SHEEP FARM.
ARE THE SHEEP OKAY?
NO, THE SHEEP ARE
FINE, THEY HEADED NORTH.
BUT YOU MIGHT WANT
TO AIR OUT YOUR ROOM,
THEY WERE
PRETTY SCARED.
WE'RE OUT HERE BY
THE MAIN HIGHWAY AT
HUMPHREY'S EVERYTHING STORE
TO LEARN A LITTLE BIT
MORE ABOUT COLLECTIBLES
AND ANTIQUES
FROM THE STORE OWNER,
DALTON HUMPHREY.
YOU CAN ACTUALLY MAKE
MONEY WITH THIS STUFF,
CAN YOU DALTON?
WELL, YOU KNOW, RED,
IF YOU KNOW THE
MARKETPLACE
AND WHAT'S HOT, YOU
CAN DO QUITE WELL
ON ANTIQUES.
ALL RIGHT.
FOR INSTANCE,
TAKE THIS TOASTER.
NOW STINKY PETERSON
SOLD THIS TO ME
FOR A NICKEL.
A NICKEL.
YEAH.
TO HIM IT WAS JUST
A DIRTY OLD RUSTED
OUT OLD TOASTER.
BUT, YOU KNOW, TO
A COLLECTOR OF
OLD TOASTERS,
SOMEONE WHO KNOWS
THE HISTORY OF THE
MANUFACTURER,
WHO HAS SCOURED THE
MARKETPLACE FOR
ANTIQUE TOASTERS.
YEAH.
YOU GUESS WHAT THAT
WOULD BE WORTH
TO THEM.
WELL, BY GOSH, IT MUST
BE WORTH 50 BUCKS AT
LEAST I WOULD THINK.
NO, A QUARTER.
STINKY PETERSON SOLD
THIS TO ME FOR
FIVE CENTS.
THAT'S 400
PERCENT MARKUP.
RED: DO YOU HAVE ANY REALLY,
REALLY VALUABLE ITEMS
HERE DALTON?
LIKE SAY SOMETHING
OVER A BUCK?
OH, I GOT A HUGE
CONVEYER SYSTEM
FROM BUSTER HADFIELD,
YOU KNOW,
THE METAL PART.
OH, SURE, YEAH.
THE RUBBER CONVEYER
BELT MARKET HAS GONE
SOFT, YOU KNOW,
SOME COLLECTOR IN
NOVA SCOTIA DECIDED
HE'S GOING TO
FLOOD THE MARKET.
BUT I'VE TWO COLLECTORS
LOCKED IN A BIDDING WAR
FOR, YOU KNOW,
THE METAL PART.
THE EUROPEAN BIDDER
HAS OFFERED ME $8.
A THERE'S A WOMAN IN
CALIFORNIA WHO SAYS SHE
MIGHT GO AS HIGH AS 10.
IF I WERE YOU I WOULD
JUST SELL THAT TO THE
SCRAP METAL DEALER.
WHAT HE'S GOING
TO GIVE ME FOR
IT, A BUCK?
OH, NO, NO.
YOU GOT A LOT OF
STEEL IN THAT UNIT
AND YOU GOT THE NICKEL
AXLES IN THERE.
THERE MUST BE FIVE OR SIX
MILES OF COPPER WIRE.
YOU'RE PROBABLY
LOOKING AT 9 OR 10,000.
DOLLARS?
YEAH, YEAH, I WOULD
SAY 9 OR $10,000, YEAH.
OKAY.
HERE WE GO.
ATTENTION FELLOW POSSUMS:
I, MOOSE THOMPSON, HAVE
FIGURED OUT HOW TO GET
MY VCR TO STOP
FLASHING 12:12:12.
OH, GREAT.
OKAY.
UNPLUG IT WHEN YOU'RE
NOT USING IT.
THANKS MOOSE.
$10,000?
MAYBE A LITTLE MORE,
PROBABLY 10,000 THOUGH.
CANADIAN?
CANADIAN DOLLARS
SURE, YEAH.
BOTH:
10,000 CANADIAN DOLLARS.
FOR SALE: WAFFLE IRON,
POPCORN MAKER, DEEP FRYER,
FRENCH FRY MACHINE.
WILL TRADE FOR
ROWING MACHINE.
SELLER IS VERY MOTIVATED,
JUST HAD THIRD
HEART ATTACK.
THAT'S A ONE.
YEAH.
AND THEN A ZERO AND
A ZERO AND A ZERO
AND A ZERO
AND A DOT, AND
TWO MORE ZEROS.
THAT'S 10,000, YEAH.
10,000!
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
THAT'S WHAT I'M
SAYING TO YOU.
THAT'S BETTER THAN
A BUCK, ISN'T IT?
EXCUSE ME.
THAT WAS NOT A HIGHLIGHT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHY DOES IT SMELL
LIKE OIL IN
HERE BATMAN?
DON'T PRETEND YOU'RE NOT
JEALOUS OF MY CONVEYER
BELT RAINCOAT, HAROLD.
OH, DOES IT SHOW?
THEY HAVEN'T INVENTED
THE STORM THAT CAN GET
THROUGH THIS BABY,
I'LL YOU THAT.
YOU KNOW, BUSTER WILL
MAKE YOU ONE, HAROLD,
IF YOU GIVE HIM
YOUR SIZE.
OH, OKAY.
10-W-30.
YOU LOOK LIKE A PIECE
OF LICORICE CANDY
OR SOMETHING.
WELL, LAUGH IF
YOU WANT, HAROLD,
BUT SINCE WE'VE CUT
UP THE CONVEYOR BELT,
THERE'S ALL KINDS OF
THINGS THAT WE CAN MAKE:
FLOOR MATS, KITCHEN MATS,
CAR MATS, WELCOME MATS,
BATH MATS, RV MATS, MATS.
UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED,
I THINK MAYBE YOU
SHOULD JUST STICK
WITH THE
RAINCOAT IDEA.
I BET YOU'RE AS
DRY AS CAN BE
IN THAT.
WELL I WAS FOR THE
FIRST FEW MINUTES.
I GUESS SHE'S A LOT
COOLER WHEN IT'S
RAINING, HUH?
IT MUST BE THE WOOL
LINER FROM THE
SHEEP WE HIT.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH IT'S MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO
AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN
AN HOUR OR SO.
AND, HAROLD, HIT
THAT POWER SWITCH
WHEN I TELL YOU TO.
OKAY.
YEAH.
SO IF MY WIFE IS
WATCHING,
I WILL BE COMING
STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING
AND I AM BRINGING
ENOUGH BLACK RUBBER
TO LAST A LIFETIME.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD,
HIT THE SWITCH!
NO HAROLD.
HIT THE OTHER SWITCH!
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
'TILL NEXT TIME,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
RED: ALLRIGHT, HAROLD,
GET 'EM UP.
HAROLD: OKAY, ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
I'D LIKE TO PROPOSE A TOAST.