AND MAKE IT BETTER.
AND BELIEVE ME,
THAT'S A RARE THING
FOR A MIDDLE-AGED, MARRIED
PERSON TO BE ABLE
TO PULL OFF.
BUT I THINK
I'VE DONE IT HERE.
I'VE TAKEN THIS
WINDSHIELD WIPER
AND MOUNTED IT
ON A SUCTION CUP.
I'VE GOT A LEAD SINKER
ATTACHED TO THE END,
USING THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON.
NOW, WE ALL HAVE
WIPERS ON THE FRONT
TO KEEP THE
WINDSHIELD CLEAR.
BUT WOULDN'T IT BE BETTER
IF YOU COULD SEE OUT
ALL YOUR WINDOWS?
NOW, YOU MOUNT THESE BABIES
ON EACH OF THE WINDOWS.
THEY SWING UP
ON THE SUCTION CUP,
AND THEN THE LEAD SINKER
BRINGS THEM BACK DOWN.
NOW ALL WE NEED IS SOMETHING
THAT WILL MAKE THEM MOVE.
I KNOW, YOU'VE ALREADY
GUESSED IT, HAVEN'T YOU?
THAT'S RIGHT,
A MODEL TRAIN.
I STUCK AN OLD ICE SCRAPER
ACROSS THE COW-CATCHER HERE
AND THAT'LL KNOCK
THE WIPER HANDLES
EVERY TIME OL' 49 HERE
GOES RUMBLIN' BY.
I ALSO HAVE COMPLETE
CONTROL OVER THE SPEED
OF MY AUXILIARY WIPER SYSTEM
WITH THIS TRAIN TRANSFORMER.
I CAN SET HER
FROM SHUNTING SPEED
ALL THE WAY
TO FULL SPEED AHEAD.
AND I'M RUNNING THE WHOLE
DEAL OFF THE CAR BATTERY,
GOT IT HOOKED UP TO THE
CIGARETTE LIGHTER HERE.
I CAN EVEN DO THIS.
THAT'S MY INTERMITTENT.
OKAY, I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR MY DEMONSTRATION,
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO USE YOUR IMAGINATIONS
A FAIR BIT HERE.
PRETEND I'M ON THE HIGHWAY.
PRETEND IT'S RAINING.
AND PRETEND
THIS ACTUALLY WORKS.
[applause]
[cheering and applause]
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
GOT A BIT OF A PROJECT GOING
ON UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
HAROLD WANTS US TO GET
RID OF ALL THE JUNK
THAT'S LYING AROUND HERE.
BUT I SAY, NO, WE JUST
NEED ANOTHER SHED.
USUALLY WE JUST
MAKE OUR OWN SHEDS.
WE JUST STAND
A BUNCH OF CANOES UP,
DUCT TAPE THEM TOGETHER.
AND I WANT TO BUY ONE OF
THOSE FANCY STEEL SHEDS
THEY GOT ON SALE DOWN
AT THE LUMBER YARD.
NOW ALL WE GOTTA DO IS FIND A
WAY TO RAISE THE CASH.
YOU KNOW, IF THOSE PEOPLE
WOULD TAKE A CHEQUE,
NONE OF THIS
WOULD BE NECESSARY.
RED, RED, I THINK
I GOT THE ANSWER.
YOU REMEMBER ALL THOSE CANS OF
FOOD WE PUT IN THE BASEMENT
FOR THAT Y2K SCARE?
YEAH.
OH, REMEMBER THAT, EH?
THE SKY IS FALLING.
OKAY, WELL YOU KNOW,
WE COULD SELL THESE
FOR SOME MONEY.
WE'VE GOT HUNDREDS
OF THESE THINGS.
WELL, THEY HAVEN'T GOT
ANY LABELS, DALTON.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE THE LABELS.
NO, NO, NO,
WE JUST DON'T KNOW
WHICH CANS THEY CAME OFF.
WELL, YOU KNOW, THAT
WOULD CUT INTO THE
SALES POTENTIAL,
I WOULD THINK,
DALTON.
YOU LEAVE THAT TO ME.
IT'S MARKETING, RED.
YOU DON'T KNOW
MUCH ABOUT MARKETING.
WELL, I KNOW A CAN
OF CORN IS $1.69.
IT'S SHINY, AND IT'S
GOT A LABEL ON IT.
SO HOW MUCH WOULD I
PAY FOR A RUSTY CAN
OF WHO KNOWS WHAT?
YOU KNOW A PENNY
SOUNDS HIGH TO ME.
WELL, THAT'S THE THING.
YOU DON'T SELL THE STEAK.
YOU SELL THE SIZZLE.
STEAK AND SIZZLE
COME IN CANS, DO THEY?
RED,
IT'S A METAPHOR.
WE'RE GOING TO SELL THESE
GRAB-BAG SURPRISE PACKAGES.
IT'S A LOTTERY, HUH!
OH, SO YOU BUY A CAN.
YOU'RE KIND OF HOPING
THAT IT'S PEAS,
BUT IF YOU'RE LUCKY,
IT MIGHT EVEN BE CARROTS.
CAVIAR, RED.
IS THAT IT?
IT COULD BE CAVIAR.
NO, NO, DALTON.
HANG ON A SECOND.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO ADD
A CAN OF CAVIAR
INTO THE MIX,
THAT'S GOING TO COST
YOU AN EXTRA 300 BUCKS.
YOU SEE, I DON'T HAVE
TO PROVIDE CAVIAR, RED.
I HAVE TO PROVIDE THE
POSSIBILITY OF CAVIAR.
[laughing maniacally]
YOU KNOW, I THINK
HE'S LOOKING AT THE
POSSIBILITY OF JAIL TIME.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheering and applause]
AND TODAY'S WINNER WILL
RECEIVE ONE FREE SHOE SHINE.
YOUR CHOICE, ONE RIGHT SHOE
OR ONE LEFT SHOE.
CLOSE YOUR EARS, HAROLD.
OKAY, RED, YOU'VE GOT
30 SECONDS
TO GET HAROLD TO SAY
THIS WORD...
YEAH,
ALL RIGHT, DALTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, HAROLD,
THIS IS SOMETHING
ALL MEN LIKE TO HAVE.
EXCUSES.
NO, UM, THIS IS
A PHYSICAL THING.
IF YOU LOOKED AT THE ARMS
OF MOST OF THE GUYS
AT THE LODGE,
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
TATTOOS.
SCARS.
BURNT HAIR.
BURNT HAIR!
NO. NO. NO.
RING IT!
THIS IS A
BODY PART, OKAY?
AND MOOSE THOMPSON
HAS REAL BIG ONES.
I'M NOT ALLOWED IN
THE COMMUNAL SHOWER.
I DON'T KNOW.
YEAH, OKAY.
TIME'S ALMOST UP, RED.
YOU KNOW, UH,
HAROLD,
IF WOMEN SEE
A REAL GOOD LOOKING MAN
THEY'LL SAY, "BOY, I'D
REALLY LIKE TO SEE HIS..."
PORTFOLIO.
REMEMBER WE WENT TO THE
STEAKHOUSE LAST WEEK?
AND TO GET YOUR KNIFE THROUGH
THE BEEF YOU HAD TO
USE ALL YOUR...
I DON'T EAT RED MEAT.
I HAD THE MUSSELS.
THAT'S IT!
[applause]
SEEMS LIKE EVERYBODY
LIKES TO LOOK WEALTHY.
SOME GUYS DO IT WITH CLOTHES
OR CARS OR JEWELLERY.
SOME GUYS
DO IT WITH WIVES.
DO IT WITH EMPTIES.
TO ME, THERE'S NOTHING
THAT SAYS MONEY
MORE THAN HAVING
A RIDING LAWN MOWER.
SO THIS TIME,
ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW YOU CAN BUILD
YOUR OWN STYLISH,
AND YET EXTREMELY
AFFORDABLE, RIDING MOWER.
OKAY, ALL YOU NEED
IS AN EAVESTROUGH,
A CHUNK OF TWO-BY-SIX,
A GAS PUSH MOWER,
A GARAGE DOOR OPENER,
AND, OF COURSE,
A TOILET PLUNGER.
STEP ONE, YOU WANT TO PUT
AN EXTRA HANDLE ON
YOUR MOWER THERE
SO YOU CAN
SWING BOTH WAYS.
THEN YOU RUN YOUR TWO-BY-SIX
RIGHT THROUGH THE TWO OF THEM.
THAT BECOMES THE
MOUNTING PLATFORM FOR
YOUR PULLING MECHANISM.
IT ALSO DOUBLES
AS A SEAT.
I WOULD SAY
DON'T EVEN SAND THAT.
SLIVERS MAY HURT A LITTLE,
BUT THEY SURE KEEP YOU
FROM SLIDING OFF.
ALL RIGHT, THE NEXT THING
YOU WANT TO DO IS
TAKE YOUR GARAGE DOOR OPENER
AND YOUR EAVESTROUGH
AND MOUNT THEM DEAD
CENTRE ON THE TWO-BY-SIX.
NO, LET ME REPHRASE THAT.
THE INSURANCE COMPANY
DOESN'T LIKE TO HEAR THINGS
LIKE DEAD CENTRE,
OR BLEED THE LINES,
OR I'M GONNA USE
THE BIG HAMMER.
YOU KNOW, EVERY LAWNG MOWER
HAS A LITTLE GENERATOR IN IT
TO MAKE THE
SPARK PLUG GO.
SO I'M USING SOME
OF THAT ELECTRICITY
TO RUN MY
GARAGE DOOR OPENER.
PROBABLY NOT EXACTLY
THE RIGHT VOLTAGE,
BUT I FIND
WITH ELECTRICITY,
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BE ALL THAT CLOSE.
NOW, WHEN YOU MOUNT YOUR
GARAGE DOOR OPENER ON THERE,
MAKE SURE YOU DO IT
WITH JUST ONE BOLT.
THAT WAY IT
CAN SWING AROUND.
I'LL SHOW
YOU WHY LATER.
OKAY, NOW GET ALL THE
CABLE OUT OF THE OPENER
AND ATTACH THE END OF IT
TO YOUR TOILET PLUNGER.
NOW ALL YOU NEED IS SOMETHING
TO SHOOT THAT PLUNGER
OUT OF THERE.
GOTTA BE SOMETHING STRONG,
BUT STRETCHY.
OH, I KNOW JUST THE --
YEAH, UM, DOCTOR TOLD
ME TO WEAR THESE.
SAID THEY'D
IMPROVE MY CIRCULATION.
BOY, WAS HE WRONG.
WHEN I HAVE THEM ON, WOMEN
DON'T EVEN WANT TO TALK TO ME.
OKAY, SO I POSITION THE
LAUNCHER INTO MY ROCKET SILO,
AND THEN I DROP MY
ARROW IN THERE,
AIM HER ALL UP,
AND WE'RE READY
FOR A DEMONSTRATION.
I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW SHE WORKS.
[breathing heavily]
[mower starting]
ALL RIGHT, NOW, WE JUST
TAKE OUR PLUNGER
AND WE AIM HER
AT SOMETHING SOLID.
LIKE, SAY,
A DOG HOUSE.
OKAY, NOW, OF COURSE,
WE WANT TO HEAD BACK
THE OTHER WAY.
SO WE SWING OUR FIRING
DEVICE ALL THE WAY AROUND.
WE AIM AT SOMETHING ELSE.
I'M THINKING MAYBE THAT
MAILBOX ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE STREET.
[applause]
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
OLDER GUYS OUT THERE.
YOU KNOW, AS WE AGE,
THE LINE BETWEEN "WITH IT,
MIDDLE-AGED GUY,"
AND "OUT-OF-IT,
HOPELESS GEEZER"
STARTS TO BLUR.
NOW, I KNOW THERE'S NO WAY
THAT YOU'RE A GEEZER,
BUT MAYBE SOME
OF YOUR FRIENDS
ARE STARTING TO
SHOW THE TELLTALE SIGNS,
START SAYING THINGS LIKE,
"I REMEMBER WHEN THEY'D
DELIVER THAT WITH A HORSE."
OR, "I SEE BELL BOTTOMS ARE
COMING BACK IN STYLE."
OR, "COMPUTERS MAKE
YOUR BRAIN GO SOFT."
ACTUALLY, COMPUTERS DO
MAKE YOUR BRAIN GO SOFT,
BUT IT TAKES A GEEZER
TO NOTICE IT.
NOT THAT THERE'S ANYTHING
WRONG WITH BEING A GEEZER.
I MEAN, SOME OF THE
BEST LAWN ORNAMENTS
AND CLOTHES PEG RECIPE CARD
HOLDERS ARE MADE BY GEEZERS.
BUT I'M JUST THINKING YOU'RE
NOT QUITE READY TO
JOIN THE CLUB
WHERE THE DUES ARE PAID
IN BALLS OF OLD STRING.
NO, SIR, YOU'VE GOT YEARS
IN THE FAST LANE AHEAD OF YOU
BEFORE YOU PULL OFF
ON THE EXIT TO GEEZERDOM.
BUT WHAT DO YOU DO IF SOME OF
YOUR FRIENDS AREN'T SO LUCKY?
WELL, YOU DO EVERYTHING YOU
CAN TO MAKE THEM FEEL
LIKE THEY'RE STILL HIP
AND HAPPENING.
IF YOU SEE THEM HEADING OFF
TO THE MALL IN THEIR
BEDROOM SLIPPERS,
YOU DO THE SAME THING.
JUST SO THEY WON'T
FEEL OUT OF PLACE.
IF THEY SHOW YOU THEIR
COLLECTION OF HOTEL SOAPS,
YOU'VE GOT TO ADMIRE IT
AND SHOW THEM YOURS.
AND NEVER EVER TELL THEM
THEY'VE BECOME A GEEZER.
THEY MIGHT DO THE SAME
FOR YOU SOME DAY.
MAYBE THEY ALREADY HAVE.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
OKAY, MIKE.
I'M HERE. NOW WHAT?
RED, YOU GOT TO FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO GET ME OUT OF HERE.
RED: I assume coming out
the front door is out
of the question.
THAT'S VERY ASTUTE OF YOU.
RED: Mike, how do you get
yourself into these shamozles?
SHE SAID HER DAD WOULD
BE AWAY ALL WEEKEND
AND HE WASN'T COMING
HOME UNTIL MONDAY.
AND GET THIS,
HE'S MY PAROLE OFFICER.
Small world, isn't it?
YEAH, SMALL WORLD,
SMALL JAIL CELL.
YEAH, WELL, THAT'S
WHERE YOU COME IN.
GO TO THE FRONT DOOR
AND START TALKING TO HIM.
AND THAT'LL GIVE ME THE CHANCE
TO SNEAK OUT THE BACK WAY.
AND I'LL MEET YOU
BACK IN THE POSSUM VAN.
OKAY.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO TELL HIM?
SAY THAT I SENT YOU WITH
A MESSAGE FOR HIS DAUGHTER,
THAT I KNEW SHE WANTED
TO GO OUT WITH ME TONIGHT,
BUT I DIDN'T
THINK IT WAS RIGHT,
so i stayed
home to read my Bible.
YOU EXPECT HIM
TO BELIEVE THAT?
WELL, IT'S
BEEN MY EXPERIENCE
THAT PAROLE OFFICERS WILL
BELIEVE PRETTY WELL ANYTHING.
RED: Okay.
[knocking]
YEAH, I GOT A MESSAGE
FOR YOUR DAUGHTER.
SHE WANTED TO
GO OUT WITH MIKE,
BUT HE'S NOT GOING
TO BE COMING.
HE'S STAYING HOME READING
THE OLD TESTAMENT.
SO HE WON'T BE
DROPPING AROUND.
JUST WANTED
TO LET YOU KNOW THAT.
OKAY, FINE.
GOOD NIGHT.
AND DON'T FORGET
TO WEAR YOUR SEATBELT.
MIKE, ARE YOU IN HERE?
HOW'D IT GO?
OH, FINE.
GOOD.
HE'S NOT CONCERNED
ABOUT HIS DAUGHTER.
HE'S WONDERING WHAT
HAPPENED TO HIS
TELEVISION SET.
OH.
JUDGING BY THE INVENTORY,
I'D SAY WE MAY HAVE
OVERESTIMATED
CONSUMER DEMAND FOR
UNMARKED, RUSTY FOOD CANS.
I THINK WE HAVE PROBLEM.
OH, YEAH,
MR. MARKETING GENIUS?
DID YOUR SIZZLE
KIND OF FIZZLE?
THE IGNORANCE OF THE
PEOPLE IN THIS COMMUNITY
CAN JUST BE EXTREMELY
FRUSTRATING.
ARE YOU SAYING
THEY DIDN'T GET EXCITED
ABOUT THE CHANCE
TO BUY CHEAP CAVIAR?
THEY DIDN'T EVEN
KNOW WHAT CAVIAR WAS.
WELL, DID YOU TELL THEM
IT WAS FISH EGGS
YES.
IN A BLACK, GOOEY SAUCE?
NOTHING.
AND?
NO.
NO KIDDING?
I'VE GOT
A BETTER IDEA.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
A POT-LUCK SUPPER DOWN
AT THE COMMUNITY CENTRE.
WE'RE GOING TO PUT ALL
THE CANS IN A BIG CAULDRON.
WE'RE GOING TO CALL IT
POSSUM LODGE STEW.
CHARGE FIVE BUCKS A BOWL.
HOW MUCH FOR THE ANTIDOTE?
NO, I THINK IT MIGHT
WORK, YOU KNOW?
FOR ANY EX-CON THAT WOULD
BE LIKE A STROLL DOWN
MEMORY LANE.
YEAH, IT'S FIVE BUCKS.
IT'S ALL-YOU-CAN-EAT.
IT'S A BARGAIN!
FOR ME, I COULDN'T
EAT 50 CENTS WORTH.
YOU KNOW WE'RE
GOING TO MAKE IT A FUN NIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO OPEN
A THOUSAND CANS OF FOOD.
LET THE CHIPS
FALL WHERE THEY MAY,
AND WE'RE GOING
TO CALL IT...
THE NIGHT OF
A THOUSAND CANS!
YOU KNOW,
NIGHT OF A THOUSAND
CRAMPS MIGHT WORK BETTER.
Red: A BUNCH OF US WERE
TAKING DOWN A PUP TENT
BEHIND THE LODGE THERE.
WE'D DONE OUR BIT.
KIND OF LEFT WALTER TO
CLEAN IT UP, FINALLY.
ODD THING HAPPENED.
WE HAD A KIND OF
A LOW BREEZE COME IN.
I BELIEVE IT'S CALLED
A RISING THERMAL,
AND, UH, IT TOOK WALTER UP
600 OR 700 FEET, I BELIEVE.
YOU CAN'T COUNT ON THERMALS,
AS MOST OF US KNOW,
BUT THIS GAVE
US A GREAT IDEA.
WE COULD TRY PARASAILING
USING THE PUP TENT.
AND ALL WE NEEDED -- WE
NEEDED SOME KIND OF A VEHICLE
IF WE COULD GET
SOMETHING TO PULL IT.
AND MIKE HAD AN IDEA.
HE HAD JUST THE VEHICLE
IN MIND, APPARENTLY.
SO ALL WE HAD TO DO WAS
TALK WALTER INTO DOING IT.
HE WAS QUITE IMPRESSED
BEING UP THERE,
AND WE SAID THAT
WE HAD A GREAT PLAN.
AND, UH, I DIDN'T REALIZE
MIKE HAD A MOTORCYCLE.
I GUESS HE HAD
JUST PICKED THIS ONE UP.
AND, UH, VERY GENEROUS.
HE WAS ALLOWING WINSTON
TO RIDE IT.
HE DIDN'T WANT TO BE
ON IT FOR A WHILE.
SO WINSTON TURNED
HER AROUND,
AND ALL WE WERE GOING
TO DO WAS JUST HOOK
WALTER WITH A ROPE.
YOU'RE GOING TO REALLY
ENJOY THIS, WALTER.
YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE THIS.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
THE TIME OF YOUR LIFE.
NOW ALL WE GOT TO DO
IS ATTACH THE OTHER END
TO THE MOTORCYCLE.
THERE WASN'T REALLY ANYTHING
WE FELT WAS STRONG
ENOUGH ON IT,
AND WINSTON GOT THE IDEA
THAT INSTEAD OF TYING
IT TO THE MOTORCYCLE,
HE'S ON THERE SO WHY DIDN'T
WE JUST TIE IT AROUND
HIS WAIST?
NOW, WE FIGURE, WALTER,
ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS
JUST JUMP.
YOU'LL LOVE THIS.
IT'S LIKE AN AMUSEMENT PARK.
AND THEN WE'LL -- MIKE AND I
WILL THROW THE TENT.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
NOW, DON'T FORGET,
YOU GOTTA JUMP.
TAKE HER.
GO!
THERE WE GO!
JUMP.
JUMP, WALTER.
UP YOU GO.
UP YOU GO, WALTER.
JUMP. JUMP.
UP YOU GO.
GIVE HER THE GUN
THERE, WINSTON.
GIVE HER SOME --
OH! OH! OHH!
ALL RIGHT.
SO WE CHECKED THE MANUAL.
AND THAT'S
HOW THEY DO IT.
OH, OKAY.
NOW, YOU PUT WALTER RIGHT
ON THE BACK OF THE
MOTORCYCLE,
AND, OF COURSE,
WE'RE UP TO LET --
TO LET THE SAIL
GO FROM THE TOP OF THE VAN,
TO RELEASE THE SAIL.
AND UP HE GOES!
AND THAT'S GREAT.
BUT WE FORGOT
WINSTON WAS ATTACHED.
WELL, NOW THEY'RE
FLOATING UP THERE.
MIKE BRINGS THE ANCHOR ROPE.
THAT WAS A GOOD IDEA.
ALL WE GOTTA DO
IS ANCHOR THEM.
THAT'S THE
WRONG END, MIKE.
YOU WANT TO THROW
THE ANCHOR UP THERE
AND HOOK IT TO SOMEWHERE,
ANYWHERE ON THEM.
AND...
GOT 'EM.
AND IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
AND WE SAVED HER AGAIN.
PERFECT.
OOPS.
UMM... UMM...
OKAY, GUYS,
I GOTTA GO.
HEY THERE, GORD.
HANG ON A SECOND.
I'M PICKETING HERE.
I'M GORD! I'M BORED!
GET USED TO IT!
WHAT'S GOING
ON HERE, GORD?
I'M ON STRIKE,
RED, OKAY?
YOU KNOW, POWER TO
THE PEOPLE AND ALL THAT.
AND WOULDN'T THIS
WORK BETTER
IF YOU WENT DOWN WHERE
PEOPLE COULD ACTUALLY
SEE YOU?
YEAH, PROBABLY.
BUT I COULDN'T BRING
MYSELF TO LEAVE MY POST.
WELL, THIS COULD BE A
FIRST IN ORGANIZED LABOUR.
YOU'RE YOUR OWN SCAB.
[laughter and applause]
LOOK, I'M NEW
AT THIS, OKAY?
HOW COME YOUR
SIGN IS BLANK?
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE TOO
SPECIFIC ABOUT MY DEMANDS.
I JUST WANTED TO SHOW
MY GENERAL DISPLEASURE.
NOW, THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOMETHING THAT'S
BOTHERING YOU.
ARE YOU AFTER A RAISE?
I'D LIKE
TO BE PAID, OKAY?
THEN WE CAN TALK
ABOUT A RAISE.
ARE YOU SAYING YOU
STILL HAVE NEVER BEEN PAID?
NO.
IT'S A BIT
OF A SORE SPOT.
TO SEEM GREEDY.
I DON'T WANT
OKAY, SO --
I UNDERSTAND, BUT
IF YOU COULD GET PAID,
THAT WOULD -- THAT WOULD
DO IT FOR YOU?
OH, SURE.
AND A VACATION
WOULD BE NICE.
A LITTLE "ME" TIME.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT IT'D BE NICE
TO HAVE ST. PATRICK'S DAY OFF.
NO. YOU KNOW, NOBODY
GETS ST. PATRICK'S DAY,
BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT I WOULD SAY?
WHY DON'T YOU GET THE
BIG VACATION STRETCH
THAT YOU HAVE NOW,
LIKE THE TIME BETWEEN, SAY,
CHRISTMAS AND NEW YEAR'S?
CHRISTMAS
IS A HOLIDAY?
YOU KNOW, GORD, I THINK
YOU HAVE A DECISION TO MAKE.
I THINK YOU HAVE
TO GET ANOTHER JOB,
OR YOU HAVE TO KEEP GOING THIS
ONE AND NOT GET PAID FOR IT.
DO YOU KNOW ANYBODY
ELSE THAT WOULD HIRE YOU?
OH, SURE. YEAH.
I HAVE EXCELLENT
COMPUTER SKILLS.
I'VE GOT A
MATTEL INTELLIVISION.
OH, YEAH!
64K OF MEMORY,
FOUR COLOUR.
I THINK THEY'RE COMING
OUT WITH A KEYBOARD TOO.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
THAT'S EXCITING.
I DON'T KNOW, RED.
DO YOU THINK I SHOULD
GET A NEW JOB?
I WOULD RECOMMEND MEDICAL
TREATMENT OF SOME KIND,
AND THEN JUST TAKE
IT FROM THERE, YOU KNOW?
NO. NO.
RED, I'M GOING
TO KEEP THIS JOB.
BUT, GORD,
IT'S TERRIBLE HOURS,
AND YOU DON'T GET PAID.
NOBODY ELSE IN THE
WORLD WOULD DO THAT.
THAT'S RIGHT, RED.
THAT'S WHAT THEY
CALL JOB SECURITY.
OKAY?
OKAY, I GOTTA GO.
SEE YOU!
WELL, OUR POT LUCK DINNER
WAS NOT A TOTAL SUCCESS.
WELL, IT WASN'T THAT BAD.
NOT EVERYBODY GOT SICK.
JUST THE ONES
WHO ATE THE FOOD.
LUCKILY, THE SMELL
TURNED MOST PEOPLE OFF.
YOU KNOW, THEY TELL ME
THAT SOME OF THOSE TREES
WILL NEVER
HAVE LEAVES AGAIN.
YOU KNOW I
JUST DON'T GET IT.
MOST OF THOSE CANS
WERE BEANS OR CORN.
WHAT WENT WRONG?
WELL, THEY WEREN'T ALL
BEANS OR CORN, DALTON.
THAT'S WHAT WENT WRONG.
SOME WERE FLOOR WAX;
SOME WERE BODY FILLER.
YEAH, WELL, I THINK
IT WAS THE HAND CLEANER
OH, MAN.
THAT DID THE REAL DAMAGE.
TURNED EVERYBODY
INTO A SOAP DISPENSER.
WELL, NO HARM DONE.
EVERYBODY GOT THEIR
MONEY BACK.
NO HARM DONE?
WE'VE GOT NO STEEL SHED,
AND NOW WE'VE GOT
NOTHING TO SELL.
YEAH, BUT THERE
WERE NO FATALITIES,
NO PERMANENT
INJURIES.
AROUND HERE, THAT'S WHAT
WE CALL NO HARM DONE.
YEAH, I SUPPOSE.
YEAH, YEAH.
HEY, MR. GREEN!
I'VE GOT A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
NO DESSERT, MIKE.
I COULDN'T GO THERE.
NO, NO, NO.
I STACKED UP ALL THE EMPTY
CANS AND MADE A SHED
OUT OF THEM.
WELL, MY GOSH, YOU KNOW
THAT'S PRETTY SMART.
IT'S RIGHT OUTSIDE.
DO YOU WANT TO SEE IT?
WELL, LET'S NOT KILL
MY ENTHUSIASM THAT
FAST, OKAY, MIKE?
YOU SEE THERE, RED?
WHEN WE PUT OUR MINDS TOGETHER
WE ALWAYS SOLVE THE PROBLEM.
YEAH.
I SUPPOSE SO.
HOPE YOU DIDN'T
POLLUTE THE LAKE
WHEN YOU RINSED
THOSE CANS OUT, EH?
RINSE THE CANS OUT?
HOW DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, IF YOU DON'T
RINSE THE CANS OUT,
YOU'RE GOING
TO ATTRACT ANIMALS.
ATTRACT ANIMALS,
HOW DO YOU MEAN?
[dogs barking]
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME.
LET'S GO.
SEE YOU LATER.
[applause]
WELL, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I'LL BE
COMING HOME HUNGRY.
YOU KNOW, YOU ALWAYS
TELL ME TO WATCH WHAT I EAT.
I COULDN'T EVEN
LOOK AT THAT DINNER.
SO I WAS HOPING, MAYBE LATER,
WE COULD HAVE A BIG STEAK,
AND THEN AFTER WE COULD
HAVE A LITTLE SIZZLE.
AND TO REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND THE
WHOLE GANG UP HERE AT
POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheering and applause]
SIT DOWN, GUYS.
HAVE A SEAT.
DOWN, DOWN, DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, WE GOT
A CALL FROM THE WIVES.
AND ANY OF YOU WHO HAD THE
POSSUM LODGE STEW,
YOUR WIVES ASKED YOU NOT TO
COME HOME FOR A FEW DAYS.
[applause]