♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: HI, THIS IS RED GREEN
ON TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD IS
GOING TO TALK ABOUT SEX
OF ALL THINGS,
BILL IS GOING TO WORK
ON HIS SAILBOAT,
AND I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO DISCOURAGE TAILGATERS.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: AND NOW HERE'S
A LIVING LEGEND,
A GIANT WHO EVEN MAKES
PAUL BUNYAN LOOK SMALL
IN OVERSEAS TELEVISION
SALES ANYWAY.
HERE HE IS THE STAR OF OUR SHOW,
MR. RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
INTERESTING INTRO THERE HAROLD,
I'VE NEVER BEEN COMPARED TO
PAUL BUNYAN BEFORE.
I GUESS THAT MAKES YOU
HIS PET OX BLUE.
>>HAROLD: WELL CAN HIS
PET OX BLUE DO THIS?
>>RED: YEAH IF HE
EATS ENOUGH BRAN.
WELL YESTERDAY WE ALL GOT
BORED AGAIN SO WE FIGURED
POSSUM LODGE COULD USE
A FEW IMPROVEMENTS,
WE KICKED AROUND THE IDEA
OF MAKING A WATER PURIFICATION
SYSTEM OR MAYBE A COMPOSTER OR
SOME KIND OF A RECYCLING UNIT,
AND THAT STRUCK US AS A BIT
OF A YAWN SO WE DECIDED
TO MAKE A SUBMARINE PEN.
>>HAROLD: A SUBMARINE PEN?
WHAT DO WE NEED A
SUBMARINE PEN FOR?
WE DON'T EVEN HAVE A SUBMARINE.
>>RED: WELL WE MAY HAVE SOME
DAY AND MOST OF OUR BOATS
ARE ALMOST SUBMARINES.
>>HAROLD: YEAH THAT'S RIGHT,
THAT'S TRUE YEAH.
>>RED: OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
MADE A SUBMARINE QUITE
A FEW YEARS AGO BACK WHEN
HE WAS KNOWN AS MIDDLE AGED
MAN SEDGEWICK BUT IT HAD
AN ENGINEERING FLAW IN IT,
HE PUT A SCREEN DOOR ON HER
AND SHE SANK, BUT HE ENDED UP
DONATING IT TO THE LODGE.
>>HAROLD: OH IS THAT WHY
THE SEPTIC TANK HAS A
CONNING TOWER AND A PERISCOPE?
>>RED: YEAH.
SO THE FIRST STEP IN BUILDING
OUR SUBMARINE PEN WAS TO GET
STINKY TO FIRE UP HIS CEMENT
TRUCK AND DROP OFF A LOAD
OF CONCRETE.
AND WE WERE ALL RIGHT IN
THE MIDDLE OF POURING IT
AND THEN WELL, WE TOOK A BREAK
TO GO INTO THE LODGE AND WATCH
GILLIGAN'S ISLAND AND YOU KNOW
HOW MEN KIND OF GLAZE OVER WHEN
THEY'RE WATCHING TELEVISION.
THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW
IT'S 9 O'CLOCK THIS MORNING,
THE CEMENT HAS HARDENED
AS SOLID AS A ROCK.
SO NOW WHAT WE'VE GOT IS
A CONCRETE TRUCK AND 60 FEET
OF POURING TROUGH CEMENTED
TO THE SHORELINE.
BUT JUNIOR SINGLETON SAYS HE
CAN GET THE WHOLE MESS OUT
OF THERE WITH ABOUT
4 FEET OF STRING.
>>HAROLD: HOW DOES THAT WORK?
>>RED: THAT'S THE FUSE
FOR THE DYNAMITE HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: WELL I'LL BE SPENDING
THE REST OF THE DAY IN MY ROOM.
>>RED: GOLLY WE SHOULD
DO THIS MORE OFTEN.
♪ MY GREAT GRANDDADDY ♪
♪ WAS THE BEST OF THEM ALL ♪
♪ TOUGH AS A TREE STUMP ♪
♪ AND DAMN NEAR AS TALL ♪
♪ HE DRANK AND HE SMOKED ♪
♪ FROM THE DAY HE WAS BORN ♪
♪ CAROUSED AND HAD THE ♪
♪ BELOW AVERAGE HYGIENE ♪
♪ PLUS HE ATE A LOT ♪
♪ OF JUNK FOOD ♪
♪ AND HE WAS NEVER SICK ♪
♪ A DAY IN HIS LIFE ♪
♪ AND HE LIVED TO BE ♪
♪ ALMOST 27 ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE GOING
TO SHOW YOU A FEW SIMPLE
PROJECTS THAT WILL MAKE OUR
HIGHWAY SAFER, AT LEAST FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW MOST MEN ARE
DEFENSIVE DRIVERS, JUST ASK
THEM ABOUT THEIR DRIVING,
SEE HOW DEFENSIVE THEY GET.
BUT THE KIND OF DRIVER THAT
REALLY STEAMS MY CLAMS
IS THE TAILGATER.
YOU KNOW THE GUY,
HE'S USUALLY IN A LITTLE CAR,
IT'S USUALLY A RED ONE
AND IT'S ABOUT THE SIZE
OF A SHOEBOX AND SMELLS
AROUND THE SAME
AND HE'S ALWAYS OH 18 YEARS OLD.
SOMETIMES THEY'RE 18 AND A HALF,
BUT YOU VERY RARELY SEE
ANYONE OVER 25 TAILGATING
BECAUSE THEY TEND TO HAVE REAL
SHORT CAREERS AND YOU KNOW YOU
CAN'T REASON WITH TAILGATERS
BECAUSE THEY CAN'T HEAR YOU
OVER THAT HOLE IN THEIR MUFFLER
OR ELSE THEY GOT THAT STEREO
THUMPING, PUMPING WITH THE
SUPER TURBO BASS ON THERE.
AND THE LITTLE, THIN SHEET METAL
ON THE JAPANESE CARS ARE JUST
PUMPING AND PUMPING AND GRINDING
LIKE THAT AND MAKE YOU SICK
TO YOUR STOMACH.
THERE IS ONE THING
TAILGATERS DO UNDERSTAND, FEAR.
HERE'S AN IDEA ONE OF
OUR VIEWERS SENT IN.
YOU TAKE A LUNCH PAIL OR
A THERMOS OR EVEN A BRIEFCASE,
OR ALL 3 IF YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY
MADE OF MONEY AND YOU SCREW
THEM RIGHT TO THE ROOF OF YOUR
CAR WITH THESE DRYWALL SCREWS.
ALL RIGHT THOSE ARE REALLY
ON THERE, THEY'RE NOT GOING
ANYWHERE, OF COURSE NOW YOUR
TAILGATER DOESN'T KNOW THAT,
HE FIGURES YOU JUST PUT THESE
UP HERE WHILE YOU KNOW REACHED
AROUND IN YOUR POCKETS FOR
YOUR CAR KEYS AND THEN ONCE YOU
FOUND THEM YOU JUST GOT IN AND
YOU DROVE AWAY AND YOU FORGOT
ABOUT THEM, SO I'LL TELL YOU,
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO GET A
TAILGATER IF YOU'RE DOING 60
MILES AN HOUR DOWN THE HIGHWAY,
THESE PEOPLE TEND TO STAY BACK.
HERE I'LL SHOW YOU ANOTHER
TRICK THAT WORKED REAL WELL,
THE FIRST STEP IS YOU GOT
TO REMOVE YOUR BACK BUMPER.
NOW THAT MAY TAKE A LITTLE
LONGER FOR THOSE FUSS BUDGETS
OUT THERE WHO HAD THE
THING RUST PROOFED.
ALL RIGHT NOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED TO FINISH THIS PROJECT
IS A BALL OF TWINE OF SOME KIND
AND A COUPLE OF OLD PENS
AND A ROLL OF THE HANDYMAN
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT NOW I'VE REATTACHED
THE BUMPER WITH THESE LITTLE
PIECES OF STRING WHICH ARE
ACTUALLY STRONGER THAN
THE OLD RUST BALLS THAT
WERE HOLDING THEM ON IN
THE FIRST PLACE.
NOW THESE ARE ALL SLIPKNOTS,
IT'S IMPORTANT,
YOU'LL SEE WHY IN A MINUTE.
NOW TO KEEP THE STRINGS ALL
SEPARATE WE RUN THEM UP THROUGH
THESE OLD BALLPOINT PENS,
YOU CAN GET BALLPOINT PENS
REAL CHEAP ESPECIALLY IF YOU
WAIT UNTIL THE GUY'S WHO'S
GOING TO CHECK YOUR OIL
AT THE GAS STATION
YOU JUST TAKE THEM,
THEY DON'T MIND.
AND THEN TAKE THEM ALL UP
HERE AND TIE THEM IN A KNOT
AND GET DOWN AND HOOK THEM
RIGHT INTO YOUR DASHBOARD.
SO NOW YOU'RE DRIVING ALONG,
YOU'RE DOING MAYBE 40, 50 MILES
BELOW THE SPEED LIMIT AND
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT SOME
GOOFBALL IS COMING RIGHT UP
TO YOUR BACK BUMPER,
I MEAN JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE IN
THE PASSING LANE I GUESS AND
YOU'RE GETTING A LITTLE TICKED
BUT JUST WAIT, JUST WAIT,
I'M WATCHING THE REARVIEW MIRROR
AND WHEN HE GETS UP REAL CLOSE
AND YOU CAN SEE THE WHITES
OF HIS EYES, JUST PULL
AND THE BUMPER FALLS
RIGHT OFF THERE.
IT USUALLY GETS INTO A KIND OF
AN END OVER END THING AND WILL
GET UNDER HIS CAR AND PUNCTURE
ALL OF HIS TIRES AND PROBABLY
RIP OFF HIS OIL TANK THERE AND
GET RIGHT THROUGH THE GASOLINE
THAT'S GOING TO AND THEN
YOU REALLY SEE THE WHITES
OF HIS EYES.
BUT YOU KNOW IF YOU WANT TO
TRY A LITTLE MORE SUBTLE TACTIC
THERE IS ANOTHER THING
YOU CAN USE
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED A CAN
OF SPRAY PAINT AND A, YUP,
VERY GOOD AND YOU'LL NEED SOME
OF THE HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON,
PUT YOUR GLASSES ON HAROLD,
DUCT TAPE, AND WE'LL SHOW YOU
HOW THAT, AND YOU ALSO NEED
AN OLD PIANO, DON'T BOTHER!
THIS IS GOING TO TAKE A
LITTLE WHILE SO WHY DON'T
I JUST RIG THIS UP AND YOU
GO BACK TO THE SHOW,
WHEN I GET HER ALL DONE
AND WE'LL HAVE YOU BACK
AND I'LL SHOW YOU SOMETHING
REALLY NEAT,
(PAINT CAN SPRITZ)
OH FOR GOD'S SAKE!
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S THAT
PART OF THE SHOW WHERE WE
EXPOSE THOSE 3 LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND IT SO
DIFFICULT TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT
ONCE AGAIN ON 'THE EXPERTS'
PORTION OF THE SHOW IS MY
UNCLE RED AND HIS GOOD FRIEND,
MR. BOB STUYVESANT.
ALL RIGHTY, 'DEAR EXPERTS,
AT WORK RECENTLY I PUNCHED
OUT A COLLEAGUE OVER
THE LAST CUP OF COFFEE,
WHEN MY BOSS SUGGESTED
I GET MY BLOOD PRESSURE
CHECKED I HEAD BUTTED HIM,
THEN THE COURT APPOINTED
A PSYCHIATRIST TO EXAMINE ME
AND HE TOLD THE JUDGE I WAS
OVERSTRESSED AND FRUSTRATED,
THIS TICKED ME OFF SO MUCH THAT
I PUNCHED HIS LIGHTS OUT TOO.
NOW I REALIZE THAT I REALLY
DO HAVE TO RELAX AND UNWIND
ESPECIALLY SINCE I WANT
TO MAKE EARLY PAROLE.'
>>RED: WELL YOU KNOW I'VE
ALWAYS FOUND IT DIFFICULT
TO RELAX MYSELF,
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN KIND OF
A HIGH STRUNG, GO, GO, GO,
KIND OF A GUY.
>>HAROLD: YOU KNOW IF YOU
REALLY WANT TO RELAX AND UNWIND
I FIND THAT HUMOUR OFTEN TIMES
WORKS AND THAT WAS AN EXAMPLE,
SAY, THEY SAY LAUGHTER IS
THE BEST MEDICINE.
KNOCK, KNOCK.
>>RED: WHO'S THERE?
>>HAROLD: HILARY CLINTON.
>>BOB: GOLF, THAT'S RELAXING,
WHEN I WANT TO UNWIND AND
I THINK THAT A GOOD GAME OF
GOLF HELPS ME RELIEVE ALL MY
TENSION AND MY FRUSTRATION.
>>RED: YOU FINALLY PLAYED
A GOOD GAME OF GOLF BOB?
>>HAROLD: REMEMBER THAT TIME
YOU LIKE WHIPPED 9 STROKES
IN A ROW ON THAT SAME BALL,
YOU ATTACKED YOUR GOLF
CART WITH THE DRIVER.
>>BOB: NOW HAROLD YOU KNOW IN
THE LETTER, THERE'S A PERFECT
EXAMPLE OF HOW YOU HAVE TO
LET OUT YOUR TENSION,
I THINK THAT YOU KNOW HITTING
MY DRIVER ON THE GOLF
CART WAS VERY LETHARGIC,
I LET OUT A LOT OF PENT
UP EMOTION, IT JUST MADE ME
FEEL A LITTLE BETTER THAT'S ALL,
I MEAN REALLY,
WHAT DID IT COST ME?
A GOLF CART AND MY
FAVOURITE DRIVER.
>>HAROLD: HE NEVER DROVE
FOR YOU AGAIN DID HE?
>>BOB: NO HE STOPPED
CADDYING ALTOGETHER ACTUALLY.
>>RED: DO YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK
YOUR PROBLEM IS BOB,
YOU'RE STANDING TOO CLOSE
TO YOUR BALL AFTER YOU HIT IT.
>>BOB: PARDON ME!
WELL I THINK I'M GOING TO GO
OUTSIDE AND HIT A BUCKET
OF BALLS TO KINGDOM COME,
AND NOBODY BETTER STOP ME!
>>HAROLD: WHEW!
WELL USUALLY HUMOUR
RELEASES TENSION.
>>RED: YOU SEE WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE
A SENSE OF HUMOUR.
>>HAROLD: KNOCK, KNOCK.
>>RED: GREAT IDEA.
>>RED: OKAY I GOT HER ALL
RIGGED UP HERE AND ONCE AGAIN
LET'S IMAGINE THAT I'M
CRUISING DOWN THE HIGHWAY
JUST MINDING MY OWN BUSINESS,
KIND OF DRIFTING FROM LANE
TO LANE WITH MY MOOD SWINGS
AND SO ON AND SUDDENLY ALL
OF A SUDDEN I GOT MYSELF
A TAILGATER, WELL WHAT I'VE
GOT HERE IS, UP ON THE DASHBOARD
I'VE GOT THESE PIANO KEYS
CONNECTED TO SOME OLD
EMERGENCY BRAKE CABLES,
WHO USES THE EMERGENCY BRAKE?
AND THEY GO DOWN TO THE BACK
AND HOOK INTO THE PIANO HAMMERS
BUT THEY'RE NOT PLAYING STRINGS
ANY MORE, THEY'RE PLAYING
CANS OF SPRAY PAINT.
SO NOW I SAY PICK A COLOUR,
WELL WHITE KEY, WHITE PAINT,
♪ NOTE PLAYS ♪
(PAINT SPRITZ)
OR I COULD ACTUALLY PLAY
A WHOLE SYMPHONY OF COLOURS,
♪ KEYBOARD NOTES PLAYING ♪
(PAINT SPRITZ)
IF I COULD DO SAY 4 BARS OF
THE FLIGHT OF THE BUMBLEBEE,
I COULD CHANGE HIS RED SPORTS
CAR INTO ONE OF THEM
PSYCHEDELIC VANS FROM WOODSTOCK.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU THE REAL
PIECE TO RESISTANCE HERE,
I UNDO MY ROPE IN HERE BECAUSE
I HAVE SOME TAILGATER, GRAFFITI.
♪ DRUM ROLL ♪
I DROP MY HANDY DANDY STENCIL
IN THERE AND NOW THE SPRAY
PAINT IS GOING RIGHT THROUGH
THERE AND LEAVING A REAL
COLOURFUL MESSAGE ON
THE FRONT OF HIS CAR.
WE KNOW HE CAN'T DRIVE
BUT HE CAN PROBABLY READ
AND SO CAN EVERYBODY ELSE.
OKAY, I KNOW YOU CAN'T REALLY
DO ALL THIS STUFF THAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT BECAUSE WELL
IT'S DANGEROUS AND IT'S ILLEGAL
AND IT'S PROBABLY GOING TO YOU
KNOW RESULT IN THE LOSS OF LIFE
AND YOU KNOW WHAT LIVES ARE LIKE
BUT YOU KNOW IF YOU DID WANT
TO TRY SAY THE BUMPER THING
JUST BE REAL CAREFUL THAT
THE TAILGATER DOESN'T HAVE
THE FLASHING LIGHTS ON
THE TOP BECAUSE THOSE GUYS
HAVE NO SENSE OF HUMOUR.
THEY PULL YOU RIGHT OVER,
TAKE YOUR LICENSE RIGHT ON THE
SPOT AND THAT IS $125 FINE
AND YOU ONLY GET 14 DAYS TO PAY.
OR I MEAN I WOULD IMAGINE IT
WOULD BE SOMETHING IN THAT AREA.
ANYWAY UNTIL NEXT TIME,
REMEMBER IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I GOT TO GO BORROW SOME MONEY.
>>RED: YOU KNOW MY GRANDMOTHER
ON MY MOTHER'S SIDE ONCE SAID
TO ME THAT EVERY PROBLEM
IS AN OPPORTUNITY,
LIKE WHEN MY GRANDFATHER
WAS HAVING A PROBLEM
IN THE BEDROOM, SHE TOOK
THE OPPORTUNITY TO RUN OFF
WITH THE POSTMAN.
SO I SAY OUR CEMENT TRUCK AND
TROUGH MESS IS NOT A PROBLEM
IT'S AN OPPORTUNITY,
AN OPPORTUNITY TO BUILD
A WATERSLIDE.
>>HAROLD: OH BOY.
>>RED: AND THAT'LL BE JUST
THE BEGINNING OF THE POSSUM
LODGE WATER THEME PARK.
>>HAROLD: EXCUSE ME UNCLE RED
BUT I DON'T THINK YOU CAN
HAVE A THEME PARK WITH JUST
LIKE ONE ATTRACTION THERE.
>>RED: WELL WE KNOW THAT HAROLD,
WE'RE GOING TO DO ALL KINDS
OF THINGS, WE'RE PAINTING
THE SNOWMOBILES IN BRIGHT
SUMMER COLOURS SO THEY'LL FLOAT,
AND OLD MAN SEDGEWICK IS
BUILDING A PLYWOOD BEACH,
AND YOU KNOW EVERY THEME PARK
HAS TO HAVE A MASCOT,
WAIT UNTIL YOU SEE WILLY WHALE.
>>HAROLD: WILLY WHALE?
>>RED: YUP, MOOSE THOMPSON
IS GOING TO BE WILLY WHALE.
>>HAROLD: IT SAVES US
BUYING A COSTUME.
>>RED: AND ONCE THE PEOPLE
ARRIVE MOOSE IS GOING TO
WADDLE OUT INTO POSSUM BAY,
START DOING DEEP KNEE BENDS
AND WE'VE GOT AN INSTANT
WAVE POOL.
IT'S GOING TO BE BIG HAROLD,
THE PEOPLE ARE GOING TO BE JUST
RUSHING INTO WILLY WHALE'S
WATER WONDERLAND.
>>HAROLD: ABSOLUTELY!
DOCTORS, POLICEMEN, FIREMEN,
AIR AMBULANCE CREWS.
>>RED: AS LONG AS
THEY PAY TO GET IN HAROLD.
♪ THE SUNDAY SCHOOL PICNIC ♪
♪ IS A GALA AFFAIR ♪
♪ EVERYONE TREATS IT ♪
♪ WITH PRIDE ♪
♪ WITH BRIGHT, SHINY FACES ♪
♪ AND 3-LEGGED RACES ♪
♪ AND NOWHERE THE DEVIL ♪
♪ CAN HIDE ♪
♪ WE GOT ANTS IN THE COLESLAW ♪
♪ BUGS IN THE MEATLOAF ♪
♪ AND A BIG CRUNCH ♪
♪ WHEN 2 KIDS COLLIDE ♪
♪ WITH GAMES THAT INJURY US ♪
♪ FOOD THAT'S BACETERIAEOUS ♪
♪ IT'S A GOOD THING ♪
♪ THE LORD IS ON THEIR SIDE ♪
>>RED: WELL I'VE GOT
A KIND OF INTERESTING
'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'
FOR YOU THIS WEEK.
THIS IS THE TIME OF THE YEAR
WHERE EVERYBODY KIND OF GETS
THEIR BOAT READY TO PUT
AWAY FOR THE WINTER AND
BILL'S NO EXCEPTION.
HE'S SCRAPING HIS BOAT AND
EVERYTHING, YOU GOT TO CLIMB UP.
AND WHEN YOU GOT A SAILBOAT
THEY'RE KIND OF HIGH BECAUSE
OF THE KEEL AND SO ON,
SO YOU GOT TO CLIMB UP ON TOP
OF THEM TO, AND BILL HAD A,
AND THEN, WELL I'M JUST GOING
TO STEP, OKAY JUST STEP ON
MY FOOT THERE, OH.
BILL I GUESS HAD STEPPED
INTO SOMETHING OF, YEAH, EW!
>>BILL: EW!
>>RED: YEAH, WELL ANYWAY,
OKAY NOW WE GOT TO GET THE
OTHER SHOE, YEAH THE OTHER ONE,
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
NO INSTEAD OF BOTH FEET,
OH, OH, OH, OH BOY,
WELL SO WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
A LITTLE EXTRA MAINTENANCE
TO DO ON THE BOAT THIS YEAR.
BUT LUCKILY, STILL WE GOT TO
GET UP AND YOU GOT TO GET IN,
YOU GOT TO GET INTO THE COCKPIT
AND GET ALL OF THE WATER
OUT OF THE BILGE AND YOU GOT
TO GET INTO THE CABIN THERE
AND THE FORE AND AFT AND THE
GUNNELS AND THE FORESTAYS
AND THE BACKSTAYS AND SO
BILL'S GOING TO USE THE ROPE,
AND HE'LL THROW A ROPE OVER
TO ME AND THEN I'LL PULL HIM UP.
BUT YOU KNOW A SWINGING ROPE IS
NOT ALL THAT EASY AND IT WASN'T
GOING REAL WELL BUT BILL DIDN'T
SEEM TO NOTICE, BUT NOW THE
THING IS, WHAT DO YOU DO?
DO GO AND TAKE OVER OR
DO YOU JUST DIVERT?
MANAGEMENT TRAINING THING IS YOU
LET A GUY LEARN BY HIS MISTAKES
SO WE LET, YOU KNOW WHEN IT
COMES TO MISTAKES BILL IS
PRETTY WELL THE EXPERT THERE.
YOU FORGOT TO HANG ONTO
THE END THERE BILL,
SO I GUESS WE GOT TO SORT OF,
SOMETIMES YOU GOT TO TAKE
CHARGE AND SAY NOW HERE'S
HOW YOU DO IT,
YOU GO STAND OVER THERE,
I'LL HOLD THE END,
SEE HOW IT WORKS?
NOW THROW THIS AROUND,
WATCH, NOW GRAB IT BILL
GRAB IT! GRAB IT!
>>RED: BILL?
(BILL MOANING)
>>RED: NOW WHAT HE WANTS TO
DO IS, SEE BILL YOU GOT TO TIE
THAT TO SOMETHING SOLID SO
WHEN YOU PULL AGAINST IT.
YEAH, OH THE POSSUM VAN
IS PRETTY SOLID I GUESS,
NOW I'LL TAKE UP THE SLACK HERE
AND THEN YOU CAN PULL DOWN ON
THAT AND JUST, MEANWHILE WHAT
I DIDN'T REALIZE,
OH, THE SLACK'S NOT,
YEAH, WHAT I DIDN'T REALIZE
IS THAT THERE WAS A FILM
FESTIVAL GOING ON OF ALL
CARTOONS DOWN AT THE POSSUM
THEATRE AND HAROLD WANTED TO GO,
SO HE HAD HID IN THE VAN
AND HE DROVE OFF AND WHAT
I DIDN'T REALIZE IS,
I GUESS BILL HAD DECIDED
TO GO WITH HIM.
YOU BOYS HAVE A GOOD TIME AT
THE SHOW, I'LL SEE YOU LATER!
>>RED: AND NOW HERE'S
HAROLD WITH SOMETHING FOR
ALL YOU TEENAGERS,
MY ADVICE IS YOU MIGHT
AS WELL GO FOR A SODA.
>>HAROLD: WELCOME TO THE TEEN
SHOW THAT TALKS TO TEENS ABOUT
TEEN STUFF AND WELL TODAY'S
TOPIC IS SEX MYTHS.
OKAY WELL THE OLDEST SEX MYTH
AROUND HERE IS MY UNCLE RED.
TAGGED HIM, OKAY, WELL, HI, HI,
DID YOU JUST HEAR WHAT I SAID?
>>RED: NO WHY,
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
>>HAROLD: OH NOTHING,
OH YOU KNOW, NOTHING.
ACTUALLY THE OLDEST SEX MYTH
IS THAT THE MALE SEX IS
THE DOMINANT ONE OF
THE HUMAN SPECIES.
>>RED: HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: YES.
>>RED: DID YOU JUST SAY THAT
I WAS THE OLDEST SEX MYTH?
>>HAROLD: A LITTLE YEAH.
ANYWAY, YOU KNOW IT'S NOT TRUE
THAT THE MALE HAS TO BE
THE DOMINANT ONE IN ANY
RELATIONSHIP, NO, NO, NO, NO,
BECAUSE SOME MEN ARE VERY
SENSITIVE YOU KNOW AND SHY,
IN SUCH A CASE THEREFORE IT
WOULD BE YOU KNOW PERFECTLY
ACCEPTABLE AND SENSIBLE AND
YOU KNOW MORE OFTEN THAN NOT
NECESSARY FOR THE FEMALE
TO ASK HIM OUT,
THAT WOULD BE A VERY 90'S
UPFRONT THING FOR LADIES
TO DO, IT WOULD.
>>RED: HAROLD, DON'T BEG.
>>HAROLD: IT SHOWS DOES IT?
>>RED: OH YEAH.
>>RED: I KNOW A LOT OF YOU
TEENAGERS ARE ENJOYING YOUR
DATING YEARS GOING OUT WITH
DIFFERENT BOYS AND GIRLS
DEPENDING ON WHO YOU'RE IN
LOVE WITH AT THAT MOMENT OR
WHO HAS A CAR OR WHO HAS
MCDONALD'S COUPONS.
I KNOW IT'S FUN SOWING YOUR
WILD OATS OR WHEAT OR BRAN
OR WHATEVER YOUR ORIENTATION IS.
BUT YOU KNOW EVENTUALLY THAT
FUN IS GOING TO HAVE TO COME
TO AN END, IT'LL BE TIME TO
GET MARRIED OR LEAVE TOWN.
I SUGGEST YOU GET MARRIED,
NOT THAT MARRIAGE IS PERFECT
BUT AT LEAST IT GIVES YOU ONE
LESS THING TO WORRY ABOUT
AS YOU LOSE YOUR LOOKS,
SO MY POINT IS THAT WHILE
YOU'RE DATING BE REALLY
CAREFUL BECAUSE NOBODY'S GOING
TO WANT TO MARRY YOU IF YOU'RE
FLAT BROKE OR IN PRISON OR
IF YOU HAVE SOME KIND OF
UNIDENTIFIED RASH,
OR IF YOU'RE HAROLD.
>>RED: HEY GLEN, GOOD NEWS,
I GOT SOME BUSINESS FOR YOU.
>>GLEN: I GOT SOME BETTER
NEWS RED, I'M ON VACATION.
YUP, I'M OFF TO ONE OF THE
BIGGEST AMUSEMENT PARKS
IN ALL OF FLORIDA,
ELMER'S EEL WORLD.
YUP, THEY GOT TRAINED EELS
THERE RED, THEY GOT MARVIN
THE MAGNIFICENT MORAY WHO CAN
PLAY THE XYLOPHONE ALL BY
HIMSELF JUST BANG, IT'S GREAT.
>>RED: BUT GLEN
IT'S HIGH SEASON.
>>GLEN: OH THAT'S OKAY BECAUSE
ELMER'S IS NEVER, EVER BUSY.
>>RED: NO, NO, NO,
I MEAN IT'S HIGH SEASON HERE,
WHAT ABOUT YOUR CUSTOMERS?
>>GLEN: OH WELL, GEEZ I COULD
TAKE MAYBE 8 OF THEM BUT
NO WHINERS, NO SMOKERS AND
CERTAINLY NOBODY WITH
A SMALL BLADDER.
>>RED: NO, NO, NO, GLEN,
NO I MEAN BECAUSE OF YOUR
MARINA HERE, HOW ARE YOU GOING
TO BE ABLE TO SELL BOATS
IF YOU'RE NOT EVEN HERE?
>>GLEN: WELL I DON'T NEED
TO RED, I'VE ALREADY MET
MY QUOTA FOR THE YEAR.
>>RED: OH YEAH,
WHO SET YOUR QUOTA?
>>GLEN: I DID.
>>RED: ARE YOU TELLING ME
THAT YOU'VE ALREADY MADE ENOUGH
MONEY FOR THE WHOLE SEASON?
>>GLEN: WELL NO NOT EXACTLY RED,
WHAT I'VE DONE IS I MADE ENOUGH
TO BORROW AGAINST NEXT
YEAR'S QUOTA, IT GIVES
ME A BETTER TAX SITUATION.
>>RED: WELL I'M SORRY GLEN
BUT I HAVE TO BUY A BOAT
FOR OUR WATER PARK.
>>GLEN: OH THAT'S A PROBLEM RED
SEE BECAUSE I'VE ALREADY DONE
MY BOOKS FOR THE WHOLE YEAR,
SO IF I MAKE ANOTHER SALE THAT
THROWS OFF MY BALANCE SHEET
REAL BAD, WHAT I COULD DO
THOUGH IS I COULD SELL YOU
A BOAT NOW AND YOU COULD
TAKE DELIVERY NEXT SUMMER.
>>RED: NO, NO, NO, NO
THAT WON'T WORK,
MAYBE YOU COULD RENT ME A BOAT?
>>GLEN: WELL I COULD DO THAT
SURE EXCEPT THEY'RE ALL BROKEN.
>>RED: WELL YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO FIX ONE OF THEM GLEN.
>>GLEN: OH I CAN'T DO THAT RED,
NO, NO, WHAT I COULD DO IS I
COULD RENT YOU A BOAT AS IS
AND I COULD RENT YOU SOME TOOLS
AND THEN YOU CAN HELP YOURSELF.
YOU SEE I'M GONE,
DON'T YOU GET IT?
I'M GONE, I'M GOING HOME,
I'M GOING TO PICK UP MY LOVELY
WIFE, MY 7 BEAUTIFUL DAUGHTERS
AND I'M GOING TO SURPRISE THEM
WITH A TRIP TO ELMER'S EEL WORLD
♪ EEL WORLD ♪
♪ IT'S THE REAL WORLD ♪
♪ IT'S THE SQUEALLY, REALLY ♪
♪ EEL WORLD ♪
RED I'LL SEE YOU IN
A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
>>RED: IT COULD BE A TAD
SHORTER THAN THAT GLEN.
>>RED: WELL WILLY WHALE'S WATER
WONDERLAND WAS A WASHOUT,
YOU TRY TO DO SOMETHING NICE
FOR PEOPLE AND ALL YOU
GET IS COMPLAINTS.
>>HAROLD: I DON'T KNOW UNCLE RED
I THINK THOSE PEOPLE ON THE
WATERSLIDE WERE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT
I DON'T SEE ANY FUN MYSELF
BEING YOU KNOW ROLLED AROUND
INSIDE OF A CEMENT TRUCK
AND THEN DUMPED OUT ONTO
A CONCRETE TROUGH.
>>RED: AND OF COURSE MOOSE
THOMPSON'S KNEE GOES OUT
SO THAT'S THE END OF OUR
WAVE MACHINE, THEN HE TRIES
TO MAKE DUE BY DUCT TAPING
THE BARN DOOR TO THE PILE DRIVER
AND THUMPING THAT INTO THE WATER
WHICH WAS A CERTAIN AMOUNT OF
OVERKILL NOT TO MENTION WHAT
THE BARN DOOR DID TO THE LAKE.
>>HAROLD: YOU SHOULD HAVE
SMELLED THAT, WHEW!
IT WAS LIKE AN OLD HORSE
ON A HUMID DAY YOU KNOW.
>>RED: HAROLD I SAID
DO NOT TO MENTION.
>>HAROLD: OH.
>>RED: THAT WAS ONE GREAT WAVE
MACHINE I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
>>HAROLD: THAT WAS
A TIDAL WAVE MACHINE.
>>RED: WHAT DO YOU CALL
A WAVE THAT SIZE HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: TSUNAMI.
>>RED: GAZOONTITE.
SO ANYWAY WE'VE DECIDED TO TAKE
THE PROBLEM OF THE PERSONAL
INJURY AND PROPERTY DAMAGE
LAWSUITS AND TURN THEM INTO
THE OPPORTUNITY OF CLOSING
THE WATER THEME PARK FOREVER.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH, OKAY.
WELL WHAT ABOUT THE FACT THAT
YOU'VE SOAKED THE ENTIRE
POSSUM LAKE AREA?
>>RED: WELL THAT'S GOOD BECAUSE
IT MEANS THE RISK OF FOREST
FIRE IS DOWN TO ZERO.
>>HAROLD: SO IS THE WATER
LEVEL IN POSSUM LAKE.
>>RED: GOOD, WE'LL GET
THE SNOWMOBILES BACK.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: CALL OF THE MEETING,
I'M GOING TO GO DOWN.
>>RED: YEAH OKAY HAROLD YOU
GO AHEAD, I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
>>RED: WELL IT WASN'T AN
UNPARALLELED SUCCESS I GUESS
BUT ALL OTHER THINGS BEING
CONSIDERED WE DID OKAY.
AND IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING I'LL
BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME AFTER
THE MEETING AND MY CLOTHES
ARE ALL SOAKED HERE
SO I'M JUST GOING TO THROW
THEM IN THE DRYER AND THEY
COULD REALLY USE A QUICK TUMBLE,
COME TO THINK OF IT
I'M SOAKING WET MYSELF...
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF HAROLD AND MYSELF
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
♪ ♪ ♪
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: SIT DOWN.
NOW I'D LIKE TO KIND OF KEEP
THE MEETING MOVING ALONG TONIGHT
BECAUSE I'M A LITTLE
UNCOMFORTABLE HERE,
I GOT WATER IN SOME VERY SPECIAL
PLACES AND I'D KIND OF LIKE TO
GET HOME AND KIND OF REVERSE
THAT WHOLE PROCESS SO.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca