HOW MANY TIMES HAVE YOU BEEN
IN THE MIDDLE OF A HOT SHOWER
WHEN SOMEBODY FLUSHES
THE TOILET SOMEWHERE
AND YOU UNDERGO A REAL QUICK
CHANGE IN TEMPERATURE
AND HEART RATE?
I'LL TELL YOU IT'S THE
BIGGEST SHOCK YOU CAN
GET IN THE BATHROOM
SINCE THE INVENTION OF
THE FULL-LENGTH MIRROR.
WELL, I HAVE A
REAL SIMPLE SOLUTION.
GET YOURSELF A BUNCH
OF THESE SAFETY FLARES.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE JUST THROW
THEM INTO THE TRUNK
OF THEIR CAR,
AND THEN THEY
FORGET ABOUT THEM.
SO NOBODY'S GONNA MIND IF YOU
JUST KINDA HELP YOURSELF.
WHAT YOU DO IS YOU
JUST WRAP THESE BABIES
IN AROUND YOUR
SHOWER HEAD, SEE?
JUST LIKE THAT THERE.
THEN WHEN YOU LIGHT 'EM,
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN IS
THEY'RE GONNA HEAT THE WATER
AS IT COMES THROUGH THE PIPE.
WHICH MEANS ALL YOU GOTTA DO
IS TURN ON THE COLD WATER.
THAT SAVES YOU MONEY.
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY,
IT'S FLUSH PROOF.
PERFECT.
AND YOU KNOW,
UNDER THIS WARM GLOW,
EVEN US MIDDLE AGED GUYS
DON'T LOOK TOO BAD NAKED.
I WONDER WHAT BERNICE
IS DOING RIGHT NOW?
[laughter and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE THAT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
IT'S OUR ANNUAL
MR. POSSUM LAKE COMPETITION
WITH CARIBOU LODGE THERE.
IT'S BASED ON
STRENGTH AND SPEED.
ONE YEAR WE BASED IT ON LOOKS,
BUT EVERYBODY CAME IN FOURTH.
SO WE'VE GONE BACK
TO STRENGTH AND SPEED
BECAUSE IF YOU CAN'T BE
STRONG, YOU GOTTA BE FAST;
IF YOU CAN'T BE FAST,
YOU GOTTA BE STRONG.
IF YOU CAN BE BOTH YOU
CAN BE MR. POSSUM LAKE.
IF YOU CAN'T BE EITHER,
YOU CAN BE HAROLD.
[laughter and applause]
HI, UNCLE RED.
WHAT'S WITH
THE BASKET?
YOU ON YOUR WAY
TO GRANDMA'S HOUSE?
HA-HA, NO!
I WAS COLLECTING
PINE CONES.
AND I SAW THE GUYS
LINED UP DOWN AT THE DOCK.
WHY IS MOOSE THOMPSON
IN A THONG?
IT MAY BE A THONG NOW,
BUT WHEN HE PUT IT ON
IT WAS BERMUDA SHORTS.
THEY'RE ACTUALLY GETTING
READY FOR THE STRENGTH
COMPETITION.
THEY'VE GOTTA
LIFT THIS BOX --
I'M GONNA TAKE IT DOWN
TO THEM IN A MINUTE.
YOU SEE, THE WAY IT
WORKS IS THAT EACH
OF THE TWO LODGES
HAS TO PICK JUST ONE
GUY TO REPRESENT THEM.
SO WE HAVE TO
PICK OUR GUY.
I DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU DO IT LIKE THAT.
I THINK EVERYBODY SHOULD
BE ABLE TO COMPETE.
YOU KNOW, THAT WAY GUYS
LIKE ME WOULD HAVE A CHANCE.
HAROLD, GUYS LIKE YOU
NEVER HAVE A CHANCE.
IF WE LET
EVERYBODY COMPETE,
WE WOULD NEED A
BIGGER HOSPITAL.
FINE. FINE.
MAYBE I SHOULD
TRY OUT, THOUGH,
BECAUSE THIS YEAR THEY'RE
LOOKING FOR STRENGTH, SPEED
AND INTELLIGENCE.
WHAT?
YEAH, THEY CHANGED
THE RULES.
YEAH, YOU NEED SOMEBODY WHO'S
STRONG, FAST AND SMART.
OH, BOY. OKAY.
OH, NO!
LET ME TRY.
OH, HAROLD,
REALLY?
MY HANDS ARE SWEATY.
THAT'S THE THING.
THEY'RE SWEATY.
I JUST GET A
LITTLE POWDER.
[coughing]
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU SHOULD BE GOOD
AT THIS, HAROLD.
"CLEAN" AND "JERK"
ARE YOUR MIDDLE NAMES.
THERE YOU GO.
HEY! HUH? HUH?
[laughter and applause]
OW-W-W!
THAT'S GOOD WORK.
BRING IT DOWN TO THE
DOCK SO I CAN PUT THE
WEIGHTS IN IT.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[laughter and applause]
TONIGHT'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FOR A WHOLE WEEKEND
OF PONY RIDES...
IN A 1984 HYUNDAI PONY.
OFFER SUBJECT TO
AVAILABILITY OF TOW TRUCK.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
EARS THERE, MIKE.
RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MIKE HAMAR
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, MIKE,
WHAT DO YOU HAVE
WHEN YOU HAVE
24 BOTTLES OF BEER?
BLURRED VISION?
OKAY. OKAY, MIKE,
WHEN YOU'RE IN TROUBLE,
THIS IS WHAT YOUR
LAWYER PLEADS.
TO PAY HIS FEE.
OKAY, YOU'RE
FAMILIAR WITH THESE.
IT'S CALLED AN
OPEN AND SHUT...
CASH REGISTER.
OKAY, THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
MOST BUSINESS MEN HAVE,
A BRIEF...
AFFAIR?
OKAY, SAY THERE'S
A CRIME WAVE, OKAY,
AND THE POLICE CHIEF HAS
KIND OF A NEWS CONFERENCE,
HE'LL SAY MY BEST
DETECTIVES ARE ON THE...
TAKE.
YOU GUYS ARE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME HERE.
OKAY, MIKE, WHEN
YOU APPEAR IN COURT
WHAT DOES THE
BAILIFF ANNOUNCE?
UH, HE SAYS, HEY, EVERYBODY,
IT'S MIKE HAMAR AGAIN!
AND SOMETIMES
HE EVEN LAUGHS,
BUT THAT'S A
WORST-CASE SCENARIO.
THERE WE GO!
[quirky upbeat music]
WELCOME TO THE EXPERTS
PORTION OF THE PROGRAMME
THIS IS WHERE WE ADDRESS
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO
HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
THAT'S TRUE,
ISN'T IT?
OKAY, TODAY'S LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
I RECENTLY TURNED 18,
"AND I AM READY
TO BECOME A MAN."
I HOPE THIS IS
FROM A GUY.
OH, WOMEN DON'T COME TO YOU,
UNCLE RED, FOR ADVICE.
WOMEN DON'T COME TO YOU
FOR ANYTHING, HAROLD.
[laughter]
"DEAR EXPERTS --
TO MAKE MYSELF MORE MATURE
"I WANT TO GROW SOME
KIND OF FACIAL HAIR.
"UNFORTUNATELY, I CAN'T
DECIDE BETWEEN A BEARD,
"A MUSTACHE, A SOUL PATCH,
A GOATEE, SIDE BURNS
"MUTTON CHOPS, CHIN MUSIC,
HANDLE BARS,
"FIVE O'CLOCK SHADOW,
FU MANCHU
"OR THE GOOD OL'
SIGMUND FREUD.
"WHAT DO YOU THINK?"
WELL, FIRST OF ALL,
YOU'RE ON THE RIGHT TRACK
BECAUSE THAT'S A GREAT
WAY TO BE VIRILE.
TO ME, THERE'S
NOTHING MORE MANLY
THAN A FULL, THICK BEARD.
ESPECIALLY IF YOU
HAVE A FULL THICK HEAD.
[laughter and applause]
UH, YOU KNOW,
I'M WITH MR. GREEN
ON THIS ONE, HAROLD.
UH, LIKE, A BEARD CAN BE
A GREAT WAY TO ALTER
YOUR APPEARANCE.
AND THAT CAN
BE EXTREMELY USEFUL.
I JUST DON'T THINK
YOU HAVE TO GROW
ALL THESE WILD WHISKERS
ALL OVER YOUR FACE.
YOU KNOW, A SIMPLE, SUBTLE
MOUSTACHE WILL DO NICELY.
LIKE MINE.
YOU HAVE A
MOUSTACHE, HAROLD?
YES!
I'M JUST VERY
FAIR HAIRED.
THAT'S ALL. SEE?
THAT'S NOT A MOUSTACHE,
THAT'S MARMALADE.
THE POINT IS...
FACIAL HAIR HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH MAKING A MAN.
THIS VIEWER CAN
DO WHATEVER THEY LIKE.
THERE'S ALL SORTS OF BEARD
CHOICES TO BE HAD OUT THERE.
JUST LOOK AT ANY
STYLE MAGAZINE.
OR IF YOU WANT A
BEARD LIKE HAROLD'S,
LOOK IN THE JAMS
AND JELLIES SECTION.
[applause]
HAVE YOU REACHED
THAT POINT IN YOUR LIFE
WHEN YOU REALISE THAT
YOU'RE NOT ALL THAT SPECIAL?
OR MORE IMPORTANTLY,
HAS YOUR WIFE REALISED IT?
WELL, TODAY I'M
GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO GET THE ATTENTION AND
RESPECT OF YOUR NEIGHBOURS.
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
THEY'VE MET YOU.
BUT, HEY,
THAT'S NOT MY FAULT.
YOU KNOW WHEN YOU
LOOK AT PICTURES
OF FANCY HOUSES
IN THESE MAGAZINES
THEN TAKE A LOOK
AT YOUR OWN HOUSE?
NOTICE A DIFFERENCE?
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT
THE NICE TREES
AND THE NO TARPS ON THE ROOF
AND THE LACK OF K-CARS
TURNED UPSIDE DOWN
ON THE FRONT LAWN.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THAT
FANCY GINGERBREAD TRIM
THEY HAVE ON THE EAVES OF SOME
OF THE NICE LOOKING HOUSES.
WOULDN'T YOUR HOUSE LOOK
GOOD WITH THAT KIND OF
TRIM ON IT?
OH, I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE THINKING...
WHERE AM I GONNA
GET THE MONEY TO DO THAT?
OR HOW AM I GONNA
PULL THAT ONE OFF?
OR, HEY, WAIT A SEC,
I'M NOT EVEN MARRIED.
WELL, YOU KNOW, LIKE SO MANY
SO MANY THINGS IN LIFE
A LOT OF TIMES THE ANSWER'S
RIGHT IN YOUR OWN BACKYARD.
CHANCES ARE YOU'VE GOT A
BUNCH OF TOYS THAT YOU
DON'T USE ANY MORE
BECAUSE YOUR KIDS
HAVE GROWN UP AND GONE.
OR MAYBE YOUR GRANDFATHER
CHARGED THEM ALL ON
YOUR VISA CARD
BEFORE YOU HAD
HIM PICKED UP.
WELL, I'VE GOT SOME
GREAT NEWS FOR YOU
BECAUSE THIS ISN'T JUST JUNK
LYING AROUND YOUR YARD
ANY LONGER.
IN ABOUT ONE COAT
OF PAINT FROM NOW,
IT'S GOING TO BE YOUR
BEAUTIFULLY DECORATIVE
GINGERBREAD TRIM.
OKAY, NOW, IF YOU USE THAT
PAINTING TECHNIQUE
YOU MAY GET A LITTLE
OVERSPRAY THERE.
YOU'LL NEVER EVEN SEE
THAT ONCE THE SNOW FLIES.
NOW YOU JUST TAKE ALL YOUR
DECORATIVE ITEMS
AROUND TO THE FRONT LAWN,
YOUR SCONCES, YOUR FINIALS,
YOUR BRIC-A-BRAC,
WHATEVER.
THEN YOU JUST ATTACH
EVERYTHING TO YOUR EAVES
IN AN ARTISTIC, YET SUBTLY
SYMMETRIC PATTERN.
OH, YEAH,
ONE OTHER RULE...
INFLATABLE TOYS DON'T
LIKE STAPLE GUNS.
AND THERE WE GO.
BRING THE LADDER DOWN
SO WE GET A BETTER LOOK.
OOP! OH! OH!
YEAH, THAT'S GOT IT.
OKAY, NOW, WHAT DID
THAT COST US, EH?
A GALLON OF PAINT,
A BACK LAWN
AND A COUPLE OF
MUSCLE SPASMS.
WELL WORTH IT.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
THIS PROJECT WILL
MAKE YOUR WIFE
FEEL PRETTY DARNED SPECIAL.
THE NEIGHBOURS ARE
REALLY GONNA NOTICE YOU NOW!
[applause]
[quirky upbeat music]
YOU EVER NOTICE THE
WAY MARRIED COUPLES DRESS
AFTER THE TEN-YEAR MARK
OF A MARRIAGE?
THE HUSBANDS
TEND TO DRESS, SAY,
A LITTLE MORE CASUALLY
THAN THE WIVES DO.
I'M SURE YOU'VE SEEN MIDDLE
AGED COUPLES AT THE MALL,
AND SHE LOOKS GREAT.
GOT THE SHARP OUTFIT
WITH THE MATCHING PURSE;
HE'S WEARING TORN JEANS
AND A STAINED SWEATSHIRT,
BOTH OF WHICH FIT
HIM SEVERAL YEARS
AND HUNDREDS OF BIG MACS AGO.
I'LL TELL YOU REASON FOR
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
MEN AND WOMEN.
WOMEN CHOOSE CLOTHES BASED ON
HOW THEY MAKE THEM LOOK,
MEN CHOOSE CLOTHES BASED ON
HOW THEY MAKE THEM
FEEL.
HUH? OH, YEAH.
SEE, MEN AREN'T THAT CONCERNED
WITH THEIR APPEARANCE,
MARRIED MEN EVEN LESS SO.
WHENEVER YOU SEE
A DRESS CODE, YOU KNOW,
AT A FUNCTION
OR AT A CLUB,
THAT'S FOR MARRIED MEN,
BELIEVE ME.
SEE, THE SINGLE MEN ARE STILL
MAKING THE SALES PRESENTATION.
MARRIED MEN HAVE
ALREADY CLOSED THE DEAL.
THEY'RE JUST TRYING
TO HONOUR THE CONTRACT
WITHOUT LOSING
ALL THEIR DIGNITY.
BUT YOU LADIES
BE CAREFUL OUT THERE,
'CAUSE EVERY MAN
WANTS SOMETHING.
THE BETTER HE'S DRESSED
THE MORE HE WANTS.
A MIDDLE AGED MARRIED GUY,
ALL HE WANTS IS
TO BE LEFT ALONE.
SO WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
WHEN HE'S WEARING THE RATTY
SWEATSHIRT AND TORN JEANS,
HECK, HE'S DRESSED
FOR SUCCESS.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU,
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
PROPANE HEATS HOUSES
FOR COUNTRY FOLK.
BUTANE IS USED TO
LIGHT UP YOUR SMOKE.
METHANE'S A GAS
WHO'S NOT UNDERSTOOD,
BUT YOU CAN TELL BY THE SMELL
HE'S UP TO NO GOOD.
HAROLD!
HAROLD, CONGRATULATIONS.
PARDON?
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU WON THE
QUALIFYING FOOT RACE.
I JUST THOUGHT YOU GUYS
WERE CHASING ME AGAIN.
NO. YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS?
THAT MEANS YOU'RE NUMBER ONE
IN THE SPEED CATEGORY.
OH! OH! HOW DID
I DO WITH STRENGTH?
YOU'RE NUMBER ONE
IN THE SPEED CATEGORY.
OKAY. WELL, HOW
ABOUT INTELLIGENCE?
WE DON'T HAVE THOSE
RESULTS BACK YET.
NOBODY EXPECTED YOU TO
ANSWER ALL THE QUESTIONS.
YOU'RE DRIVING THE
JUDGES CRAZY WITH THAT.
HEY, RED,
GOT THE RESULTS
OF THE INTELLIGENCE
PORTION.
AND HERE'S A SHOCKER...
I'M NOT AS STUPID
AS ANN MARIE SAYS I AM.
OH, SURE YOU ARE.
OH, MY GOSH.
HAROLD, YOU CAME
IN FIRST IN SPEED,
AND FIRST IN INTELLIGENCE.
OH! EXCELLENT!
OH, YES!
AND 157th IN STRENGTH,
JUST AHEAD OF
OLD MAN SEDGWICK.
WELL, ACTUALLY
OLD MAN SEDWICK BEAT HIM,
BUT HE FAILED
THE URINE TEST
BECAUSE HE COULDN'T
PRODUCE A SAMPLE.
PROSTATE?
NO, JUST STINGY.
WELL, IT DOESN'T
MATTER, DALTON.
I CAME IN
FIRST OVERALL,
SO I'M GONNA
REPRESENT POSSUM LODGE
IN THE MR. POSSUM LAKE
COMPETITION.
W-WAIT A MINUTE,
HAROLD.
DID YOU TURN IN
A URINE SAMPLE?
NO, HE JUST GAVE
THEM HIS MATTRESS.
Red [voiceover]:
WALTER WANTED TO FLY
HIS LITTLE MODEL AIRPLANE,
SO I CAME OUT TO
HELP HIM ON THAT.
AND HE'S ALL
EXCITED ABOUT IT.
IT'S THE OLD, THEY CALL
THEM SPITFIRE OR SOMETHING,
FLYING TIGER OR SOMETHING.
OKAY, WALTER,
WE GET IT.
YOU KNOW, SAD TO SEE
HIM GO LIKE THAT.
SO I WAS GONNA
START HER UP THERE,
THE LITTLE 049,
GOT HERE GOING.
AND THE PROBLEM WITH THESE,
I ALWAYS FIND,
IS PEOPLE GET DIZZY
WHEN THEY'RE RUNNING.
AND WALTER WAS
NO EXCEPTION.
YOU GET SPINNING THERE
BECAUSE YOU GOTTA MOVE
YOUR FEET AROUND.
OKAY. THEN HE
STARTS LOSING IT.
NOW THE PLANE'S
COMING AFTER ME.
SO I HEAD FOR THE SHED,
AND IT JUST KNOCKED
THE GARBAGE CAN LID THERE.
KIND OF SPLIT THE
LID A LITTLE BIT.
SO WE NEED
ANOTHER PLAN HERE.
FIRST WE GOTTA FIND THE --
THE PLANE ACTUALLY WENT
INTO THE GARBAGE CAN.
BUT I SAW THE LID THERE,
AND IT GAVE ME AN IDEA.
I THOUGHT, OKAY, YOU SPLIT
HER THERE WITH THE PROP,
BUT IF WE PUT THAT
BACK TOGETHER AGAIN,
AND I'M THINKING IF YOU
ACTUALLY STOOD ON THE LID,
AND THAT WOULD KIND OF SPIN
AROUND ON THE GROUND,
MAYBE HE WOULDN'T
GET SO DIZZY,
BECAUSE HE'S NOT TURNING.
SEE, THE THING IS JUST STAND
THERE AND JUST --
LIKE I SAY,
IT WAS ONLY A THEORY.
SO WE GET WALTER
ON THERE AND, UH --
YOU KNOW, IN HINDSIGHT,
I PROBABLY SHOULD'VE
DUCT TAPED OVER THE SPLIT
THAT WAS THERE FROM THE PROP.
ANYWAY, I GOT HER GOING.
AND I --
IT STARTED TO WORK,
AND HE STARTED TO SWING
AROUND NICELY ON IT.
BUT THEN THE SPLIT OPENED
AND SHE STARTS TO --
HE STARTS TO AUGUR
HIMSELF INTO THE GROUND.
AND IT'S GETTING REAL LOW
AND GETTING RIDICULOUS NOW.
I GOTTA ACTUALLY
JUMP OVER THE PLANE.
AND THEN HE BINDS UP --
NOW WE GOT A REAL PROBLEM.
AND THEN THE PLANE
TURNS AND HEADS FOR HIM.
SEE, NOT ALWAYS GOOD TO HAVE
A MEAL ON A FLIGHT, I FIND.
[applause]
I'LL TELL YOU, THE WORST PART
OF PART OF CUTTING YOUR LAWN
IS HAVING TO MOW AROUND TREES
OR CORNERS LIKE THIS ONE.
OKAY, I SUPPOSE YOU COULD GET
ONE OF THOSE WEED WHACKERS,
IF YOU'RE MADE OF MONEY.
OR YOU COULD HAVE
A BRUSH FIRE,
BUT YOU'D HAVE TO
BE ON MUCH BETTER TERMS
WITH YOUR LOCAL FIRE
DEPARTMENT THAN I AM.
BUT AS ALWAYS, I'VE COME UP
WITH A SOLUTION THAT'S
AFFORDABLE,
AND -- WELL, LET'S JUST
STAY WITH AFFORDABLE.
THESE HERE ARE
CARPET REMNANTS --
YOU KNOW THOSE LITTLE BITS
AND PIECES OF CARPETING
YOU HAD LEFT OVER WHEN
YOU DECIDED TO REFINISH
THE HARDWOOD FLOORS YOURSELF,
AND THEN REALISED THE
ONLY WAY OUT OF THAT MESS
WAS TO COVER EVERYTHING
IN THE WALL TO WALL?
WELL, NOW YOU CAN USE
ALL THESE LITTLE CHUNKS
YOU STOPPED YOUR WIFE
FROM THROWING AWAY.
ALL'S YOU HAVE TO DO IS
PAINT THEM TO MATCH
YOUR LAWN DECOR.
NOW, THAT'S WHAT
I CALL CUTTING CORNERS.
YOU CAN ALSO PUT
THESE BABIES TO WORK
SO YOU NEVER HAVE TO TRIM
AROUND TREE TRUNKS AGAIN.
EVEN IF YOU HATE DANCING
YOU CAN STILL CUT A RUG.
GOOD THING YOU
DON'T HATE CHEESE.
DON'T WORRY.
IT'S SCOTCH-GUARDED.
[applause]
Mike:
I'M HAVING A LOT OF TROUBLE
FINDING THE RIGHT WOMAN.
Red:
WELL, SHE'S NOT HERE.
Dalton: YOU KNOW, MIKE,
SOMETIMES THE WRONG WOMAN
CAN BE A LOT MORE FUN.
Mike: I'M TALKING
ABOUT THE REAL THING,
A LASTING RELATIONSHIP.
I WANNA BE MARRIED,
JUST LIKE MY MOTHER --
EXCEPT JUST
ONCE AT A TIME.
AND BY A REAL MINISTER,
NOT JUST A GUY WITH
A LIQUOR LICENSE.
Red: WELL, YOU KNOW, WE CAN
PROBABLY HELP YOU THERE,
BECAUSE DALTON AND I HAVE
BEEN MARRIED QUITE A WHILE.
Dalton: OH, YEAH.
Red:
I'M SURE WE COULD ANSWER ANY
QUESTIONS YOU MIGHT HAVE.
Mike:
GREAT! OH, YEAH.
OKAY, UM...
I DON'T
UNDERSTAND WOMEN.
LIKE, WHEN I'M IN
A RELATIONSHIP,
I ONLY THINK OF ONE
THING AT A TIME, RIGHT,
BUT THE WOMAN, SHE THINKS OF
EVERYTHING ALL AT ONCE.
IT'S EXHAUSTING.
Dalton:
YOU KNOW, MIKE, A MAN'S MIND
IS A LOT LIKE A NET.
YOU KNOW, HE'LL GO
THROUGH A LOT OF INFORMATION
AND HE'LL FILTER
OUT WHAT HE WANTS,
AND THAT IS WHAT
HE HANGS ON TO.
Red: BUT A WOMAN'S MIND
IS LIKE A -- LIKE --
WELL, IT'S LIKE
A BUCKET, EH?
AND WHEN SHE GOES
THROUGH THE INFORMATION,
SHE GATHERS UP EVERY
LITTLE BIT OF IT.
AND IF THE DAY EVER COMES
WHEN YOU'VE FORGOTTEN
SOME OF THAT INFORMATION,
WELL, SHE'S ONLY TOO HAPPY
TO REFRESH YOUR MEMORY.
Mike:
SO, LIKE, YOU'RE SAYING A
MAN'S MIND IS LIKE A SIEVE.
Dalton:
NO, NO, LIKE A NET.
Red:
LIKE A NET.
A MAN WILL GO THROUGH A
TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF
INFORMATION --
Mike:
AND COME UP WITH NOTHING.
[sigh]
OKAY, MIKE, LOOK.
THE MAN IS -- IS --
IS THE ANCHOR --
THE ANCHOR.
Dalton:
IN THE MARRIAGE.
WITHOUT THE ANCHOR
THERE IS NO MARRIAGE.
THERE'S
NO MARRIAGE.
Dalton: WITHOUT AN
ANCHOR, YOU ARE SUNK.
OH, GEEZ!
OH!
LUCKILY THERE'S A WOMAN
THERE TO BAIL US OUT.
[applause]
WELL, THIS WAS HAROLD'S
BIG DAY REPRESENTING
POSSUM LODGE
IN THE MR. POSSUM LAKE
COMPETITION AGAINST
CARIBOU LODGE.
I COULDN'T GO.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT TO
PUT THE PRESSURE ON HIM.
DIDN'T WANNA
WATCH HIM LOSE,
AND IF HE WINS, THAT WOULD
PROBABLY EVEN BE UGLIER.
UNCLE RED! UNCLE RED!
OH, HAVE I GOT
NEWS FOR YOU.
WHAT A SURPRISE.
WHAT IS IT,
AS IF I DIDN'T KNOW.
I FOUND THE
PERFECT PINE CONE.
WHAT?
WHAT ARE TALKING
ABOUT, HAROLD?
QUIT KIDDING AROUND.
I'M NOT! LOOK AT IT.
THE SHAPE, THE COLOUR.
THERE'S SO MANY THINGS
YOU CAN DO WITH A PINE CONE.
I'M THINKING OF ONE
RIGHT NOW, HAROLD.
DID YOU WIN THE
MR. POSSUM LAKE
COMPETITION?
OH, THAT... NO.
WELL, HAROLD, THERE
WERE ONLY TWO OF YOU.
YOU MUST HAVE
WON SOMETHING.
OKAY, LET ME SEE.
IN STRENGTH
I CAME IN SECOND.
AND THEN THERE WAS SPEED.
I GOT THE SILVER IN THAT.
THEN THERE WAS THE
INTELLIGENCE COMPETITION,
AND THE PERSON
FROM CARIBOU LODGE,
THEY CAME IN SECOND LAST.
SO YOU LOST IN ALL
THREE CATEGORIES?
VERY MUCH SO, YES.
BUT I'M OKAY
WITH THAT, YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO HAVE PRESENT
THE MR. POSSUM LAKE TROPHY AT
THE LODGE MEETING TONIGHT.
THIS IS HUMILIATING,
YOU KNOW THAT?
WE DIDN'T PICK YOU
BECAUSE WE WANTED
TO LOSE.
OH, I KNOW.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
IF YOU WANTED TO LOSE,
YOU WOULD'VE GONE IN YOURSELF.
[possum squealing]
OH, MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
OKAY.
I'M FAST!
WELL, IF MY
WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I WAS HOPING MAYBE WE COULD
PLAY A GAME OF CARDS OR CHESS
OR ANYTHING WHERE YOU
CAN JUST LET ME WIN
WOULD BE GREAT.
MAYBE A BELCHING CONTEST.
I CAN WIN THAT UNLESS
YOUR SISTER'S THERE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF AND HAROLD AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[laughter and applause]
EVERYBODY TAKE YOUR SEATS.
MEETING'S COMING
TO ORDER HERE.
HAVE A SEAT.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
MEN, IT PAINS ME
TO TELL YOU,
FOR THE 12th
YEAR IN A ROW
WE HAVE LOST TO
CARIBOU LODGE.
AND IT IS MY DISPLEASURE
TO PRESENT THE TROPHY
TO THE PERSON WHO BEAT HAROLD
IN EVERY CATEGORY
OF THE COMPETITION.
[sigh]
FROM CARIBOU LODGE,
THE NEW
MR. POSSUM LAKE...
[applause]