♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: HI THIS IS RED GREEN,
IN TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD'S
FLY GET STUCK
WHILE MINE GETS CRUSHED,
AND WE'RE GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW EASY IT IS TO DO
YOUR OWN PLUMBING.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: WELL THEY SAY
WHAT GOES AROUND COMES AROUND,
WELL HERE'S A MAN WHO'S
BEEN AROUND WITHOUT
EVER BUYING A ROUND,
MY UNCLE, THE STAR OF
THE RED GREEN SHOW,
MR. RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
THANKS FOR TUNING US IN.
A REAL EXCITING WEEK UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
MAYBE SOME OF YOU ALREADY
NOTICED WE GOT HAROLD
HERE ON CASTERS.
>>HAROLD: WHY AM I WEARING
THESE AGAIN?
>>RED: WELL HAROLD I JUST
TOLD YOU 5 MINUTES AGO.
>>HAROLD: YEAH I KNOW BUT
I'D FORGOTTEN BECAUSE I WAS
STARING AT THAT PIECE OF FOOD
IN YOUR TEETH,
YOU GO FOR IT NOW AND
I'LL COVER YOU, SET, GO!
NO, MISSED IT.
>>RED: WELL HAROLD WASN'T
LISTENING BUT THERE IS A REASON
WE GOT HIM ON WHEELS,
WE GOT A BIG EVENT
GOING ON UP HERE.
>>HAROLD: SOME KIND OF
SPORTING EVENT RIGHT?
YEAH LIKE SOMETHING TO
DO WITH THE OLYMPICS?
>>RED: YEAH THAT'S
RIGHT HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: I REMEMBER NOW
BECAUSE ALL THE DIFFERENT
POSSUM LODGE MEMBERS
FROM ALL OVER NORTH AMERICA,
ALL THE DIFFERENT CHAPTERS
THEY GATHER HERE FOR THE
BIANNUAL POS-OLYMPICS.
>>RED: YEAH, YOU SEE,
YOU DO REMEMBER.
>>HAROLD: AND THEY HAVE ALL
THESE DIFFERENT WEIRD EVENTS,
YOU TOLD ME ABOUT ALL THE
DIFFERENT, WEIRD EVENTS LIKE
THE DESSERT TRAY WEIGHTLIFTING,
I REMEMBER THAT ONE,
AND THEN THERE WAS THE
40 MAN VOLKSWAGEN BOBSLED RACE.
>>RED: YEAH HAROLD THAT'S IT.
>>HAROLD: AND THEN I SAID
TO YOU, WELL HOW COME I GOT
TO WEAR ROLLERBLADES?
YOU SAID, WELL YOU'RE WEARING
ROLLERBLADES FOR
THE SHIRT SAILING
AND I SAID, WELL WHAT
SHIRT SAILING?
AND YOU SAID, WELL SHIRT SAILING
HAROLD IS WHEN YOU PUT ON A
GREAT BIG SHIRT AND YOU HOLD
OUT THE SIDES OF IT THERE
AND YOU LET THE WIND CATCH IT
AND THEN YOU GO DOWN THE HILL
LIKE THAT HAROLD AND THE WIND
WOULD CATCH ME AND I'D
GO FLYING DOWN THE HILL.
AND I SAID, WELL WHAT KIND
OF SPORT IS THAT?
AND YOU SAID...
>>RED: SHUT UP HAROLD!
>>HAROLD: SHUT UP HAROLD,
YOU SAID SHUT UP
I REMEMBER ALL THAT NOW,
I REMEMBER NOW.
WHAT DID YOU WANT AGAIN THOUGH?
>>RED: WELL HAROLD I JUST
WANTED YOU TO COME OVER
HERE FOR A MINUTE.
>>HAROLD: OH IS THAT IT?
>>RED: YEAH.
>>HAROLD: OH OKAY.
(HAROLD CRASHING & BANGING)
>>RED: YEAH THAT WAS IT.
♪ PADDLING UP THE RIVER ♪
♪ AS FAST AS WE CAN GO ♪
♪ 3 REALLY FAT GUYS ♪
♪ IN A STOLEN CANOE ♪
♪ ROW YOU PORKERS ROW ♪
♪ PADDLING UP THE RIVER WITH ♪
♪ A POLICE BOAT IN PURSUIT ♪
♪ WE'RE STILL GOING ♪
♪ UP THE RIVER ♪
♪ BUT NOW IT'S IN A VAN ♪
♪ WITH BARS ON THE WINDOW ♪
♪ AND VIRTUALLY NO ♪
♪ CREATURE COMFORTS ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE GOING
TO GET UP CLOSE AND PERSONAL
ABOUT YOUR PLUMBING OR I SHOULD
SAY YOUR HOUSE'S PLUMBING.
YOU KNOW THE WORD PLUMBING
ACTUALLY COMES FROM THE
ANCIENT ROMAN WORD FOR LEAD
WHICH WAS PLUM BUM, WHICH WAS
ACTUALLY HAROLD'S NICKNAME
FOR AWHILE.
NOW OF COURSE THE ANCIENT ROMANS
THEY USED LEAD FOR ALL
THEIR WATER PIPES,
THEY'RE ALL DEAD NOW.
NOW THERE'S 2 SIDES TO PLUMBING
REALLY, THERE'S SUPPLY AND
DEMAND OR DRAINAGE, DRAINAGE.
NOW THE DRAINAGE SIDE YOU GOT
THE BIG PIPES THERE AND YOU GOT
HOLES IN THE GROUND AND YOU
GOT YOU KNOW WHAT YOU KNOW,
AND I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING,
PAYING $50 BUCKS TO A
PROFESSIONAL TO HANDLE THAT
IS WELL WORTH EVERY PENNY.
BUT NOW THE SUPPLY SIDE
THAT'S A DIFFERENT KETTLE
OF FISH ENTIRELY,
IT'S SO DARN EASY AN IDIOT
CAN DO IT AND I CAN PROVE IT.
NOW WHAT YOU WANT TO START
WITH IS COPPER PIPE, NOT LEAD,
AND YOU CAN GET IT ANY LENGTH
BUT WE KIND OF LIKE THE 12 FOOT
LENGTHS BECAUSE WE GET
THE 12 FOOTERS BECAUSE
(CRACKLING OF ELECTRICITY)
WE JUST FIND THAT WITH THE
12 FOOTERS IT'S JUST EASIER
TO WORK WITH.
OKAY SO ONCE YOU'VE GOT
YOUR COPPER PIPE WHAT YOU WANT
IS TO GET SOME FITTINGS SO THAT
YOU CAN GO AROUND JOISTS AND
BEAMS AND MAYBE PICTURES OR
WHATEVER IT IS THAT YOU JUST
DON'T FEEL LIKE MOVING.
SO YOU GOT YOUR VARIOUS KINDS
OF FITTINGS HERE, YOU GOT YOUR
45 DEGREE ELBOW, YOU GOT YOUR
90 DEGREE WHICH COME IN LEFT
AND RIGHT, OF COURSE THEY
DON'T MARK THEM YOU KNOW,
SO WHAT I DO IS I JUST,
I BUY THEM BY THE BOX AND THEY
GENERALLY WORK OUT AROUND 50/50
AND YOU GOT THIS UNIT HERE
WHICH I GUESS WOULD BE
180 DEGREE ELBOW AND THIS ONE
WHICH GOES RIGHT ON THE END
OF THE PIPE WHICH IS A 360.
AND THEN YOU GOT YOUR T-JOINER
FOR JOINING 2 PIPES TO ONE
AND YOU GOT YOUR Y-JOINER FOR
ANY OF YOU WHO HAVE NOT
YET JOINED THE 'Y',
A LITTLE PLUMBING HUMOUR THERE.
ALL RIGHT ONCE YOU'VE GOT YOUR
PIPE CUT UP INTO THE VARIOUS
LENGTHS THAT YOU NEED,
YOU GET THEM ALL TOGETHER AND
YOU GOT TO ROUGH UP THE ENDS
OF THE PIPES SO THAT THE SALDER
WILL STICK TO THEM,
THIS ALMOST LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING
THAT ZANFEAR WOULD PLAY
DOESN'T IT?
ANYWAY WHEN IT COMES TO ROUGHING
UP THE PIPE THERE'S AN EASY WAY
TO DO THAT USING THE BELT SANDER
JUST LIKE THAT.
OKAY NOW WE CAN ASSEMBLE
THE PIPING, WE TAKE THE ELBOWS
AND YOU FILL THEM UP WITH GREASE
NOT ELBOW GREASE BUT THIS OTHER
STUFF, IT'S CALLED FLUX AND
YOU STICK IT RIGHT ON THERE.
THIS IS GOING TO PROBABLY
TAKE ME A LITTLE WHILE TO
PUT TOGETHER, SO WHY DON'T WE
GET ON WITH THE SHOW AND WHEN
I'M DONE WE'LL COME RIGHT BACK.
>>HAROLD: ONCE AGAIN IT'S THAT
TIME OF THE SHOW WE EXPOSE
THOSE 3 LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN
FIND SO DIFFICULT TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT
JUST ONE MORE TIME IS MY
UNCLE RED AND OF COURSE
MR. DOUGIE FRANKLIN.
WELL THIS WILL BE INTERESTING,
WE HAVE A LETTER FROM TEXAS
THIS WEEK, UNITED STATES.
OH EXCELLENT, OKAY.
'DEAR EXPERTS, LAST YEAR
THE MISSUS AND I VACATIONED
IN ENGLAND, IT WAS A REAL CUTE,
LITTLE COUNTRY, BUT EVEN THOUGH
THEY SPOKE KIND OF LIKE
AMERICANS THE PLACE WAS LIKE
A REAL FOREIGN COUNTRY
OR SOMETHING, WHEN I ORDERED
A BAG OF CHIPS I GOT FRIES,
EVERYONE DROVE ON THE WRONG SIDE
OF THE ROAD AND THEIR MONEY
LOOKED REAL WEIRD.
THIS YEAR WE'RE GOING TO COME UP
TO CANADA AND VISIT YOU PEOPLE,
IS IT WEIRD THERE TOO?'
I THINK BY WEIRD
HE MEANS DIFFERENT.
>>RED: WELL THAT MAKES
YOU DIFFERENT THEN
DOESN'T IT HAROLD?
OH YOU KNOW I DON'T THINK
YOU KNOW THERE'S ANY DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN CANADIANS AND AMERICANS.
DOUGIE YOU'RE AN AMERICAN,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY WE'RE
ABOUT THE SAME?
>>DOUGIE: NO, SIR I WOULDN'T,
YOU CANADIANS ARE WEIRD.
>>RED: HOW'S THAT?
>>DOUGIE: WELL I MEAN YOU KNOW
UP HERE A 240 ZEE IS A 240 ZED,
WHAT IS A ZED?
I MEAN YOU KNOW IT SOUNDS
LIKE SOMETHING OFF HEE-HAW,
LOOKIE UP ON THE PORCH,
IT'S UNCLE ZED.
>>RED: WHAT'S IN A NAME DOUGIE,
IT DOESN'T MATTER A 'ZEE'
OR A 'ZED', IT'S THE SAME CAR,
IT GOES JUST AS FAST AND GETS
THE SAME GAS MILEAGE UP HERE.
>>DOUGIE: NO SIR IT DOESN'T,
YOU GO 100 KILOMETERS AN HOUR,
YOU GET MAYBE WHAT DO YOU SAY,
10 KILOMETERS TO THE LITER,
NOW I DON'T KNOW WHETHER
THAT'S GOOD OR BAD,
I DON'T KNOW WHETHER ANYBODY
WHO WAS BORN HERE KNOWS EITHER.
>>HAROLD: OKAY, ALL RIGHTY,
BUT YOU KNOW WE'RE REALLY GOING
THE SAME SPEEDS AND YOU KNOW
WE DRIVE ON THE SAME SIDE OF
THE HIGHWAY AS THE AMERICANS.
>>DOUGIE: NO SIR YOU DON'T.
ALL YOU CANADIANS, Y'ALL
DRIVE IN THE PASSING LANE.
NOW IN THE UNITED STATES OF
AMERICA WE GOT YOUR DRIVING LANE
WE GOT YOUR PASSING LANE,
UP HERE YOU JUST GOT LIKE LANES,
IT'S LIKE BOWLING,
YOU JUST GO ANYWHERE YOU KNOW
THAT HAPPENS TO BE OPEN AND
THERE YOU ARE, YOU TRY THAT
IN THE 'US OF A', YOU COME
FACE TO FACE WITH THE COPS.
>>RED: WELL YOU HAVE THE
SAME PROBLEM UP HERE DOUG.
>>DOUGIE: ABSOLUTELY NOT,
NOPE, NO SIR YOU WOULDN'T,
YOU'D GET PULLED OVER BY YOUR
MOUNTIES AND OF COURSE YOU KNOW,
LOOK AT THE WAY THOSE FELLOWS
ARE DRESSED WOULD YOU?
THEY'RE LIKE SECURITY GUARDS.
NOW BACK HOME WE GOT
STATE TROOPERS, THEY'RE
GUSSIED UP WITH GOLD BRAID
THEY GOT YOUR BIG GUNS,
10 GALLON HATS.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN PULLED
OVER BY A MOUNTIE
WEARING A 40 LITER HAT?
I'M TELLING YOU, YOU CANADIANS
ARE DIFFERENT THAN US AMERICANS,
THE CAT IS OUT OF THE BAG.
>>HAROLD: WELL PERHAPS IT'S
JUST BECAUSE WE'RE MORE TOLERANT
AND WE'RE LESS LIKELY TO JUDGE
FOREIGNERS AND WE'RE LIKE
A LITTLE LESS CLOSE MINDED
ABOUT DIFFERENT CULTURES.
>>DOUGIE: NO SIR, NO SIR
THAT'S ONE THING ACTUALLY
WE HAVE IN COMMON, YOU'RE JUST
AS NARROW MINDED AS WE ARE
ONLY WE'RE UPFRONT ABOUT IT
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU TALK TO AN
AMERICAN LIKE THIS, HE'S GOING
TO BE JUST AS TICKED OFF AS
YOU ARE BUT HE'LL LET YOU KNOW
INSTEAD OF HIDING BEHIND YOU
KNOW SOME KIND OF CONSTIPATED
SMILE MAKING LIKE NONE
OF THIS IS BUGGING HIM.
>>RED: WELL THANKS SO
MUCH FOR DROPPING BY DOUG.
>>HAROLD: IT'S GREAT
HAVING YOU HERE.
>>RED: YUP, YUP,
VERY INFORMATIVE, EXCELLENT.
>>DOUGIE: YES, WEIRD.
>>RED: IT IS SPRING,
I WALK THROUGH THE WOODS
I FEEL LIKE I DID WHEN I WAS 15,
I WALK INTO A BEEHIVE,
MY FACE GETS STUNG 100 TIMES
NOW I LOOK LIKE I DID
WHEN I WAS 15.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT,
SO NOW YOU'VE GOT YOUR
PIPES SET RUNNING FROM YOUR
INLET OUT TO SAY YOUR BATHROOM
OR OVER TO YOUR KITCHEN AND UP
INTO THE LAUNDRY ROOM AND OUT
INTO THE LAWN SPRINKLER,
MAYBE INTO YOUR BIDET AND
THEN OUT INTO THE SPITTOON.
AND ONCE YOU GOT ALL YOUR
JOINTS SET LIKE THAT
YOU GOT TO NOW MAKE THEM
REAL SOLID BY USING SOME SORT
OF SALDERING DEVICE LIKE
THIS SALDERING TORCH.
NOW I KNOW SOME PEOPLE
ARE NERVOUS ABOUT USING
THESE TORCHES, BUT THE TRUTH
IS THAT THEY'RE OF ABSOLUTELY
NO DANGER AT ALL FOR USING
AROUND THE HOUSE AS LONG
AS YOU REMEMBER TO TURN
THEM OFF YOU KNOW.
WHERE DID I PUT
MY MATCHES HERE?
YEAH I KNOW THE PROFESSIONALS
USE THE BIG 20 POUNDERS
BUT TO BE HONEST WITH YOU,
OH HERE WE ARE,
BUT TO BE HONEST WITH YOU
I DON'T TRUST THOSE BIG
PROPANE TANKS YOU KNOW,
I THINK THOSE DARN THINGS
COULD EXPLODE ON YOU.
(LOUD EXPLOSION)
>>RED: (COUGHING)
ALL RIGHT NOW YOU MIGHT WANT
TO HAVE A SECOND PROPANE TORCH
AROUND JUST AS MORE
OR LESS A BACKUP.
AND THEN YOU JUST HEAT UP
THE JOINTS UNTIL ALL THE FLUX
STARTS BOILING IN THERE AND
THEN JUST PUT THE SALDER ON
THERE AND SHE'LL JUST MELT
RIGHT IN THERE,
IT'S JUST THAT EASY REALLY.
HAROLD DO YOU WANT TO COME
IN HERE AND LIGHT THIS TORCH?
AND THERE WE GO,
SHE'S READY TO RIP.
ALL RIGHT HAROLD TURN
THE WATER ON THERE,
OH, OH, HOLD IT, HOLD IT HAROLD,
HOLD IT HAROLD, HOLD A MINUTE!
HOLD A MINUTE, HOLD A MINUTE!
YEAH THAT'S GOT HER THAT TIME,
WE GOT HER, WE GOT HER HAROLD,
LET HER RIP, LET HER ROLL,
HOLD IT! HOLD ON!
DO YOU HAVE TO TURN IT
ON SO HARD HAROLD?
ALL RIGHT THAT LOOKS BETTER,
WE GOT HERE, ALL RIGHT HAROLD,
TURN HER ON GENTLY, PERFECT!
(WATER DRIPPING)
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
I'LL TRY TURNING THE WATER
ON HERE, OH, OH BOY, OH BOY,
HAROLD! HAROLD! HAROLD!
>>RED: BUZZ?
>>BUZZ: YO RED MAN,
HOW'S IT GOING?
>>RED: NOT BAD, GETTING ALL
READY FOR THE POSSUM OLYMPIC
OPENING CEREMONIES ARE YOU?
>>BUZZ: OH MAN I'M GETTING
READY FOR THE BIG FLY PASS,
I'M GOING TO TIE THIS BANNER
TO MY PLANE, CHECK THIS OUT.
>>RED: OH YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>>BUZZ: IT SAYS TO
THE VICTOR GOES.
(RIPPING OF CLOTH)
>>BUZZ: AH MAN I HATE THAT,
LOOK AT THAT, 8 MINUTES OF
WORK RIGHT DOWN THE DRAIN!
>>RED: OH BOY.
>>BUZZ: ANYWAY IT SAYS TO
THE VICTOR GOES THE SPOILS
AND THE BEER.
OH I PROBABLY SHOULD OF WAITED
FOR THE PAINT TO DRY RIGHT
BEFORE I FOLDED IT UP.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>BUZZ: OH WELL,
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I'LL DO?
>>RED: NO.
>>BUZZ: I'LL PAINT THIS ON
A SHEET OF PLYWOOD AND FLY IT
BEHIND ME, THAT'LL BE SAFE.
>>RED: OH YEAH.
>>BUZZ: AND CHECK THIS OUT,
WHEN I FLY PAST THE GRANDSTAND
AND LEAN OUT THE DOOR.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
>>BUZZ: YOU WANT ME TO WHIP
OUT THE BALLOONS THERE RIGHT?
>>RED: YEAH THE BALLOONS,
BUT THEY'RE FILLED
WITH HELIUM RIGHT?
>>BUZZ: NO I COULDN'T
GET HELIUM.
>>RED: NO?
>>BUZZ: NO, SO I FILLED
THEM FULL OF WATER.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>BUZZ: HEY HAROLD THIS IS
THE COOLEST, CHECK THIS OUT,
WATER BOMBS CATCH!
OH THIS IS FUNNY,
NORMALLY THEY'RE SUPPOSE
TO BREAK, LISTEN I'M SURE
THEY'LL BREAK AT 2,000 FEET
(AIR BOMBING WHISTLE)
>>BUZZ: IT'LL BE FABULOUS.
>>RED: YEAH IT'LL BE FABULOUS.
>>BUZZ: AND I GOT A PLANE
FULL OF STREAMERS RIGHT
AND I GOT ALL THIS STUFF TOO,
WHAT'S THIS STUFF CALLED?
>>RED: CONFETTI.
>>BUZZ: CONFETTI,
YEAH IT'LL BE GREAT.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>BUZZ: LISTEN I GOT TO
GO RIGHT AND PRACTICE MY
DEMONSTRATION SPORT, AIR HOCKEY.
>>RED: OH YEAH, AIR, OH I KNOW,
I KNOW THE ONE, IT'S GOT THE
TABLE AND THE AIR COMES UP AND
YOU SHOOT THOSE LITTLE THINGS
AROUND THERE.
>>BUZZ: AH MAN NOT THAT, NO,
ICE HOCKEY YOU PLAY ON ICE.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>BUZZ: FIELD HOCKEY
YOU PLAY ON A FIELD.
>>RED: YEAH THAT'S RIGHT.
>>BUZZ: AIR HOCKEY RED
IS PLAYED IN THE AIR.
>>RED: HOW DOES THAT WORK?
>>BUZZ: WELL IT'S SORT
OF LIKE POLO RIGHT?
>>RED: YEAH.
>>BUZZ: BUT INSTEAD OF RIDING
A HORSE AND HITTING A BALL.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>BUZZ: YOU FLY AROUND IN
A PLANE AND YOU TRY
AND HIT THE ZEPPELIN.
>>RED: WOW!
>>BUZZ: SHERWOOD'S GOT THE
ZEPPELIN, HE SHOOTS, HE SCORES!
>>RED: HAROLD!
ON THE EVE OF THE INTERNATIONAL
POSSUM OLYMPICS I GOT TO
TELL YOU THE OLYMPIC SPIRIT
AS YOU CAN SEE IS RUNNING
PRETTY HIGH UP HERE
AT THE LODGE.
BY THE WAY HAROLD
WHAT IS THAT?
NEW HEAD GEAR FOR YOUR BRACES?
>>HAROLD: NO I'M IN TRAINING,
I'M GOING TO GO INTO
THE BOXING COMPETITION,
I'M IN THE FLY WEIGHT CATEGORY.
>>RED: I'M BETTING ON THE FLY.
>>HAROLD: HA! HA! HA!
YOU JUST HOLD ON AND YOU WAIT
AND SEE BECAUSE I'M GOING
TO FLOAT LIKE A BUTTERFLY
AND STINK LIKE A BEE.
>>RED: THAT'S STING HAROLD
NOT STINK.
>>HAROLD: IT IS?
>>RED: YEAH.
>>HAROLD: I BETTER GET
ANOTHER CATEGORY THEN.
>>RED: WELL ANYWAY WE'RE
ALL GEARED UP HERE,
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK HAS CLEANED
OUT THE BARBEQUE SO WE CAN
LIGHT THE TORCH WITH IT,
AND THEN FOR THE OPENING
CEREMONIES OF COURSE
STINKY PETERSON IS DOING
HIS BIG NUMBER WITH
THE 3 RIPE CABBAGES AND
THE ICE-CREAM SCOOP,
THAT'S ALWAYS A CROWD PLEASER
AND FOR THE CLOSER
MOOSE THOMPSON HAS
GOT US A WATER CANNON.
>>HAROLD: WAIT A SECOND
UNCLE RED, YOU'RE MISSING
THE TRUE SPIRIT OF THE
OLYMPICS THOUGH.
>>RED: OH I DON'T KNOW HAROLD,
WE'VE ALREADY HAD 5 COUNTRIES
BOYCOTT US.
>>HAROLD: NO, I'M TALKING
ABOUT THE MODERN TRUE SPIRIT,
MARKETING AND LICENSING.
THINK ABOUT THAT HUH?
WE NEED LIKE AN OFFICIAL
SOFT DRINK AND AN OFFICIAL
FILM AND WE NEED AN
OFFICIAL AIRLINE, OH YEAH.
>>RED: WELL WE GOT AN OFFICIAL
POSSUM VAN AND WE GOT AN
OFFICIAL OUTHOUSE AND WE
CAN NAME AN OFFICIAL TREE.
>>HAROLD: NO, NO, NO, NO,
YOU'RE MISSING IT YOU SEE,
WE NEED LIKE A LOGO MAYBE
AND A LITTLE CARTOON CHARACTER
OF AN ANIMAL THAT WE CAN
MARKET TO DEATH YOU KNOW.
>>RED: WELL WHAT KIND OF CUTE
LITTLE CHARACTER COULD WE
HAVE FOR POSSUM LODGE AT
THE POSSUM OLYMPICS?
>>RED: NOW IT'S TIME ONCE AGAIN
FOR 'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT BILL HAD
IN MIND THIS WEEK.
OH, OH IT'S HORSESHOES,
OH THAT'S NOT SO BAD
I UNDERSTAND THAT HORSESHOES
IS ONE OF THE SAFEST SPORTS
EVER DEVISED BY MAN.
AS FAR AS I KNOW NO ONE'S EVER
BEEN INJURED FROM HORSESHOES.
THERE MIGHT BE ONE OR 2
EXCEPTIONS I SUPPOSE
OR 3 OR 4...
ANYWAY THE FIRST STEP IS
TO PUT THE STEEL ROD.
>>BILL:OH!
>>RED: OH NOW I'M NOT
GOING TO COMMENT ON THAT,
WELL HE HAS HOPEFULLY ANOTHER
STRONGER ROD THERE.
YUP AND HE WANTS ME TO
HOLD IT, THIS IS,
I GOT TO LOOK AWAY,
THIS IS A LITTLE BIT TOO,
AND BY GOD NO, I DIDN'T REALLY
FEEL HIM HIT THE THING,
I DIDN'T QUITE KNOW WHAT
WAS GOING ON AND I JUST,
(THUD OF SHOE HITTING HEAD)
OH I DID HEAR SOMETHING THOUGH
AND WHY WOULD HE BE LYING DOWN?
OH WELL, SO HE TAPED THE
HEAD BACK ON THAT AND I TAPED
THE HEAD BACK ON THAT
AND THEN WE COULD TRY AGAIN.
SO HE GOT THE THING LINED UP
JUST GIVE HER A LITTLE,
YOU KNOW THE SINKHOLES AROUND
THE LODGE ARE REAL HANDY
SOMETIMES, BUT THAT SEEMED,
I THOUGHT THAT, OH BOY!
IT IS A DANGEROUS SPORT
ISN'T IT BILL?
>>BILL: OH!
>>RED: YEAH I THINK IT IS,
YEAH, ANYWAY I THOUGHT
WELL THAT POLE BEING SO
LOW IN THE GROUND YOU KNOW,
I DON'T KNOW, I THINK
THAT'S MORE DANGEROUS,
HOW ARE YOU GOING TO BE
ABLE TO CATCH THE THING?
WOULDN'T IT GO RIGHT OVER
LIKE THAT, INTO THAT?
WOULDN'T THAT HAPPEN BILL?
THAT DOESN'T SEEM TO
BOTHER HIM TOO MUCH,
IT WASN'T HIS VAN.
BUT THEN HE STARTS JUST KIND
OF FIRING THEM AND THEN WE
HAD KIND OF A GANG SHOOT HERE,
OH MY GOSH AND HMM,
OH YEAH, I DON'T KNOW QUITE
HOW TO SCORE THOSE.
I WAS NOT REAL WITH BILL
THAT WAS ALL MY STUFF.
JUST EASY, RELAX, RELAX,
YOU GO GET THE HORSESHOES.
HE'S GOT AN IDEA,
WHAT HE'S GOING TO DO NOW
TAKE THAT RAKE AND STICK IT
ON THERE AND HE'S GOING TO
DUCT TAPE THAT TO THE
LITTLE POLE,
NOW HE'S GOT A GREAT
BIG POLE TO SHOOT AT,
YEAH THAT SEEMS A LITTLE MORE
SENSIBLE BUT JUST IN CASE
HE'S GOING TO BACK UP JUST,
YEAH, YEAH, TAKE SOME OF
THE DANGER OUT OF THE SPORT.
AND HE THROWS A WHOLE BUNCH
AT ONCE THERE AND OH THEY'RE
COMING IN LIKE THE B-49 BOMBER,
AND DOWN GOES THE POLE
AND THEN UP SHE COMES,
FIRES THEM RIGHT BACK TOWARDS
BILL AND THERE'S, OH BOY!
1..2..AND 3..
BOY GOLLY THAT'S A RINGER,
YEAH BILL YOU'RE A RINGER,
3 POINTS.
>>RED: THIS IS FOR ALL
THE YOUNG PEOPLE WHICH
MEANS I DON'T HAVE TO
WATCH IT.
>>HAROLD: WELL IT'S TIME TO
GET UP AND GET DOWN AND
SHAKE YOUR BOOTIE AND
THEN DANCE UNTIL YOU DROP
AND THEN GET BACK UP AGAIN.
DANCING HAS BEEN CALLED
MAKING LOVE WHILE STANDING UP
WHICH I GUESS THAT'S WHY
MY DAD'S FAVOURITE SONG
IS THE MINUTE WALTZ.
ALL RIGHT, WELL ANYWAY DANCING
IS A LOT MORE THAN JUST GOING...
FIRST YOU NEED MUSIC.
♪ UPBEAT TUNE PLAYS ♪
YEAH JUST LIKE THAT
BUT YOU GOT TO START SLOW
JUST LET ONE FOOT DO SOME
OF THE WORK, THERE YOU GO
MR. ONE FOOT, LET HIM FEEL IT
A LITTLE WHILE, HE'LL TELL
THE REST OF THE BODY,
HE'S MENTIONING IT
TO THE LEG NOW,
THERE YOU GO...
EVERYONE'S STARTING TO
FEEL IT IN THE WHOLE BODY,
LET THE RHYTHM FLOW,
THERE YOU GO, MR. SHOULDER
HEARD ALL ABOUT IT.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: HAROLD! HAROLD! HAROLD!
HOPEFULLY HE'LL DANCE ALL THE
WAY OUT INTO THE BUG ZAPPER.
(SIZZLE OF ZAPPER)
>>HAROLD: WOO!
>>RED: WE ALL LIVE FOR
THE GOOD DAYS, DON'T WE?
>>RED: WELL HAROLD'S GOT THESE
CONTRACTS HE'S DOING UP AND WE
JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU KNOW
THAT THE I'S ARE CROSSED
AND THE T'S ARE DOTTED.
>>REG: WELL I'M NOT SO GOOD
AT THE FINE PRINT ANY MORE RED,
YOU SEE MY EYESIGHT'S GOTTEN
SO BAD I CAN BARELY SEE MY HAND
IN FRONT OF MY FACE.
(RIFLE FIRES)
>>REG: WHAT DID I HIT?
>>RED: IT LOOKS LIKE A SHRUB
OF SOME KIND, THEY'RE TOUGH
TO CLEAN AREN'T THEY REG?
>>RED: WELL THE DREAM IS DEAD,
THE POS-OLYMPICS HAVE
BEEN CANCELLED,
CANCELLED BEFORE THE SPRAY
PAINT WAS EVEN DRY ON THE GOLD,
SILVER AND BRONZE MEDALS.
>>HAROLD: CANCELLED?
OH YOU CAN'T CANCEL UNCLE RED!
I JUST SIGNED A MULTI DOLLAR
TELEVISION DEAL, WELL WE GOT
LIKE PRIMETIME ON CABLE 10,
MIDNIGHT TO 3 EVERY NIGHT.
>>RED: WELL I'M SORRY HAROLD
BUT EVERY ATHLETE WAS CAUGHT
TAKING A PERFORMANCE
ENHANCING SUBSTANCE.
>>HAROLD: OH.
>>RED: BEER.
>>HAROLD: BEER?
BEER DOESN'T ENHANCE
YOUR PERFORMANCE.
>>RED: OH HAROLD YOU
SOUND JUST LIKE MY WIFE.
BEER ENHANCES AN ATHLETE'S
PERFORMANCE IN HIS OWN
MIND HAROLD, THEY THINK THEY
CAN JUMP HIGHER, RUN FASTER
AND THROW UP FARTHER,
ALL THEY DO IS FALL DOWN
AND HURT THEMSELVES.
>>HAROLD: BUT UNCLE RED
LOOK, I JUST DESIGNED
A POS-OLYMPIC LOGO, WATCH
♪ IMITATING TRUMPET ♪
AND THEN OF COURSE THERE'S
A POS-OLYMPIC MOTTO,
'BE THE VERY BEST YOU
CAN BE, CONSIDERING...'
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH THAT'S
THE SQUEAL OF THE POSSUM,
WE GOT A MEETING NOW.
>>RED: YEAH WELL YOU GO ON
DOWN AND FAN THE OLYMPIC FLAMES
HAROLD AND I'LL BE DOWN
IN A MINUTE OKAY.
>>HAROLD: OKEY DOKE.
>>RED: WELL THIS IS PROBABLY
THE ONLY SPORTING EVENT IN
HISTORY WHERE YOU CAN SAY THERE
ARE NO WINNERS AND NO LOSERS
HERE TODAY AND MEAN IT.
EXCEPT FOR THE PART ABOUT
THE LOSERS.
ANYWAY IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING AND I AM
NO LONGER IN TRAINING WHICH
MEANS I CAN RELAX SO TO SPEAK.
TONIGHT I'D LIKE TO GO FOR
THE GOLD, THAT'S CODE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR WATCHING
AND KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
♪ ♪ ♪
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE, ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUONDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: A COUPLE OF QUICK
ANNOUNCEMENTS FOR YOU IN
THE MEETING, ALL THE POS-OLYMPIC
PARAPHERNALIA IS AVAILABLE AT
COST THROUGH ANY OF THE MEMBERS
OR WHATEVER TRUSTEES ARE
APPOINTED BY THE RECEIVER.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca