ONE OF THE DIFFERENCES
BETWEEN MEN AND WOMEN
IS THAT WOMEN KIND OF
SEE THE BIG PICTURE,
WHEREAS MEN KINDA
SEE EVERYTHING IN
LITTLE WEE PARTS.
THAT'S WHY MOST WOMEN
ARE INTO HOLISTIC MEDICINE,
WHEREAS MOST
SURGEONS ARE GUYS.
TO A WOMEN A CAR IS
A MEANS OF TRANSPORTATION,
TO A GUY IT'S A BUNCH
OF COMPONENTS,
PARTS THAT HE CAN FIX OR
CUSTOMIZE OR CHANGE
AROUND IN SOME WAY.
IF HE CAN TAKE A CAR
AND CUT IT IN HALF,
BUMPER TO BUMPER,
HE'S GOT TWO MOTORCYCLES.
I THINK THAT'S WHY
GUYS NEVER THROW
ANYTHING OUT,
THEY'RE WAITING TO SEE
WHAT IT DEVOLVES INTO.
IT'S NOT SMART OR CORRECT
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT MAKES US
WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
TODAY ON THE RED GREEN
SHOW WE HAVE EDGAR
K.B. MONTROSE,
GLEN BRACKSTON IS
SUCKING IT UP DOWN
AT THE MARINA,
BILL IS GOING TO TRY
AND DRILL US A WELL,
I'VE GOT SOME
HYDROGEN IN MY HAT,
AND AS ALWAYS HAROLD
IS UP THE CREEK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND NOW HERE IS THE MAN
WITH THE MOST LUMBER
IN HIS JACK,
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU.
AND NOW THAT YOU
MET THE LUMBERJACK,
MEET THE LUMBERING JERK,
MY NEPHEW, HAROLD.
IT'S BEEN KIND OF A
GOOD NEWS WEEK IN A
WAY FOR ME UP HERE.
I GOT TO LOSE A
LITTLE BIT OF WEIGHT.
I GOT A CHECK UP COMING
UP PRETTY SOON.
NO, NOTHING YET.
BUT I HEARD THAT THIS
WATER DIET IS A REAL
GOOD THING
AND APPARENTLY THE WATER
IN POSSUM LAKE
HAS JUST BEEN DECLARED
OKAY FOR HUMAN
CONSUMPTION.
REALLY?
I WOULDN'T DRINK IT.
WELL, SO WHAT, I SAID
HUMAN CONSUMPTION.
WELL, IF THE WATER
IN POSSUM LAKE HAS
BEEN DECLARED OKAY,
THERE'S OBVIOUSLY SOMETHING
WRONG WITH THE TESTING
EQUIPMENT.
THE WATER IS
FINE, HAROLD.
IF WE'RE GOING TO GET
INTO CRITICIZING
THE GOVERNMENT,
WE'RE IN FOR A LONG
NIGHT, ALL RIGHT?
WHAT ABOUT ALL THAT
STUFF FLOATING IN IT?
KEEP YOUR
TEETH CLENCHED.
ANYWAY, NOW
THAT THE WATER IS
OFFICIALLY OKAY,
WE JUST GOT TO FIND
A WAY TO MAKE IT
TASTE BETTER.
HOW YOU GOING
TO DO THAT?
THAT WATER TASTES
LIKE BAD EGGS.
WELL, WE'LL ADD
BAD BACON BITS
TO MAKE IT TASTE
LIKE A BAD BREAKFAST.
ACTUALLY, JUNIOR
SINGLETON HAD
A GOOD IDEA,
YOU KNOW, HE THOUGHT
WE COULD CARBONATE
THE LAKE.
YOU KNOW HOW THEY
CARBONATE THINGS
LIKE GRAPEFRUIT POP
SO THEY DON'T
TASTE TOO BAD?
SO MOOSE SAID LOOK
IF WE ALL JUST BACK
OUR CARS DOWN,
YOU KNOW, GET THE
EXHAUST PIPES IN THERE,
HE FIGURES THE CARBON
DIOXIDE COMING OUT
OF THE TAILPIPE
WILL CARBONATE
THE LAKE.
THAT'S CARBON MONOXIDE.
IT'S VERY MUCH LIKE
CARBON DIOXIDE EXCEPT
IT KILLS ALL LIFE.
OTHERWISE GOOD PLAN.
YEAH, WELL WE'RE NOT
GOING TO DO THAT.
WE'RE GOING TO USE
ELECTRICITY.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU PUT
A NINE-VOLT BATTERY
ON YOUR TONGUE,
IT KIND OF FEELS
LIKE CARBONATION?
WELL, WE FIGURE WE DROP
ONE OF THEM HIGH-TENSION WIRES
DOWN INTO THE LAKE,
YOU KNOW, JUST FOR
AN HOUR OR SO,
CARBONATE HER RIGHT UP.
WON'T THAT KILL ALL THE
ELECTRICITY AROUND HERE?
NO.
[ PHONE RINGING ]
[OH I LIKE HONEY ]
[I LIKE JAM ]
[I LIKE MYSELF
JUST THE WAY I AM]
[I DON'T MIND THE PIMPLES]
[AND I DON'T MIND THE WARTS]
[AND I REALLY DON'T CARE
HOW BAD I LOOK IN SHORTS]
[I GOT SKINNY ARMS]
[AND A GREAT BIG NOSE]
[I GOT HAIR IN MY EARS]
[HAIR ON MY TOES]
[PEOPLE SAY I'M UGLY
BUT I DON'T MAKE A FUSS]
[BECAUSE I ALWAYS GET A
SEAT BY MYSELF ON THE BUS]
OKAY.
YOU JUST PULLED IN YOUR
DRIVEWAY AND IT'S LATE
AND YOU DIDN'T TELL
ANYBODY YOU WERE
GOING TO BE LATE.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
BE ABLE TO SNEAK
INTO THE HOUSE
AND YOU KNOW THE
VERY FIRST THING
YOU'RE GOING TO HEAR
AS SOON AS YOU GO
THROUGH THAT
FRONT DOOR,
TOGETHER:
WHY DIDN'T YOU CALL?
AND YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED AN ANSWER
TO NEED THE TRUTH.
AND THE TRUTH IS
YOU DON'T HAVE
AN ANSWER.
SO THE TRUTH BECOMES
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO MAKE SOMETHING UP.
AND IT'S GOING
TO HAVE TO BE
A HUMMER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SO WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO DO
IS WE'RE GOING TO MAKE
SOME UP FOR YOU NOW
AND THEN YOU CAN USE
THEM LATER WHEN
YOU NEED THEM.
OKAY, HERE'S
A GOOD ONE.
SORRY I DIDN'T
CALL, HONEY,
BUT I GAVE ALL
MY MONEY TO A
HOMELESS FAMILY
WHO IS LIVING IN THE
PARKING LOT BEHIND THE
BAR IN THE DUMPSTER
AND I JUST DIDN'T HAVE
THE HEART TO ASK THEM
FOR CHANGE FOR THE PHONE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OR YOU CAN SAY
THE POLICE COME INTO
THE BAR AND THEY SAID
THEY'RE TRACKING ALIENS
WHICH APPARENTLY
ARE PURE ENERGY,
WHICH I'D NEVER HEARD,
BUT ANYWAY THEY SAID
NOBODY CAN USE THE PHONE,
INCLUDING THE TABLE
DANCERS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OR I GUESS YOU
COULD JUST SAY,
AH SORRY HONEY
I DIDN'T CALL,
IT WAS
THOUGHTLESS OF ME,
I FEEL REALLY BAD,
I LOVE YOU VERY MUCH,
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
BUT TRY THE
OTHER TWO FIRST.
OH, YEAH.
THIS WEEK ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
WHAT WITH ME TRYING
THAT NEW WATER DIET,
I THOUGHT I WOULD SHOW
YOU HOW YOU CAN MAKE
YOUR VERY OWN HOME
WATER PURIFICATION SYSTEM.
DO YOU REALIZE THAT THE
HUMAN BODY IS I BELIEVE
AROUND 70 PERCENT WATER
AND THE REST IS FAT
AND ADDITIVES?
ALL RIGHT, FIRST THING
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
IS A LARGE CONTAINER
OF SOME KIND.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
CLEAN THAT OUT
REAL GOOD.
THERE WE GO.
THAT'S NOT ENOUGH.
YOU GOT TO STERILIZE
IT, WHICH IS A SCARY
TERM FOR MOST MEN.
THE TRUTH IS MOST
GERMS AND BACTERIA CAN
SURVIVE SOAP AND WATER
BUT THEY DIE IN A
GOOD PROPANE FLAME.
I SAY IF YOU CAN'T
TAKE THE HEAT, GET OUT
OF THE WATER PURIFIER.
THAT WAS A BAD BIT.
GLAD I DIDN'T
DRINK THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S GOT HER.
NOW, YOU WANT TO PUT
SOME PILLS IN THERE
BECAUSE IN THE REAL
WATER PURIFIERS
THEY USE...
HALACIDE -- HALOGEN --
HALACIDE OR SOMETHING
HALAZONE TABLETS.
I GOT THESE PILLS FROM
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S ROOM
SO THEY'RE
HALITOSIS PILLS.
I FIGURE THAT'S GOT
TO BE CLOSE ENOUGH.
FIRE THOSE IN THERE.
I ALSO GOT HIS NITRO
PILLS WHILE I WAS
IN THERE.
HOPE HE HAS A NICE DAY.
I'LL PUT THEM
IN BECAUSE I CAN.
ALL RIGHT, NOW TO
DO THE ACTUAL FILTERING,
I'M THINKING YOU
KNOW THE FISH IN THE
AQUARIUM AND SO ON?
THEY USE CHARCOAL
IN THEIR FILTERS,
AND FISH DON'T
JUST DRINK WATER,
THEY DO EVERYTHING IN IT.
CHARCOAL MUST
BE REAL GOOD.
JUST OPEN THIS UP,
JUST LIKE TAKING OUT
THE APPENDIX STITCHES
AND SOCK THE OLD
CHARCOAL IN THERE.
THERE WE GO.
THAT'S GOING TO
MAKE IT CLEAN.
YOU'RE FILTERING OUT HERE
GERMS AND BACTERIA
AND CHEMICALS,
ALSO ODORS
I'M THINKING.
BAKING SODA WORKS
IN YOUR FRIDGE, RIGHT?
I WILL JUST GET
THE KID-PROOF TOP --
KID-PROOF TOP ON
THAT NO PROBLEM.
AND I'LL PUT THAT
IN THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
ALSO GOOD WITH
DEALING WITH ODORS
AND ALSO DOING
FILTERING IS KITTY LITTER.
NOW, I WOULD RECOMMEND
YOU USE FRESH KITTY LITTER.
I'M ALL FOR RECYCLING
BUT ONLY UP TO A POINT.
DUMP THAT IN THERE.
USE A LOT OF
KITTY LITTER.
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT.
THE WATER IS GOING
TO BE CLEAN ENOUGH I
THINK AT THIS POINT.
SO THE DIRTY SCUMMY
WATER IS GOING TO
GO IN THE TOP
AND THE CLEAN FRESH
WATER IS GOING TO
COME OUT THE BOTTOM,
SO YOU GOT TO DRILL A
HOLE SO YOU CAN PUT
A PIPE IN THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, NO, YOU WANT
TO STERILIZE THIS.
THIS I MEAN.
AND THERE WE GO.
AGAIN I MAY HAVE OVERDONE
IT WITH THE STERILIZING
AND HEATING.
ANYWAY, ONCE YOU GOT
THE HOLE IN THERE,
GET YOURSELF A TAP
AND PUT IT ON A PIECE
OF COPPER PIPE LIKE THIS,
JAM THAT IN THE HOLE,
AND THIS WAY YOU
WILL BE ABLE TO
CONTROL THE FLOW
OF THE PURE, CLEAN,
FILTERED WATER.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW WE TURN
THAT OFF FOR A SEC,
POUR THE CRUMMY WATER
INTO THE TOP, AND
NOW WE'RE READY.
JUST WAIT A FEW SECONDS
AND OUT COMES PURE
SPRING WATER.
ALL RIGHT, WE SEEM
TO HAVE SOME KIND
OF A CHEMICAL --
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
MAYBE THE NITRO PILLS...
ALL RIGHT.
MAYBE THAT SPRING
WATER WAS A LITTLE
TOO SPRINGY.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S HEADING
RIGHT OVER INTO POSSUM
LAKE, WHICH IS GOOD,
THAT'LL PURIFY THE
WATER OVER THERE.
AND NOW I'LL BE ABLE
TO CATCH RAIN WATER.
YOU CAN'T GET BETTER,
PURER, CLEANER WATER
THAN THAT.
AND THEN NEXT WEEK
WE'LL SHOW YOU HOW
TO PATCH A ROOF.
SO UNTIL THEN REMEMBER,
IF WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
I HOPE IT RAINS SOON
THAT KITTY LITTER
MAKES YOU THIRSTY.
RED: STAY TUNED.
BILL'S GOING TO
DRILL A WELL,
YOU DON'T WANT
TO MISS THAT,
AND HAROLD AND I ARE
GOING TO HAVE A
MAN-TO-MAN TALK
WHICH IS TOUGH
TO DO WITH HAROLD.
I WANT TO TALK TO ALL
YOU MIDDLE-AGE GUYS
ABOUT YOUR EYESIGHT.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GOING THROUGH,
HOLDING THE NEWSPAPER
BETWEEN YOUR TOES
SO YOU CAN
FOCUS ON THE PAGE.
TRYING TO LOOK UP
A PHONE NUMBER
AND SQUINTING SO HARD
YOU THROW YOUR BACK OUT.
NOW A LOT OF
GUYS OUR AGE ARE
GETTING GLASSES.
I SAY DON'T DO IT.
DETERIORATING EYESIGHT
IS PART OF THE
MASTER PLAN.
MOTHER NATURE IS
PRETTY SMART, YOU KNOW,
LIKE THE WAY THAT AS
YOU GET SHE MAKES
YOUR TEETH FALL OUT
SO YOU'LL EAT OATMEAL
AND OTHER STUFF THAT'S
GOOD FOR YOU.
IT'S THE SAME KIND OF
THING WITH YOUR EYESIGHT,
BECAUSE GUYS OUR AGE
ARE A LOT HAPPIER
NOT KNOWING
EXACTLY WHAT
THEY LOOK LIKE
OR WHAT EACH OTHER
LOOKS LIKE
IF YOUR PARTNER IS
AROUND THE SAME AGE.
A LOT YOUNGER THAN YOU,
IT SOUNDS TO ME LIKE
THEY'RE THE ONES THAT
NEED THE GLASSES.
AS FAR AS BOOK READING
IS CONCERNED,
YOU GOT TO GET ALL THAT
IN BY THE TIME YOU'RE 30
SO YOU'LL HAVE TIME TO
APPLY ALL THE KNOWLEDGE
YOU PICKED UP.
ANY KNOWLEDGE THAT
YOU GET AT MY AGE,
THERE'S NOT ENOUGH
TIME TO UNDERSTAND
AND NOT ENOUGH
NERGY TO PRACTICE.
SO I SAY JUST LET
YOUR EYES GO.
THEY SAY YOUR EYES ARE THE
WINDOW TO YOUR MIND AND
IF YOUR EYES ARE FAILING
THERE'S A PRETTY GOOD
CHANC YOUR BRAIN IS ON
ITS LAST LEGS, TOO.
SO JUST LET THEM GO
AND THEN WHEN YOU DIE
YOU CAN WILL THEM TO
SOMEBODY YOU DON'T LIKE.
REMEMBER, I'M
PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ SLURPING SOUNDS ]
WELL, WE GOT EVERYTHING
ALL STRAIGHTENED OUT
WITH ELECTRICITY.
YOU CAN RELAX,
HAROLD, CODE NORMAL.
SO WHAT DID YOU TELL
THE REPAIRMAN FROM
THE ELECTRIC COMPANY?
WELL, NOT MUCH, JUST
EXPLAINED HOW THAT
BIG GUST OF WIND
HAD BLOWN THE HIGH
TENSION WIRE DOWN
INTO THE LAKE.
NO HARM,
NO FOUL.
NO WAY.
YOU GUYS HARM
FOWL ALL THE TIME.
REMEMBER THOSE TURKEYS
YOU GUYS TRIED TO BREED,
THEY JUST SWELLED
RIGHT UP --
IT'S JUST AN
EXPRESSION, HAROLD,
YOU KNOW, THE STRANGEST
THING HAPPENED
BECAUSE A CLOUD
FORMED OVER THE LAKE
COMING UP ALL THE
BUBBLES OUT OF WATER.
THAT'S ELECTROLYSIS.
ELECTROLYSIS?
YOU MEAN WE'VE REMOVED
ALL THE FISHES' UNSIGHTLY
FACIAL HAIR?
NO, NO, IT'S WHEN YOU
PUT ELECTRICITY
INTO THE WATER,
THE H2O BREAKS INTO
HYDROGEN AND OXYGEN.
WE JUST TOOK
THIS IN SCHOOL.
THAT'S ELECTROLYSIS.
SO THE CLOUD OVER POSSUM
LAKE IS PROBABLY JUST
LIKE HYDROGEN.
HYDROGEN LIKE
IN A BLIMP?
YES, BECAUSE HYDROGEN
IS LIGHTER THAN AIR.
YEAH, LIKE YOU PUT HYDROGEN
IN ZEPPELINS, YOU KNOW,
NOT LIKE THE BAND
LED ZEPPELIN OR ANYTHING.
AHH! YOUR HAT'S
A GHOST.
I MUST HAVE GOT SOME
HYDROGEN IN MY HAT
HERE, HAROLD.
HOW DO I GET IT
OUT OF THERE?
WELL, YOU CAN RELEASE IT INTO
THE AIR BUT THAT'S GOING TO
WRECK THE OZONE,
SO DON'T EVEN
THINK ABOUT THAT.
IT BURNS.
HYDROGEN BURNS
REALLY WELL.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TRY THAT.
STAND REAL CLOSE.
REMEMBER THE HINDENBERG?
YOU KNOW THE STORY
OF OUR CANADIAN NORTH
IS REALLY THE STORY
OF OUR DAREDEVIL
BUSH PILOTS.
AND TODAY CARRYING ON
THAT TRADITION ARE GUYS
LIKE BUZZ SHERWOOD HERE
OF BUZZ OFF AIRLINES.
YO' RED MAN,
HOW'S IT GOING?
IT'S GOING GOOD.
IT'S GOING VERY
WELL INDEED.
SO, BUZZ, TELL THE
PEOPLE AT HOME
NOW YOU FERRY
IN TOURISTS,
DO YOU NOT,
AND YOU WATER BOMB
FIRES I THINK.
AND I WATER BOMB
PEOPLE THAT TICK
ME OFF.
ALL RIGHT.
AND, OF COURSE,
I DO THAT COURIER
THING TOO,
YOU KNOW,
SHERWOOD EXPRESS.
WHEN IT ABSOLUTELY
HAS TO GET THERE
AND YOU DON'T CARE
WHAT SHAPE IT'S IN
WHEN IT DOES.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SO BUZZ FLIES MAIL
IN THAT TYPE OF THING, RIGHT?
RED, I FLY ANYTHING
THAT FITS IN THAT PLANE.
THERE YOU GO.
OR ON THE PLANE
OR TOWED BEHIND
THE PLANE OR --
IS THAT -- IS THAT
A CANOE FLOATING
UP THERE, RED
OR AM I GETTING
ONE OF MY FLASHBACKS?
NO, NO, NO,
THAT'S A CANOE.
SHE MUST BE FULL OF
HYDROGEN FROM THAT
ELECTROLYSIS THING WE DID.
FAR OUT.
I COULD USE THAT
IN MY PARCEL DELIVERY.
YOU KNOW INSTEAD OF
SWIMMING TO SHORE
WITH LIKE A PIANO
OR SOMETHING.
SO, AS I SAY,
THERE YOU GO,
YOU SEE THE INNOVATION
GOING ON HERE.
GUYS LIKE BUZZ
SHERWOOD HERE
BRINGING CIVILIZATION
AND ORDER TO THE NORTH.
IT'S ON FIRE.
IT'S BURNING.
OH LADIES AND GENTLEMEN
I CAN'T BEAR TO WATCH.
OH THE HUMANITY.
THE HUMANITY.
OH.
[ SLURPING SOUNDS ]
[ BELCHES ]
UNCLE RED, WHY DO YOU
THINK PEOPLE SMOKE?
DON'T KNOW,
DON'T CARE HAROLD.
WELL, YOU SHOULD,
BECAUSE THEY'RE
RUINING THEIR HEALTH
AND THEY'RE RUINING YOURS
WITH SECONDHAND SMOKE.
WELL, EVERYTHING ELSE
I HAVE IS SECOND HAND,
I DON'T SEE WHY I
SHOULD BE GETTING
BRAND NEW SMOKE,
EXCEPT FROM MY VAN.
WELL, WHY DO YOU
THINK THEY DO IT?
I GOT A THEORY, YOU
WANT TO KNOW WHY?
I GOT A THEORY.
DO YOU THINK MAYBE
IT'S BECAUSE THEY
WEREN'T WEANED PROPERLY?
DO YOU THINK SMOKING
IS LIKE BREAST FEEDING?
ONLY IF YOU
INHALE, HAROLD.
LIKE I WISH EVERYONE
IN THE WORLD WOULD JUST
GROW UP AND STOP SMOKING.
I THINK YOU GOT A
FISH ON YOUR HOOK
THERE, HAROLD.
I KNOW, I'VE BEEN
TRYING TO WIGGLE
HIM OFF FOR AN HOUR.
I'LL TAKE IT.
IT MIGHT BE A SALMON.
I CAN MAKE MY
FAMOUS SMOKED SALMON
OR I GUESS IN THIS
CASE IT WOULD BE
SECONDHAND SMOKED
SALMON, EH, HAROLD?
DON'T INHALE.
IT'S TIME FOR
ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
BILL HAD ASKED ME
OVER TO GIVE HIM A
LITTLE BIT OF HELP.
I WAS STILL LOOKING
FOR SOME FRESH WATER,
SO HE WAS GOING TO
DRILL A WELL
AND HE PICKEA SPOT
RIGHT THERE TO DRILL IT.
NO, NO, NO, I THINK
HE'S CHANGED HIS MIND.
YEAH, HE'S GOING TO
PICK RIGHT THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
SO I WILL JUST START
THE HOLE A LITTLE BIT.
BUT BILL'S GOT ONE OF
THESE AUGER THINGS
THAT LOOKS A
BIT LIKE A --
OH, OH, OH.
AND HE'S GOT A
LONG, OHH --
THE EXTRA LENGTH
OF HANDLE ON THERE.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA BILL.
SO HE PUTS THAT ON
THERE FOR A LITTLE
EXTRA LEVERAGE
AND THE AUGER GOES
BUT THEN THE THING IS
THAT IT CATCHES ON
A ROCK AND IT STOPS.
BILL IS NOW USING
THE LONG LEVER TO --
REALLY TO HIS
OWN DISADVANTAGE.
HE'S BENDING THAT STEEL.
A LOT OF TENSION ON THERE.
AND THEN BILL DECIDED
TO GO INTO MY VAN
FOR SOME REASON.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
I GUESS HE DIDN'T FIND
WHAT HE WAS LOOKING FOR.
SO THEN WE DECIDED TO
TRY ONE OF THESE
POWER AUGERS
WHICH HAS GOT THE
MOTOR ON THERE.
IT'S ABOUT A 300-HORSE
ENGINE ON IT.
BUT THE THING IS, IT
WASN'T DIGGING IN,
IT WAS JUST
RIDING ON TOP.
SO THEN BILL SAYS WE
NEED TO PUSH DOWN HARDER,
GET MORE WEIGHT
ON IT.
BILL I WOULDN'T
CLIMB ON.
BILL THAT'S NOT
COMPLETELY SAFE, BILL.
WHAT AM I ASKING HIM?
AND THERE HE GOES.
THAT LOOKS LIKE
KIND OF FUN.
EASY BILL,
SLOW 'ER DOWN.
SLOW 'ER DOWN BILL.
OH FOR GOSH SAKE
YOU'RE GOING TO FLY OFF.
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
WELL, I BET HE
DOESN'T TRY THAT AGAIN.
I KIND OF WISH HE WOULD.
OH YOU'RE FINE.
QUIT YOUR WHINING.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY
SAY, WHERE THERE'S A
WELL, THERE'S A WAY.
GOOD THINKING, BILL.
SO HE GETS THE HOLE
ALL DRILLED IN THERE
AND NOW HE'S JUST GOT
TO PUT THE PIPE DOWN
TO GET DOWN TO WHERE
THE WATER IS.
THAT'S A STEEL PIPE.
WE GOT SO MANY ROCKS
AROUND THE POSSUM
LODGE AREA.
I THINK WHAT HAPPENED
IS HE HIT A ROCK,
STARTED TO BEND THE
PIPE UP SO IT COME
UP BEHIND HIM.
NEITHER ONE OF US
SAW THIS
BUT IT'S ACTUALLY HEADING
TOWARDS MY GRILL OF
THE POSSUM VAN.
THANK YOU BILL.
WELL, YOU GOT WATER.
IT MIGHT BE OUT OF
THE RAD THERE, BILL
AND IT'S GOT THE
ANTIFREEZE IN IT,
ARE YOU SURE
THAT'S WHAT --
YEAH, YEAH.
RED: STAY TUNED FOR
SPECIAL GUEST
GRAHAM GREENE
AND SOME WORDS OF
ADVICE FROM BUZZ
SHERWOOD
FOR THOSE OF YOU
WHO WILL LISTEN
TO ANYTHING.
WELL, LET'S SEE HOW MY
WATER DIET IS WORKING.
MM-HMM.
NOTHING.
UNCLE RED, WHAT IS THAT
ATTACHED TO THE CEILING?
OH, THAT'S THE VACUUM
CLEANER, HAROLD.
WE SUCKED UP ALL
THE HYDROGEN.
YOU KNOW IF THAT BAG
IS NOT SEALED TIGHT,
THAT BABY IS GOING
TO DROP LIKE A STONE.
OH, NO, WE'RE FINE.
NO, NO, IT'S
TIGHTER THAN A
DRUM THERE, HAROLD.
IF THERE EVER WAS
ANY DANGER WITH THE
HYDROGEN, THAT'S OVER NOW.
UNCLE RED, WHAT
ARE WE GOING TO
DO WITH THE VACUUM?
IT MIGHT MAKE
A GOOD LAMP.
OH, HAROLD, YOU'D
MAKE A GOOD LAMP.
WE'D BOTH MAKE
GOOD LAMPS
BECAUSE I'M BRIGHT
AND HE'S BURNED OUT.
HI, WINSTON ROTHCHILD
HERE FROM ROTHCHILD
SEWAGE AND SEPTIC
SUCKING SERVICES
WHERE WE PUT
THE P-U IN PUMP.
I'M HERE WITH
GLEN BRACKSTON OF
BRACKSTON'S MARINA
FOR THIS WEEK'S
BOATING TIP.
HI RED.
I THOUGHT WE'D TALK
ABOUT LAUNCHING YOUR
OWN BOAT TODAY BY YOURSELF.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE
HOW MANY PEOPLE COME UP
AND ASK ME TO HELP THEM, RED.
LIKE I DON'T
HAVE A JOB.
WELL, ACTUALLY, GLEN,
I GOT TO LOSE SOME
WEIGHT IN A HURRY
AND I WAS KINDA
HOPING YOU COULD
TALK ABOUT DIETING.
I THOUGHT YOU
WANTED A BOAT TIP?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
IF YOU'RE THIN THEN
YOUR BOAT IS NOT
GOING TO SINK.
AND I ALSO THOUGHT
YOU WOULD BE A GUY
WHO'D PROBABLY KNOW
A LOT ABOUT DIETS.
OH?
AND WHY WOULD YOU
THINK THAT RED?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU HAVE A LOOK --
YOU JUST --
I JUST --
I ASSUMED THAT
YOU WOULD BE A DIET
EXPERT, THAT'S ALL.
WELL, NO, NOT
REALLY, BUT IF
YOU WANT TO TRY
TO EAT WHAT I
EAT, GO AHEAD.
NO, NO, NO,
FORGET IT.
NO RED, MODERATION,
THAT'S THE KEY TO IT.
YOU GOT TO HAVE
TO HAVE SELF-CONTROL
AND YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY SELF-CONTROL, RED,
SO, THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE GETTING
AS BIG AS A HOUSE.
THANK YOU, GLEN,
YOU'RE A REAL INSPIRATION.
LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF THE SPARE TIRE
YOU GOT THERE, RED.
SAYS MR. EIGHTEEN
WHEELER.
I GOT BIG BONES.
YOU GOT A
BIG BELLY BONE.
IF I HAD YOUR HEALTH,
I'D TAKE A LOT BETTER
CARE OF MYSELF, RED.
GLEN DO YOU SUPPOSE I
COULD BORROW THIS
OLD PROPANE TANK?
YEAH, SURE.
IT'S EMPTY.
WE HAD A BIG RIB
ROAST LAST WEEK.
OH, NO, I WANT
AN EMPTY ONE.
I WANT TO HOOK IT
UP TO A VACUUM CLEANER.
OH, RED, YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO TRY
THAT SELF-LIPOSUCTION
STUFF, ARE YOU?
I READ ABOUT A GUY
THAT DID THAT LAST WEEK.
HE HOOKED IT UP TO
HIS BELLY BUTTON
INTO A CENTRAL VAC
AND HE SUCKED HIMSELF
INSIDE OUT, HIS
WHOLE BODY.
OH, MY GOD.
DID THEY EVER GET
HIM BACK TO NORMAL?
I DON'T KNOW, I DIDN'T
FINISH THE ARTICLE,
THE NEXT AVAILABLE
CASHIER OPENED UP.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THIS WEEK CLAIMING TO
BE AN EXPERT WITH
MY UNCLE RED
IS EDGAR K.B. MONTROSE.
TODAY'S LETTER
IS FROM A VIEWER
IN BRANDON, MANITOBA.
IT SAYS: DEAR EXPERT,
I LOVE TO BARBECUE
BUT LATELY OUR NEIGHBOURHOOD
HAS BEEN OVERRUN
BY A HUGE FLOCK OF SEAGULLS
THAT RUIN EVERYTHING.
WHAT CAN I DO?
ANY IDEAS THERE EDGAR?
WELL, RED, IF THIS GUY
IS FROM BRANDON, LIKE
IT SOUNDED LIKE HE WAS.
YES.
AND IF HE
LOVES TO BARBECUE,
HE PROBABLY HAS A SPARE
PROPANE TANK SITTING
BY SOMEWHERE.
SO WHAT I RECOMMEND IS
HE TAKE THE TANK AND HE
COVER IT WITH BACON FAT,
ROLL IT IN BIRDSEED AND
PUT IT IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE LAWN.
OH YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH, TO DRAW OUT
THE BIRDS.
YEAH, LIKE AT OUR HOUSE,
YOU KNOW, WE GOT LIKE
A BOWL OF SUGAR WATER
TO DRAW OUT THE BEES,
YOU KNOW, SO WHEN
WE'RE EATING
THEY DON'T COME NEAR
US AND THEY DON'T
SCARE US
AND STUFF
LIKE THAT.
OR, YOU KNOW, OR
THEY LAND ON YOUR NOSE
AND YOU'RE PARALYZED
IN FEAR, YOU KNOW.
I REMEMBER ONE TIME --
REMEMBER ONE TIME --
REMEMBER THIS ONE TIME,
THIS ONE TIME, RIGHT,
THIS BEE LANDED RIGHT
ON MY EAR, RIGHT.
AND MY MOM SAID DON'T MOVE,
RIGHT, SO I DIDN'T MOVE
BECAUSE WHEN MOM SPEAKS,
YOU KNOW, RIGHT?
BUT IT WAS A QUEEN BEE.
IT WAS A QUEEN BEE.
AND THE QUEEN BEE BUILT
THIS HUGE HIVE RIGHT
ON MY EAR.
IT WAS HUGE.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
I MISSED THE WHOLE
WEEK OF SCHOOL.
IT WAS GREAT.
BUT DAD SPRAYED
IT WITH RAID
AND THEN ON THE
WAY TO THE HOSPITAL HE
COLLECTED ALL THE HONEY.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
I MEANT, HAROLD.
WHEN THE BIRDS COME
BY TO FEED OFF THE CAN,
HE TAKES HIS RIFLE,
SAY A THREE OT SIX.
OH, NO, HEY,
HEY, YOU DON'T
SHOOT THE SEAGULLS.
NO, YOU SHOOT THE CAN
AND THEN KABOOM!
NO MORE BIRDS.
NO MORE PROBLEM.
AND THE CONCUSSION WILL
SHATTER ANY SEAGULL EGGS
WITHIN TWO MILES.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU CAN'T
BE WITH THE PLANE
YOU LOVE,
LOVE THE
PLANE YOU'RE WITH.
WELL, I THINK I GOT
THIS DIET THING LICKED.
UNCLE RED I WAS ONLY
KIDDING ABOUT YOU
BECOMING A LAMP.
NO, NO, HAROLD, I
REVERSED THE WIRING
ON THE VACUUM CLEANER
AND I COMPRESSED
ALL THE HYDROGEN DOWN
INTO THIS PROPANE TANK.
OH, SO WHAT, YOU WANT TO
BE LIKE A CENTREFOLD
IN POPULAR SCIENCE
WITH A BARBECUE TANK
ATTACHED TO YOUR NAVAL?
NO, NO.
WATCH HOW THIS
WORKS, HAROLD.
SAY I'M 35 POUNDS
OVERWEIGHT,
WATCH, 25, 20, 10,
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
BLAST OFF!
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
IT'S MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN AS
SOON AS I GET
THE SHRAPNEL OUT
OF MY SHORTS.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I WILL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING
AND YES I CAN EXPLAIN
THE PINK RUBBER
IN MY UNDERWEAR.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD,
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI