♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN,
IN TODAY'S EPISODE HAROLD GIVES
A DRIVE-BY SCIENCE LESSON,
BILL HAS A COLD CAN OF POP,
AND I TURN A CAR INTO
A BICYCLE.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: HERE'S THE MAN
I CALL UNCLE, MY UNCLE,
HUSBAND TO THE WOMAN
I CALL AUNT AND FAVOURITE
AND ONLY BROTHER TO
THE MAN I CALL DAD,
HERE HE IS, RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
THANK YOU, THANK YOU AND WELCOME
ALL OF YOU TO THE SHOW,
AND HOW ARE YOU TODAY HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: EVER EXCELLENT
AS ALWAYS.
>>RED: OH YEAH THAT'S RIGHT,
YOU DON'T GET SICK DO
YOU HAROLD,
YOU'RE MORE OF A CARRIER.
>>HAROLD: I'M NOT JUST
A CARRIER,
I'M A LASER TRANSPORTER.
>>RED: WELL WE'VE BEEN HAVING
A BIT OF FUN THIS WEEK
UP AT THE LODGE,
THE GUYS ARE LOOKING AT SOME
OF THAT BUNGEE JUMPING
YOU KNOW WHERE THEY TIE A BIG
JOCKSTRAP ONTO YOUR ANKLE
AND HEAVE YOU OFF A BRIDGE
YOU KNOW AND THEN THE BLOOD
ALL RUSHES TO YOUR HEAD
AND YOU DAMN NEAR KILL YOURSELF,
AND IT MAKES YOU FEEL
YOUNG AGAIN APPARENTLY.
>>HAROLD: YOU KNOW ACTUALLY
THAT BUNGEE JUMPING IS NOT SAFE
AND IT'S BEEN BANNED IN A LOT
OF AREAS, CEMENT AREAS I THINK.
>>RED: WELL OF COURSE WE CAN'T
AFFORD THE REAL OFFICIAL BUNGEE
JUMPING GEAR OR ANYTHING,
BUT JUNIOR SINGLETON GOT
THE IDEA THAT IF YOU CLIMB
TO THE TOP OF A REAL SPRINGY
TREE LIKE YOU KNOW A WILLOW
OR SOMETHING YOU KNOW,
AND YOU SAY YOU TIE YOUR
FOOT OFF TO THE TOP BRANCH
AND THEN YOU JUST DIVE
IT'S GOT TO BE THE SAME
AFFECT REALLY.
>>HAROLD: YOU KNOW YOU'D HAVE
TO BE A PRETTY GOOD IDIOT
TO DO THAT.
>>RED: WELL THANKS FOR
VOLUNTEERING HAROLD BUT WE
GOT A WHOLE LINEUP OF GUYS AHEAD
OF YOU, IN FACT THEY'RE WAITING
FOR THIS ROPE SO MAYBE WE
SHOULD GET ON WITH THE SHOW.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH, OKAY,
SURE, EXCELLENT,
BECAUSE WE HAVE A SUPERLATIVELY,
EXCELLENT SHOW FOR YOU
THIS EVENING.
>>RED: PRETTY MUCH
THE SAME AS ALL THE OTHERS
AS FAR AS I KNOW.
>>HAROLD: HE HAS
NO UNDERSTANDING OF
THE TELEVISION BUSINESS.
>>RED: OBVIOUSLY.
♪ I OFTEN LOOK BACK ♪
♪ AS I GET OLDER ♪
♪ AT THE FUN WE HAD ♪
♪ WITH MURPHY'S BOULDER ♪
♪ IT WAS 6 FEET ACROSS ♪
♪ MUST HAVE WEIGHED 9 TONS ♪
♪ ROUND AND SMOOTH ♪
♪ AS A BABY'S BUM ♪
♪ WE'D LEAVE MESSAGES ON IT ♪
♪ AND LEAN AGAINST IT ♪
♪ IT WAS LIKE A FRIEND ♪
♪ WHO WAS SOLID AND TRUE ♪
♪ THEN AFTER DARK WE'D ♪
♪ ROLL IT INTO THE LAKE ♪
♪ AND WATCH BOATS ♪
♪ SMACK INTO IT ♪
♪ REALLY, REALLY HARD ♪
>>RED: YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
OH THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH.
THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE GOING
TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING THAT
YOU CAN DO WITH THAT OLD WRECK
OF A CAR THAT YOU MAY HAVE
SITTING OUT ON YOUR
FRONT LAWN SAY OR PERHAPS
WEDGED INTO THE GARDEN SHED.
NOW UP HERE AT THE LODGE
OF COURSE WHEN A CAR GETS
TOO DANGEROUS TO DRIVE
WE JUST SELL IT
TO ANOTHER MEMBER.
BUT WHAT DO YOU DO
WHEN A CAR LITERALLY
FALLS TO PIECES?
SELL IT AS A KIT CAR.
(CRASHING & BANGING)
NOW A LOT OF PEOPLE WOULD
SEE THIS AS A BIG PILE OF
CRAP AND FIGURE, WELL THIS
IS NO LONGER A VIABLE
MEANS OF TRANSPORTATION,
BUT A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE NOT ME.
I LOOK AT THIS STUFF AND
I SAY WITH A LITTLE ELBOW
GREASE AND SOME IMAGINATION
I CAN BUILD MYSELF
A FREE 10-SPEED BICYCLE.
GOLLY IF THE MOTOR HADN'T
OF SEIZED UP I COULD
BUILT A MOPED.
ALL RIGHT THE FIRST THING
YOU NEED IS TO MAKE YOURSELF
A 2-WHEEL BICYCLE,
OF COURSE IT'S 2 WHEELS.
I GOT 4 TO CHOOSE FROM
SO I THREW THE 2 UGLY ONES
AWAY AND I GOT HAROLD'S
TOOTHBRUSH AND CLEANED
ALL THE ROAD KILL OUT
OF THE THREADS OF THESE.
BUT YOU WANT TO MAKE
SURE THAT THERE'S NO
LEAKS IN THESE THINGS,
SO WHAT YOU DO IS YOU TAKE
THE TIRE AND JUST STICK HER
DOWN INTO A BUCKET OF WATER
AND WATCH FOR THE BUBBLES
COMING TO THE SURFACE,
SORT OF LIKE OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
IN POSSUM LAKE, I'LL JUST STICK
THAT DOWN THERE AS EASY AS PIE.
IT'S A LITTLE SMALL FOR THE,
(WATER SPLASHING OUT)
ALL RIGHT, WELL WE'LL ASSUME
THERE'S NO LEAKS THERE.
NOW I'M GOING TO NEED TO
MAKE A FRAME FOR THE BICYCLE,
BY GOLLY THIS WILL WORK
RIGHT HERE, THE EXHAUST
SYSTEM OUT OF THE UNIT
THAT SHOULD BE FINE.
BOY MAKE NO WONDER GAS
STATIONS ARE SO MESSY,
ALL RIGHT TAKE A HACKSAW
AND YOU WANT TO START
HACKING THIS THING UP,
YOU'LL NEED 3 2-FOOT LENGTHS
AND 2 3-FOOT LENGTHS,
SO THAT'S 3-2'S AND 2-3'S
WHICH IS A FULL HOUSE I BELIEVE.
BY GOLLY, BOY HACKSAWS ARE
FRAGILE THINGS AREN'T THEY?
ALL RIGHT, SO ONCE YOU
GOT YOUR PIPE CUT YOU GOT
ENOUGH PIECES NOW TO START
BUILDING YOUR FRAME.
YOU KNOW YOU MIGHT JUST WANT
TO FILE THOSE EDGES A LITTLE
SMOOTHER ESPECIALLY IF YOU
RIDE YOUR BIKE IN SHORTS.
NOW TO PUT ALL THE PIECES
TOGETHER YOU COULD USE
STOVE BOLTS OR YOU COULD
A WELDING TORCH OR YOU
COULD USE THAT'S RIGHT,
THE HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
YOU GOT ANOTHER ROLL
THERE HAROLD.
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT,
AND IF THAT ISN'T A REAL HEAD
TURNER OF A BICYCLE FRAME
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IS.
NOW THIS MUFFLER IS
A DANDY PLACE TO HOLD
WATER FOR YOU LONG DISTANCE
RIDERS WHO CAN'T HOLD YOUR WATER
AND YOU'RE PROBABLY THINKING
TO YOURSELF, WHAT AM
I GOING TO USE FOR PEDALS?
NOW HERE WE GO,
HOW ABOUT WINDOW WINDERS?
AND THEN FOR A CHAIN I'LL,
NOT MUCH OF A...
OH HERE WE GO, HERE WE ARE
WE'LL JUST RUN A FAN BELT FROM
THE PULLEY UP TO ANOTHER PULLEY
AND THERE WE GO THERE,
AND AS FAR AS THE GEARS
GO AND WHATEVER....
HERE'S YOUR FULL GEARS,
THERE'S GEARS EVERYWHERE
IN A CAR, THAT'S NOT
GOING TO BE A PROBLEM,
YOU SEE THE SECRET IS TO
MAKE DO WITH WHAT YOU HAVE,
THIS IS NOT JUST RECYCLING,
IT'S BI-CYCLING.
SO I'LL GET THIS ALL RIGGED
TOGETHER BUT IT'S GOING
TO TAKE A LITTLE WHILE,
WHY DON'T YOU GO BACK TO
THE SHOW AND WHEN I GOT HER
ALL DONE I'LL HAVE YOU COME
BACK IN HERE AND I GET TO
DO A LITTLE SHOWING OFF.
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S THAT
PART OF THE SHOW WHERE WE
EXPOSE THE 3 LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE NOW IS THE EXPERT,
MY UNCLE RED AND OF COURSE
HIS GOOD FRIEND,
MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSY,
LOCAL FISHERMAN AND RACONTEUR.
ALL RIGHTY, 'DEAR EXPERTS,
THERE'S A GUY AT WORK
THAT DRIVES US ALL CRAZY,
WHENEVER HE TELLS YOU SOMETHING
IT'S SO FULL OF LIES AND
EXAGGERATIONS THAT YOU
CAN'T BELIEVE ANY OF IT,
WHAT'S WITH THIS GUY?'
>>RED: WELL HAP THIS SOUNDS
LIKE IT'S MORE IN YOUR AREA.
>>HAP: WELL IT'S A SELF
CONFIDENCE PROBLEM ISN'T IT?
PEOPLE WHO STRETCH THE TRUTH
ARE GENERALLY TRYING TO MAKE
THEMSELVES MORE IMPORTANT
THAN THEY REALLY ARE,
YOU KNOW JUST TO MAKE UP
FOR THEIR POOR SELF IMAGE.
>>HAROLD: WELL THAT'S
VERY INSIGHTFUL.
>>HAP: YEAH, THAT'S WHAT
SIGMUND FREUD TOLD ME,
BUT THE VERY WORST
BRAGGER AND BOASTER
THAT I EVER MET WAS ON ONE
OF OUR CLIMBS UP EVEREST.
WE HAD 7 ATTEMPTS
ALL OF THEM WERE SUCCESSFUL
BUT YOU SHOULD OF HEARD THIS GUY
AND THE STORIES THAT CAME OUT
OF HIS MOUTH, SPACE EXPEDITION,
RUNNING THE 2 MINUTE MILE,
PLAYING BILLIARDS WITH THE POPE,
I HAPPEN TO KNOW THE POPE
ONLY PLAYS STRIPES AND SOLIDS.
BUT THIS GUY GOT TO ME SO
MUCH I HAD TO LEAVE THE TENT,
I HAD TO GET OUT OF THERE
AND SLEEP ON THE GLACIER
BETTER TO RISK ANOTHER ENCOUNTER
WITH THE ABOMINABLE SNOWMAN
THAN TO SPEND ANY MORE
TIME WITH THIS MAN.
>>RED: YEAH I KNOW WHERE
YOU'RE COMING FROM THERE HAP.
>>HAP: BUT OF COURSE I DIDN'T
EXPECT THE AVALANCHE,
350,000 TONS OF SNOW
CLEAVED OFF THAT MOUNTAIN
AND LANDED RIGHT ON THAT KNEE,
THE BAD KNEE.
WELL I WANTED TO SCREAM
BUT SOME OF THE CREW WERE
STILL SLEEPING,
SO I QUIETLY JUST TRIED TO DIG
MYSELF OUT OF IT AND AFTER A
FEW HOURS I CAME UPON THIS GUY,
THIS SAME GUY LYING
THERE UNCONSCIOUS, HIS HEAD
STUCK IN AN ICE CREVICE,
AND I HAD A 7 POUND PICK WITH ME
AND I COULD OF CHIPPED HIM
OUT BUT I COULDN'T GUARANTEE
HE'D STILL HAVE EARS.
>>RED: WELL RIGHT NOW I WOULD
ENVY SOMEONE WITHOUT EARS.
>>HAP: SO I TRIED THIS LITTLE
TRICK THAT I LEARNED DURING
THE WAR FROM DE GAULLE,
I MELTED THE GUY OUT OF THERE
YOU KNOW WITH A POT OF HOT
COFFEE AND A TURKEY BASTER.
>>RED: AND HOW ABOUT YOUR
SELF CONFIDENCE HAP,
DO YOU THINK YOU HAVE
A POOR SELF IMAGE?
>>HAP: USE TO,
BEFORE I WAS KNIGHTED.
>>RED: DON'T ASK HIM HAROLD.
IT IS SPRING,
THE BEARS EMERGE
FROM HIBERNATION
DESPERATE FOR COHABITATION
THE BIRDS FLY HOME
TO MATE AND NEST,
THE SALMON RETURN
TO SPAWN AND REST,
THE DEER COME BACK
TO RUT AND ROAM,
WHAT I'M SAYING IS
HI HONEY I'M HOME!
>>RED: AND THERE YOU HAVE IT
SHE'S PRETTY WELL ALL
RIGGED UP, LOOKING PRETTY
GOOD ISN'T IT?
GOT THE HORN ON HERE,
I CALL THAT THE MATTERHORN
BECAUSE IT'S A MOUNTAIN BIKE.
AND I PUT REFLECTORS ALL OVER
THE BACK AND SO FORTH SO YOU
CAN DO SOME NIGHT RIDING,
AND I'VE GOT THE LIGHT
ON THE FRONT HERE,
AND REMEMBER THE OLD-FASHION
GENERATORS YOU USE TO HAVE
ON YOUR BIKE, WELL I JUST,
ACTUALLY THAT ONE IS AN
ALTERNATOR BUT SHE'S PRETTY
WELL SET TO GO,
I GOT A LITTLE WIND INDICATOR
RIGHT UNDER THE SEAT,
IT MAKES SENSE,
AND LET'S JUST TAKE
HER FOR A SPIN.
(LOUD SIZZLE)
OKAY THAT MUFFLER'S STILL
A LITTLE BIT WARM,
GOT TO WATCH FOR THAT,
AT LEAST WE'VE LEARNED
THERE'S SOMETHING,
I'LL JUST CLIMB RIGHT UP.
AND ALL RIGHT,
WELL I'M GOING TO TAPE
A FEW THINGS UP AND MAYBE
I NEED ANOTHER COUPLE OF ROLLS
OF DUCT TAPE AND I'LL
TAKE CARE OF THAT,
MAYBE THIN OUT THE FRAME AND
WHAT HAVE YOU AND FIX HER ALL UP
AND I THINK SHE'LL LOOK QUITE
A BIT DIFFERENT BY THE TIME
I DO THIS PROPERLY.
IT'S ONE OF THOSE
I'LL JUST...CUT!
AND THAT'S ALL IT TAKES,
THAT LITTLE EXTRA TIME AND
EFFORT AND I'VE MADE THIS
INTO REALLY A LOVELY 10-SPEED
BIKE THAT COINCIDENTALLY
LOOKS EXACTLY LIKE HAROLD'S
BIKE THAT'S HOW GOOD OF
A JOB I'VE DONE EH?
RIGHT DOWN TO THE NAME
ON IT AND EVEN THE DENTS,
IT'S JUST AMAZING
I'M PRETTY PROUD OF THAT.
ANYWAY REMEMBER IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
HAROLD WE'VE TRADED
BIKES BY THE WAY,
HAROLD, HAROLD, HAROLD?
(LOUD CRASH)
>>RED: WELL AS IT TURNS OUT
THE DIAMETER OF THE TREE
AND THE SPRINGINESS DIDN'T TURN
OUT TO BE NEARLY AS IMPORTANT
AS SAY THE STRENGTH OF THE ROPE.
>>HAROLD: WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE REST OF THE ROPE?
>>RED: WELL A LOT OF IT
IS STILL TANGLED AROUND THE
TOP OF THE TREE AND THE REST
IS KIND OF KNOTTED AROUND
MOOSE'S NETHER REGIONS.
>>HAROLD: BOY THAT MUST OF
REALLY HURT WHEN MOOSE HIT
THE GROUND BECAUSE
HE'S A BIG EATER.
>>RED: YEAH HE'S
A BIG FALLER TOO.
HE WAS DOING A SWAN DIVE
THERE AND I BELIEVE HE'D BE
HITTING ABOUT A MOCK 4
WHEN HE STRUCK PAY DIRT,
LUCKILY HE LANDED ON THAT PILE
OF SCRAP IRON AND BRICKS
WE HAD LEFT,
REMEMBER THE PROPANE
TANK WENT UP?
YEAH, SO THAT KIND OF
BROKE HIS FALL BUT HE HIT
SO HARD THAT HE ACTUALLY
CRACKED THE EARTH'S CRUST.
>>HAROLD: IS THE PLANET
GOING TO BE OKAY?
>>RED: OH YEAH
IT'LL HEAL HAROLD.
BUT YOU KNOW WHEN WE STOPPED
LAUGHING AND SO ON,
WE WENT OVER TO HIM AND
WE ROLLED HIM OVER AND THERE
WAS LIKE AN UNDERGROUND
CAVERN THERE.
>>HAROLD: A GROTTO?
>>RED: WELL HE WAS FOR AWHILE
BUT WE LOOKED CLOSER AND
IT WASN'T JUST A CAVERN,
IT WAS AN ABANDONED MINE.
>>HAROLD: A MINE?
>>RED: YEAH.
>>HAROLD: THIS IS EXCELLENT!
THAT'S GREAT, WHAT WAS IT
LIKE A GOLD MINE
OR A PLATINUM MINE?
A PLATINUM CAN BE A DIAMOND MINE
A DIAMOND MINE WE'D BE RICH,
IF WE HAD DIAMONDS WE'D BE RICH
IT COULD BE A DIAMOND MINE,
THIS IS EXCITING!
>>RED: YEAH AND TO THINK IT
ALL STARTED WITH SOMETHING
AS HARMLESS AS TREE DIVING.
>>HAROLD: GO FIGURE.
>>RED: BOY I CAN'T.
♪ THERE'S A SECRET TO SURVIVAL ♪
♪ THAT ALL THE WOODSMAN KNOW ♪
♪ AND I'M ABOUT TO PASS ♪
♪ IT ONTO YOU ♪
♪ NEVER RUN WHEN YOU CAN WALK ♪
♪ NEVER STAND WHEN YOU LIE ♪
♪ AND NEVER LIE WHEN ♪
♪ A HALF TRUTH OR IN FACT ♪
♪ NOT ANSWERING AT ALL ♪
♪ WILL DO ♪
>>RED: WELL FOR THIS WEEK'S
'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'
HE INVITED ME TO COME DOWN
AND HAVE A LITTLE PICNIC
OUT BEHIND THE LODGE,
WHICH I THOUGHT WE WERE
GOING TO GET SOME
ICE-CREAM CONES THERE,
SO I LOVE ICE CREAM
BUT IT WAS A BEAUTIFUL DAY
AND YOU KNOW SOMETHING,
I JUST NEED A HOT SUMMER DAY
TO OH, OH, OH, ALL RIGHT,
WELL I DON'T THINK
I WAS THAT LATE,
WELL LUCKILY I HAD SOMEWHERE
TO CLEAN MY HAND OFF ANYHOW
AND SOME BUTTER THERE
AND ALL RIGHT,
NOW AT THIS POINT WE'RE
STARTING TO GET SOME ICE CUBES
AND, YES, YES I SEE, I THINK
WHAT BILL IS TRYING TO SAY HERE
IS THAT THE SUN MELTS STUFF.
AND NOW BILL APPARENTLY WAS
GOING TO TEACH ME SOME HIGHLY
SECRET SCIENTIFIC PRINCIPLES
WHICH IS HOW YOU CAN MAKE
A REFRIGERATOR
BOY, OUT IN THE WOODS.
OKAY HE PUTS ALL OF THE STUFF
THAT HE WANTS TO KEEP COOL
INSIDE THERE AND CLEANS
OFF THE TABLE, OH MY GOSH,
AND NOW THAT'S,
IT'S LIKE A POTATO BAG,
BURLAP BAG, OH, OH,
IT COULD HAVE BEEN WORSE,
I COULD HAVE BEEN STANDING
OVER THERE.
AND THEN YOU THREAD THE
ROPE UP THROUGH HERE,
AND NOW THIS IS REAL
INTERESTING BECAUSE WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO DO IS
YOU'RE GOING TO COVER UP
ALL THAT STUFF,
PUT THE THING RIGHT OVER
THE TOP OF IT AND THAT KEEPS IT,
AND I FIGURE OKAY,
THAT'S THE SHADE,
YOU'RE GOING TO KEEP
THIS IN THE SHADE, BUT OH NO, NO
YOU HANG IT UP IN A TREE SO
THAT THE ANIMALS I GUESS CAN'T
GET IT AND WHAT HAVE YOU.
AND NOW TO KEEP IT COOL
YOU NEED SOME SORT OF A,
WELL LUCKILY HE HAD A PIE
PLATE IN HIS PANTS THERE,
AND THEN HE JUST, WOW!
HE'S USING ONE OF MY,
HOW DID THAT?
OH WELL, HE'S USING THAT
AS KIND OF A WICK THING,
AND THEN HE PUTS WATER IN
THE PLATE AND I THINK IT'S
CALLED CAPILLARY ACTION
THAT TAKES THE WATER
DOWN THROUGH THE,
WELL BILL, NO, NO, NO,
THAT'S GRAVITY ACTION.
ANYWAY AND THAT KEEPS
IT COOL, THE WATER
EVAPORATES OR SOMETHING,
I DON'T KNOW HOW IT WORKS BUT
APPARENTLY IT WORKS REAL WELL.
OH WELL, I THINK IT'S NOT
ALL THAT WELL AND HERE'S
ANOTHER THING,
THIS IS A BAG THAT'S GOT
ALL HOLES IN IT, A MESH BAG,
HE SHOULDN'T OF GOT HIS FINGERS
IN THERE BECAUSE WE'RE GOING
TO TRY TO PUT SOME OF THE POP,
THE SODA IN, OH, OH, OH, OH!
ALL RIGHT, WELL BILL'S COOLED
ALREADY SO IT'S WORKING.
AND HE PUTS ALL THE CANS
OF SODA POP IN THERE
AND TAKE THEM DOWN,
AND THE IDEA HERE IS YOU TIE
A ROPE TO IT AND YOU THROW IT
OUT INTO THE LAKE YOU KNOW
WHERE'S IT'S COOLER AT
THE BOTTOM AND SO ON,
AND ACTUALLY IT SHOULD BE,
THERE'S A COUPLE OF FRIDGES
DOWN THERE I THINK.
OH ALL RIGHT,
WELL I'M GOING TO HELP HIM OUT.
I MEAN I UNDERSTAND THAT THIS
IS NOT VERY SCIENTIFIC THIS ONE,
I THINK THE WATER'S COOLER
THAN THE AIR AND IT'S GOING
TO KEEP THE POP COLD,
SO I TELL BILL TO HOLD ONTO
THE ROPE, I SHOULD OF TOLD HIM,
MY FAULT, I SHOULD OF TOLD
HIM TO HOLD ONTO THE END
OF THE ROPE.
>>BILL: WHOA!
>>RED: HE'S SCIENTIFIC,
HE'S NOT SMART.
NOW WE'LL GO BACK AND WE'LL
WAIT FOR THE POP TO COOL,
AND WE WAIT THERE 5, 6,
IT WAS PROBABLY AROUND 7 SECONDS
I GUESS AND THEN WE DECIDED
WE YOU KNOW, WE WORKED UP
A PRETTY POWERFUL THIRST,
SO BILL HAULS IT IN AND
HAUL IT IN THERE BILL,
HO! HO! HEAVE-HO! HO-HEAVE!
BOY OH BOY THAT'S A SCARY SIGHT,
ANYWAY UP SHE COMES AND WE
EACH GET OUT A CAN OF POP,
OF COURSE SHE'S BEEN SHAKEN
UP PRETTY GOOD THERE SO,
I FORGOT THAT BILL GOT A GOOD
LAUGH OUT OF ME HERE BECAUSE
I COVERED MYSELF WITH THE STICKY
OH THAT'S FUNNY ISN'T IT BILL?
WHAT, YOURS IS OKAY?
>>BILL: AH!
>>RED: AND NOW HERE'S
SOMETHING FOR YOUNG MINDS FROM
SOMETHING WITH A SMALL MIND.
>>HAROLD: YO! WELCOME TO
A BRAND NEW FEATURE ON
THE RED GREEN SHOW WHICH
I'M SURE IS GOING TO BE
INTEREST TO ANYONE UNDER
THE AGE OF 80.
OKAY NOBODY TELLS YOU
HOW TO BE A TEENAGER BUT
EVERYBODY TELLS YOU HOW
NOT TO BE ONE RIGHT?
LIKE DON'T LEAVE
YOUR ROOM A MESS,
DON'T LEAVE THAT FRIDGE
DOOR OPEN ALL NIGHT,
DON'T GO STEALING A CAR
AND GO JOYRIDING.
THAT'S WHY KIDS JOIN GANGS,
SO THEY KNOW HOW TO BEHAVE
THAT AND YOU KNOW TO PROTECT
THEM FROM OTHER GANGS
OF COURSE, WELL, OKAY,
WELL IF THERE'S GOING
TO BE GANGS, WHY CAN'T
THERE BE LIKE GOOD GANGS?
HOW ABOUT TAKING
YOUR SWITCHBLADE?
APPLYING IT TO THE END
OF A STICK, PICK UP LITTER HUH?
INSTEAD OF DRIVE-BY SHOOTINGS,
WE'D HAVE LIKE DRIVE-BY
SCIENCE CLASSES,
DID YOU KNOW THE PEREGRINE
FALCON FLIES UP TO
170 MILES PER HOUR?
IMAGINE THE UNITED WAY GANG
VERSUS THE UNICEF WAY GANG
IN LIKE A FUNDRAISER HUH?
THAT'D BE PRETTY NEAT,
OR INSTEAD OF STREET FIGHTS
WE CAN HAVE LIKE STREET
THEATRE RIGHT?
BECAUSE REMEMBER THE GANG
IN WEST SIDE STORY,
THEY ALL SANG AND DANCED
DIDN'T THEY?
♪ WHEN YOU'RE HOT YOU'RE HOT ♪
REMEMBER?
>>RED: HEY WRAP IT UP
THERE HAROLD, THERE'S
A GANG FORMING OUT HERE.
>>HAROLD: OH EXCELLENT!
>>RED: WELL I DON'T THINK
YOU'LL SAY THAT WHEN
YOU SEE WHAT THEY DID
TO YOUR BIKE.
>>HAROLD: EXCELLENT.
>>RED: SORRY HAROLD,
I COULDN'T STOP THEM THOUGH,
THEY WERE BIG GIRLS.
>>RED: YOU KNOW THEY SAY
THAT THE YOUNG PEOPLE
ARE THE FUTURE OF
THIS COUNTRY,
WELL I SAW SOME YOUNG PEOPLE
TODAY HANGING OUT AT
MURRAY'S STORE AND FROM WHAT
I CAN TELL THE FUTURE IS GOING
TO BE BALD ON THE SIDES
WITH A LONG PIECE OF HAIR ON
THE TOP, SPIT, SWEAR, SMOKE
AND WEAR PANTS THAT ARE
5 SIZES TOO BIG FOR IT.
I SAID TO THEM BOY IF YOU
PEOPLE ARE THE FUTURE I'M
GLAD I'LL BE DYING SOON,
AND THEY SEEM PLEASED
WITH THAT THEMSELVES.
>>BOB: OH!
>>RED: IS THAT AN
EXTRA CLUB THERE BOB?
>>BOB: OH HI RED,
NO I WAS CONDUCTING AN
AIR DENSITY TEST FOR THE
DEPARTMENT OF NATURAL RESOURCES,
YOU SEE HOW THAT DRIFTED
AND THEN CAUGHT A THERMAL?
THAT'S VERY IMPORTANT IN
ENVIRONMENTAL DATA STUFF,
IF I CAN JUST DO THE
SAME TEST WITH A BALL.
>>RED: OH I'M SORRY.
OH NOW BOB! BOB! BOB!
>>BOB: OH!
>>RED: BOB, BOB, BOB, BOB, BOB,
BOB, HERE GIVE ME THAT.
THE PROBLEM IS YOU CAN'T
READ THE AIR WIND THERMAL
STUFF AND HIT THE BALL
AT THE SAME TIME,
SO I'LL DO THE EASY PART.
>>BOB: OH ALL RIGHT.
WELL RED THERE'S A SAND TRAP
ON THE LEFT SIDE SO TRY AND
STAY ON THE RIGHT SIDE.
>>RED: YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
>>BOB: HMM, THAT'S RIGHT
ON THE GREEN RED.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH.
>>BOB: WELL THAT'S GOOD TOO.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
>>BOB: LISTEN WOULD YOU,
LET ME TAKE THAT WOULD YOU,
WOULD YOU LIKE TO FINISH
MY ROUND FOR ME?
>>RED: WELL DID YOU GET
THE WIND INFORMATION YOU
NEEDED FROM THE BALL THERE?
>>BOB: HMM, OH YEAH.
WELL DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT,
WE'VE GOT 35 MORE HOLES TO PLAY.
>>RED: DO YOU KNOW BOB
I WANTED TO ASK YOU,
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
AN OLD MINE OVER ON THE EAST
SIDE OF THE LODGE
MAYBE A LONG TIME AGO?
>>BOB: OH YEAH, YEAH,
THEY CLOSED THAT MINE
ABOUT 50 YEARS AGO,
IT WAS AN OLD COAL MINE.
>>RED: OH.
>>BOB: BUT IT NEVER PRODUCED
ENOUGH COAL TO PAY FOR ITSELF,
SO OF COURSE THEY SOLD IT
TO THE GOVERNMENT.
>>RED: WELL EVERYBODY AND
HIS BROTHER HAD A SUGGESTION
ABOUT WHAT TO DO WITH
THE OLD MINESHAFT.
MAKE IT INTO A GARBAGE DUMP,
STORING NUCLEAR MISSILES,
MAKE AN UNDERGROUND SKYSCRAPER.
STINKY PETERSON HERE WANTS
TO PUT AN OUTHOUSE OVER IT
AND IT WON'T HAVE TO
MOVE FOR 1,000 YEARS.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED DID YOU
HAPPEN TO READ MY SUGGESTION?
>>RED: NO, NO I HAVEN'T YET
HAROLD BUT WHEN I READ THAT ONE
OH YEAH A FUNNY ONE!
WHAT AN IDIOT THIS GUY!
THIS GUY'S SAYS,
WHY DON'T YOU USE THE MINE
SHAFT AS A TIME CAPSULE, OH MAN!
OH SORRY HAROLD, SORRY.
WELL OLD MAN SEDGEWICK NOW
HE SAID WHAT HE WOULD LIKE
TO DO IS HE WOULD LIKE
TO MINE GASOLINE.
>>HAROLD: HOW WOULD THAT WORK?
>>RED: WELL IT WOULDN'T
HAROLD BASICALLY,
BUT IT JUST GOES TO SHOW
WHAT WE ALREADY KNEW WHICH
IS OLD MAN SEDGEWICK DOESN'T
KNOW HIS GAS FROM A HOLE
IN THE GROUND.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH THAT IS IT
UNCLE RED IT'S MEETING TIME,
MEETING TIME!
>>RED: OKAY HAROLD,
YOU GO AHEAD,
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT,
WELL THAT'S ABOUT OUR
SHOW FOR THIS TIME,
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING
AND I THINK I FOUND AN
IDEAL RETIREMENT HOME FOR
YOUR PARENTS AS LONG AS THEY
DON'T MIND THE SMELL OF COAL.
AND FOR THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON
THE ICE.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUONDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
♪ ♪ ♪
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca