IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S A MAN
WHO NEEDS NO INTRODUCTION
BUT OFTENTIMES AN ALIBI...
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS VERY MUCH!
ATTABOY, HAROLD.
(Applause)
THANK YOU.
WE HAD A PROBLEM YESTERDAY.
JUNIOR GOT A NEW
REAR-VIEW MIRROR FOR HIS CAR.
HE BORROWED A CORDLESS DRILL
FROM ALFIE DINKLE
TO INSTALL THE THING.
THIS WAS A HUGE MIRROR.
IT WAS FROM THE SPACE SHUTTLE.
ABOUT FOUR FEET WIDE --
KIND OF A REAR-VIEW MIRROR
IMAX DEAL.
HE GOT THAT MOUNTED.
HE CAN SEE EVERYTHING
BEHIND HIM.
DOESN'T HAVE TO TURN HIS HEAD.
HE SEES EVERYTHING
BEHIND THE CAR.
IT'S TOO BAD
THE BLUEBERRY STAND
WAS IN FRONT OF IT.
HE HIT IT HEAD-ON!
HE WIPED 'ER OUT OF THERE!
NAILED 'ER -- OH, MAN!
IT'S OK, THOUGH --
NOBODY WAS HURT.
THE BLUEBERRIES ACTED
LIKE A MILLION LITTLE AIRBAGS.
JUNIOR'S CAR'S
NOT WHITE ANY MORE.
IT'S LIKE A BLUEBERRY BLUE.
YEAH, BUT HE'S GONNA TAKE
THAT MIRROR OFF,
BUT HE CAN'T BORROW
THE CORDLESS DRILL FROM ALFIE
BECAUSE ALFIE WAS ALSO THE
OWNER OF THE BLUEBERRY STAND.
HE'S A LITTLE TICKED.
HA! HE'S CRUSHED.
(Laughing)
SO NOW, GET THIS, GET THIS.
JUNIOR HAS GIVEN HAROLD
100 BUCKS -- SHOW 'EM --
TO BUY HIM
A NEW CORDLESS DRILL.
HOW ABOUT THAT, HUH?
THAT'S EXCELLENT!
BUYING A POWER TOOL
MAKES YOU A MAN.
(Audience laughing)
THEN YOU BETTER MAKE SURE
YOU GET IT HALF-OFF.
(Audience laughing)
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MESSAGE BEING, FOR
GOSH SAKES, DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
I HOPE HAROLD CAN HANDLE
THE PRESSURE
OF BUYING THIS DRILL.
THIS COULD BE A TURNING POINT.
MAYBE THE KIDS WON'T BEAT UP
ON HIM SO BAD.
WHEN THEY SEE
THAT CORDLESS UNIT,
MIGHT GIVE THEM THE IDEA
TO DRILL HIM ONE!
UNCLE RED, I GOT IT!
IT'S SUCH A BEAUTIFUL DRILL.
IT'S CORDLESS, IT'S REVERSIBLE.
IT'S GOT EXTRA BATTERIES
AND A CHARGER,
BITS, CARRYING CASE,
TOP OF THE LINE, $97.
"YES, PLEASE, RING IT THROUGH.
"HAVE A RAINBOW DAY."
(Laughing)
97 BUCKS, HAROLD?
BOY, THEY SAW YOU COMING,
DIDN'T THEY?
I GOT IT AT LENNY'S
ELECTRICAL SHOP.
DON'T BUY FROM LENNY'S.
HE HATES US --
WE OWE HIM MONEY.
IF I ONLY SHOPPED PLACES
YOU DON'T OWE MONEY TO,
I'D HAVE TO GO TO FRANCE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BUY STUFF
FROM LENNY.
HE'S JUST A MIDDLEMAN.
HE'S GOT OVERHEAD.
IT'S A SHOP HE RUNS
OUT OF HIS BASEMENT!
THAT CAN'T BE CHEAP.
THE SUMP PUMP'S ALWAYS RUNNING.
THAT'S CRAZY --
$97 IS A FAIR PRICE.
THEY'RE $94.50
AT THE HARDWARE AND SUCH.
YEAH, OK, THREE BUCKS,
BIG DEAL.
YOU SAVE THREE BUCKS A DAY
FOR A MONTH,
HOW MUCH HAVE YOU GOT?
THAT DEPENDS ON THE MONTH.
WELL, NO, IT DOESN'T.
THREE BUCKS IS THREE BUCKS,
WHETHER IT'S FEBRUARY OR MAY!
THESE KIDS TODAY,
THEY GOT NO MONEY SENSE.
I'LL GET A DRILL SO CHEAP,
IT WILL MAKE YOUR HEAD SPIN.
IF IT MADE HIS HEAD SPIN,
WE WOULDN'T NEED A DRILL.
(Audience laughing)
(Red): LATER, WE'LL HAVE
THE "ADVENTURES WITH BILL".
WHAT HE'LL BE DOING THIS WEEK,
REAL EXCITING.
NO, IT'S NOT
WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
HE'S GONNA DO
SOME POLE-VAULTING.
OH, YEAH.
OOOH!
BY GOLLY!
FOR HIS FIRST CHALLENGE,
HE'S GONNA TRY
AND VAULT OVER THE VAN.
GOSH, I HOPE THIS GOES WELL.
(Bill): EEEEEYAH!
OHHHH!
(Red): PERFECT!
OHHHHH
HAPPY, HAPPY PEOPLE
CALL ME ON THE PHONE
TO TELL ME ABOUT
SOME NUT-BAR PRODUCT
THEY THINK I SHOULD OWN
IF YOU LOOK BACK
THROUGH HISTORY
AT THE CAUSE
OF EVERY WAR
YOU'LL FIND
HAPPY, HAPPY PEOPLE
AND AN ARMY OF GUYS
LIKE ME
WHO JUST COULDN'T TAKE IT
ANY MORE
AOOO!
WE'RE PLAYING
FOR THE GRAND PRIZE
OF A TURNIP FARM
AND FOUR TONS OF WAX.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. BUZZ SHERWOOD
TO SAY THIS WORD...
BUZZ? EXCELLENT.
THE WORD IS...
"QUIET".
OH, WE GET IT.
AND GO!
OK, BUZZ.
OH, COOL!
A MACHINE THAT ISN'T LOUD IS...
BROKEN!
(Audience laughing)
NO, IF YOU DON'T MAKE
ANY NOISE, YOU'RE...
OH, YOU'RE DEAD, MAN!
(Laughing)
I'M NOT...
PEACE AND...
CARROTS!
NOT PEAS! PEACE!
OH, PEACE.
PEACE AND...
LOVE? UH, COME TOGETHER?
RASH?
NO, NO, HOLD IT.
PEOPLE COME UP TO POSSUM LODGE
FOR THE PEACE
AND...
WITNESS RELOCATION!
(Audience laughing)
WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
I KNOW --
I'M THINKING...
THINK MOVIES, OK?
"ALL 'SOMETHING'
ON THE WESTERN FRONT".
UM... FOOD STAINS!
(Singing)
UM... CHEST HAIR?
I WISH YOU'D JUST
BE QUIET FOR A SECOND!
WHOA!
(Applause)
THERE YOU GO.
WE'RE OUT OF TIME.
ONE BIG DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
MY GENERATION AND HAROLD'S
IS HE NEVER GOT TO EXPERIENCE
THOSE REAR-ENGINE,
REAR-WHEEL-DRIVE CARS.
YOU KNOW, THE VOLKSWAGEN
BEETLE, THE CORVAIR.
THEY SAY THE CORVAIR
WAS UNSAFE AT ANY SPEED.
I'M SORRY HAROLD MISSED THAT.
SO THIS WEEK
ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
WE'RE GONNA TAKE
A FRONT-ENGINE,
FRONT-WHEEL-DRIVE CAR
AND TURN IT INTO A REAR-ENGINE,
REAR-WHEEL-DRIVE CLASSIC.
ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS JUST
TAKE THE ENGINE OUT, MOVE THAT.
YOU GOTTA MOVE THE RAD
AND THE BATTERY
AND THE WINDSHIELD...
ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S NOT ENOUGH DUCT TAPE
IN THE WORLD FOR THAT JOB.
NOW WE'RE SCUPPERED...
UNLESS...
YOU KNOW, THAT JUST MIGHT WORK.
EVEN IF IT DOESN'T,
I DON'T CARE.
THIS IS OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S CAR.
TO TURN A FRONT-ENGINE
FRONT-WHEEL-DRIVE VEHICLE
INTO A REAR-ENGINE,
REAR-WHEEL-DRIVE VEHICLE
TURN EVERYTHING AROUND.
PUT THE CONTROLS AT THE BACK.
HAVE THE SEATS FACING
THE OTHER WAY.
THERE YOU ARE --
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
TO GET THE FRONT SEAT OUT,
ALL YOU NEED IS
MAYBE SOME TOOLS, SOME OIL...
OR... JUST SOME RUST.
I MEAN, RUST IS
A NATURAL PROCESS.
IT'S ALWAYS GOOD
TO WORK WITH NATURE.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
ONCE YOU GOT THE SEAT REMOVED,
AND YOU'VE REMOVED
THE UPHOLSTERY --
WHICH YOU SHOULD REPLACE
FROM TIME TO TIME --
LET 'ER COOL DOWN,
AND TAKE THE DRIVER'S SEAT
AND PUT 'ER
IN THE CAR BACKWARDS.
YOU WANT TO SECURE THAT.
YOU CAN BOLT IT DOWN,
YOU CAN WELD IT,
OR YOU COULD DO
WHAT I LIKE TO DO --
USE THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON...
DUCT TAPE.
YOU COULD USE THIS
AS YOUR NEW UPHOLSTERY.
IF YOU PUT IT ON
STICKY-SIDE-OUT,
YOU WOULDN'T EVEN NEED
SEATBELTS.
(Sizzling)
ONCE YOU GOT 'ER ALL DONE,
YOU JUST MOUNT 'ER INSIDE...
(Grunting)
... WITH MORE OF THE SAME.
RATHER THAN TAKE THE CONTROLS
AND MOUNT THEM ON THE BACK,
GET DIFFERENT CONTROLS
OUT OF A BOAT...
MAYBE A BOAT
YOU DON'T WANT,
OR SOMEBODY DOESN'T WANT...
OR AT LEAST THEY WON'T,
AS SOON AS THEY FIND OUT
THE CONTROLS BEEN RIPPED OUT.
TAKE THE STEERING WHEEL
FROM THE BOAT
AND HOOK THAT UP
TO THE CAR'S STEERING WHEEL.
YOUR GAS PEDAL, YOU HOOK UP
TO THE HAND THROTTLE
FROM THE BOAT,
AND AS FAR AS THE BRAKES GO,
USE YOUR ANCHOR ROPE.
(Grunting)
I GOT OUR CONTROLS
ALL HOOKED UP.
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS, WE GOT
THE HEADLIGHTS AT THE BACK.
WE GOT THE TAIL-LIGHTS
AT THE FRONT.
TO CORRECT THAT,
WE GOTTA TAKE THOSE OFF...
OK, IT'S A PHILLIPS
SCREWDRIVER.
YOU'LL NEED
PLASTIC FLOWER-HOLDERS
AND YOU CAN TURN HEADLIGHTS
INTO TAIL-LIGHTS.
WE GOT THE CONTROLS ALL SET UP
AND SHE'S READY TO GO BOATING--
OR, I SHOULD SAY, DRIVING --
WATCH THIS.
(Squeaking)
AND START 'ER UP.
(Engine whirring)
IT'S JUST THAT EASY
TO TURN A FRONT-WHEEL-DRIVE,
FRONT-ENGINE CAR
INTO A REAR-WHEEL-DRIVE,
REAR-ENGINE CAR.
JUST PUT EVERYTHING IN REVERSE.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
IT'S THE BEST OF BOTH WORLDS.
SHE LOOKS LIKE A CAR,
DRIVES LIKE A BOAT...
"THE TITANIC"!
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
WANT TO TALK
TO YOU LADIES OUT THERE
SO THAT YOU DON'T PANIC
WHEN YOUR HUSBAND
STARTS GOING A LITTLE WACKY.
(Audience laughing)
A MAN GETS TO A CERTAIN AGE,
HE LOOKS AROUND AND HE REALIZES
HE BASICALLY HAS NOTHING
TO SHOW FOR HIS LIFE.
HE MAY HAVE SPENT THE LAST
25 YEARS SITTING AT A DESK,
OR MAYBE BEING ON THE PHONE
ALL THAT TIME,
AND THE ONLY PROGRESS HE'S MADE
IS BUILDING A HUGE GUT
THAT PROTECTS HIS BELT
FROM THE SUN.
(Laughing and applause)
SO...
(Laughing)
YOU MAY FIND, AT THIS POINT,
THAT YOUR MAN WILL GO OUT AND
BUY HIMSELF SOME POWER TOOLS
AND START DISAPPEARING
INTO THE GARAGE
FOR LONG PERIODS OF TIME.
THERE'S NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
WHAT HE'S DOING IS BUILDING
SOME HUGE, CLUMSY,
ODD-LOOKING PIECE OF CRAP
THAT HE'S GONNA LEAVE BEHIND
SO PEOPLE WILL REMEMBER HIM.
THEY WON'T BE FOND MEMORIES,
BUT HE DOESN'T NEED
TO KNOW THAT NOW.
AND I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING.
IF HIS MOTHER HAD KEPT
THAT 65-POUND ASHTRAY
HE BROUGHT HOME IN GRADE 5,
NONE OF THIS
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED.
HERE'S SOMETHING
FOR YOU MOMS TO REMEMBER.
WHEN YOUR SON COMES HOME
WITH HIS FIRST PROJECT,
YOU TREASURE IT.
LEAVE IT OUT ON THE COUNTER
WHERE EVERYBODY GETS
TO LOOK AT IT ALL THE TIME.
YOU'LL BE DOING HIS FUTURE WIFE
A HUGE FAVOUR.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Laughing and applause)
DOES IT HURT
YET?
CUT IT OUT, HAROLD.
I FOUND THE SAME CORDLESS DRILL
AT THE DRILL DEPOT.
INSTEAD OF $97,
IT WAS $86.99, HAROLD.
WOW, THAT'S LIKE
A $10.01 SAVINGS.
BUT THERE WAS NO CASE
AND NO DRILL BITS.
SO THE ONE I GOT IS OK.
NO, BECAUSE THEN I WENT TO
POWER TOOLS R US.
THAT'S POWER TOOLS RUST --
THE "T" FELL OFF THE SIGN.
WELL, THEY HAD IT FOR
EIGHT BUCKS LESS.
SO YOU GOT THAT ONE.
IT DIDN'T COME WITH
A CHARGER.
THEN I WENT TO NUMBER LUMBER.
I THOUGHT WE WEREN'T ALLOWED
BACK IN THAT STORE.
WELL, I WAITED TILL
HIS WIFE LEFT.
I PROMISED TO PAY HIM CASH.
THAT HELPS.
HE HAD THE DRILL, THE CASE,
THE CHARGER, AND DRILL BITS,
80 BUCKS.
EXCELLENT, OK.
BUT NO STOCK.
SO NOW I'M GOING TO
BILL'S BUILD-ALL IN BUILDINGS.
WHAT ABOUT
ALL YOUR TIME AND GAS?
HAROLD, WHEN YOU GET TO MY AGE,
TIME AND GAS IS
ALL YOU HAVE LEFT.
(Applause)
ALL RIGHT, TIME FOR
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL".
BILL'S GONNA DO
SOME POLE-VAULTING.
THAT GROUND'S PRETTY HARD.
YOU'RE GONNA BREAK
EVERY BONE IN YOUR BODY.
HE'S GOT ANOTHER IDEA.
HE'S GOT SOME TYPE OF PADDING
LEFT FROM THE DISCO ERA.
BOY OH BOY.
OH MY GOSH.
HOLY MACKEREL!
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN
UNCOMFORTABLE TO SIT ON.
HE'S GONNA USE THAT AS A...
THAT WOULD BE
THE LANDING AREA THERE.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
NOW WHAT, BILL?
ALL RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW QUITE
WHAT HE'S GOT IN MIND,
BUT WE'LL SEE.
THAT CAN'T BE
ALL THERE IS TO IT.
ALL RIGHT, UH...
AWAY HE GOES.
THE HARD GROUND.
SHE WON'T DIG IN.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU'RE TOO CLOSE!
OH BOY.
YOU'RE TOO CLOSE.
SO HE NEEDS TO MAKE
A SPOT THERE.
SO, HE'S GONNA HAVE ME...
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WAS THINKING OF HERE.
BUT HE WANTED TO USE MY FOOT
AS THE BACK-STOP
FOR THE POLE.
I'M GETTING A LITTLE...
SO I JUST...
OH BOY, OH BOY, OH BOY.
LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT.
WHOA!
OH, HEY, HEY!
HEY, THAT'S COLD.
MAKE A WISH.
ALL RIGHT,
HE'S GOT A BETTER IDEA.
HE'S GONNA PLANT A HOLE...
OW!
... RIGHT IN MY FOOT.
THANK YOU, BILL.
THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT, THERE YOU GO.
BACK HE GOES.
JUST BACK AWAY.
AND HERE HE COMES --
MR. ATHLETE.
AND
THERE HE GOES!
YOU'RE GONNA CLEAR IT.
IT'S GONNA TAKE A FEW MINUTES
TO GET BILL'S HEAD OUT
FROM HIS SHOULDER BLADES.
WE'LL FINISH THE ADVENTURE
A LITTLE LATER.
WITH MY 12-STEP PROGRAMME,
I CAN HELP YOU OVERCOME
THAT BIOLOGICAL IMPERATIVE.
NO MORE "SORRY,
IT'S A GUY THING."
I WANT TO START BY
CALLING ON MY UNCLE RED.
OH, MAN -- NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NEVER MIND.
ALL RIGHT, UH...
MY NAME IS RED AND I'M A MAN.
HI, RED.
LET'S DO THE
"MEN ANONYMOUS" PLEDGE.
(All): I AM A MALE,
BUT I CAN CHANGE
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
OK.
WELL DONE, WELL DONE.
LET'S JUST OPEN THE MEETING.
LET'S GET STARTED.
WHO WANTS TO SHARE
THEIR FEELINGS?
OK, WHO WANTS TO TELL
A GOOD STORY ABOUT THEMSELVES?
OH, OK, GREAT.
UM, DALTON.
(Clearing
throat)
ALL RIGHT,
UH...
MY NAME'S DALTON.
(All): HI, DALTON.
I'M A MAN,
AND I HAVE BEEN
EVER SINCE THE AGE OF 9.
(Audience laughing)
I'M WORKING ON IT,
AND UH, YOU KNOW,
ONE DAY AT A TIME.
ANYWAY, I WAS OUT IN THE GARAGE
THE OTHER DAY,
AND I FOUND THIS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT'S FOR
AND I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT DOES.
IT'S NOT WORTH MUCH, OBVIOUSLY.
I CAN'T THINK OF A THING
TO USE IT FOR,
SO... I THREW IT OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
VERY GOOD.
OH BOY.
UH, YOU KNOW,
I KNOW THAT SOMEDAY
I'M GOING TO BE
WORKING AROUND THE HOUSE,
AND I'M GONNA NEED IT, BUT...
IT WILL BE THE PERFECT THING.
I THREW IT OUT.
HOW COME YOU STILL HAVE IT?
I THOUGHT OF
WHAT I COULD USE IT FOR,
SO I PULLED IT
OUT OF THE GARBAGE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
USE IT FOR?
WELL...
WELL, TO BRING TO THE MEETING.
YOU KNOW, TO SHOW, TO SHOW YOU.
TO SHOW MY RESOLVE.
I'M GONNA KEEP THIS
AS A REMINDER
OF HOW STRONG I AM
WHEN I PUT MY MIND TO IT.
THIS IS A TROPHY!
YEAH.
YUP.
(Red): ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE ARE TO FINISH OFF
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL".
HE'S DECIDED THAT ONE POLE
ISN'T LONG ENOUGH.
THAT'S WHY
HE'S NOT CLEARING THE BAR.
SO WE GOT A COUPLE TOGETHER.
BOY, THAT...
THAT LOOKS SAFE AND STURDY.
AND SO DOES THE POLE.
AND HE COMES AND HE COMES.
HE PLANTS THAT.
AND THEN UP, UP, UP, UP.
WAY YOU GO.
UP, UP.
THIS HAPPENS TO A LOT OF MEN
BILL'S AGE.
COME ON, BILL, GIVE IT UP.
SO WHAT HE DECIDED HE NEEDS
IS MORE SPEED.
THAT'S WHERE THE VAN...
IT'S SIR VAULT-A-LOT.
UP HE GOES.
AND AWAY YOU GO OVER THE BAR.
HEY, THAT'S THREE POINTS.
OW!... OHH!
I THINK THAT WE'VE FINALLY GOT
THIS THING FINISHED OFF,
DON'T WE, BILL?
YEAH, HE'S FINISHED OFF.
SPECIAL THANKS
TO A VIEWER
FOR THESE
BAND-AIDS
MADE FROM
DUCT TAPE.
THERE IS NOTHING
LIKE GETTING BARGAINS
TO MAKE YOU FEEL GOOD.
THEN, WITH THE MONEY YOU SAVE,
YOU CAN BUY MORE BARGAINS.
HOW MUCH WAS
THE CORDLESS DRILL?
OH -- WE ALMOST BOUGHT ONE
UP IN PORT ASBESTOS.
YOU WENT ALL THE WAY
TO PORT ASBESTOS
TO SAVE A FEW BUCKS?
TO SAVE AN EXTRA DOLLAR,
YOU GOTTA GO AN EXTRA MILE.
AN EXTRA 125 MILES?!
DID YOU SAVE AN EXTRA $125?
'CAUSE IF YOU DID,
THAT MEANS YOU SPENT
MINUS $28 ON THE DRILL.
THEY HAD ONE AT
THE SHOPPERS CLUB, $72.50.
MIND YOU, YOU HAD TO BE THERE
FOR THE SPECIAL,
CLIP THE COUPON,
CASH IN YOUR AIR MILES,
THEN YOU HAD
TO SCRATCH-AND-SAVE
AND MAIL IN THE REBATE.
SO HOW MUCH DID YOU PAY?
WELL, NOTHING, HAROLD.
THERE WAS
SO MANY OTHER BARGAINS.
CHEESE, THEY HAD 25 POUNDS
OF CHEESE FOR 10 BUCKS.
AND IT LOOKED GREAT.
REALLY ORANGEY.
AND THEN YOU GET
THAT MUCH CHEESE,
YOU GOTTA GO WITH THE CRACKERS.
A HUGE BUCKET OF CRACKER,
23 BUCKS.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK GOT
A BIG BARREL OF LEGO.
HOW MUCH TO JOIN THIS CLUB?
ONLY 45 BUCKS.
YOU SEE WHY WE DIDN'T HAVE
MONEY TO BUY A CORDLESS--
NOW WE'RE GOING TO GO
WHERE THE REAL BARGAINS ARE,
ACROSS THE BORDER.
NO.
OH, YEAH.
DUTY-FREE PERFUME, BEER.
CHEAP SHOES, CHEAP SHIRTS,
CHEAP DRILLS.
GOD BLESS AMERICA.
GOD SAVE AMERICA.
WANT TO TALK TO YOU YOUNG KIDS,
IF ANY OF YOU ARE WATCHING.
I FEEL SORRY FOR YOU GUYS.
GOTTA BE TOUGH
BEING A KID THESE DAYS.
AS SOON AS YOU FIND
SOMETHING COOL TO WEAR OR DO,
SOME DORKY PARENT
DOES THE SAME THING
'CAUSE IT MAKES THEM
FEEL YOUNG.
MAYBE IT'S WEARING
YOUR CAP BACKWARDS
OR YOUR PANTS INSIDE-OUT,
OR MAYBE THAT MOSH-PIT THING.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT IT IS.
PARENTS GET INTO IT
AND THAT MAKES IT UNCOOL.
HOW MUST YOU FEEL WHEN
A SENIOR CITIZEN
CAN DO IT BETTER THAN YOU?
YOU KNOW WHAT I SAY?
YOU GOT TO GET INTO
WEIRDER AND WEIRDER MUSIC,
WEARING WILDER
AND WILDER CLOTHES,
AND DOING STRANGER
AND STRANGER BEHAVIOUR.
EVENTUALLY YOU'LL BE
SO FAR OUT THERE
THAT NO ADULT IN
THEIR RIGHT MIND WILL TRY IT.
BUT DON'T GET YOUR HOPES UP.
ADULTS IN THEIR RIGHT MIND
ARE A MINORITY.
(Grunting)
OW, OW.
IS THAT YOU, UNCLE RED,
OR THE PATH OF THE TORNADO?
HAROLD, YOU MISSED OUT ON
SOME GREAT BARGAINS.
HOW DID YOU GET
ACROSS THE BORDER?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE ALLOWED
$300 WORTH OF STUFF?
WE NEVER GOT TO THE BORDER.
OH, THE LAWN SALES.
MAN!
UNBELIEVABLE.
THAT WOULD EXPLAIN THE WHEEL.
I GOT THREE MORE LIKE IT
FOR 20 BUCKS.
THINK OF THE STUFF
WE CAN MAKE.
COFFEE TABLE, COAT RACK,
LAZY SUSAN, YOU KNOW.
WHERE HAVE YOU SEEN
A LAWN CHAIR FOR FIVE BUCKS.
OH, BOY, THERE YOU GO.
THIS IS JUST ME THINKING.
I'M THINKING THERE.
DID YOU HAPPEN TO PICK UP
A CORDLESS DRILL
FOR JUNIOR SINGLETON?
THINK BACK.
I GOT ONE FOR 10 BUCKS.
LOOK AT THAT.
CORDLESS, VARIABLE SPEED,
REVERSIBLE,
AND NEVER NEEDS CHARGING.
OK, FINE,
BUT I'M KEEPING THIS ONE.
I LOVE THIS.
I'VE BEEN DRILLING.
SANDING AND BORING ALL DAY.
HAROLD, YOU'VE BEEN BORING
ALL YOUR LIFE.
A-HA-HA.
(Imitating John Wayne):
I'VE FIXED 9,000 THINGS
WITH THIS TODAY.
HA HA HA.
I WOULD HAVE FIXED MORE, BUT
I RAN OUT OF SCREWS.
I KNOW WHERE
WE CAN GET 'EM CHEAP.
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT!
DON'T YOU DO THAT!
(Possum
squeal)
IT'S TIME FOR THE MEETING.
I'LL SEE YOU DOWNSTAIRS THEN,
MR. BARGOON.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE,
MR. TOTAL-GOON.
(Laughing)
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE HOME AFTER THE MEETING,
UNLESS I GO BY A YARD SALE
OR A GARAGE SALE...
OR A DUMP.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
(Red): GET OFF THERE, HAROLD.
(Harold): EVERYBODY
TO THEIR SEATS.
HE'LL GET GROUCHY
IF YOU'RE NOT IN YOUR SEATS.
YOU DON'T WANNA SEE THAT.
HIS BEARD ALL FOAMY
AND CRUMBS--
OH, HE'S HERE.
ALL RISE.
WHAT ARE YOU SITTING DOWN?
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN.
ALL THESE YEARS
I'VE BEEN WAITING
TO DRILL HAROLD.