(Chewing)
(Burping)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE MAN
WHO'S MADE POSSUM LODGE
WHAT IT IS TODAY --
BUT, SO FAR,
NO CHARGES HAVE BEEN LAID --
YOUR HOST, MY UNCLE,
RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
REAL EXCITING WEEK
UP AT THE LODGE.
OUR FORMER POSTMASTER,
LUCKY BALDERSON,
HAS TURNED A SET-BACK
INTO A CAREER MOVE.
HE GOT LAID-OFF
DURING THE LATEST CUT-BACKS.
NOT REALLY -- HE WAS
JUST USELESS, HAROLD.
WOULD HAVE BEEN FIRED
DURING THE GOLD RUSH.
I HEARD HE MIGHT OPEN ONE OF
THOSE FAST-FOOD FRANCHISES,
A REAL POPULAR ONE, TOO.
SOMETHING LIKE MOBY DICK'S
DEEP-FRIED WHALE FINGERS.
NO, HE COULDN'T AFFORD THAT.
BUT HE MIGHT GET
A WILLY'S WEANIES.
OR ONE OF THOSE
JOHN DeLOREAN'S RIBS AND RUMPS.
MAYBEVEVEN MEL TILLIS
HOUSE OF B-B-BEEF.
BUT, WHATEVER HE GETS,
I'LL BE DOING ALL THE ADS
FOR HIM.
WOW, CELEBRITY ENDORSEMENTS.
SO, HAVE YOU GOT ANYONE
TO DIRECT YOUR COMMERCIALS YET?
THERE MIGHT BE A SPOT FOR YOU.
MIND YOU, YOU'D PROBABLY END UP
WORKING FOR WEANIES.
(Laughing)
WELL, I KNOW ALL ABOUT THAT.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): THEY SAY THERE'S NOTHING
ON T.V.
RANGER GORD PROVES IT.
MIND YOU, I DON'T CARE.
I'M ON CABLE.
AND WE GOT HAROLD KIND OF...
WELL, BEING HAROLD.
AND HAP SHAUGHNESSY INTRODUCES
A NEW CONCEPT.
WELL, LUCKY
WAS UNABLE TO SECURE
A FAST-FOOD FRANCHISE.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
POSSUM LAKE ISN'T
A BIG ENOUGH AREA
TO SUPPORT
A FAST-FOOD RESTAURANT.
LUCKY AND I ARE GOING TO START
OUR OWN FRANCHISE, CALLED
"I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S NOT CHICKEN."
WHAT KIND OF MEAT IS IT?
NOT CHICKEN.
I DON'T KNOW FOR SURE.
LUCKY'S GETTING THE MEAT --
HE KNOWS A GUY.
WHAT DOES IT TASTE LIKE?
WITH FAST FOOD,
TASTE DOESN'T MATTER.
IT'S MARKETING --
YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE A HOOK.
WE THINK "NOT CHICKEN" IS IT.
WHOA, WHOA, UNCLE RED.
I THINK IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE
THE SPOKESPERSON
BE CAREFUL WHAT YOU SAY.
I'M NOT GOING TO LIE.
I'LL SAY SOMETHING LIKE
"I DON'T CARE WHERE YOU GO
OR WHO YOU KNOW,
"I'LL TELL YOU ONE THING,
THIS IS NOT CHICKEN."
THEN WE HAVE A LITTLE JINGLE.
HOT LICKING,
IT'S NOT CHICKEN
THE PLOT THICKENS
AND THEN A LITTLE ANIMAL
FROM MARS WOULD COME OUT.
HAVE YOU INVESTED
A LOT OF MONEY IN THIS?
I'M NOT STUPID.
ALL I PUT UP WAS MY NAME
AND MY REPUTATION.
(Laughing)
SO THERE'S
NO RISK.
(Laughing)
(Clearing throat)
THAT IS NOT CHICKEN.
(Laughing)
ANOTHER THING WE'RE DOING --
OW.
ANOTHER THING WE'RE DOING
IS SPONSORING A SOCCER TEAM.
THAT'S BILL WITH THE
"I CAN'T BELIEVE" UNIFORM.
WE'LL HAVE MORE OF THAT LATER.
WHEN YOU SPONSOR A TEAM
YOU GET THE COMMUNITY PROFILE.
PEOPLE THINK MORE OF YOU.
IT'S KIND OF SOMETHING TO BE...
PROUD OF.
TODAY I'D LIKE TO
SHOW THE LODGE MEMBERS
THE RIGHT AND THE WRONG WAY
TO PUT OUT A CAMP-FIRE.
WHAT IS THIS -- KINDLING?
YEAH.
NO, NO, NOT YET, NO.
THIS IS MY TELEVISION SET.
I THOUGHT I WOULD DO
A TELEVISION PRESENTATION.
RED, YOU CAN HELP.
WHERE ARE THE REST
OF THE LODGE MEMBERS?
THEY DECIDED TO WATCH IT
ON T.V. AT THE LODGE.
OH, GREAT.
HI, GUYS.
OK, HERE WE GO.
ARE YOU READY, RED?
YEAH, SURE.
OK.
OK, TURN ON THE T.V.
OK, RIGHT HERE.
OK?
YEAH -- I GOT IT ON.
(Making buzzing noise)
HI, EVERYBODY.
THIS IS RANGER GORD.
AND HERE'S MY FRIEND,
MR. BAD CAMPER.
(In deep voice):
I'M MR. BAD CAMPER.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO
PUT OUT A CAMP-FIRE.
(In high voice):
I'M MR. GOOD CAMPER.
I DO KNOW HOW TO PUT OUT
A CAMP-FIRE.
(In normal voice):
MR. GOOD CAMPER KNOWS HOW
TO PUT OUT A CAMP-FIRE --
YOU MUST BE SAD.
(In deep voice): I SURE AM.
(In normal voice): WHY DON'T WE
HELP MR. BAD CAMPER
LEARN TO PUT OUT A CAMP-FIRE?
(In high voice): FIRST,
LET'S SEE THE RED FLAMES.
(In normal voice): OK,
HERE WE GO.
(Mumbling)
(In high voice): FIRST,
AIM THE WATER
AT THE BASE OF THE FLAMES.
HERE WE GO.
(Coughing)
OK, I GUESS THAT'S IT.
(In deep voice): THAT WAS EASY.
NOW I'M MR. GOOD CAMPER.
(In high voice):
HOW ABOUT A HUG?
(In deep voice): OK.
IS THAT IT?
THAT'S IT.
WELL, THAT WAS... INFORMATIVE,
I GUESS YOU'D SAY.
LET'S SEE IF YOU'VE GOT
SOMETHING ELSE ON THERE.
"THE WIDE WORLD OF SPORTS"
WITH THE THRILL OF VICTORY,
AND THE AGONY OF DEFEAT.
OHHH!
OH!
A WORD TO ALL YOU
YOUNG LADIES
WHEN YOU'RE OUT THERE
LOOKING FOR A MATE
FIND YOURSELF
AN UGLY GUY
AND THAT'S THE ONE
YOU SHOULD DATE
'CAUSE UGLY GUYS
ARE NICER
UGLY GUYS ARE SMART
UGLY GUYS
WILL LOVE YOU FAITHFULLY
UGLY GUYS ARE HONEST
UGLY GUYS ARE TRUE
'CAUSE WHEN
YOU GOT A FACE
LIKE THE BACK END
OF A BOVINE
YOU PRETTY WELL
HAVE TO BE
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER"
HAROLD HAS JOINED ME,
UNFORTUNATELY.
WE'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE
YOUR OWN NEON SIGN.
A T OF YOUNG PEOPLE
ARE PUTTING NEON LIGHTS
UNDER THEIR VEHICLES
FOR SOME REASON.
UNCLE RED, THAT'S A STATEMENT.
THE STATEMENT IS
"I HAVE TOO MUCH MONEY
"AND NO IDEA
WHAT TO DO WITH IT."
WE'LL MAKE OUR "I CAN'T
BELIEVE IT'S NOT CHICKEN" SIGN.
GET SOME NORMAL NEON LIGHTS,
THEN BEND THEM INTO
WHATEVER SHAPE YOU WANT.
GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
OH, OK.
WELL, UH... OUR "I CAN'T
BELIEVE IT'S NOT CHICKEN" SIGN
STARTS WITH AN "I".
DONE.
OH, OH, IN FACT,
IT HAS 1, 2, 3, 4 "I's"!
LIKE YOU, HAROLD.
OH, LOOK AT THIS --
YES, EXCELLENT.
IT EVEN HAS
AN EXCLAMATION POINT.
BING!
YOUR TURN.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WE NEED TWO "C's"
ON THAT.
SO, I WOULD SAY WE PUT THAT
INTO THE VICE.
WAIT A SEC, WAIT A SEC,
UNCLE RED.
SAFETY FIRST.
FOR GOSH SAKES, HAROLD.
NO, SAFETY.
OW, OW, OW, OW!
SORRY,
I'M SORRY.
LET'S TRY
IT AGAIN.
THERE.
ALL
RIGHT?
YEAH.
PUT THE TUBE INTO THE VICE.
DON'T TIGHTEN HER UP TOO MUCH.
JUST GET IT A LITTLE SNUG.
SEE WHAT I MEAN?
THAT WAS A LITTLE TOO MUCH.
DON'T EVEN GO WITH
THE VICE ON THAT.
JUST TAKE IT AND BEND IT AROUND
SOME KIND OF A PIPE.
YOU GONNA HELP ME?
NO -- THANK YOU, THOUGH.
ALL RIGHT.
JUST BEND THAT NICE AND
SNUG HER RIGHT UP.
OK --
THAT WAS NOT QUITE PERFECT.
SO, WE'LL ADD SOME HEAT.
HAROLD,
FIND MY PROPANE TORCH, WILL YA?
I WAS SOLDERING THE OTHER DAY.
I PUT IT DOWN SOMEWHERE.
OH.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
RIGHT WHERE I LEFT IT.
WE'LL TAKE A BULB, AND GET
THE THING TO SOFTEN UP...
OH!
HAROLD, HELP ME OUT HERE!
HAROLD.
HAROLD, HAROLD, HAROLD.
IT TURNS OUT THAT GLASS
WASN'T NEARLY AS PLIABLE
AS HAROLD THOUGHT IT WAS.
TO MAKE LETTERS FOR
OUR SIGN WE'LL NEED SOMETHING
THAT'S LONG AND RUBBERY
AND FULL OF GAS.
SHOOTING FISH IN A BARREL,
UNCLE RED.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
SO, I'VE GOT
THE LITTLE BALLOONS
THAT MAGICIANS USE
TO MAKE THOSE LITTLE ANIMALS.
(Blowing air)
ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S GOING TO BE--
THAT WAS
A BALLOON.
STRETCH THAT OUT
A LITTLE BIT.
I'M SORRY, HAROLD.
NOT
A PROBLEM.
NOT REALLY.
HAROLD, WHY DON'T YOU
GIVE THIS A TRY?
GO AHEAD.
YOU YOUNG PEOPLE,
YOU GOT THE...
AND I DON'T WANT IT,
BUT YOU...
OOO, OH, OH.
WELL, SHE'S ALL WET NOW,
SO...
I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
OH, OH.
WOO.
WELL, WITH THE HELP OF
MY PROPANE TANK,
I'VE FILLED THE BALLOONS
AND FINISHED THE FIRST
TWO WORDS OF OUR SIGN.
NOW ALL I GOT TO DO IS
PLUG HER IN AND GIVE HER A TRY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
HAROLD, COME ON IN HERE.
NO, NO, NO.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
NOW I CAN PLUG HER IN
AND GIVE HER A TRY.
OH BOY, BEAUTIFUL.
STAY TUNED
WHILE HAP TRIES TO GUESS
WHAT'S MISSING IN HIS LIFE.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU GUYS
ABOUT LOOKING GOOD.
I'M NOT GONNA GIVE YOU
ANY BEAUTY TIPS OR ANYTHING.
BESIDES,
MOST OF US ARE MARRIED,
AND HOW WE LOOK
COULDN'T MATTER LESS.
(Laughing)
BUT, IT IS IMPORTANT
TO LOOK GOOD TO OTHER WOMEN.
FOR A STARR,
WASHING'S A GOOD IDEA.
YOU DON'T WANNA GO
TOO FAR WITH THAT.
EVERY MAMMAL GIVES OFF
CHEMICALS CALLED PHEROMONES.
APPARENTLY
THEY DRIVE WOMEN CRAZY.
SO YOU DON'T WANT TO
WASH THEM OFF.
BUT, IF, ON THE OTHER HAND,
STRAY DOGS HOWL
WHEN YOU WALK BY,
IT MIGHT BE TIME
TO GET ACQUAINTED
WITH SOME WET SOAP.
YOUR WARDROBE
IS ALSO IMPORTANT.
IF STRANGERS YELL THINGS LIKE,
"HEY, BOZO, JUGGLE THIS!"
CHANCES ARE YOU'RE OVER-DRESSED.
EITHER TONE IT DOWN
OR MOVE TO NEW YORK.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
IS YOUR ATTITUDE.
IF YOU THINK YOU LOOK GOOD,
IT SHOWS.
AND IF IT SHOWS,
YOU PROBABLY MISSED A BUTTON.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause and whistling)
IF IT'S GOOD ENOUGH FOR ME,
IT'S GOOD ENOUGH FOR ANYBODY.
WHY DO WE HAVE TO DO
THE COMMERCIAL OVER AND OVER?
DO YOU THINK SPIELBERG QUITS
STRIVING FOR PERFECTION?
STRIVING FOR PERFECTION
WILL DRIVE YOU NUTS.
LOWERED EXPECTATION
IS THE KEY TO A HAPPY LIFE.
MAYBE NOT PERFECTION,
BUT YOU HAVE TO AT LEAST
PRONOUNCE
WORCESTERSHIRE SAUCE PROPERLY.
WHY DON'T I JUST CALL IT
BROWN STUFF?
IT'S NOT CHICKEN, I KNOW.
BUT WHAT KIND OF MEAT IS IT?
THAT'S OUR SECRET,
OUR PROFIT MARGIN
AND MARKET POSITION.
AND IN A PINCH,
IT'S OUR LEGAL POSITION.
FIRST TIME I EVER SEEN
A DRUMSTICK WITH TWO ELBOWS.
HAROLD, PEOPLE ONLY CARE
ABOUT PRICE.
LOOK AT THIS COMBO MEAL.
LARGE POTATO TOTS,
SIDE SALAD, HOT LARDY BUN,
BIG SHAKEY, AND 7 PIECES
OF NOT-CHICKEN FOR 89 CENTS.
WOW.
IT'S A DOLLAR EXTRA IF
YOU DON'T WANT THE NOT-CHICKEN.
YEAH, BUT IT'S WORTH IT.
OH, YEAH.
(Applause)
WE'RE WITH HAP SHAUGHNESSY
TO PLAY
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
WHAT ARE WE PLAYING FOR?
THE GRAND PRIZE IS
A MISMATCHED SET OF ASHTRAYS
FROM THE POSSUM LAKE HOTEL
AND MORTUARY.
ALREADY GOT A SET.
HAROLD, GIVE HIM THE WORD.
SHOW THE FOLKS AT HOME.
NOW, RED, YOU READY?
YOU GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET ME TO SAY THAT WORD.
GO WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
UH... QUEEN ELIZABETH
AND I ARE...
OPPOSITES.
NO --
BUT OUR RELATIONSHIP IS...
OH, IMAGINARY.
SHE CALLS ME FOR ADVICE
BECAUSE WE'RE...
DELUDED... HALLUCINATIONS...
DREAMING.
I- I- I DATED ALL THREE GIRLS
ON THE HIT SERIES CALLED...
"HAMMY HAMSTER"?
"THE SMURFS"
I DON'T KNOW.
OK, OK, OK.
ROBERT REDFORD AND I
ARE BEST...
KEPT APART.
FINE, FINE, FINE, RED.
I AM ONE OF YOUR CLOSEST...
OH, LIAR.
YOUR CLOSEST...
UH... LIAR?
LIAR?
WHAT KIND OF A PERSON
WOULD CALL ME A LIAR?
HAP, I'M SORRY, BUT
ALL YOUR FRIENDS DO.
YOU KNOW, IN A FRIENDLY WAY.
(Bell ringing)
THAT WAS IT?!
(Laughing)
THAT WAS GREAT.
YOU'RE GOOD AT THIS.
HEY, HANDYMEN,
NOTHING TAKES THE PIZZAZZ
OUT OF A PROJECT FASTER
THAN HAVING TO CLEAN UP
THE EXTENSION CORD
WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
HERE'S A TIP FOR YOU.
LET THE TOOL DO THE WORK.
(Motor starting)
THE ADS FOR OUR RESTAURANT
HAVE STARTED
AND, BOY,
ARE WE GETTING A RESPONSE.
IT'S OK, HAROLD, I'M ALONE.
THOSE ADS ARE THE WORST THING
I'VE EVER SEEN ON TELEVISION.
YOU SHOULD WATCH
SOME OF THE STUFF
ON THE WOMEN'S NETWORK.
(Applause)
HEY, HAROLD, THE ADS WORK.
THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
I HAVE MY INTEGRITY
AS A POWERFUL NEW ARTIST
IN THIS WONDERFUL MEDIUM.
WE'RE DOING A LOT OF BUSINESS
AND IT'S BECAUSE OF THOSE ADS.
REALLY?
EXCELLENT, COOL.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
LUCKY'S THINKING ABOUT
OPENING ANOTHER BRANCH,
BUT HE MAY NOT BE ABLE TO GET
ENOUGH NOT-CHICKEN,
SO WE MAY START SERVING
NOT-BEEF AND NOT-SALAD.
WHEN I WAS SHOOTING THESE ADS,
I LOOKED AT
THE DAILIES, THE RUSHES,
AND I THOUGHT
"HEY, HAROLD, HEY, MAYBE
YOU HAVE MANAGED TO CAPTURE
"THE ESSENCE, THE MAGIC."
THE CAMERA ANGLES
AND LIGHTING.
I THINK IT'S MORE
THE CONCEPT OF A COMPLETE LUNCH
FOR 29 CENTS.
WHATEVER -- I DON'T CARE.
AS LONG AS I HAVE A SUCCESSFUL
AD CAMPAIGN ON MY DEMO REEL,
CAN A FEATURE FILM
BE FAR BEHIND?
"NOT-CHICKEN, THE MOVIE."
NOT-CHICKEN?
OR NOT-BEEF.
NOT LIKELY.
MEANWHILE BACK AT THE...
THANK YOU, BILL.
MEANWHILE BACK AT
THE SOCCER PITCH,
UH, BILL'S PRACTISING HERE.
WE NEVER PLAYED SOCCER
WHEN WE WERE KIDS.
OF COURSE, WE NEVER DID--
SOMETIMES THAT'S OBVIOUS.
SHOULD HAVE NOTICED
THE VAN, BILL.
DIDN'T REALIZE THAT
IT'S NOT ALL SPONGY.
WHEREAS, WITH BILL,
JUST THE OPPOSITE IS TRUE.
ALTHOUGH I NEVER PLAYED SOCCER,
IT'S NOT A BAD THING FOR KIDS.
YOU DON'T NEED A LOT OF MONEY
TO GET INVOLVED.
YOU JUST NEED A BALL A SHIRT,
A PAIR OF SHORTS
IN SOME AREAS.
AND YOU DON'T NEED
A LOT OF...
YOU DON'T NEED
A LOT OF ATHLETIC ABILITY.
YOU DO NEED SOME
ATHLETIC ABILITY.
BUT THE IDEA IS
YOU GET THE RUNNING,
AND YOU GET THE KICKING.
YOU DON'T ALWAYS
GET THE KICKING.
LOOK AT THAT.
THERE'S A GOAL.
AND THAT JUST WITH
A FEW MINUTES PRACTISE.
MIND YOU, HE DID MOVE IN
A LITTLE CLOSER.
I'M GONNA BE STANDING IN GOAL.
HE'LL TRY AND
SCORE AGAINST A REAL GOALIE.
THE FANCY FOOTWORK IS --
YOU CAN GET TOO FANCY THOUGH.
ANYWAY, UH, BILL IS PROBABLY --
IF BILL CAN DO IT...
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING.
CAN BILL DO IT,
THAT'S THE QUESTION.
OH BOY.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
OK, MAYBE I'LL TAKE A TRY
AND GET BILL IN GOAL.
THERE'S NOT THAT MUCH TO IT.
IT'S A BIG...
IT'S A BIG NET TO COVER.
OH BOY.
HE BLOCKED.
NICE SAVE!
EXCELLENT.
HE'S GONNA KICK ONE
WAY DOWN THE FIELD.
BUT, HE'S THE ONLY ONE
ON THE TEAM,
SO, HE'S GOT TO GO
CATCH HIS OWN PASS.
USED TO HAPPEN IN HIGH SCHOOL.
IN EVERY SOCCER GAME
YOU HAVE TO HAVE A...
TIME OUT.
RIGHT, BILL?
OH BOY.
STAY TUNED
WHILE DOUGIE FIGURES OUT
WHAT TO BUY HIS MOTHER.
WELL, SO MUCH FOR
THE NOT-CHICKEN RESTAURANT.
OUR MISTAKE WAS RUNNING
THIS CONTEST
AS A PROMOTIONAL THING.
IF YOU CAN GUESS
WHAT YOU'RE EATING, IT'S FREE.
A VISITING ZOOLOGIST DID,
AND THE HEALTH INSPECTOR
SHUT US DOWN.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THIS?
"DEAR MR. SPIELBERG,
I'M THE DIRECTOR THAT STARTED
"THAT 'NOT-CHICKEN' PHENOMENON,
AND I WOULD APPRECIATE
"A SEVEN-PICTURE DEAL
AT YOUR EARLIEST CONVENIENCE."
THE NOT-CHICKEN BUSINESS
IS NOW THE NOT-OPEN BUSINESS.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO NOW?
IN THE RESTAURANT BUSINESS,
LOCATION IS EVERYTHING.
SO WE'RE GOING TO MAKE
A FLOATING RESTAURANT.
WE CAN GO ANYWHERE,
SUBJECT TO TIDE AND CURRENT.
WE'LL CALL IT "I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S NOT FISH".
THE COPS WILL NEVER
MAKE THE CONNECTION.
CAN YOU EXPLAIN HOW THIS
IS GOING TO BE DIFFERENT
FROM YOUR EARLIER VENTURES?
WE GOT PRIZES: POWER RANGERS,
WRESTLING ACTION FIGURES.
WE'VE GOT POGS OF THE SMURFS.
POGS, YOU GOT POGS?!
THEY'RE FREE WITH
THE NOT-SHRIMP MELT.
OH, I'M ALLERGIC TO SEAFOOD.
NOT THIS SEAFOOD.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW.
THIS WEEK WE HAVE MY UNCLE RED,
AND MR. DOUGIE FRANKLIN!
(Cheering and applause)
THIS IS HOW THE LETTER GOES.
THE LETTER GOES AS FOLLOWS.
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"THIS YEAR I WANT TO MAKE
MY MOTHER'S BRTHDAY SPECIAL.
"I'M HOPING TO BE OUT OF PRISON
BY THEN..."
(Laughing)
"... ONE WAY OR ANOTHER."
"DO YOU HAVE ANY SUGGESTIONS?
"I MEAN FOR A BIRTHDAY GIFT,
"NOT HOW TO BUST OUT OF
THIS JOINT."
SIGNED "SID IN CELL 'C'
BY THE SEASHORE."
WELL, SID, I THINK YOU SHOULD
STAY IN THE SLAMMER
A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
YOU MIGHT WANNA
GO INTO OVERTIME,
'CAUSE IT SOUNDS LIKE THE REHAB
HAS NOT QUITE KICKED IN AS YET.
NOW RED, I THINK THERE'S
A VERY SPECIAL BOND
THAT EXISTS BETWEEN
A MAN AND HIS MOM
THAT TRANSCENDS
ALL RATIONAL THOUGHT,
PARTICULARLY IF HE'S
HER FAVOURITE SON.
OF COURSE, MY BROTHER BEN
WOULD KNOW MORE ABOUT THAT.
THEN AGAIN,
YOU KNOW, HE KNOWS EVERYTHING.
HE'S THE APPLE OF MOM'S EYE.
BUT TO ME, HE'S JUST PLAIN
ROTTEN TO THE CORE.
THIS FELLOW'S
LOOKING FOR GIFT IDEAS.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL... THAT'S
A TOUGH ONE, HAROLD.
I KNOW WHAT MOMS DON'T LIKE.
A SET OF RACING TIRES.
BOY,
THAT SURE WAS A WASTE
OF TWO GRAND.
AND A HELL OF A LOT OF
WRAPPING PAPER, AS WELL.
WOMEN, GO FIGURE.
THEY ARE SO UNPREDICTABLE.
MY MOM, ON HER BIRTHDAY,
I TAKE HER OUT FOR DINNER,
BUY HER FLOWERS.
I GET HER THAT ALL THE TIME.
I THINK YOUR MOTHER
WOULD PREFER IT
IF YOU WERE IN PRISON,
LIKE THIS FELLA.
(Applause)
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE OUT IN A RESTAURANT
ON A RAFT IN THE LAKE.
WHAT IS THE LAST THING
YOU'D EXPECT,
HAROLD?
A CUSTOMER.
(Laughing)
A FIRE --
WHOLE THING WENT UP IN FLAMES.
I SAID "DON'T RUN THAT
OUTBOARD MOTOR ON PROPANE."
OR WAS IT A GREASE FIRE?
NO, NEITHER ONE.
THAT NOT-FISH STUFF KIND OF
SPONTANEOUSLY COMBUSTED.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BURN
TO THE WATER-LINE,
BUT THE MORE SHE BURNED,
THE HIGHER SHE FLOATED.
WE LOST THE WHOLE UNIT.
AT LEAST YOU CAME OUT
WITHOUT A LOSS OF LIFE.
THAT'S A PLEASANT SURPRISE.
(Squealing)
MEETING TIME.
GO AHEAD,
HAROLD.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I'VE LOST MY APPETITE
FOR FAST FOOD,
OR FAST ANYTHING,
SO THAT SHOULD BE GOOD NEWS.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF HAROLD, MYSELF,
AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and whistling)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): ALL RISE.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Harold): THE FIRE DEPARTMENT
WON'T COME FOR
HEART ATTACKS ANY MORE.
SO IF YOU HAVE A HEART ATTACK,
SET YOURSELF ON FIRE.