WHEN I WAS GROWING UP WE
WERE TAUGHT TO WORK HARD
AND GO, GO, GO.
I DIDN'T TAKE IT TOO
SERIOUSLY BUT A LOT
OF THEM DID.
SO NOW WE'RE STUCK
WITH A GENERATION OF
PEOPLE WHO WORK HARD.
UNFORTUNATELY A LOT OF THEM,
ESPECIALLY THE MEN,
AREN'T PUTTING A LOT OF
THOUGHT INTO WHAT THEY'RE
WORKING HARD AT.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE
SO MANY STOCKBROKERS.
MOST MEN WOULD RATHER
START DRIVING THAN
LOOK AT A MAP.
FORGET THE BLUEPRINTS
AND LET'S BUILD.
GO, GO, GO.
NOT WHERE,
WHERE, WHERE.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT MAKES
US WHAT WE ARE.
[quirky upbeat music]
ON TODAY'S SHOW, I'M
GOING TO TURN A CAR
INTO A PORTABLE
DRIVE-IN MOVIE,
DALTON HUMPHREY IS
GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO ADD VALUE TO
A PRECIOUS HEIRLOOM,
BILL IS CALLED
OUT AT THE PLATE,
AND HAROLD FINDS
OUT WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU TURN YOUR
BACK ON A RELATIVE.
AND NOW HERE'S A
MAN WHO'S ALL BARK,
EVEN THOUGH HE'S
OUT OF HIS TREE,
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN.
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AND PLEASE WELCOME
THE GUY WE REFER TO AS
FREE TO GOOD HOME,
MY NEPHEW, HAROLD.
SCARY STUFF.
A BIT OF EXCITEMENT
THIS WEEK AT THE LODGE.
BUSTER HADFIELD AND
HIS WIFE JUST GOT BACK
FROM A TRIP WHERE THEY
DROVE ALL OVER THE COUNTRY.
WOW, REALLY?
I JUST THOUGHT THEY
WERE GOING TO GO VISIT
THEIR RELATIVES
LIKE A COUPLE HUNDRED
MILES FROM HERE IN
PORT ASBESTOS.
YEAH, WELL, THAT
WAS THE PLAN,
BUT BUSTER HATES TO
PULL OVER AND ASK
FOR DIRECTIONS
WHEN HE GETS LOST.
SO HE DROVE ALL OVER
THE CONTINENT INSTEAD?
WELL, I DON'T
BLAME HIM, HAROLD.
IT'S EMBARRASSING,
YOU KNOW, TO LOOK LIKE
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
YOU DON'T WANT
PEOPLE THINKING
YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
ESPECIALLY WHEN
THEY'RE RIGHT.
WELL, THE GOOD THING
WAS HE COULD DRIVE
PRETTY MUCH NONSTOP,
BECAUSE WITH HIS
WIFE YELLING AT
HIM LIKE THAT,
HE DIDN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT FALLING ASLEEP
AT THE WHEEL.
OH, HIS POOR WIFE.
THAT MAKES FOR A LONG
TIME WHEN YOU'RE SITTING
BESIDE SOMEBODY GOING,
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING,
WITHOUT ANY PROOF.
YEAH, IT'S LIKE HAVING
YOU AS A PRODUCER/
DIRECTOR.
SO THE ONE TIME THEY
PULLED OVER FOR GAS,
SHE WENT IN,
BOUGHT A CAMERA SO
SHE COULD TAKE PICTURES
THAT THEY COULD USE
AT THE DIVORCE TRIAL.
BUT BY THE TIME
THEY GOT HOME,
OF COURSE,
ALL WAS FORGIVEN.
NOW THEY'VE INVITED
A WHOLE BUNCH OF US
TO COME OVER
TO THEIR PLACE TO
SEE THEIR PICTURES.
OH... WELL, OKAY.
I GOT SO MUCH TO
DO I CAN'T GO.
YOU KNOW, I GOT TO
CLEAN MY GLASSES,
FLOSS MY TEETH,
YOU KNOW.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT,
BECAUSE IF YOU'RE
NOT GOING,
I'LL BE ABLE
TO GO.
OH, OKAY.
MAKE SURE YOU GET
DIRECTIONS BEFORE
YOU LEAVE.
IT WOULD BE
REALLY HARD TO DO
THE SHOW FROM MEXICO.
YOU'RE WATCHING
THE RED GREEN SHOW.
ONE MAN'S JUNK IS
ANOTHER MAN'S TREASURE.
WELL, IF YOU'RE ASKED
ON A PICNIC AND YOU
CAN'T REFUSE
BE EXTRA CAREFUL IN
THE SANDWICH YOU CHOOSE
HAM IS OKAY UNLESS
IT'S GREEN AND WET
EGG IS DICEY AND
SARDINE IS A THREAT
IF YOU'RE IN DOUBT,
DON'T TAKE A CHANCE
ONLY EAT THE FOOD THAT'S
COVERED WITH THE ANTS
IF THERE AREN'T ANY ON IT
THAT'S AN IMPORTANT CLUE
BECAUSE IF THE
BUGS WON'T EAT IT
THEN NEITHER
SHOULD YOU
TODAY ON MEET YOUR
MEMBER WE'RE TALKING
TO WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
WHO IS C.E.O.,
C.O.O. AND C3-PO
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING
SERVICES.
WINSTON, MAYBE YOU
COULD TELL OUR
VIEWERS
HOW YOU GOT TO
WHERE YOU ARE,
WHEREVER THAT MIGHT BE.
WELL, YEAH,
THANKS, RED.
I'M FROM ABOUT 70 MILES
FROM HERE, A SMALL
LITTLE VILLAGE.
DIDN'T HAVE A NAME, EH,
COULDN'T AFFORD ONE.
I GUESS YOUR DAD
WAS IN THE SEWAGE
BUSINESS BEFORE YOU.
NO, NO, NO.
DAD WAS IN THE RAILROAD
THERE FOR MOST OF
HIS LIFE, EH?
YOU KNOW, HE SPENT 30
YEARS AS A COAL MAN.
OH, YEAH.
AND THEN HE -- I DON'T
KNOW WHAT HAPPENED,
THREE OR FOUR YEARS LATER
THEY WENT TO DIESEL
ELECTRIC, EH,
AND SO HE'D JUST GO
IN TO WORK AND FALL
ASLEEP IN THE BOXCAR.
THAT WOULD BE A
FASCINATING JOB,
I WOULD THINK.
AND THEN AFTER 30 YEARS
THE RAILROAD FIRED HIM, EH,
JUST LIKE THAT,
LIKE HE WAS NOTHING.
I GUESS IT WOULD
BE HARD FOR HIM
TO FIND ANOTHER JOB
THAT HE WAS
KIND OF SUITED FOR.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT, EH?
AND EVEN AFTER
THE $500,000 WRONGFUL
DISMISSAL SETTLEMENT, EH?
HE WAS BITTER.
YEAH, I'LL NEVER
FORGET THAT VERY DAY,
HE COME HOME AND HE
SAID, WINSTON,
THREE THINGS:
NUMBER ONE, START
YOUR OWN BUSINESS;
NUMBER TWO, BE
YOUR OWN BOSS;
NUMBER THREE, GET OFF
THE COUCH I GOT TO
TAKE A NAP.
WELL, WINSTON,
I'LL TELL YOU,
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE DONE
WELL FOR YOURSELF.
I MEAN, AROUND HERE YOUR
NAME IS SYNONYMOUS
WITH SEWAGE.
I TELL YOU, YOU
HAVE NEVER EXPERIENCED
FULL BLOWN
TERMINAL BOREDOM
UNTIL YOU SIT THROUGH
THOSE HOLIDAY PICTURES
TAKEN BY BUSTER HADFIELD,
OR, AS WE CALL HIM,
THE ACCIDENTAL TOURIST.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU,
EVEN IF YOU GOT
GREAT PICTURES
LIKE MY SLIDES,
YOU STILL CAN'T GET
PEOPLE TO COME OVER TO
YOUR HOUSE AND LOOK AT THEM.
SO THAT'S WHY THIS
WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I THOUGHT I WOULD SHOW YOU
HOW TO MAKE A PORTABLE
PROJECTION SYSTEM.
AND I'M NOT JUST
TALKING A BOUT A
SLIDE PROJECTOR ON WHEELS,
I'M TALKING ABOUT THIS.
[groaning and grunting]
[crash!]
YOUR VERY OWN DRIVE-AWAY
DRIVE-IN THEATER,
BECAUSE DRIVE-INS ARE FUN,
AND THEY'RE ROMANTIC,
ESPECIALLY THE BACKSEAT.
NOW, YOUR GUESTS ARE
GOING TO SIT IN HERE,
JUST LIKE THEY DO
AT A DRIVE-IN.
BUT WITH OUR UNIT THE
SCREEN IS MUCH MORE
INTERACTIVE,
BECAUSE WHAT WE'RE GOING
TO DO IS JUST POP THE
HOOD UP LIKE THIS,
WE'LL MOUNT A SCREEN
ON THE INSIDE
AND THE SCREEN IS
RIGHT THERE IN
THEIR FACE.
OH. ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, WELL, THIS HOOD
OPENS THE WRONG WAY.
NICE WORK, HAROLD.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
I'LL JUST TAKE HER OFF
AND WE'LL MOUNT
HER PROPERLY.
NOW, WHEN YOU REMOUNT THAT,
YOU COULD WELD ON
THE OLD HINGES
OR YOU COULD BOLT
ON NEW HINGES
OR YOU COULD USE
WHAT I USE,
THE HANDYMAN SECRET
WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
NOW IT OPENS
THE RIGHT WAY.
THANK YOU JUST
THE SAME, HAROLD.
AND WE'LL PROP
THAT UP IN THERE.
AND NOW WHAT WE NEED
IS SOMETHING TO USE
AS A SCREEN.
I'M THINKING SOMETHING
CLEAN AND WHITE,
MAYBE ONE OF THE
LODGE SHEETS.
SOMETHING A LITTLE
CLEANER AND WHITER
THAN THAT.
I GOT AN IDEA.
DOOR OFF A FRIDGE.
USE THAT SIDE THERE.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO TAKE
THE DOOR OFF A FRIDGE
BEFORE YOU THROW
IT OUT ANYWAY,
AND WE'LL HAVE
TO THROW THAT ONE
OUT NOW FOR SURE.
OKAY, SO WE GOT OUR SCREEN
MOUNTED INSIDE THE
HOOD THERE,
AND I'VE RUN THE POWER
SUPPLY BACK FROM THE BATTERY
COURTESY OF A COUPLE
OF SETS OF JUMPER CABLES,
USE AS MANY AS YOU LIKE.
AND THEY'RE GOING TO
POWER THE SLIDE
PROJECTOR HERE
WHICH I'M GOING TO THROW
IN UP ON TO THE BACK
SHELF OF THE CAR,
WHICH IS NOT REALLY
GOOD FOR ANYTHING ANYHOW.
HOOK THOSE UP.
THERE WE GO.
NOW TO POWER THE
WHOLE UNIT UP,
ALL'S WE HAVE TO DO
IS START THE CAR.
OH BOY, THAT'S
BRIGHT, ISN'T IT?
WOW.
BUT WE'VE LEFT OUT
THE ONE THING
THAT TEENAGERS ENJOY
DOING MOST AT A DRIVE-IN...
EATING POPCORN.
SO ALL'S WE GOT TO
DO IS TAKE THE LID OFF
OUR JAR OF POPCORN HERE
AND TURN HER UPSIDE DOWN
OVER THAT HOLE
THAT'S MAKING ALL THE
NOISE IN THE EXHAUST
MANIFOLD.
THERE WE GO.
NOW THE HEAT OF THE
ENGINE WILL POP
THE POPCORN.
[corn popping]
THERE WE GO.
AND SHE COMES
OUT BACK HERE.
OF COURSE WHAT
YOU WANT TO DO
IS TO ATTACH A PIECE
OF FLEXIBLE PIPING
SO YOU CAN CHANNEL
THAT POPCORN
UP INTO SOME KIND OF
A CONTAINER LIKE THAT.
AND YOU CAN
HAVE YOUR VARIOUS
OTHER TREATS IN HERE,
YOUR CHOCOLATE BARS, YOUR
DRINKS, YOUR WHAT HAVE YOU.
AND THERE YOU HAVE YOUR
VERY OWN PORTABLE
DRIVE-IN THEATRE
WITH ALL
THE ACCOUTREMENTS.
SO REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
LET'S GET BACK
TO OUR SLIDE SHOW.
OH BOY, OH BOY, YOU'RE
GOING TO LOVE THIS.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, IT'S A LITTLE
OUT OF FOCUS, I KNOW,
BUT SEE THAT GUY THERE,
I FORGET HIS NAME,
HE WAS FUNNY.
OH YEAH, THIS IS A
PICTURE OF HIS WIFE.
OH NO, THAT'S THE ROCKIES.
Red Green:
STAY TUNED.
HAROLD IS GOING TO CALL
FOR MY HIGH INSIDE HEAT
AND I'M GOING TO
TALK TO YOU TEENAGERS
ABOUT THOSE DARN
BICYCLES OF YOURS.
I SEE A LOT OF
YOU TEENAGERS ARE
RIDING BICYCLES OUT THERE.
AND I KNOW THAT'S GOOD
FOR THE ENVIRONMENT
AND EVERYTHING
BUT WHAT A PAIN.
YOU RIDE IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE LANE
AND YOU COME AROUND
CORNERS JUST LIKE YOU
WERE A VEHICLE OR SOMETHING.
AND YOU'RE PRACTICALLY
INVISIBLE, YOU KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU WEIGH,
60 POUNDS?
AND YOU WEAR ONE OF
THEM SPANDEX SUITS
WRAPS YOUR BODY SO TIGHT
YOU LOOK LIKE A ROLL BAR.
YOU'RE RISKING YOUR
LIVES OUT THERE,
BECAUSE IF WE GET INTO
A MISUNDERSTANDING AS TO
WHO HAS THE RIGHT OF WAY,
I'M IN THE VAN,
YOU'RE IN A HELMET,
YOU LOSE!
NOW, I DON'T WANT
TO MAKE JUDGMENTS
ABOUT HOW YOU
TEENAGERS WANT
TO KILL YOURSELVES,
BUT I WOULD SUGGEST
THAT YOU EITHER GROW
UP AND GET A CAR
OR RIDE ON THE SIDEWALK.
BUT NOT MY SIDEWALK,
THAT'S WHERE I
PARK THE VAN.
WELL, YOU SHOULD HAVE
SEEN BUSTER HADFIELD'S
PICTURES FROM HIS TRIP.
UNBELIEVABLE.
ALL TAKEN FROM
INSIDE THE CAR.
MOSTLY SHOTS OF THE
REARVIEW MIRROR,
EXCEPT FOR THE
CALIFORNIA ONES,
THEY WERE ALL
SUN VISOR SHOTS.
WELL, MAYBE THE CAMERA WAS
TOO COMPLICATED FOR HIM.
OH, YOU GOT THAT
RIGHT, HAROLD.
HE HAD 60 PICTURES
OF THE INSIDE OF
THE LENS CAP,
ALL OF THEM
OUT OF FOCUS.
AND THE REST OF THE
PICTURES WERE EITHER
OVEREXPOSED,
UNDEREXPOSED OR BORING.
I'LL TELL YOU, IF IT
WASN'T FOR THE PIMENTO
AND ONION CHEESE DIP,
NONE OF US WOULD
HAVE STAYED.
WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD,
YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE PICTURES
ARE EXPENSIVE.
I REMEMBER I PAID $12
FOR MY SCHOOL PORTRAIT.
WHEN I GOT IT BACK,
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN IT,
I LOOKED LIKE A GEEK.
[laughter]
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
NO, SERIOUSLY.
MUST HAVE GOT
MY BAD SIDE.
YEAH, YOUR FRONT.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU,
BUSTER HAS REALLY
LOST HIS MIND.
GET THIS,
HE SAYS HE CAN GET
ALL THE MONEY BACK
THAT HE SPENT
ON THE PICTURES
BY TAKING SILVER
OUT OF THE NEGATIVES.
SILVER, HAROLD, LIKE
THERE'S SILVER IN
FILM NEGATIVES.
WELL, THERE IS.
WELL, IN OLD FILM ANYWAY.
YEAH, I MEAN IT'S THE
SILVER THAT ACTUALLY
FORMS THE PICTURE.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, HAROLD?
WELL, IN PHOTOGRAPHIC
FILM, UNTIL RECENTLY,
THEY USE LIKE FORMS
OF SILVER TO TAKE
THE PICTURE.
IT'S CALLED
SILVER HALIDE.
OH, WELL, OH SILVER
HALIDE, YEAH.
NO, NO, HE SAID SILVER.
THAT'S ALL I'M QUESTIONING,
YOU KNOW, THE SILVER.
YEAH. RIGHT.
SO, YEAH, OKAY,
ALL RIGHT.
BUT HE SAYS HE CAN
GET THE SILVER OUT
OF THE SILVER HALIDE.
LIKE GOOD LUCK,
BUSTER.
WELL, HE CAN IF HE
USES THE RIGHT EMULSION.
WELL, YEAH.
NO, I DON'T THINK
HE'S GOT THE -- SEE,
WELL, OKAY.
WHERE DID YOU GET
TO BE SUCH A GENIUS?
WELL, I'M NOT.
WELL, YOU'RE
SMARTER THAN I AM.
OH, YEAH, OKAY, YOU KNOW,
I'M A GENIUS TO YOU.
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE
FOR ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES
WHERE OUR MOTTO IS:
WASTE NOT, PUMP NOT,
1-800-555-SUCK.
Red Green: WE'RE OUT HERE
BY THE MAIN HIGHWAY
AT HUMPHREY'S
EVERYTHING STORE
WITH THE MAN WHO
KNOWS THE VALUE
OF EVERYTHING,
DALTON HUMPHRIES.
HELLO, DALTON.
HOW YOU DOING?
YEAH, RED, I'M JUST
HAVING A CHUCKLE AT
SOMEBODY ELSE'S EXPENSE.
OH, YEAH, WITH THAT
SILVER CUP THERE, EH?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
THIS ISN'T SILVER,
NO, NO.
THIS POLISHED ALUMINUM.
IT DOESN'T -- IT
DOESN'T HAVE THE
WEIGHT OF SILVER.
SO THAT'S PRETTY
MUCH WORTHLESS
I GUESS.
WELL, TO YOU
MAYBE, BUT, LOOK,
I'M GOING TO GIVE IT
SOME CHARACTER HERE.
THERE, THAT'S BETTER.
I WILL JUST ENGRAVE
"BABY" ON IT OR
SOMETHING
AND MAYBE
THE DATE 1802
AND I'LL SELL IT
FOR 400 BUCKS TO
SOME SUCKER.
THAT'S VERY
COMMENDABLE.
DALTON, DID YOU KNOW
WE GOT A PROJECT GOING
WHERE WE'RE TAKING
SILVER OUT OF FILM
NEGATIVES?
OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW THERE'S A BETTER
WAY TO DO IT THAN THAT.
I SHOULDN'T BE
TELLING TRADE
SECRETS HERE,
BUT TAKE A LOOK AT
THIS PLATE HERE.
YEAH.
YOU SEE RIGHT AROUND
THE EDGE THERE
THERE'S A LITTLE BEADING
OF SILVER SOMEONE'S
PAINTED ON THERE?
YEAH.
UH-HUH.
YEAH, WELL,
THAT'S SILVER.
THAT'S REAL SILVER.
ISN'T THAT SOMETHING?
OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW I GOT 400
OF THE THESE PLATES.
I GOT THEM WHEN THE
HOTEL WENT OUT
OF BUSINESS
OR MAYBE IT WAS AN
ASYLUM OR SOMETHING.
ANYWAY, I'M GOING
TO SIT DOWN WITH
A PUTTY KNIFE
FOR TWO OR
THREE WEEKS.
YEAH.
CHISEL ALL THAT
SILVER OFF THE EDGE.
AND WHEN I'M FINISHED,
I'M GOING TO HAVE
A WHOLE BAG FULL
OF SILVER,
A WHOLE BAG FULL,
A WHOLE BAG.
YOU KNOW WHAT I
NOTICED, UNCLE RED,
WHEN GUYS TAKE
THEIR DATES OUT,
YOU KNOW, TO PLAYS
AND RESTAURANTS AND
MOVIES AND STUFF,
BUT AFTER THEY GET
MARRIED, THEY HARDLY
EVER GO OUT ANY MORE.
WELL, NO, THAT'S
ONE OF THE MAIN REASONS
FOR GETTING MARRIED.
WELL, IF I GET MARRIED,
I'M GOING TO TAKE MY
WIFE OUT ON DATES
ALL THE TIME
JUST TO SHOW HER
THAT I LOVE HER.
I THINK IT WILL LOOK
MORE LIKE GRATITUDE
THAN LOVE, HAROLD.
JUST BECAUSE A
COUPLE DON'T GO
OUT TOGETHER ANYMORE
DOESN'T MEAN THEY
DON'T LOVE EACH OTHER,
THEY JUST GET
BUSY, THAT'S ALL.
BUSY?
WHAT CAN BE MORE
IMPORTANT THAN SPENDING
TIME WITH YOUR SWEETHEART?
WELL, THE PRIORITIES
OF DAILY LIVING,
HAROLD.
BILLS TO PAY, MAYBE
OVERTIME AT THE OFFICE,
WORK AROUND THE HOUSE,
PERHAPS A SPORTING
EVENT ON TELEVISION,
THAT KIND OF THING.
I JUST HAPPEN
TO THINK THAT
MARRIED SPOUSES
TAKE EACH OTHER
FOR GRANTED.
WELL, HAROLD, YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU SPEND A LOT OF
TIME WITH SOMEBODY,
IT DOESN'T NECESSARILY
MAKE YOU EAGER TO SPEND
MORE TIME WITH THEM.
YOU AND I
HAVE PROVEN THAT.
THAT'S DIFFERENT.
WE'RE LIKE, YOU
KNOW, GUYS,
WHEREAS A GUY AND
A GIRL ARE LIKE,
YOU KNOW.
WELL, THERE'S
SOMETHING ELSE YOU
SHOULD KNOW, HAROLD.
AFTER YOU
GET MARRIED, 99
PERCENT OF THE TIME
SLEEPING TOGETHER
MEANS SLEEPING
TOGETHER.
NO WAY.
I'LL NEVER
BE THAT TIRED!
WELL, MAYBE NOT,
BUT EVERY GIRL WITHIN
100 MILES OF YOU
WILL BE THAT
TIRED, BELIEVE ME.
NO PROBLEM,
I'LL MOVE.
Red Green:
WELL, HAROLD AND I HAD A
BIG DAY OF RELAXING PLANNED
BUT BILL HAD ASKED US
TO COME OUT AND TAKE PART
IN AMERICA'S
FAVOURITE PAST-TIME,
WHICH I WAS DISAPPOINTED
TO SEE WAS BASEBALL.
SO ANYWAY, HE HAD
ALL THE GEAR THERE
AND HE WANTED
ME TO GO OUT AND
PITCH THE BALL.
WHY HE HANDED ME
A BATTING HELMET I
COULDN'T UNDERSTAND,
BUT WITH BILL,
YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE ALWAYS
BETTER TO HAVE SOME
PROTECTIVE GEAR ON.
SO HAROLD'S GOING
TO BE THE CATCHER
I GUESS
AND BILL
IS HELPING HIM.
THIS IS HELPING
I SUPPOSE.
OH MY GOSH.
IT COULD BE A
WHILE I SUPPOSE.
ALL RIGHT, HE GOT THE
ONE LEG GOING ON,
NOW THEY GOT THE OTHER--
THE CATCHER HAS
TO HAVE THE PADDING
ON AND EVERYTHING.
BUT I THINK MAYBE
HAROLD MIGHT BE
BETTER ON HIS OWN.
OF COURSE, I'VE
ALWAYS SAID THAT.
YOU GUYS GOING
TO BE LONG?
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY
A LOT OF PEOPLE COME
OUT TO SEE THESE GAMES.
OH, THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
OH!
HOW CAN YOU HAVE
STRIKE ONE ON YOU
AND THE BALL HASN'T
EVEN BEEN THROWN YET?
YEAH, HE'S FINE
BILL, YEAH.
HAROLD?
NO, HAROLD.
OVER HERE.
HERE BOY.
THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT, FINALLY.
DON'T KNOW WHETHER TO GIVE
HIM MY KNUCKLER
OR MY SLIDING,
SINKING FAST BALL.
WHAT?
TIME OUT.
WHAT'S HIS PROBLEM NOW?
HE DOESN'T LIKE THE BAT.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
ALL RIGHT, JUST
PICK A BAT, BILL.
BY NOW HAROLD AND
I ARE GETTING A
LITTLE BORED
AND HAVING A
GAME OF CATCH.
WELL, ONE OF US IS.
OH MAN.
OH, OH, OH, OH,
OH, OH, OH.
OH, LOOK OUT.
OH, OH.
NICE ONE.
I SEE YOU PICKED
YOURSELF A BAT
THERE, EH, BILL?
ALL RIGHT.
OH MY GOSH.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
WHAT?
OH FOR GOSH SAKE.
I HAVE NOTHING TO
SAY ABOUT THAT.
ALL RIGHT, I'M
LOOKING FOR MY SIGN.
NO, NO, DON'T
LIKE THAT ONE, NO,
NO, NO.
YES, SIR, THAT'S
THE ONE I LIKE.
HIGH HEAT.
I BELIEVE YOU'RE
OUT AT THE PLATE, SIR.
THAT A BOY, HAROLD,
NICE GRIP, THAT'S WORKS.
STAY TUNED FOR
SOME DRY DOCK POETRY
AND THEN WINSTON TRIES
TO GET A HOLD OF A BIG ONE.
"APRIL LOVE," BY ME.
"ON A SUNNY APRIL
DAY YEARS AGO,
"MY MOTHER
TURNED SWEET 16.
"THEN MY FATHER MET MY
MOTHER ON ANOTHER
SUNNY APRIL DAY.
"AND ON A THIRD SUNNY
DAY IN APRIL,
"THEY FIRST KISSED
AND FELL IN LOVE.
"AND ANOTHER APRIL
DAY THEY WED
"AS THE SUN SHONE
FROM ABOVE.
"AND I WAS BORN YET
ANOTHER SUNNY DAY IN APRIL.
"I'M TOLD THAT WAS
ONE OF THE FEW APRILS
"WHERE WE HAD FIVE
SUNNY DAYS IN A ROW."
WELL, THIS IDEA OF
GETTING SILVER OUT
OF THE FILM NEGATIVES
HAS KIND OF STARTED A
BIT OF A GOLD RUSH UP
HERE AT THE LODGE.
EVERYBODY IS GOING BACK,
DIGGING UP ALL THEIR
OLD STUFF
AND THROWING IT
INTO THE POT.
A LOT OF WEDDING
PHOTOS SHOWING UP THERE.
EXCEPT FOR
OLD MAN SEDGWICK,
I THINK YOU GUYS
SHOULD REALIZE,
YOU KNOW,
THAT GETTING SILVER
FROM FILM IS A VERY
LOW YIELD EXERCISE.
WELL, LOW YIELD IS KIND
OF OUR SPECIALTY UP
AT THE LODGE.
BUT THERE'S LIKE A MILLIONTH
OF A SMIDGE OF SILVER
IN EACH PHOTOGRAPH,
YOU KNOW.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
LIKE 100 ROLLS OF FILM
JUST TO GET ONE
OUNCE OF SILVER.
YOU KNOW HOW
MUCH ONE OUNCE OF
SILVER IS WORTH, $6.
YOU KNOW WHAT 100 ROLLS OF
OUR FILM IS IS WORTH?
NOTHING.
UNLESS MAYBE WE COVER
THEM WITH MOLASSES
AND USE THEM
AS FLY STRIPS.
YEAH, BUT WHAT
ABOUT ALL THE HOURS
OF WORK YOU PUT INTO IT,
YOU KNOW, THE MONEY
YOU SPENT ON CHEMICALS?
YOU'RE NO FURTHER AHEAD.
WELL, SURE WE
ARE, HAROLD.
WE'RE LEARNING
SOMETHING, WE'RE
HAVING FUN,
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY
WE'RE NOT OUT IN CARS
OR OUR BOATS
WHERE WE DO THE REAL
EXPENSIVE DAMAGE.
YOU GUYS HAVE A VERY
WARPED SENSE OF ECONOMY.
WELL, HAROLD, WHEN
YOU GET TO OUR AGE,
YOU GIVE UP ON WINNING,
YOU JUST TRY TO LOSE
AS SLOWLY AS POSSIBLE.
WELL, ALL THIS TALK
OF SILVER STOCKS AND
PROFIT MARGINS
HAS GOT OUR
HEADS SPINNING,
SO I THOUGHT WE'D GET SOME
SOUND BUSINESS ADVICE
FROM WINSTON ROTHSCHILD,
BECAUSE WHEN WINSTON
TALKS, PEOPLE BACK OFF.
WELL, IF IT ISN'T RED,
THE SILVER FOX.
HEY, WINSTON,
HOW'S BUSINESS?
IT SUCKS.
SORRY TO HEAR THAT.
NO, NO, IT'S A JOKE.
IT SUCKS.
HOSE, SEPTIC,
SUCK, YOU KNOW.
LISTEN, I GOT SOME
FILM HERE FOR YOU,
IF YOU WANT TO BUY IT.
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURPRISED YOU WANT
TO PART WITH THESE
FAMILY MEMENTOS.
ACTUALLY THEY'RE
RECENT PICTURES OF
MY OLD MAN, EH,
AND TO TELL YOU
THE TRUTH, YOU'D BE
DOING HIM A FAVOUR, EH,
BECAUSE MOST OF THEM
COULD BE USED AGAINST
HIM IN A COURT OF LAW.
OH. SURE. YEAH.
SO WINSTON, DO YOU HAVE
ANY BUSINESS ADVICE FOR
US ON THIS DEAL?
RED, YOU GOT TO
FOLLOW YOUR HEART.
ALL RIGHT.
YEAH.
FOLLOW YOUR HEART.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU FEEL
STRONGLY ABOUT THIS
SILVER PROJECT,
I SAY GO
FOR IT, EH?
LIKE YOU'RE NOT IN
IT FOR JUST THE
MONEY, ARE YOU?
NOT SO FAR.
THERE YOU GO.
BOY, I'LL TELL YOU,
I DONE A LOT OF
CRAZY THINGS
IN THE EARLY
YEARS MYSELF, EH?
LIKE, FOR INSTANCE,
ONCE I STARTED OUT THIS
WHOLE MAIL ORDER THING,
BUT THEN SOME IDIOT
BROKE THE CHAIN
AND NEVER SENT
A DOLLAR TO SEVEN
OF HIS FRIENDS, EH?
AND THEN I GOT INTO
THIS PYRAMID SCHEME
WHICH QUICKLY
COLLAPSED INTO
A RHOMBOID.
BOY, I LOST MY
SHIRT ON THAT ONE.
AND THEN I STARTED
SELLING SEEDS AND
GREETING CARDS,
BUT THE PRIZES WERE
NEVER AS GOOD
AS THEY LOOK
ON THE BACK OF
THE COMIC BOOKS, EH?
NO, I'VE BEEN THERE.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT,
THEN I FOUND SOMETHING
THAT I WAS GOOD AT
AND I REALLY
ENJOYED.
WELL, WHY ARE YOU
IN THE SEWAGE BUSINESS?
NO, THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
THIS IS WHAT I LIKE
MOST IN LIFE.
WOW.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
BOY, THAT WAS A
DOUBLE FLUSHER.
SO I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE THE SILVER
ESCAPADE COULD BE,
YOU KNOW,
IF YOU'RE LUCKY,
YOUR SEWAGE PLANT.
YEAH, IT
WOULDN'T SURPRISE ME.
I HEAR THE DISTANT
SOUND OF EVERYTHING
GOING DOWN THE DRAIN.
WELL, THIS GETTING
THE SILVER OUT OF
THE FILM NEGATIVES
STARTED OFF A
LITTLE BIT SLOW
BUT THEN WE GOT KIND
OF AN ASSEMBLY LINE
THING GOING THERE.
BUSTER HADFIELD WOULD
UNROLL THE FILM,
MOOSE WOULD GET THE
EMULSION OFF WITH
A BELT SANDER
AND THEN JUNIOR
SINGLETON WOULD SUCK
IT UP WITH A VACUUM
AND THEN I WOULD DISSOLVE
THE DUST INTO VINEGAR,
AND THEN OLD MAN SEDGWICK
GOT THE SILVER OUT
OF THE VINEGAR
BY USING ELECTRICITY
HOOKED UP TO HIS PACEMAKER.
I'LL TELL YOU, THERE
CAN'T BE ONE GOOD
ROLL OF FILM
LEFT IN ALL
OF POSSUM COUNTY.
MOOSE EVEN DONATED ALL
THE MUGSHOTS HE'S HAD
DONE OVER THE YEARS.
AND HOW MANY INGOTS
OF SILVER DID YOU GET
WITH ALL YOUR EFFORT?
ONE TINY LITTLE
GLOB, HAROLD,
ABOUT THE SIZE
OF YOUR BRAIN.
WELL, WELL, WELL,
WELL, WELL,
GOOD BUSINESS
MOVE, UNCLE RED.
YOU GO TO CASH
THAT IN,
YOU'LL FIND YOU
PROBABLY WORKED FOR
ABOUT, OH, TWO CENTS A DAY,
WHICH, COME TO THINK OF
IT, IS PROBABLY ALL
YOUR TIME IS WORTH.
WELL, WE'RE NOT GOING
TO CASH IT IN FOR
A WHILE, HAROLD,
WE'RE GOING TO HANG
ON TO IT UNTIL SILVER
GOES UP ENOUGH IN VALUE
THAT WE CAN MAKE
MONEY ON THIS.
WELL, I DON'T THINK THE
PLANET EARTH IS GOING TO
BE AROUND THAT LONG.
OH, SURE IT
WILL, HAROLD.
THE BIG QUESTION IS,
WHO DO WE TRUST
TO HANG ON
TO THE SILVER
WHILE WE'RE WAITING.
SO WE TOOK A PAGE
OUT OF THE LONE
RANGER'S BOOK,
WE MELTED HER DOWN
INTO A BULLET,
WE WENT DOWN AND
FIRED HER INTO
THE DEAD TREE
IN THE CENTRE OF
THE TOWN PARK.
WHICH TREE?
THE SILVER BIRCH.
WE'RE NOT
STUPID, HAROLD.
OH NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO.
[possum squealing]
THAT'S THE CRY
OF THE POSSUM.
IT'S MEETING TIME,
KEMOSABE.
WELL, I'D CALL HIM
TONTO, BUT HE'S
MORE LIKE TOTO.
I'LL BE DOWN IN
A WHILE, HAROLD.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING,
AND IF YOU'RE
WONDERING WHAT
I GOT YOUR SISTER
FOR HER SILVER
ANNIVERSARY,
TELL HER IT'S
IN THE PARK.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH
FOR WATCHING.
AND UNTIL THE NEXT TIME
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheers and applause]
[quirky upbeat music]
[possum squealing]
HAROLD:
EVERYBODY RISE UP!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI