It's the new
Red Green show!
And now, the man that
everyone's talking about --
except the members of
the jury of course --
my uncle, your hero,
Red Green!
[CHEERS & APPLAUSE ]
Than you. Sorry I’m a little late.
The bridge is out again.
Man I’m getting fed up with this.
Every spring the road washes
out between here and town.
And I'll tell ya, a lot of us
do not enjoy being cooped up
in the lodge...
for obvious reasons.
It's always dangerous to
drive in flood waters.
Unless of course if you had
an Amphicar, you'd be okay.
I saw a guy in
an Amphicar once
and he was doing just fine
until he went over the
waterfall.
So actually,
you know, yes!
Yes, it's always dangerous
to drive in flood waters.
Even if you did have an
Amphicar, that's really
highly unlikely.
They stopped making
them like 30 years ago.
I bet you can make one though.
You know, if you had, like,
a little duct tape and
lots of insurance,
you could make one.
Like I say, a lot of us get
tired being cooped up
in the lodge.
So we decided to get
the government to
look after it.
What the heck.
It's their road,
it's their problem.
All we gotta do is
get in touch with our
local representative...
anonymously of course,
because we want 'em to
think we're tax payers.
Uncle Red, who is our
local representative?
I have no idea,
Harold.
Well, who'd you vote for
in the last election?
I abstained.
The playoffs were on.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
RED: What you're
looking at here
is a bunch of segments
from this particular show.
The main message being,
for gosh sakes, don't even
think about changing
the channel.
I'll tell ya something,
if you're gonna try and make
sense out of this program,
you gotta give it
your undivided attention.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Well, I got the scoop
on our government guy.
His name is
Jerome Q. Partager,
and he's been out local
representative for the
last nine years.
Jerome, I've never
heard of him.
He's never kissed any babies
or cut any ribbons or
anything like that.
Well, there's a
reason for that, Harold.
He passed away
eight years ago.
So, he's the late
Jerome Q. Partager.
No, he's not late.
He's not coming.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait...
We had an election,
like three years ago.
How did he
run for that?
A very
quiet campaign.
Actually, Flynty McKlintock
ran against him.
Flynty didn't think
to mention that his
opponent was deceased?
That didn't seem
to matter, Harold.
You know, people around
here are very conservative,
and of course
Jerome was the incumbent.
He's re-cumbant!
Uncle Red, he's dead!
You know:
[ HAROLD WHEEZES AND CROAKS ]
Well, Harold, in politics,
if you're dead first,
it makes the other
guy dead last.
RED:
Well, later on we've got --
Oh, there's Bill there.
We're gonna have an adventure,
of course, later on.
Come on out, Bill.
Come on out.
Use the
fire exit on that.
Anyway, Bill's got
some darts here.
That's what we're gonna be
doing later on in the program.
One thing about aiming at the
ground, he can hit it usually.
So Bill's gonna get
the door back up there.
No, Bill.
C'mon, Bill.
Gosh!
Oh! Ha ha ha ha!
Oh boy. Oh boy.
There's a good
start to the day.
Boy, I've always wondered why
Bills pants fit him so well.
Cause he's got all
them darts in 'em.
Oh, life is
a wonderful mystery
Who guessed we could
do what we've done
But until you face
a pitbull in heat
you'll never know
how fast you can run
Stop that.
Okay, this is for
the big one.
The grand prize is
a 1983 Cordova.
Unlicensed, uncertified,
and on fire.
Uncle Red,
you have 30 seconds
get Mr. Bob Stymonson
to say this word...
Go!
All right, Bob.
On Sunday morning
you go to...
Play golf.
No, no.
This is where
non-golfers go.
The driving range?
This is a place where
you kneel and pray.
The green on
the 9th hole?
Okay, okay.
You've been
married four times.
Each time you got
married in a...
Hurry.
But you were
in a...
Fog.
No, no,
I'm talking about
the building you were in
when you said
you'd marry her.
Motel 6.
No, no, no.
I'm talking about --
this is a special building.
With a pointed roof.
Oh, the pro-shop.
I'm talking stained
glass windows.
Outhouse?
Oh, no, I know,
I know, I know.
All those things you've
got in your golf bag...
Funny words.
You've got niblets,
you've got mashies.
What do you call
a bottle opener?
Church key!
There you go.
[ RINGING BELL ]
This week in
handyman corner
I thought I'd take
you back to a lost art,
from an era when there were
a lot more tradesmen,
and people were
really stinking cheap.
See what I've got here,
I've got a bell
on a piece of
thread here.
And that's as long
as the thread is,
and it won't stretch.
Now, watch what happens
when I add steam to it.
The steam drives the moisture
into the cotton thread,
and adds elasticity.
Watch this.
[ STRETCHING SOUND ]
[ RED GRUNTING
WITH EXERTION ]
Whoa, baby.
Ha ha ha!
[ BELL RINGING ]
See how that works?
You know, we used to do the same
thing with hats, like this.
They'd add the steam to them,
and they could bend them
to fit whoever
was wearing 'em.
Put the steam in there,
and they'd mold it
to the guy's head.
You know, it was called
getting your hat blocked.
I guess people who had
it done were blockheads.
Now they don't
do that anymore
because everyone's wearing
their baseball caps
on backwards.
But I'm thinking to myself,
why couldn't you get
your pants blocked,
so they'll still fit ya?
You know we've all see the
passage of time, and meals,
and what that can do to a
perfectly good pair of pants
who are no longer up to the
challenge of keeping up
with the waistline
they were originally
purchased to circumnavigate.
Well, I'm saying,
why couldn't you just
add some steam in there
and then just stretch the
pants as big as you need 'em?
All right, now, the first
thing you're gonna need is
some kind of a pant container
to hold 'em while you're
steaming 'em.
Here we go.
How 'bout
hip waders, huh?
That'll work just fine.
Alls you gotta do is
lay them out there, then stuff
the pants right into 'em.
You wanna get the cuffs
way down past the ankles,
so they'll
stick in there.
And if they're
real old hip waders,
they may just stick
there on their own.
I suggest you do this
with the blinds down...
no sense starting
unnecessary rumours.
Then once you've
got the pants in there,
you wanna hang this whole unit
from the ceiling, upside down.
Now, you can see
I've put on the bottom here,
duct tape coils there,
sticky side out.
We'll just stick them
right up to the ceiling.
Great.
There we go.
Now all we have to do is
add the steam to her.
[ COUGHING ]
Well, you know,
in hindsight, there,
I would go with a newer,
cleaner pair of hip waders,
that didn't have the dried
mung hanging inside.
But anyway, the pants,
I would say,
now have
a full head of steam.
And they're ready
for the blocking.
Now, for what you need for that,
to stretch 'em out real good,
you wanna get yourself
some inner tubes.
Maybe out of a truck,
or out of a bus,
or, you know,
whatever size you are.
If you were a real big boy,
you might get a couple off
the landing gear of the
space shuttle.
Now, what you want to do with
these, is stuff them up
inside the pant legs.
But of course, first of all,
we gotta get the pant legs
outta there.
Whoa, whoo, baby.
Talk about hot pants.
All right, you wanna stuff
the innertubes down there.
And here, again, you might
wanna close the blinds on this.
And if your wife yells down,
"What're ya doin' down there,"
just say you're
blowing up your pants,
and I can
pretty much guarantee,
she'll leave you alone for
the rest of the day.
[ GRUNTING ]
Oh, oh.
Hold it, hold it.
Had a bit of a rip
in the pants there.
I'll have to
fix that up.
There we go.
Got 'em up about 19 sizes now,
much like yourself.
Now alls you gotta do is
remove those innertubes,
and you're all set.
Might be an idea
to kinda undo the zipper
and relieve the pressure.
You've done
that before.
[ LEAKING AIR NOISE ]
Oh, oh boy.
The zipper cut into the
inner tube there.
I've got
a bit of a leak.
Oh, what am
I thinking about?
It doesn't matter.
We wanna get the air
outta there anyway.
That's perfect.
So you see when you're
blocking your pants up
to a certain size,
I'll tell ya,
the skies the limit.
Remember, if women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
RED:
Stay tuned and relaxed.
Whatever this is,
we've got a lot more of it.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
I want to talk to you older
couples out there who are
saving your money
so that after you retire
you can travel.
And then when you do retire,
instead of a year-long,
around-the-world cruise,
you spend two nights
at a Motel 6
because they got the
early bird dinner and
clean washrooms.
See, I would tell ya,
do your travelling now,
'cause the older you get,
the less you like new stuff.
And I'll tell ya something,
travel is non-stop new stuff...
New food, new beer, new
language, new money.
You know how it bugs ya
that you can't understand
half the things your kids
are saying to you now?
How do you think you're
gonna enjoy some Italian
yelling at ya,
'cause you forgot which side
of the street to drive on?
ose Romance languages
can get pretty unromantic.
So I would say do a little
bit of travelling now.
Go away for a
little short trip.
Kinda get your feet wet.
You know, find out if
you enjoy standing in
a French railway station,
trying to figure out how
to flush the toilet.
I'm not just talking
about travelling.
Whatever it is you plan
to do after you retire,
find out if
you enjoy it first.
No sense spending 40 years
at a job you hate,
only to retire and do
something else you can't stand.
Remember,
I'm pulling for ya.
We're all
in this together.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Sorry, Harold.
As it turns out,
with our deceased
government rep,
they've been continuing to
deposit his pay cheques into
a community account
in the Possum Lake Bank
and Video Outlet.
That's like spooky and
weird or something.
We should just inform the
government, you know,
'cause that money could be
used to help the deficit.
Yeah, right.
Ha ha ha!
You know, I think we should use
the money to fix the road.
No, no, no, no.
You can't do that.
Why not?
It's not your money.
Well, whose
money is it?
It's not yours.
Well, the road's not mine
and I use that.
The money's not mine,
I'll use that too.
Well, you know,
I think legally,
the money belongs to the estate
of Mr. Jerome Q Partager.
Therefore we should just
notify his next of kin.
Who's his next of kin?
No one's ever admitted
being related to him,
Harold.
Especially since
that town picnic
where he was over-served
the special cider
during the
dairy princess contest
and spent most of the
evening under the
sausage wagon
with Miss Congeniality.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
So I'm standing there and I'm ready to just
you know, walk out
like I always do,
and I thought,
No, this is wrong.
So I went back in
and I put that seat down.
[ APPLAUSE ]
All right! Whoo!
Maybe someone else
would like to share
some emotions.
Dalton, you have something
you'd like to share with
the group, maybe?
Sure.
My name is Dalton,
and I am a man.
EVERYONE:
Hi, Dalton.
Hello, men.
And, uh, I guess it's
been two weeks since I
last acted like a guy.
And, I fell off
the wagon -- almost fell
off the wagon yesterday.
Ah, see, I went clothes
shopping with the wife,
and we went to that women's
store out in Port Asbestos.
You know the one?
It's across the street
from the hardware store.
Oh, yeah,
yeah, yeah.
You know, I fought
temptation,
because I could have said,
No dear, you go along inside
because I've got to pick
up something at the
hardware store,
but that would have been
acting like a guy.
And I didn't.
I could've.
'Cause they had that --
the hardware store had
the table right out
on the sidewalk,
you know, the
"Everything on this
table is a dollar" table.
They had this rolled
up window screen that --
and these cans of
dented car wax and
the screw nails.
Oh, oh, oh!
This brand new barbeque
only had one leg missing.
Oh, geez,
I wanted that!
Dalton,
Dalton, Dalton.
Well, okay.
I don't mind saying
that I could have killed
an hour at that table easy.
But I didn't.
I went back in and went
shopping with my wife instead.
[ HALTING APPLAUSE ]
'Course, you know,
after I dropped her off,
I nipped back and
got that barbeque.
[ HEARTY APPLAUSE ]
And I got this set of four
ratchets, made in China.
Four for a buck.
Two still work!
Shiny and bright!
Thank you, Dalton.
[ APPLAUSE ]
RED:
Well, meanwhile back at
Adventures With Bill,
we're all set
for our big dart game.
Bill's gonna just put
the nail in the door there,
and we're gonna hang
the dart board on the -- oh.
Bill, Bill,
that won't work.
Bill, Bill, there's
nothing to hang it on.
Bill, Bill.
No, Bill,
that can't work.
That's impossible.
See what I mean?
Okay, you're fine,
you're fine.
Oh, come on,
So we've got the door all
straightened out there
and everything.
We're all set,
and the dart --
Oh boy...
the dart tradition,
I believe, goes way back
hundreds and hundreds
of years to when they had --
I guess, they would just
throw a dart at just passing
animals or whatever.
That line's not
good enough, Bill.
This is the
manly dart line.
You know if you can see the
dart board, you're too close.
Look at that, eh?
I still got it.
Still got the touch.
Not bad. Ha ha ha ha.
Go ahead, Bill.
Go on. Away you go.
That's my dart.
Where's your dart?
Where'd your dart go?
Where the heck is it?
Oh, there it is.
Oh boy.
Wow. What?
Bill wants to
take another shot.
Here we go.
That's my dart.
Where's your dart?
Up, up, up, up.
Way up.
There we go.
Nice shot, Bill.
I'm glad we don't
have a smaller shed.
Oh.
[ BREAKING GLASS ]
Nice shot.
We're gonna be here
a while, I think.
Should I
move the van?
That's Bill's bike.
[ DOG YELPS ]
Oh, oh, oh!
I hope he's okay.
Oh, man.
All right, so Bill's --
he's done something,
I'm not quite sure what,
but I guess,
maybe he must've
been practising.
Hey, hey, all right.
Come on, now.
Take it easy.
What?
Oh, yeah,
this should go well.
Oh my god.
What?
How's this
working here?
What's going on?
Well, by golly.
He's done something
to his dart game.
That's incredible.
What're you gonna
do now, Bill?
Oh, it's a trick.
Oh, I see.
Now we're getting
into the circus stuff.
It's is only a matter
of time with Bill.
Just checkin'
the blindfold.
That's all.
Okay, I'm convinced.
He can't see.
All right, there's
your darts, Bill.
And fire away.
No, no! Not at me.
There we go.
Fire that way.
Good luck... as if.
What? What?
Say, what?
How's that work?
What's going on?
There's some strange
force at work here.
Folks, this is not normal.
I'm beginning
to suspect...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What've we got here?
What've we
got here, Bill?
What's that?
Oh, for god sakes,
it's a magnet!
Here's a couple of ties
sent by a viewer,
for a formal night
at the lodge.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Well, we're almost there with
the legal work, there,
to free up the money
in the account of our
government representative,
the late
Jerome Q. Partager.
Then we'll be able to
fix up the bridge there.
We might even call it
The Jerome Q Partager
Memorial Bridge
Or, just
Dead Jerry's Bridge.
I need you to witness
my signature on this
thing here.
I'm not gonna sign anything
that's in bad taste
or on the fringe
of being illegal.
I'm not asking you
to join the lodge,
Harold.
Just sign after
I do, okay.
Sign there.
Right there.
I need you to
witness that.
Don't read it.
Just sign it.
I'm not gonna sign
anything unless I read it.
What is this?
Signature of family member?
Since when are
you a member of
the Partager family?
Well, we're all family,
the family of man.
It doesn't mean I'm directly
related -- it's just legalese.
Just sign it,
all right.
Ha ha. Yeah.
Okay, since when --
all right whose name
is that, Red Partager?
No, it's Red Green.
Yeah right.
Since when does your
name have a "P" in it?
Harold, at my age,
everything I do has
a "P" in it.
Welcome to The Experts
portion of the show
where we explore those
three little words
that men find, oh,
so difficult to say...
AUDIENCE:
I don't know!
Cool!
Joining my Uncle Red on
The Experts portion
of the show
is the brand new lodge
person up here,
moved in kinda guy,
Kevin Black.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Already-ruskie.
Our viewer writes,
"Dear Experts, the drinking
water at our new cottage
tastes rusty,
"like I just had
a tooth pulled.
"Is there anything
I can do?"
Yeah, all right.
Ah, rusty flavour is iron.
And you've got
two choices on that.
You can get used to it.
Or you can
stop drinking it.
he wouldn't
have invented beer.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I'm actually just
building a place of
my own up here.
Now, we haven't got our
water piped in yet,
but I know the law.
Now, that
rusty flavour,
that is actually
the municipality's
responsibility.
They are obligated to provide,
we, the tax payers,
with good, clean,
drinking water.
RED:
No, they're not.
Nobody up here has
town water, Mr. Black.
What?
What are we
supposed to do?
Bring in bottled water?
That would cost a fortune.
No, we dig a well.
[ LAUGHING ]
They still
have those?
Well, almost
everyone does.
You're gonna have
to get one too, Kevin.
Kevin has just built
a modest little 400,000-
square-foot cottage,
that overlooks the lake,
and it also overlooks what
he had to do to afford it.
He bought all
of Blood Point.
It's called
Bluff Point.
Yeah, well,
we call it Blood Point,
but then,
we know mosquitoes.
The "bluff" part doesn't
kick in till he tries
to sell it.
Sell?
No, I'll never sell.
No kidding!
Oh, no, no.
No, I think you're gonna
have to go with thll
on that one there, Kevin.
Okay, well,
I will --
I will have a well dug.
Now, how does one go
about getting that done?
Well, one picks up
a little unit we like
to call a shovel.
[ LAUGHS ]
No, seriously.
Who do I hire?
How about one of
your lodge members?
Oh, I don't think
you have that much time.
Or insurance.
I'm sure I will
find somebody.
And, boy, golly-gosh,
I hope I have good
clean water.
Well, you know what
rotten eggs smell like?
Not really.
You will.
Well, I am pleased to say
that thanks to the Jerome Q.
Partager memorial fund,
set up by the late,
great Jerome Q. Partager,
hereinafter
called "The Stiff,"
to care for and maintain
the Possum Lake area
in lieu of salary
since his expenses
went way down after
his death,
thanks to all that,
plus the innovative way
that we got to get our
hands on that money,
the bridge is fixed
and the road is now
open to town.
I cannot believe the
government continues
to pay politicians
after they die.
Well, it's so hard for
them to tell, Harold.
We even kind of
covered that off.
We had a
snap election,
and we've elected Jerome Q.
Partager to a life term.
I really wouldn't
call it a life term.
Well, no,
we changed that too.
We ruled that
a politician is not
legally dead
as long as his
bank account was
alive and well.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Oh. Meeting time,
Uncle Red.
You go ahead, Harold.
I'll be right down.
If my wife is watchin',
by golly, I've had
quite a day.
Got my van
out of the river,
had my name changed
over, and back,
spent some
government money
and got a dead guy
elected for life.
And I'm still
not tired.
And for the rest of ya,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of
myself and Harold
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge,
keep your
stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
All rise!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
RED:
Sit down, guys.
Harold, you got any
entertainment for us tonight?