(Gavel pounding)
IT'S
"THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW".
HERE'S THE MAN
YOU'VE WAITED TO WATCH,
THE MAN WHO SHOULD
WATCH HIS WEIGHT,
WHICH IS EASY
'CAUSE IT STICKS OUT.
HERE HE IS,
MY UNCLE, MR. RED GREEN!
(Applause)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOT AN EXCITING SHOW.
A BUNCH OF US ARE BUILDING
A CABLE CAR RIDE
AT ROCK REEF POINT
BY DUCT TAPING GROCERY CARTS
TO A GARAGE DOOR OPENER.
ONLY NEED ONE MORE PART.
DID YOU GET
THAT NINE-VOLT BATTERY?
NO, NOT EXACTLY.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK
WAS GOING INTO TOWN.
I ASKED HIM TO PICK UP
THE BATTERY
AND GET SOME LICORICE.
HAROLD, OLD MAN SEDGWICK
IS NOT RELIABLE.
HIS BRAIN ONLY LASTED THIS LONG
'CAUSE HE NEVER USES IT.
WHENEVER HE GOES TO TOWN
HE JUST STEALS SOMETHING,
COMES HOME IN A POLICE CAR.
WELL THEN, I GUESS HE DIDN'T DO
AS I ASKED.
HE DIDN'T BRING BACK
A NINE-VOLT BATTERY, HUH?
OK, WELL THEN, MAYBE YOU
CAN EXPLAIN THIS.
WAIT A SEC, THAT'S NOT IT.
THAT'S NOT A BATTERY.
I GOT ONE -- JUST A SEC.
HOLD IT.
OHH-OO.
WHAT DO YOU SAY NOW?
(Sirens)
OFFICER, THE GUY YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR IS RIGHT HERE.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): TODAY GARTH SHOWS YOU
HOW TO GET RID OF PIGEONS.
I'LL MAKE A CABLE CAR
TO GET YOU UP THE MOUNTAIN,
BUZZ SHERWOOD HAS MADE
A TRAILER FOR HIS AIRPLANE.
HERE'S THE BAD NEWS:
HAROLD IS HAROLD.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S
IN THE SLAMMER.
IT'S OK, HAROLD,
YOU CAN COME OUT NOW.
(Audience laughing)
HE ONLY
STOLE
A BATTERY -- SURELY
THEY WON'T INCARCERATE HIM.
OR IS THERE AN ELECTION
COMING UP?
IT'S NOT SO MUCH THE THEFT.
IT WAS RESISTING ARREST,
THROWING THE MEAT PIES
AND MAKING THE BODY NOISES
IN THE BACK OF THE CRUISER.
YOU KNOW WHAT?! --
THIS IS GREAT.
I COULD BE HIS LAWYER.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I KNOW ABOUT LAW.
I'VE GOT EVERY EPISODE
OF "LAW AND ORDER" ON TAPE.
I KNOW ALL ABOUT TENETS
AND PRECEDENTS.
YOU DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT BRIEFS.
(Laughing)
AHA!
(Red): KEEPING WITH THE THEME
OF CRIMINAL ACTIVITY,
BILL'S GOING TO TEACH YOU
HOW TO WATCH OUT
FOR PICKPOCKETS.
THE MAIN THING IS
PAY ATTENTION.
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL,
WITH ANOTHER IMPORTANT TIP
ON HOW YOU CONTROL ANIMALS.
COME ON IN HERE, RED.
A BIT OF A HEAD INJURY.
CHASING BEARS IN A CAVE?
NO -- EXACTLY THE OPPOSITE.
BOY, DID I NAIL MYSELF.
SMACKED RIGHT INTO
A STALACTITE.
BEARS DIDN'T EAT ME THOUGH.
WHEN I WENT DOWN
THEY MUST HAVE THOUGHT
SOMETHING WAS WRONG WITH ME.
BEARS ARE SMART THAT WAY.
I LAY IN THAT CAVE
FOR HALF A DAY, UNCONSCIOUS.
WHEN MY BOSS, LEO, FOUND OUT,
HE DOCKED ME FOUR HOURS PAY.
I HOPE LEO DIES BEFORE I DO.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
THE LOOK ON HIS FACE
WHEN I DON'T SHOW UP
AT HIS FUNERAL.
GARTH, DO YOU HAVE A TIP
OF ANY KIND FOR US HERE?
HUH?
AN ANIMAL TIP OF ANY KIND?
OH, OH, OH -- PIGEONS.
PIGEONS ARE AN IMPORTANT LINK
IN THE ECOLOGICAL CHAIN
BECAUSE THEY TAKE THINGS LIKE
GRUBS AND FOODSTUFFS
AND THEY REDISTRIBUTE THEM
FROM THE SKY,
USUALLY ON YOUR FRONT WALK
OR YOUR WINDSHIELD.
RED, ONE WAY
TO GET RID OF PIGEONS
IS WITH A GRENADE LAUNCHER,
LIKE THIS.
(Making shooting noises)
OF COURSE, WE CAN'T DO THAT.
NO?
NO, WE CAN'T.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE DO
AT THE LODGE?
WE TAKE LEAD PELLETS,
COVER THEM WITH HONEY.
GET A PIGEON TO EAT
A FEW OF THOSE
AND HE'S TRAVELLING ON FOOT
FOR A WHILE.
I'LL PRETEND I DIDN'T HEAR THAT,
RED.
WHAT YOU NEED IS THIS STUFF,
STICKY GREASE.
PIGEONS DO NOT LIKE TO PERCH
ON GOOEY STUFF.
SO I LOAD MY SQUIRT GUN
WITH A BUNCH OF THIS
STICKY GREASE,
AND THEN I SPRAY IT
ALL OVER THE EAVESTROUGHS.
THAT GETS RID OF THE PIGEONS.
SEE, LOOK THERE.
THERE THEY GO NOW.
I'M THINKING THAT GREASE WORKS
AS A BIT OF A LAXATIVE, TOO.
ANOTHER SUPER DAY.
♪ OH, I HAVE AN OLD CAR ♪
♪ THE SEATS
ARE ALL STAINED ♪
♪ IT WAS OLD
WHEN I BOUGHT IT ♪
♪ AND THAT HASN'T CHANGED ♪
♪ I HAD
MY FIRST DATE IN IT ♪
♪ MY FIRST KISS,
MY FIRST PASS ♪
♪ MY FIRST ROMANTIC ENCOUNTER
WHEN I RAN OUT OF GAS ♪
(Laughing)
♪ MY FIRST
PARKING INFRACTION ♪
♪ MY FIRST TOXIC LEAK ♪
♪ AND STILL NOT MY FIRST
CAR PAYMENT ♪
♪ BUT I'M HOPING TO HAVE
THE MONEY TOGETHER ♪
♪ BY EARLY NEXT WEEK ♪
WITH OLD MAN SEDGWICK
IN JAIL,
AND THEM HOLDING THAT
NINE-VOLT BATTERY AS EVIDENCE,
MY PLAN FOR A CABLE CAR
IS ON HOLD.
SO I'VE COME UP WITH
AN ALTERNATE PLAN.
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW YOU CAN BUILD
ONE OF THESE YOURSELF,
EVEN IF YOU'RE LIKE ME,
NINE-VOLT BATTERY IMPAIRED.
YOU'LL NEED A SPARE TIRE
LIKE THE ONES ON YOUR CAR.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE A SPARE,
HANG AROUND
THE MALL PARKING LOTS
UNTIL SOMEBODY WITH
YOUR KIND OF CAR COMES IN.
TRUNKS ARE PRETTY EASY TO OPEN.
I SUPPOSE IF ALL THE CARS
ARE NICER THAN YOURS,
TRY HANGING OUT AT WAL-MART.
FIRST, PRY THE TIRE
RIGHT OFF THE RIM.
THERE'S A GOOD REMINDER.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS
TAKE THE AIR
OUT OF THE TIRE FIRST.
(Hissing)
OH MY GOSH, THAT SMELLS...
OH, MUST BE
PRINCE CHARLES' TIRE.
SMELLS LIKE THE "AIR"
TO THE THRONE.
ALL RIGHT, THAT TIRE
SHOULD JUST POP RIGHT OFF
I WOULD THINK.
SHE'S COMING.
(Coughing)
IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
NOW WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS ATTACH THE RIM--
(Sizzling)
YOU WANT TO LET HER
COOL OFF A BIT.
GET A CLOTHESLINE
WITH THE CLOTHES ON IT.
THESE AREN'T HARD TO COME BY.
ALL YOU NEED IS
A PAIR OF CUTTERS
AND A DARK NIGHT.
TAKE THE CLOTHES OFF.
THEN YOU WANT TO GET YOUR RIM
AND ATTACH THAT TO
THE OUTSIDE OF ONE OF
THE DRIVE WHEELS ON YOUR CAR.
THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH.
YOU CAN HOLD THIS ON
WITH BOLTS,
OR WELD THAT ON THERE,
BUT REMEMBER, THERE'S GOING
TO BE PEOPLE IN THIS CABLE CAR.
SO YOU WANT TO ATTACH THIS
WITH SOMETHING
YOU'D TRUST YOUR LIFE TO.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
THIS IS A CAR,
AND THIS IS A CABLE...
HENCE THE TERM "CABLE CAR".
ONLY NEEDS ONE MORE THING
TO MAKE IT WORK.
(Panting)
A TREE AT THE TOP OF THE HILL
TO WIND THE CABLE AROUND.
NOW, ALL'S I HAVE TO DO IS
GO BACK TO THE CAR,
ATTACH THIS TO THE FRONT.
NEXT TIME I'LL BE ABLE TO
COME UP THE HILL...
WITHOUT WALKING.
ALL RIGHT,
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS THREAD THAT THROUGH
YOUR FRONT BUMPER,
AND SECURE THAT.
SNUG HER RIGHT UP.
GET HER SNUG.
AS SOON AS I START THE ENGINE
AND POP HER INTO GEAR
IT WILL TIGHTEN THE CABLE
AND THE CAR WILL
PULL ITSELF UP THE HILL
WITH THE PASSENGERS
SAFELY INSIDE.
THEY GOT A HEATED COMPARTMENT
IN HERE.
YOU GOT MUSIC.
YOU GOT
YOUR BEVERAGE CONTAINERS.
AND THE BEAUTY IS
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE TO STEER.
LET'S GIVE HER A TRY.
(Engine starting)
(Engine revving)
ALL RIGHT, THAT WAS MY FAULT.
I JUST GOT TO ATTACH THE CABLE
TO SOMETHING
A BIT MORE SECURE.
I REMOVED SOME OF
THE EXCESS WEIGHT.
IT'S GONNA RUN BETTER NOW.
I'VE SECURED THE CABLE
TO THE FRAME.
HINDSIGHT'S ALWAYS 20-20.
USUALLY COMES FROM SOMEBODY
WHO WASN'T THERE.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
THEY'LL FIND ME
AT THE TOP OF THE SKI HILL.
(Engine starting)
(Engine revving)
STAY TUNED FOR BUZZ SHERWOOD
SAYING HELLO.
YOU GOT NEW NEIGHBOURS
MOVING IN DOWN THE STREET.
THEY LOOK OK FROM A DISTANCE.
AS YOU'RE PEERING AT THEM
THROUGH YOUR BINOCULARS
TO SEE IF THEIR FACES
LOOK FAMILIAR TO YOU
FROM TELEVISION SHOWS LIKE
"AMERICA'S MOST WANTED",
YOUR WIFE TELLS YOU TO
PUT YOUR PANTS ON,
SHE'S INVITED THE NEW PEOPLE
OVER.
I KNOW YOU'RE THINKING
YOU ALREADY KNOW MORE PEOPLE
THAN YOU WANT TO KNOW.
AND ANYBODY
WHO WOULD BUY A HOUSE
ON THE SAME STREET AS
A CHLORINE FACTORY IS AN IDIOT,
EXCEPT FOR YOU, OF COURSE.
BUT YOU'VE GOT
ENTIRELY THE WRONG ATTITUDE.
WHEN THE MOVING VAN
PULLS IN, RUN OVER,
SAY "HOWDY, NEIGHBOUR,"
ALL THE TIME,
KEEPING AN EYE ON EVERYTHING.
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR POWER TOOLS,
GARDENING EQUIPMENT
AND ESPECIALLY
A BIG-SCREEN T.V.
WHEN IT BECOMES OBVIOUS THAT
THEY'RE BETTER OFF THAN YOU,
FIGURE OUT SOME WAY
THE FAMILIES CAN GET TOGETHER
ONCE A WEEK, EVEN MORE OFTEN
DURING THE PLAYOFFS.
IT'S OK TO GIVE A LITTLE
AS LONG AS YOU GET A LOT.
THAT'S CALLED FREE TRADE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause)
WE GOT OLD MAN SEDGWICK
OUT OF THE HOOSEGOW,
BUT WE HAD TO SIT THROUGH
QUITE A FEW CASES.
THE COURTROOM WAS PACKED.
I HAVEN'T SEEN
THAT MANY OLD FRIENDS
SINCE MY HIGH SCHOOL REUNION.
TELL THEM ABOUT
FLINTY McCLINTOCK
PARKING HIS CAR
ON HIS NEIGHBOUR'S ROOF.
OH NO, THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
NOT WHEN IT'S ON THE ROOF.
IN THE LIVING ROOM
OR THE LAWN MAYBE,
BUT NOT THE ROOF.
FLINTY'S BRAKES FAILED.
THOSE LADDERS HAPPENED
TO BE LEANING AGAINST THE HOUSE
THE SAME DISTANCE APART
AS FLINTY'S WHEELS,
AND UP SHE WENT.
IT HAPPENS.
HOW COME THE SHINGLES
WERE SO MESSED UP?
WELL, IT TOOK HIM
A COUPLE
OF TRIES.
THE JUDGE WAS GOING TO
LET OLD MAN SEDGWICK OFF,
BUT F. LEE DOOFUS
SPOKE UP FOR HIM.
HE GOT SENTENCED TO 100 HOURS
OF COMMUNITY SERVICE.
WE DON'T HAVE
THAT BIG A COMMUNITY.
THAT MEANS WE EACH HAVE TO
SPEND AN HOUR WITH THE GUY,
SO WE ALL GET PUNISHED.
THE JUDGE RELEASED
MR. OLD MAN INTO
UNCLE RED'S CUSTODY.
ARE YOU READY TO BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR A MISFIT?
I'M PRETTY MUCH USED TO IT
ACTUALLY.
SAFETY IS EVERYTHING,
BUT IT'S GOT NOTHING
ON BUZZ SHERWOOD.
HEY, IT'S THE BIG RED GUY!
HAROLD!
THAT'S FUN.
HEY, I GOT SOMETHING
TO SHOW YOU.
I GOT A NEW PLANE TRAILER.
A TRAILER TO PUT
YOUR PLANE ON,
TOW BEHIND THE CAR.
IT'S PROBABLY A LOT SAFER
THAN FLYING HER.
NO, NO, NO,
I GOT A PLANE TRAILER.
A TRAILER THAT MY PLANE
CAN TOW.
YOU'RE GOING TO TOW THIS
BEHIND YOUR PLANE?
HOW ELSE ARE YOU GOING TO GET
A BOAT TO FLY?
I EVEN GOT THE MIRRORS
FOR BACKING UP.
RED, I WAS THINKING,
WITH MY PLANE TRAILER,
I CAN CARRY MORE STUFF,
MORE PEOPLE,
MAKE FEWER TRIPS,
USE LESS FUEL.
AREN'T YOU AFRAID OF CRASHING?
WHY?
FROM THE EXTRA WEIGHT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THE EXTRA WEIGHT OF THIS UNIT
IS PROBABLY GOING TO MAKE
YOUR PLANE CRASH.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOUR PLANE CAN ONLY CARRY
SO MANY POUNDS, RIGHT?
WHICH IS SO GREAT
ABOUT THE PLANE TRAILER.
IT TAKES ALL THE EXTRA WEIGHT.
YEAH, BUT IT'S ATTACHED
TO THE PLANE.
WHICH DOESN'T HAVE TO
CARRY A THING.
ALL RIGHT, OK,
MAYBE I'M WRONG.
YOU CARRY ON.
JUST DO ME A FAVOUR.
DON'T FLY THIS STUFF
OVER THE LODGE, ALL RIGHT?
RIGHT, RIGHT, SURE.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK
SEEMS TO BE DOING OK
WITH HIS MANDATORY
COMMUNITY SERVICE.
HE VOLUNTEERED
AS A CROSSING GUARD
IN FRONT OF THE LEGION.
IT'S ODD TO SEE THOSE GUYS
WHO SERVED IN COMBAT
TO HAVE TO ASK PERMISSION
TO CROSS THE STREET.
HE'S GONNA GET SOMEBODY KILLED.
HE'S GOT EVERYBODY WAITING
TILL A VEHICLE COMES.
THEN HE JUMPS IN FRONT OF IT
WITH A BIG SIGN
MAKING BIG GESTURES.
BIG STUFF, BIG WOW!
IT'S CHILDISH.
HE'S A CROSSING GUARD.
IF HE DOESN'T STOP TRAFFIC,
HE SERVES NO PURPOSE.
IT WOULD BE LIKE
IF YOU DIDN'T SELL THIS SHOW
TO A MAJOR
NETWORK.
I DIDN'T.
EXACTLY.
WE DID HAVE ONE SET-BACK.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK
STOLE THE STOP SIGN
AND A FEW OF THE GUYS MEDALS.
HE'S A KLEPTO.
HE NEEDS HELP,
LIKE A PSYCHOLOGIST.
A PSYCHOLOGIST JUST MOVED HERE.
DR. STAN.
HE'S QUITE GOOD.
VERY COMFORTABLE CHAIRS.
(Audience laughing)
I THINK I CAN GET HIM
AN APPOINTMENT
FOR ROUGHLY 2:45 TOMORROW.
THERE COULD BE A CANCELLATION.
NO, HAROLD.
I'LL TAKE OLD MAN SEDGWICK
TO MY HOUSE,
LET MY WIFE LOOK AT HIM.
BERNICE IS GOOD WITH PEOPLE.
SHE USUALLY KNOWS
WHAT TO DO WITH A NUT-CASE.
MARRIES
'EM?
(Laughing)
THIS IS A CLAW HAMMER.
THE HAMMER PART IS FOR
BANGING NAILS IN.
THE CLAW PART IS FOR
TAKING NAILS OUT.
AS I TOLD YOU EARLIER,
BILL'S GOING TO SHOW US
HOW TO WATCH OUT
FOR PICKPOCKETS.
HE'S PRETENDING TO BE FRIENDLY,
PATTING AROUND.
YOU KNOW WHAT HE'S DOING,
DON'T YA?
HE'S TRYING TO
STEAL STUFF FROM ME.
HE HAD MY WATCH.
HE GRABBED MY WALLET,
MY PEN KNIFE AND SO ON.
CAR KEYS --
UNBELIEVABLE WHAT HE CAN DO.
SOME CHANGE AND SO ON.
AND...
OH, MY GOSH.
I GUESS I HAD A HOLE
IN ONE OF THE POCKETS.
AND WHAT...
MY SOCKS.
HOW... HOW... HOW...
HE TOOK MY SOCKS AND SHOES
RIGHT OFF.
THAT IS SLEIGHT OF HAND.
HE'D GONE THROUGH, APPARENTLY,
ALL THE GUYS IN THE LODGE.
I GUESS SOMEBODY HAD BEEN
ON THE PHONE
WHEN HE WAS DOING
THE PICKPOCKET WITH THEM.
THAT'S UNBELIEVABLE, ISN'T IT?
APPARENTLY, THEY SAY,
THE HAND IS QUICKER
THAN THE EYE.
THERE'S A FUNNEL.
SOMEBODY HAD THE TOWEL.
THE ROLLERBLADES.
BY GOLLY, THAT'S AMAZING.
BILL IS VERY GOOD
WITH HIS FINGERS.
NOT REALLY ALL THAT GOOD
WITH HIS HEAD.
SOMEBODY HAD THE PAIL THERE.
HE TOOK THAT OUT OF
SOMEBODY'S POCKET.
NOW HE'S GOING TO
SHOW ME HOW TO DO IT.
HE'S SAYING TO ME,
"IT'S JUST THAT EASY."
I'VE GOT A TRICK FOR HIM.
(Laughing)
OH, YOU'RE FINE.
GETTING BACK TO MY LESSON.
HE'S SAYING,
"YOU JUST GRAB IT
"BETWEEN A COUPLE OF FINGERS
LIKE THAT."
HE WANTS ME TO TRY IT.
HE'S GOT THE WALLET.
IT'S NOT THAT HARD --
BUT LOOK.
HE THINKS HE'S SO SMART.
OH YEAH, OH BILL.
YOU ARE THE EPITOME OF FUNNY.
I'M GOING TO HOOK
THE WHOLE UNIT THERE
ONTO SOMETHING THAT CAN GET
THIS WALLET PULLED OUT.
HOOK THAT ONTO MY RAD.
SOMETHING THAT'S NOT RUSTED OUT
TOO BAD.
LET'S SEE HOW MUCH TRACTION
THE OLD GIRL'S GOT.
GOT THE BIG EIGHT IN HER.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
YOU WANNA HANG ONTO
YOUR MONEY, HUH?
YOU'D BETTER GUARD YOUR HEALTH,
YOUNG MAN.
I GOT TO GIVE HIM CREDIT.
IT'S REALLY DIGGING IN,
BUT, UH...
HIS CLOTHES WEREN'T.
I'LL BE CLEANING THE WINDSHIELD
TILL A YEAR FROM TUESDAY.
I DIDN'T JUST PICK HIS POCKET.
I PICKED HIS WARDROBE,
INCLUDING EVERYTHING.
AND I MEAN EVERYTHING.
OH MY GOSH.
HE'S PACKING HEAT.
HERE'S A WORD WE USE LOT,
EXCEPT IT'S SPELLED WRONG.
BERNICE PRETTY MUCH HAD
OLD MAN SEDGWICK FIGURED OUT.
HOW LONG DID IT TAKE?
'CAUSE SESSIONS CAN BE LONG.
OFTEN IT TAKES FOUR HOURS
TO GET INTO
THE TRUE INNER SELF.
OH, NOT WITH BERNICE
IT DOESN'T.
SHE WOULDN'T LET HIM IN.
SHE WAS AFRAID
HE'D STEAL SOMETHING.
SHE SAID EVERYTHING MEN DO
IS A SHOUT FOR ATTENTION.
WE HAVE TO SPEND TIME
WITH OLD MAN SEDGWICK.
THEN HE'LL STOP STEALING.
IT IS RARELY THAT SIMPLE,
UNCLE RED.
DR. STAN SAYS --
OR I ASSUME HE'D SAY --
THAT OLD MAN SEDGWICK
IS GOING THROUGH
A DIFFICULT TRANSITION PERIOD,
COMPOUNDED BY
HIS FEAR OF GIRLS
AND BAD SKIN.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT YOU, HAROLD.
HE SHOULD TRY PRIMAL SCREAMING
IN A CRYSTAL PYRAMID.
WAAAA!
AAAAAH!
HAAAA AHHH!
AH!
HAAA!
I THINK IT'S--
HAAAA!
SOUNDS LIKE IT'S TIME TO GO
A SIZE UP ON THE PANTS TO ME.
I THINK WE'VE
TURNED THE CORNER
WITH OLD MAN SEDGWICK.
HIS STEALING DAYS ARE OVER
AS FAR AS I CAN SEE.
YEAH, RIGHT, OK.
WHERE ARE YOUR SUSPENDERS?
THE GUY'S A BORN THIEF.
HEY!
UNCLE RED.
THIS IS THE BIG ONE.
YOU HAVE A CHANCE TO WIN
TWO DOZEN DAY-OLD DOUGHNUTS.
IT'S THE BONUS ROUND.
WHOA, BABY.
OK, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO MAKE MY UNCLE
SAY THIS WORD.
OK, 30 SECONDS, GO.
DEPENDABILITY.
MADE IN
JAPAN.
IN GOD WE...
FEAR.
YOU'VE GOT MONEY TO GIVE
YOUR KIDS, YOU PUT IT IN A...
SOCK DRAWER.
NO!
HAROLD IS YOUR ASSISTANT.
YOU WHAT HIM?
MAKE FUN OF HIM,
LAUGH AT HIM.
OK, OK, HE PRODUCES,
HE DIRECTS THE SHOW.
THAT'S BECAUSE...
I WANT HIM OUT
OF MY FACE.
YOU GIVE HAROLD
SOMETHING TO DO.
HE BOTCHES IT UP --
WHAT ARE YOUR FIRST WORDS?
TRUST YOU
TO SCREW--
YES, YES, YES!
DOUGHNUTS!
WE GAVE IT AN HONEST TRY.
THE GUYS TOOK TURNS
SPENDING TIME
AT OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S HOUSE.
WE REALIZED WHY
WE TRY TO AVOID HIM.
THAT'S
CRUEL.
YOU SHOULD BE TOLERANT,
AND NOT AVOID PEOPLE
'CAUSE THEY'RE DIFFERENT.
HOW IS DR. STAN ANYWAY?
GOOD -- HE SAYS HELLO.
WE CURED HIM
OF HIS KLEPTOMANIA.
WHILE WE WERE AT HIS HOUSE,
WE NOTICED HE'S GOT NICE STUFF.
EVERY TIME OLD MAN SEDGWICK
STOLE SOMETHING,
WE'D STEAL FROM HIM.
WHEN HE RETURNED IT,
WE'D GIVE HIS BACK.
THAT'S A PROVEN TECHNIQUE
FOR SOLVING
PSYCHOLOGICAL PROBLEMS
THAT ARE BEHAVIOURAL
RATHER THAN CLINICAL.
(Bell ringing)
WHAT'S
THAT FOR?
TO SEE IF IT MAKES YOU DROOL.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK
REALIZED THAT HIS THIEVING
WAS CAUSING HIM TO BE ROBBED.
HE CUT OUT THE MIDDLE MAN
AND STOP SWIPING STUFF.
(Possum
squeal)
MEETING
TIME.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
IN THE SPIRIT OF
OLD MAN SEDGWICK,
I'LL TAKE ANOTHER SHOT
AT STEALING YOUR HEART,
WHICH WILL SIGNIFY THAT
I NEED ATTENTION.
(Bell ringing)
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF HAROLD
AND MYSELF AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): ALL RISE.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.