IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW."
AND, NOW, HERE'S
THE MAN WITH THE
PERSONALITY AS BIG
AS ALL OUTDOORS,
AND WHO IS AS OUT
AS ALL BIG DOORS,
YOUR HOST,
YOUR HERO,
MY UNCLE,
RED GR-E-E-E-N!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
YEAH, YEAH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK.
GOT OUR FIRST INTERNATIONAL
BREAKTHROUGH.
I SOLD THE SHOW
TO EUROPE.
EXCUSE ME, 'YOU' SOLD THE SHOW?
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
GREAT NEWS, WE SOLD
THE SHOW TO EUROPE.
'WE' SOLD THE SHOW?
UNCLE RED, 'I' SOLD THE SHOW.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
EUROPE BOUGHT THE SHOW.
EUROPE DID NOT BUY THE SHOW.
EUROPE'S NOT A COUNTRY.
YES, YES, WE SOLD IT TO
A COUNTRY IN EUROPE
BUT NOT TO EUROPE.
WHY? BECAUSE EUROPE
IS NOT A COUNTRY.
HE THOUGHT EUROPE
WAS A COUNTRY.
AND HE THOUGHT
I CARED.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
SWEDEN BOUGHT THE SHOW.
WE'RE SEEN IN SWEDEN NOW,
SO BONJOUR, SWEDEN.
NOT SWEDEN, IT'S SWITZERLAND.
WELL, IT'S THE
SAME THING, HAROLD.
IT'S LIKE HOLLAND AND THE
NETHERLANDS: THE SAME THING.
OR QUEBEC AND "K" BECK,
YOU KNOW, SAME.
CHINA AND JAPAN, YOU KNOW?
IT'S THE SAME PLACE;
DIFFERENT NAMES.
SWEDEN AND SWITZERLAND,
THAT'S THE SAME COUNTRY.
HELLO, THERE,
YOU SWISS SWEDES,
WHEREVER YOU ARE --
IN EUROPE, I 'M PRETTY
SURE ABOUT THAT.
NO, NO, NO, UNCLE RED, NO.
SWEDEN AND SWITZERLAND, I MEAN,
THEY GOT, LIKE, TWO DIFFERENT
LANGUAGES, YOU KNOW?
THEY LIVE COMPLETELY
SEPARATE LIVES,
AND THEY HAVE NO SIMILAR
HISTORY OR CULTURE OR ANYTHING.
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY,
WHAT KIND OF COUNTRY IS THAT?
CANADA.
(QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC)
THIS LITTLE PREVIEW WILL
SHOW YOU SOME OF THE STUFF
WE'RE GOING TO DO ON THIS
PARTICULAR SHOW.
THESE LITTLE CLIPS ARE SUPPOSED
TO GET YOU INTERESTED ENOUGH
YOU'LL STAY WITH US THE
WHOLE HALF HOUR.
KIND OF SAD, ISN'T IT?
IMAGINE THE STUFF WE LEFT
OUT OF THIS THING.
SWITZERLAND.
YEAH, SWITZERLAND, WHATEVER.
WELL, THE MEDIA'S JUMPIN'
ALL OVER IT TOO.
THE REVIEWS ARE IN.
"THE POSSUM LAKE POST,"
ALL RIGHT?
'GO FIGURE.'
"THE PORT ASBESTOS JOURNAL"...
'SWITZERLAND GOES FROM
NEUTRAL TO REVERSE.'
YOU CANNOT BUY
PUBLICITY LIKE THAT.
PEOPLE WHO DON'T
EVEN LIKE THE SHOW
ARE WATCHING IT NOW.
YOU KNOW, IT'S LIKE WE'RE
SOME BIG AMERICAN NETWORK
PROGRAM OR SOMETHING.
UNCLE RED, THAT IS THE
POWER OF HYPE.
HYPE WORKS;
HYPE IS COOL.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HAVE TALENT,
GOOD LOOKS, BRAINS, NOTHING
IF YOU'VE GOT ENOUGH HYPE.
YOU KNOW, I'M THINKING
HYPE COULD REALLY
HELP YOU, HAROLD.
YOU'RE HYPER NOW, SO JUST
BACK OFF ONE LETTER,
AND YOU'RE THERE.
YEAH.
TELL YOU SOMETHING
ELSE ABOUT THESE SWEDES.
THEY REALLY GET BEHIND
A SHOW WITH PUBLICITY
AND WITH GIFTS TOO.
HERE, HAROLD,
THIS IS FOR YOU.
O-O-O-H,
O-O-O-H.
O-O-O-H, I LOVE THESE.
IT'S A SWISS ARMY KNIFE.
OH, THESE ARE GREAT,
THEY GOT EVERYTHING.
THEY MUST REALLY LIKE ME.
LOOK AT THAT.
IT'S GOT A PENKNIFE AND A
CARVING KNIFE AND A SCALING
KNIFE AND A STEAK KNIFE,
A FORK AND SPOON;
AND THERE'S A CORKSCREW
AND A BOTTLE OPENER AND
A MAGNIFYING GLASS;
THERE'S A PENCIL SHARPENER,
A PENCIL, PEN, ERASER,
WIRE CUTTERS;
AND, RIGHT THERE, LOOK AT THAT,
YOU GOT, LIKE, A WOOD FILE
THING, THERE;
YOU GOT NAIL CLIPPERS, AND YOU
GOT, LIKE, SIX DIFFERENT KINDS
OF SCREWDRIVERS --
THAT'S HARD TO GET IN THERE, SIX
DIFFERENT KINDS OF SCREWDRIVERS.
THEY'RE ALL RIGHT INSIDE THERE.
YOU GOT, LIKE, A GUITAR PICK,
AN ALLEN KEY, AND THERE'S
A SKELETON KEY.
OH, THIS IS FANTASTIC.
OH, AND, LOOK, RIGHT DEEP
INSIDE THERE, THAT'S THE
LATEST VERSION OF "DOOM."
THAT'S SO GREAT.
THAT'S FOR ME.
(APPLAUSE)
THEY LIKE ME
SO MUCH OVER THERE.
BOY, I LIKE YOU TOO.
SO WHAT DID
YOU GET?
OH, I GOT A LITTLE
CHOCOLATE BAR, HAROLD.
O-O-O-H, THAT'S --
THAT'S A LOT
OF CHOCOLATE.
IT'S SO REALLY, REALLY
BIG, ISN'T IT?
THAT'S -- IT'S --
THAT'S CHOCOLATE.
O-O-O-H.
YOU'RE GOING TO SHARE IT,
THOUGH, WITH ME, RIGHT?
WELL, SURE, I'LL
GIVE YOU THE BOX.
YOU CAN MAKE A
PERISCOPE, THERE.
HAROLD, REALLY, YOU EAT
THIS MUCH CHOCOLATE, YOU'LL
TURN INTO A BIG, PLAID ZIT.
THAT'S NOT EVEN TRUE.
I TALKED TO MY DOCTOR,
AND HE SAID YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT MEDICINE.
YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT
WHAT GIVES PEOPLE ZITS,
AND YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT WHAT
MAKES TEENAGERS GO BLIND TOO.
OH, HE POPS A WHEELIE
RIGHT BY THE DOOR
THE TIRES ARE SMOKIN' GOOD.
HE MISSES A SHIFT
FROM SECOND TO THIRD
AND A FLAME POPS UP
UNDER THE HOOD
HE HITS THE WALL IN A
FOUR-WHEEL DRIFT
BUT THAT'S THE PRICE YOU PAY
WHEN YOU GO TO THE
FANCY HOTEL IN TOWN
HAND YOUR CAR
KEYS TO THE VALET
YOU KNOW, THE FREEDOM OF THE
OPEN ROAD APPEALS TO MOST MEN.
I THINK THAT'S BECAUSE SO MANY
OF US ARE STUCK IN LIFE'S DITCH.
IT'S BETTER TO BE A CHILD OF THE
ROAD THAN A SON OF A DITCH.
IS THERE NOTHING I WON'T SAY?
WELL, THINK ABOUT THIS ONE.
FOR 60 YEARS OR MORE, THE
GREATEST SYMBOL OF FREEDOM
HAS BEEN THE FABULOUS
AIRSTREAM TRAILER.
BUT, YOU KNOW, ONE OF THESE
AIRSTREAMS COST MORE THAN
I MAKE IN A DOG-YEAR,
WHICH IS SEVEN HUMAN YEARS.
SO I FIGURED THIS WEEK ON
"HANDYMAN CORNER,"
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW TO
MAKE YOUR OWN "AIRSTREAM."
I MEAN, WHAT HAVE
YOU GOT HERE?
A COUPLE OF WHEELS,
CURVED ALUMINUM BOTTOM,
CURVED ALUMINUM TOP,
ALUMINUM SIDES.
YEAH, YOU GOT A FRIDGE AND
STOVE, BUT YOU CAN GET
THAT STUFF ANYWHERE.
FIRST THING I NEED IS
A COUPLE OF WHEELS
WHICH WE HAVE RIGHT HERE
ON THIS OLD BOAT TRAILER.
NOW, ALL WE NEED IS
OUR ALUMINUM BOTTOM
AND TOP AND SIDES.
WELL, MY GOSH, FOR THE BOTTOM,
THERE'S THIS OLD ALUMINUM BOAT.
AND FOR THE SIDES, I'VE GOT
THESE APPLIANCE DOORS.
APPLIANCES ARE MADE OF ALUMINUM
OR SOME KIND OF METAL --
COULD BE ALUMINUM.
AND, LOOK, YOU COULD USE, LIKE,
THIS FRIDGE DOOR AS YOUR
OUTSIDE WALL,
AND ON THE INSIDE,
YOU GOT BUILT-IN AUTOMATIC
STORAGE, THERE, EH?
PUT YOUR EGGS OR YOUR CHEESE
OR YOUR GOLF BALLS OR SCREWS --
DIFFERENT SIZE IN EACH EGGCUP.
HERE'S SOMETHIN'.
YOU WANNA GO UPSCALE A BIT,
HOW ABOUT THIS?
ADD ONE OF THEM FANCY
NAUTICAL-STYLE PORTHOLE
WINDOWS IN THE END.
YOU'LL NEED ABOUT, I WOULD SAY,
10-20  APPLIANCES FOR
THE SIDES, THERE.
AND YOU GET TO GLOAT TO YOUR
WIFE ABOUT HOW SMART YOU ARE
TO KEEP THOSE APPLIANCES
ON YOUR FRONT PORCH FOR
THE LAST 16 YEARS.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S
THE BOTTOM AND SIDES.
WELL, FOR THE TOP, WE USE
THIS OTHER BOAT, EH?
JUST BECAUSE SHE'S NOT
SEAWORTHY, DOESN'T MEAN
SHE'S NOT ROADWORTHY.
OH, YEAH, LOTS OF HEADROOM...
AND SPIDERS.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY OUT.
ALL ASHORE, SPIDERS.
MAN, THOSE DOCK SPIDERS
ARE BIG, AREN'T THEY?
OH, OH, OH, GIT OUTTA THERE.
GIT OUT. GIT OUT.
MAN, I HAD NO IDEA I WAS
ALLERGIC TO SPIDER BITES.
NOW IT'S TIME TO
START ASSEMBLING
OUR AIRSTREAM TRAILER.
OH, NO, NO. HAROLD TOLD ME NOT
TO SAY AIRSTREAM, OR THEY'LL
BE SUING US FOR STEALING
THEIR DESIGN.
ALL RIGHT, WE WANT TO ATTACH
ALUMINUM TO ALUMINUM HERE.
WHICH YOU CAN DO WITH A
WELDING TORCH, BUT I DON'T
RECOMMEND THAT BECAUSE THAT
REQUIRES ABILITY,
WHICH PUTS IT OUTSIDE
MY SKILL CHART.
AND, OF COURSE, YOU'VE GOT THE
RIVETS AND SCREWS, THERE,
BUT YOU GOT TO BE DEAD ACCURATE
WITH THEM, AND THAT TAKES THE
FUN OUT OF ANY PROJECT.
SO, INSTEAD, I RECOMMEND YOU USE
THE HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
HAND ME ANOTHER
FRIDGE DOOR, HAROLD.
ALRIGHTY.
THERE WE GO.
OOPS, SPIDER! SPIDER!
AND THERE'S YOUR VERY OWN
HOUSE TRAILER.
AND ALL IT COST YOU WAS SOME OLD
APPLIANCES AND A COUPLE OF
SPIDER BITES.
I TELL YOU, THAT IS A SMALL
PRICE TO PAY TO HAVE YOUR
OWN AIRSTREAM --
OH, NO, I CAN'T SAY AIRSTREAM:
THEY'RE GOING TO BE SUING US
FOR COPYING THEIR DESIGN.
NO, NO, I THINK WE'RE OKAY...
NOT EXACTLY THE SAME.
BY THE WAY, DON'T TAPE
THE ROOF ON THERE.
LET GRAVITY HOLD HER ON.
THEN, WHEN YOU GET
TO YOUR CAMPSITE,
YOU FLIP HER OFF, YOU GOT
YOURSELF A BOAT, EH?
OKAY, LET'S HOP INSIDE
THROUGH THE UH...
OH, MAN.
NOW, WHERE THERE'S A WASHING
MACHINE, THERE'S A WAY.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE ALL SET
TO HIT THE OPEN ROAD.
AND, BY GOLLY, CAN YOU IMAGINE
THE LOOKS OF ENVY ON THE OTHER
DRIVERS, EH?
'CAUSE THEY HAD TO BUY
THEIR HOUSE TRAILER.
YOU DON'T JUST HAVE A HOUSE
TRAILER, HERE,
YOU'VE GOT A HOUSEBOAT.
SO REMEMBER, IF WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
OH, MY GOLLY, THE FRIDGE LIGHT
DOES GO OUT WHEN YOU
CLOSE THE DOOR.
I THINK THERE'S A LIGHT IN THE
BUTTER DISH. YEP.
SPIDER!
GOT HIM.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU OLDER
FOLKS ABOUT YOUR KIDS.
YOU KNOW WHEN THEY COME
OVER TO VISIT WITH THE
GRANDCHILDREN?
AND START ASKING QUESTIONS LIKE,
"HOW MUCH LONGER ARE YOU GOING
TO LIVE IN THIS PLACE?"
OR "WHERE ARE YOU GOING
TO LIVE WHEN YOU'RE OLDER?"
OR, THE WORSE ONE: "HOW MUCH
OLDER DO YOU THINK YOU'LL GET?"
AT FIRST, YOU THINK IT'S KIND
OF NICE, THEM PAYING ATTENTION
TO YOU AND ALL THAT.
AND THEN YOU REALIZE WHEN
THEY'RE HOLDING THE PAINT
CHIPS UP AGAINST THE WALL
WHILE THEY'RE TALKIN' TO YOU,
THEY'RE WAITING AROUND
FOR THE INHERITANCE.
SEE, THEY THINK YOU'RE LOADED.
YOU AND I KNOW THAT'S NOT TRUE,
BUT THEY DON'T NEED
TO KNOW THAT.
THEY ALSO DON'T NEED TO KNOW
THAT THE DOCTOR SAYS YOU'RE
IN EXCELLENT HEALTH.
KIND OF GO WITH IT A BIT.
YOU KNOW, WHEN THEY WERE YOUNG,
THEY'D NEVER EVEN TALK TO YOU.
NOW, THEY'RE FAWNING
ALL OVER YOU.
WELL, GO FOR IT.
ENJOY THE ATTENTION THEY'RE
GIVING YOU WHILE THEY SEARCH
FOR THIS MYTHICAL INHERITANCE.
START SAYING THINGS LIKE,
"OH GOLLY, I HAVE LEFT MY
SLIPPERS IN THE OTHER ROOM."
OR "YOU KNOW, I COULD REALLY GO
FOR A COLD BEER RIGHT NOW."
IT'S GOOD FOR THEM.
THEY'LL BE RESPECTIN'
THEIR ELDERS,
AND THEY'RE NOT DOIN'
IT FOR MONEY --
THEY JUST DON'T KNOW IT YET.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(APPLAUSE)
AH, WE HIT A FEW SNAGS WITH THIS
SWITZERLAND SALE THING.
TRYING TO PUSH ME
AROUND A LITTLE.
I'D JUST AS SOON TAKE A PASS,
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
I FEEL LIKE GIVING THEM BACK
THAT CHEQUE AND EVEN THAT
GIANT CHOCOLATE BAR.
WHERE DID THAT GET TO, HAROLD?
(LAUGHTER)
I DON'T KNOW.
SO MUCH FOR CHOCOLATE NOT
AFFECTING YOUR COMPLEXION,
EH, HAROLD?
OH, OKAY. WHAT ABOUT YOU?
I THOUGHT THE SWITZERLAND DEAL
WAS A DONE SALE, HUH?
HOW'D YOU WRECK THAT?
YOU SHOULDA JUST LET
ME TALK TO THEM.
NO, NO, HAROLD, I
DON'T THINK YOU'D
HAVE UNDERSTOOD
THEIR ACCENT.
IT'S LIKE A
FOREIGN LANGUAGE.
IT IS A FOREIGN LANGUAGE,
IT'S GERMAN.
YOU DON'T SPEAK GERMAN.
WELL, I FIGURED IF YOU SPEAK
ENGLISH LOUD ENOUGH,
EVENTUALLY THEY'LL
FIGURE IT OUT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, WHAT HAPPENED
THERE WAS THE CREATIVE
DIFFERENCES BROUGHT THE
DEAL TO ITS KNEES, HAROLD.
THEY WANTED ME TO
ADD STUFF TO THE SHOW...
ALPENHORNS
AND LEDERHOSEN.
THEY ASKED ME
TO "SWISH IT UP."
I DIDN'T LIKE THE
SOUND OF THAT.
YOU SURE THEY DIDN'T
SAY, "SWISS IT UP?"
AND LEDERHOSEN ARE
JUST LEATHER PANTS.
MAYBE THEY WANTED IT TO LOOK
MORE LIKE SWITZERLAND,
SO IT CAN REFLECT THEIR
AUDIENCE, AND, THAT WAY,
THEY'D BE BE ATTRACTED
TO THE SHOW.
OKAY, SO WHAT YOU'RE SAYING IS
THEY WANT ME TO CHANGE WHO
I AM; WHAT I STAND FOR; AND
WHAT I BELIEVE IN.
YES, BUT FOR MONEY.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, I'LL JUST GO AND GET
MY LOOFA OUT OF MY SAUNA.
NO, NO, SEE,
THAT'S SWEDEN.
IN MY VOLVO.
BUCK NAKED.
FRANCE.
AH, I GIVE UP.
NOPE, THAT'S ITALY.
(APPLAUSE)
HEY! WELCOME.
IT'S "THE POSSUM LODGE
WORD GAME."
YOU KNOW, EVERYBODY DREAMS OF A
TWO-WEEK VACATION IN HAWAII.
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE THAN
JUST DREAM ABOUT IT.
NOW YOU CAN SIT DOWN AND PLAN IT
OUT ON YOUR BRAND NEW
PAD OF PAPER.
(APPLAUSE)
PAD OF PAPER SUPPLIED BY
STAPLES AND SUCH, YOUR
PAD OF PAPER PEOPLE.
AND, NOW, UNCLE RED, TODAY
YOU'LL BE PLAYING WITH
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
WHERE OUR MOTTO IS, "SERVICE
WITH A SMILE, EVEN ON HOT DAYS."
OKAY.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET Mr. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
TO SAY THIS WORD:
ARTIFICIAL.
AND GO.
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON,
WHEN SOMETHING
IS FAKE, IT'S...
WRESTLING.
SOME PRODUCTS ARE
ALL-NATURAL,
YOU KNOW, FULL,
REAL FLAVOURS.
OTHERS ARE...
TASTY?
NO, NO, PLASTIC, SYNTHETIC...
OH, MY GOOD SUIT.
WAIT A SECOND.
WRESTLING IS FAKE?
SHUT UP.
OKAY, WHEN SOMEONE PRETENDS TO
LIKE A PERSON, BUT THEY DON'T
REALLY LIKE THAT PERSON,
THEY ARE...
AN EMPLOYEE.
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
OKAY, SOMEBODY WHO
IS ALWAYS INSINCERE IS...
GEARED FOR SUCCESS.
RUNNIN' OUT OF TIME.
I KNOW, I KNOW. WINSTON, YOU
REMEMBER YOU DATED THAT
CHEERLEADER,
THE ONE WITH THE
GREAT FIGURE?
ARTIFICIAL.
(BELL RINGING)
KIND OF A FUN DAY ON
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL" THIS
TIME.
BILL'S GOT THE YO-YO THERE.
BRINGS BACK A LOT OF MEMORIES
BACK IN OUR CHILDHOOD,
YOU KNOW... THE YO-YOS.
KIDS, IF YOU SEE ANYBODY IN
THE PARK DOING THIS, KEEP
YOUR DISTANCE, ALL RIGHT?
ANYWAY, BACK WHEN WE
WERE YOUNG --
GOT A BIT OF A YO-YO RANCH IN
HIS PANTS, I GUESS.
NO, I'M GOING TO
USE THIS ONE, BILL.
YEAH, I REMEMBER THEY USED TO
HAVE COMPETITIONS, DIDN'T THEY?
AND EVERYBODY WOULD COME AROUND
AND TRY THE TRICKS.
(GLASS BREAKING)
NOW, THAT'S A TRICK.
AND HE'S BACK TO
THE DRAWING BOARD,
AND HE'S GOT NOTHING BUT
YO-YOS DOWN THERE, TRUST ME.
I STILL GOT IT.
IT'S LIKE RIDIN' A YO-YO --
OH, NOW, THAT WOULD...
SEE, I HADN'T SEEN
THAT ONE EITHER.
SEE, HE'S FROM A
DIFFERENT PART OF TOWN,
AND, I GUESS, THEY'VE GOT
THEIR OWN TYPE OF TRICKS.
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
YOU KNOW, I PREFERRED JUST A...
THERE'S ANOTHER ONE, I GUESS.
OH, THAT'S GOOD.
DENTIST RECOMMEND
THAT ONE, BILL?
AROUND THE WORLD AND SNAP.
(CHUCKLING)
OH, COME ON, THAT WAS GREAT.
WHAT'S THIS ONE HERE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, I KNOW THIS ONE.
IT'S CAT'S IN THE
SILVER SPOON --
OH BOY.
MY GRANDMOTHER KNITTED
ONE OF THOSE.
YEAH, THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
TRY SOMETHING ELSE.
OH, I SEE, THAT'S THE BIRTH
CONTROL YO-YO DEAL.
I DON'T LIKE THAT ONE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
OH, YOU'RE PUMPIN' UP
OR SOMETHIN', THERE?
HOLY MACKEREL.
LOOK AT THE SIZE OF THAT UNIT.
I THINK WE HIT OUR
FOOT THERE, DIDN'T WE?
YEAH.
NOW, HERE'S SOMETHING YOU
DON'T SEE TOO OFTEN.
A ROPE WITH A BIG YO-YO
ON EACH END.
ALL RIGHT, BILL, I'M SURE YOU
KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
SO HE'S GOING TO FIRE
THIS THING OFF THE VAN,
AND SHE ROLLS DOWN, EXACTLY THE
SAME PRINCIPLE AS THE YO-YO,
THE PRINCIPLE OF YO.
AND THEN HE'S GOING TO LET
HER ROLL OUT, AND WHEN IT
GETS TO THE END,
GIVE IT A YANK.
YANK IT. YANK IT.
THERE YOU GO.
FEEL THE TENSION.
HERE SHE COMES, BILL.
YOU GOT IT?
IS THAT IT THEN?
ALL RIGHT, BILL.
SEE YOU BACK AT THE LODGE.
WAIT A MINUTE,
BETTER DRIVE SAFELY.
(YODELING)
LITTLE OL' LADY O-O-O-H.
O-O-O-O-O-H!
OH, HI.
ALL RIGHT, WHATEVER, HAROLD.
GOOEY ALMOND MINOR DAMNIT
AND HAIRY END.
DAMMEN UND HERREN.
(ACCORDION SQUEALS)
GESUNDHEIT.
HALLO, HAROLD.
HALLO MEIN ONKEL, ROTE GROENE.
WIE GETZ ES EINEN?
GESUNDHEIT, HAROLD.
WE ALSO HAVE A BRAND NEW
CHARACTER, FRITZ, THE
SWISS CUCKOO CLOCK.
HALLO, FRITZ.
SAY HALLO, FRITZ.
COME ON, FRITZ.
I DON'T THINK HE'S
SUPPOSED TO DO THAT.
WELL, THE NAME FRITZ
IS MAKING MORE SENSE.
WELCOME TO THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
"IF IT AIN'T BROKE
YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
HAP SHAUGHNESSY HAS BROUGHT
SOMETHING IN FOR US TO FIX.
WHAT YOU GOT THERE, HAP?
WELL, I GOT AN OLD
HOCKEY STICK HERE,
AND THE TAPE'S COMIN' OFF.
I WAS HOPIN' YOU'D BE
ABLE TO FIX IT FOR ME.
WELL, SURE.
TO FIX TAPE, NOW, I RECOMMEND...
TAPE.
JUST THROW HER IN
THE VISE THERE.
HEY, NO, NO, NO.
I'D BE CAREFUL THERE, RED.
DON'T WANT YOU TO
SCUFF BOWER'S AUTOGRAPH.
MAN, YOU GOT JOHNNY BOWER'S
AUTOGRAPH ON THERE.
YEAH, I GOT ALL
THEIR AUTOGRAPHS.
DAVE KEON, FRANK MAHOVLICH,
GEORGE ARMSTRONG...
YEP, THE WHOLE 1967
STANLEY CUP WINNING TEAM.
GOT EVERYONE ON
THE TEAM.
BOBBY BAUN.
HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
YEP, GOT 'EM ALL.
YOU -- YOU PLAYED ON THE
'67 LEAFS, DID YOU, HAP?
WELL, YEAH.
OKAY, WHAT WAS YOUR NUMBER?
SEVEN.
NO, NO, I THINK
TIM HORTON WORE NUMBER SEVEN.
OH, OH, YOU MEAN WHAT
NUMBER WAS I WEARING?
YEAH.
OH, I THOUGHT YOU MEANT WHAT
NUMBER WAS I IN SCORING.
I WAS NUMBER SEVEN
IN SCORING
BUT NUMBER THREE
IN ASSISTS.
OH YEAH.
NOT SELFISH,
THAT WAS MY STYLE.
NO, WHAT I'M SAYING IS WHAT WAS
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SWEATER?
ON MY SWEATER?
YEAH.
YOU MEAN JERSEY,
DON'T YOU, RED?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
ON YOUR JERSEY, ALL RIGHT?
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE NOT THE FIRST
ONE TO MAKE THAT MISTAKE.
CALLING A JERSEY A SWEATER,
LOTS OF PEOPLE MAKE
THAT MISTAKE.
OKAY, OKAY, AND
SO WHAT WAS THE NUMBER?
OH, 100s, 100s, RED. IT'S AN
EASY MISTAKE TO MAKE.
NO, NO, NO.
WHAT I'M SAYING IS...
WHAT WAS THE NUMBER ON
YOUR JERSEY
WHEN YOU PLAYED FOR
THE 1967 STANLEY CUP WINNING
TORONTO MAPLE LEAF HOCKEY TEAM?
THIRTEEN.
NO, SEE, THAT'S ODD.
I DON'T REMEMBER THERE
BEING A 13 ON THAT TEAM.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
TO THE MEMORY, RED.
NOW, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BE ASHAMED OF THAT.
THE TRUTH CAN SOMETIMES GET
HIDDEN, YOU KNOW?
OH, SHE'S NOT HIDDEN,
SHE'S GONE.
YOU SEE, YOU SEE,
THAT'S WHY YOU COULD
NEVER BE A MAPLE LEAF.
UH-HUH.
YOU'RE NOT A TEAM PLAYER, RED.
YOU COULD NEVER PULL
TOGETHER LIKE WE DID.
30 GUYS SHARING THE
SAME DRESSING ROOMS,
THE SAME SHOWERS;
THE SAME VICTORIES,
THE SAME DEFEATS.
SAME HANDWRITING.
I TAUGHT THEM ALL
HOW TO WRITE.
(APPLAUSE)
EIN PROSIT, EIN PROSIT
DER GEMUTLICHTKEIT.
(COUGHING)
READY FOR ANOTHER BEER
THERE, HAROLD?
IT'S APPLE JUICE.
IT'S THAT ADDED VITAMIN C THAT
GIVES IT THE KICK, BABY.
WELL, WE'VE HIT KIND
OF A STAND-OFF ON OUR
SWITZERLAND SALE, HERE.
TURNS OUT THE GUY WHO BOUGHT
IT DIDN'T SPEAK ENGLISH,
AND ONCE THEY TRANSLATED IT,
AND HE FIGURED OUT WHAT WE
WERE TALKING ABOUT,
HE CHANGED HIS MIND.
OH, NO, THEY
CANCELLED THE SHOW?
ARE YOU SURE?
OH, YEAH,
IT'S DEAD, HAROLD.
I HEARD THE WORDS
"STOP PAYMENT",
AND THESE ARE GUYS THAT KNOW
ABOUT BANKIN', BELIEVE ME.
OH, THAT IS SO DISAPPOINTING.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO NOW?
WELL, WE'LL DO WHAT
WE ALWAYS DO,
EXCEPT WE CAN STOP DOIN'
IT IN COWHIDE HOTPANTS.
WELL, THAT'S THE
GOOD PART, ISN'T IT?
I WAS A LITTLE BIT WORRIED ABOUT
GOIN' TO SCHOOL -- WHAT THE KIDS
ARE GOING TO SAY ABOUT ME,
YOU KNOW, WHEN THEY SAW ME ALL
DRESSED UP IN MY SWISS
OUTFIT, HERE.
MAKES ME LOOK SO NEUTRAL.
(PIG SQUEALING)
IT'S MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A
MINUTE, ALL RIGHT?
OKAY.
MY WIFE IS WATCHING, AND I'LL
BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I THOUGHT, MAYBE, WE COULD
PRETEND WE WERE SWISS TONIGHT...
YOU BE HEI AND I'LL BE SEEKY.
AND THANKS TO THE REST OF YOU
FOR WATCHING, AND ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD AND THE WHOLE
GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
(APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
COMMUNICAPTION CANADA, INC.]
Harold:  HURRY UP, SIT DOWN...
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red:  SIT DOWN.
OKAY, I'VE GOT SOME
ANNOUNCEMENTS...
THE FIRST ONE IS:  TO HELP THE
LODGE, KEEP IT NEAT AND TIDY,
WE'LL BE POSTING A JOB LIST ON
THE MAIN BULLETIN BOARD IN
THE KITCHEN --
AS SOON AS SOMEONE VOLUNTEERS TO
MAKE UP A JOB LIST AND TO PUT UP
A BULLETIN BOARD,
AND, OF COURSE,
TO PUT UP A KITCHEN...