[dog whimpering]
[man crying]
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S A MAN WHO'S ALWAYS FUN
TO GET UP CLOSE
AND PERSONAL WITH,
ESPECIALLY AFTER BATH NIGHT,
YOUR HOST, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
[applause]
WHOOOO!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THE WHOLE POSSUM LAKE AREA'S
IN A FLAP OVER... WHO GOT LOST?
SCOTTIE.
YEAH, RIGHT, SCOTTIE.
SOME 3-YEAR-OLD NAMED SCOTTIE
WENT INTO THE WOODS
AND -- SURPRISE, SURPRISE --
GOT LOST.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO RUN OUT
AND LOOK FOR HIM.
COME ON, THINK ABOUT IT --
POOR LITTLE SCOTTIE
IN THE WOODS--
OH, COME ON, HAROLD.
THE KID'S 3 YEARS OLD.
LET HIM TOUGH IT OUT, HUH?
WHEN I WAS A KID,
WE'D WALK FIVE MILES TO SCHOOL.
WE DROPPED OUT,
BUT WE WOULD HAVE WALKED.
I SAY LET SCOTTIE DUKE IT OUT
WITH SOME WOLVERINE
FOR CAVE SPACE, THERE.
BUT, UNCLE RED--
MAKE A MAN OF HIM.
PROBABLY RUN ON ALL FOURS.
SCOTTIE IS A DOG.
WHAT?
A DOG.
LITTLE
SCOTCH TERRIER.
A LITTLE SCOTTIE DOG?
THE BLACK MOUSTACHE
AND PERKY EARS
AND YOU CAN'T SEE THE LEGS?
THAT'S SCOTTIE.
WE GOT A LOST DOG TO LOOK FOR!
COME ON, LET'S GO!
[horns honking]
[geese honking]
[quacking]
(Red): TODAY,
HAROLD MAKES HIMSELF
EVEN GEEKIER THAN USUAL,
RANGER GORD TURNS HIS BRAIN
INTO A COMPUTER...
OH, BOY.
WE GOT WINSTON WITH
A LITTLE SCARY ADVICE,
AND HAP IS LYING FOR ALL
HE'S WORTH, WHICH AIN'T MUCH.
A DOG WILL TREAT YOU BETTER
THAN ANY HUMAN WILL.
THAT'S WHY WE GOTTA RESCUE
THAT TERRIER.
YOU CAN TRUST A DOG.
A DOG WON'T LIE TO YOU.
DOG WON'T STEAL YOUR CAR.
EXCEPT THAT DOG
MOOSE THOMPSON HAD.
THAT WAS MOOSE'S FAULT.
COCKER SPANIELS ARE SMART.
TEACHING IT TO FETCH
THE CAR KEYS,
IT WAS ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
TILL THE DOG
PUT TWO AND TWO TOGETHER.
NO, SIR, WE OWE IT
TO EVERY DOG
TO GO AND RESCUE SCOTTIE.
WE OWE OURSELVES
THE $200 REWARD FOR SCOTTIE.
SCOTTIE'S OWNERS
ARE REALLY RICH.
EVERYBODY AND HIS BROTHER'S
OUT IN THE WOODS
LOOKING FOR HIM.
DON'T FORGET,
IT'S POSSUM WOODS.
THAT'S NO WALK IN THE PARK.
NO, THAT'S A WALK IN THE WOODS.
REMEMBER WHEN ME AND YOU USED
TO GO WALKING IN THE WOODS?
WE USED TO GO WALKING
IN THE WOODS,
AND SOMEHOW,
WE'D ALWAYS GET SEPARATED.
HA! REMEMBER THAT?
WOW!
I'D HAVE TO FIND
MY OWN WAY HOME.
BUT I DID IT.
I KEPT COMING BACK.
YEAH, YOU
DID, HAROLD.
I GUESS I'M PART BLOODHOUND.
NOT THE GOOD
PART.
[audience laughing]
(Red): BILL'S GONNA GO LOOKING
FOR THAT LOST DOG
BY MAKING SOME SORT
OF A DIRIGIBLE ZEPPELIN THING.
HE GOT A TANK OF HELIUM
FROM THE LOCAL CIRCUS
OR FLOWER SHOP.
GOT TOO MUCH
FOR THE TABLE, BILL.
THERE YOU GO.
OH, OH, OH!
OH, BY GOLLY.
WOW! WHOA!
THIS MAY TAKE A WHILE.
HELIUM'S LIGHTER THAN AIR.
SORT OF LIKE YOUR BRAIN.
OK, THIS IS THE BIG ONE!
THE GRAND PRIZE IS FROM
MR. ED'S END OF LINE
AND ODD LOTS --
A CASE OF QUEBEC NORDIQUE
HOCKEY UNIFORMS.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. HUMPHREY
TO SAY THIS WORD.
THIRTY SECONDS, AND GO.
UH, ALL RIGHT.
EMOTIONS.
UH, MESSY.
NO, EMOTIONS.
WEIRD.
NO, WHAT'S IN YOUR HEART.
TRIPLE BYPASS.
YOU KNOW, THE STUFF
THAT'S IN THERE.
CHOLESTEROL.
NO, NO, NO.
WHEN SOMEBODY SAYS SOMETHING
MEAN, IT HURTS YOUR...
... CHANCES FOR PROMOTION.
[audience laughing]
THE WAY YOU REACT
TO FRIENDS AND FAMILY...
DEFENCE
MECHANISMS.
YOUR TIME'S ALMOST UP,
UNCLE RED.
THE MOST ANNOYING SONG
EVER WRITTEN.
"FEELINGS"!
[applause]
OH, I CAN SING LOW
AS A BULLFROG
EVEN WHEN
THEY'RE IN HEAT
BUT I CAN'T SING
AS HIGH AS AN EAGLE
BECAUSE THEY SING
AT 20,000 FEET!
A LOT OF FOLKS TRY
TO KEEP DOGS FROM RUNNING AWAY
BY FENCING THEM IN,
TYING THEM UP,
PUTTING THEM ON A LEASH.
THAT WORKS ON HUSBANDS.
THAT IS BACKWARDS THINKING.
TODAY ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW TO KEEP YOUR DOG
FROM RUNNING AWAY
BY TREATING HIM LIKE A GOD.
SEE THE WORDS?
"DOG", "GOD", EH?
THAT'S BACKWARDS SPELLING,
NOT BACKWARDS THINKING.
ALL DOGS LOVE TO EAT.
WHY NOT SERVE FOOD IN SOMETHING
THEY LIKE TO EAT OUT OF?
EVEN THE WORST RESTAURANTS
WILL TELL YOU
PRESENTATION IS EVERYTHING.
DON'T LET HIM EAT
OUT OF THE TOP OF THE CAN.
SNUG THE LID DOWN,
PUNCH A HOLE IN THE BACK.
THE DOG HAS TO WORK A BIT
FOR THE FOOD.
NOT ONLY DOES HE FEED HIMSELF,
HE FEELS LIKE
HE'S DOING SOMETHING NAUGHTY.
SAME THING WITH DRINKING WATER.
PUT THE WATER IN SOMETHING
THE DOG LIKES TO DRINK OUT OF.
WHAT DOG WILL LEAVE HOME
WHEN YOU GOT EVERYTHING HE WANTS
RIGHT HERE?
IT'S KIND OF
A REVERSE PSYCHOLOGY,
EXCEPT YOU DO IT BACKWARDS...
LIKE "GOD" AND "DOG".
IT'S IN THEIR GENES
OR HORMONES.
LIKE THE WAY THEY LIKE
TO CHEW SHOES.
BUY A BUNCH OF SHOES.
YOU CAN GET A PILE FOR ABOUT
FIVE BUCKS AT A YARD SALE.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
"ALL YOU'RE DOING
IS ENCOURAGING
"ALL THE DOG'S BAD HABITS.
"THEY SHOULD SEND HIM
TO OBEDIENCE SCHOOL."
HECK, IF YOU'RE GONNA SPEND
100 BUCKS OR SO,
WHY NOT BUY
A GREAT DOGGY TOY INSTEAD?
DOGS LOVE TO CHASE CARS.
GIVE HIM HIS OWN CAR TO CHASE.
I'VE DUCT-TAPED
THE STEERING WHEEL
IN THE FULL-TURN POSITION.
I DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT THE DOG OR THE CAR
LEAVING THE PROPERTY.
WOULDN'T WANT THIS UNIT ON
THE HIGHWAY WITH NO DRIVER.
IT WILL LOSE A WHEEL DISK.
ALL RIGHT, START HER UP.
DROP HER INTO GEAR
AND SHE'S ON HER WAY.
WITH A TANK OF GAS,
THAT BABY WILL RUN FOR A WEEK.
YOU'RE THINKING, "THE DOG'S GOT
FOOD, WATER, RECREATION --
"HE'S NEVER GONNA LEAVE."
HE MIGHT -- HE NEEDS
ONE MORE THING: ROMANCE.
DOGS GET LONELY.
I THINK IT'S THE MAIN REASON
THEY DO STRAY.
YOUR DOG WILL NEVER LEAVE
IF YOU GOT ONE OF THESE.
LOOK AT THAT.
GET A LEG UP
ON THE COMPETITION.
OR, AS WE SAY AT THE LODGE,
WHY WOULD YOU GO OUT
FOR HAMBURGER
IF YOU GOT POLYESTER AT HOME?
I'M NOT DONE WITH THIS.
I'LL WIRE IN
SOME SOFT LIGHTING,
PUT IN SOME DISCO MUSIC,
A LAVA LAMP,
BUT I'LL GET TO THAT.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
WHERE ARE MY TOOLS?
RIGHT.
STAY TUNED FOR HAROLD
AND HIS MAP.
LOOK HOW DUMB HE LOOKS.
GETTING OLDER MEANS
YOU GOT THE TIME AND MONEY
TO PURSUE THE INTERESTS
YOU'VE PUT OFF
TILL THE KIDS ARE GROWN.
YOU GET YOURSELF A DIRT BIKE
OR A JET SKI
OR ONE OF THEM
FLAMING HANG GLIDERS...
[audience laughing]
THEN THE KIDS START SHOWING UP
AT THE FRONT DOOR
ALL OF A SUDDEN...
AND YOU DON'T WANT TO SHARE,
AND THAT'S FINE.
YOU'RE OLD NOW.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO FEEL GUILTY
ANY MORE.
HERE'S WHAT YOU DO
TO GET RID OF THE KIDS.
USE THE OLD GUY'S
SECRET WEAPON -- BOREDOM.
OH, YEAH, START TALKING
ABOUT THE WEATHER
OR YOUR LATEST OPERATION
OR SOMETHING.
YOU'LL THINK OF SOMETHING --
YOU'RE OLD NOW.
YOU'VE ONLY BEGUN TO TAP IN TO
YOUR POTENTIAL TO BORE PEOPLE.
THE KIDS WILL GO AWAY AND PLAY
A VIDEO GAME OR HOPSCOTCH,
MAYBE KNOCK OVER
A LIQUOR STORE.
YOU GET TO PLAY WITH YOUR TOYS
ALL BY YOURSELF.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
COME IN -- CHECK, ANYONE.
ANYONE, COME IN.
COME IN, ANYONE.
CHECK ONE, HELLO.
COME IN.
YEAH, HAROLD,
IT'S UNCLE RED -- OVER.
OH, EXCELLENT, UNCLE RED,
THAT'S SO GREAT!
YOU'RE COMING IN FIVE BY FIVE.
THAT MEANS LOUD AND CLEAR.
I'LL HAVE A CHEESEBURGER
AND A LARGE FRIES.
SHOULD I DRIVE
TO THE SECOND WINDOW?
[screaming]
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE THERE.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
WITH THE SEARCH PARTY.
THEY JUST LEFT.
SEARCH PARTY LEFT
THREE HOURS AGO.
THE FIRST ONE DID.
THIS PARTY'S LOOKING
FOR THE SEARCH PARTY.
I'VE NARROWED DOWN
THEIR LOCATION.
I'M USING ARMY MEN
TO REPRESENT THE VOLUNTEERS,
BECAUSE KNOWING
IS HALF THE BATTLE.
THEY'RE UP HERE
AT ROCK REEF POINT.
YOU KNOW WHERE THAT
STUDEBAKER'S WEDGED IN?
THEN I GOT NOTICE THEY WERE
GOING SWIMMING AT FOAM FALLS.
THAT'S THE LAST I HEARD OF 'EM,
SO WHAT DID I DO?
I GOT THE SECOND SEARCH PARTY,
WHICH I CALL THE SEARCH PARTY
SEARCH PARTY, OR THE S.P.S.P.,
AND I'VE GOT THEM
AT WORK SOCKS SWAMP.
YOU KNOW WHERE
THE MARSH GAS IGNITES
WHEN CARS GO BY?
NO WORD FROM THEM, EITHER.
YOU CAN TAKE MOOSE THOMPSON
OFF THERE.
HE'S OVER AT MERCURY CREEK
WITH HIS HEAD IN MY TRAP.
IT'S MY FAULT FOR BAITING IT
WITH A PORK CHOP.
WHY DIDN'T YOU USE FOOD
THAT MOOSE WOULDN'T EAT?
SUCH AS WHAT?
ASPHALT?
[laughing and applause]
THE TRICK TO NOT GETTING LOST
IN THE WOODS
IS TO KNOW EVERY SINGLE ROCK
AND TREE IN IT.
TEST ME ON THIS.
OVER THERE,
THERE'S A FALLEN BIRCH LOG,
A ROCK STICKING OUT
OF THE GROUND,
SOME LICHEN MOSS
IN THE SHAPE OF AN "S",
PINE CONES, A TREE
WITH LEAVES ON IT --
32 GREEN LEAVES, ONE YELLOW
LEAF, ONE BROWN LEAF.
BESIDE THAT, THERE'S TWO ROCKS.
BESIDE THAT,
THERE'S A PINE CONE.
WELL, YOU MISSED
A PINE CONE THERE.
ON THE RIGHT-HAND SIDE, THERE.
YOU WERE CLOSE, THOUGH,
VERY CLOSE.
THAT WAS GOOD, YEAH.
MUST HAVE FALLEN
JUST THIS WEEK.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
I'D BETTER ADD THAT
INTO THE OLD COMPUTER.
FOR YOU YOUNG KIDS,
IT'S MY NEW INTELLIVISION.
[beeping and whirring]
[grunting]
[humming]
[whirring]
THERE WE GO.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME CHEESECAKE?
WOW! YOU GOT FOOD HIDDEN
IN THE WOODS?
JUST LIKE A SQUIRREL.
OVER THERE, I'VE GOT
A NICE ROAST OF BEEF.
UP THAT OAK, I'VE GOT
A NICE CAESAR'S SALAD.
ALTHOUGH SQUIRRELS HIDE
THEIR NUTS,
PEOPLE DON'T USUALLY DO THAT.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW, GORD.
NOBODY KNOWS WHERE YOU ARE.
YOU'VE DATED HER
ABOUT FIVE TIMES.
YOU'RE GETTING INTO A NICE,
COMFORTABLE ROUTINE.
PICK HER UP AT 7:00,
BURGERS AT 8:00, HOME BY 11:00.
THEN SHE GOES AND THROWS
A MONKEY INTO THE WRENCH
AND LOOKS AT YOU AND SAYS...
"I LOVE YOU".
[audience laughing]
IT'S FUNNY, ISN'T IT,
HOW THREE LITTLE WORDS
CAN SCARE A MAN?
LIKE "NO MORE BEER".
YEAH.
OR "THAT'S MY HUSBAND!"
[audience laughing]
NONE IS WORSE THAN "I LOVE YOU".
THAT'S THE BIGGIE.
DON'T ANSWER HER,
DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
SHE KNOWS YOU'RE A MAN.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO EXPRESS YOURSELF.
SHE'LL THINK
YOU'RE THE STRONG, SILENT TYPE.
THIS BUYS YOU SOME TIME.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
WHEN A WOMAN SAYS "I LOVE YOU",
COULD MEAN A COUPLE OF THINGS.
SHE MIGHT BE ENDING
THE RELATIONSHIP.
SHE'S TRYING TO FORCE YOU
TO RUN AWAY.
WOMEN WILL SAY "I LOVE YOU"
TO SPARK UP
AN OTHERWISE DEAD-END
RELATIONSHIP, TOO.
MIGHT BE TRYING
TO JUMP-START HER OWN FEELINGS.
RIGHT, OR YOURS.
GO HOME AND
DON'T CALL HER AGAIN.
YEAH.
WHEN A WOMAN SAYS "I LOVE YOU",
THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT
SHE MEANS!
[laughing and applause]
HEY, HANDYMEN, YOU WANT TO MAKE
A STRAIGHT CUT
BUT DON'T HAVE A CHALK LINE?
THIS WORKS JUST AS WELL.
THE OLD RUSTY SAW BLADE.
PERFECT.
[high-pitched voice]:
OH, I FELL OFF!
I CAN'T SWIM!
PUT THOSE PLASTIC
VOLUNTEERS AWAY.
I'M ON THE TRAIL OF THAT DOG.
I'M JUST LOOKING
FOR THE SEARCH PARTIES.
I WISH I KNEW
WHERE OLD MAN SEDGWICK WAS.
HE KNOWS THESE WOODS
BETTER THAN ANYBODY.
HE'S OVER BY MERCURY CREEK.
HE WAS STANDING IN THE TREES,
PANTING LIKE A BEAGLE.
HE'LL NEVER CATCH
THE LOST DOG THAT WAY.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
HE SAID, "WHAT LOST DOG?"
[audience laughing]
I'D TRY OVER BY POSSUM LAKE
SKI AND GOLF CLUB.
SOME OF THE GOLFERS ARE FINDING
SURPRISES IN THE SAND TRAPS.
NO, NO, NO,
UNCLE RED.
YOU CAN'T GO THERE.
REMEMBER THE RESTRAINING ORDER.
I'M NOT GOING THERE.
I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
I'M GONNA RENT
A PAIR OF BAGPIPES.
I'M GONNA PLAY THEM
AND I FIGURE IT'S GONNA LURE--
HEY! HEY, IT'S A SCOTTIE DOG.
I THINK THE BAGPIPES
WILL BRING
THE SCOTTIE DOG--
I WOULDN'T GO NEAR 'EM,
BUT BAGPIPES LURE SCOTTIE DOGS.
[audience laughing]
WELL, UNCLE RED...
[laughing]
I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANY NEED
TO INSULT OUR SCOTTISH VIEWERS.
[laughing and applause]
MAYBE NOT,
BUT IT'S SO MUCH FUN, HAROLD.
WHEN I GET THE BAGPIPES,
I'LL PLAY A POLKA
AND INSULT OUR EUROPEAN VIEWERS
AND HALF OF BUFFALO.
[laughing and applause]
(Red): MEANWHILE,
BACK AT THE HINDENBURG,
BILL HAD ATTACHED --
BEAUTIFUL! --
HELIUM-FILLED BALLOONS
TO THE CHAIR--
BILL, THE LAWN CHAIR.
BILL, IT'S... IT'S... IT'S...
YOU MIGHT WANT TO TIE THAT
TO THE GROUND OR SOMETHING...
WE GOT A HEAVIER CHAIR,
AND MORE BALLOONS.
WHERE DO YOU WANT THIS TIED?
OH!
I DON'T THINK THAT HELPS.
THERE WE GO, THERE WE GO.
THERE'S A SPOT
WITH THE FOOT-REST.
YOU CAN TIE THAT ON THERE.
WE GOT 80, 90, 100, 200, 300...
PROBABLY ABOUT
70, 40 BALLOONS UP THERE.
SHE'S STARTING TO--
OH, HANG ON, BILL.
SHE'S GOING UP.
BILL, DON'T LET--
BILL, YOU'RE-- NO, NO.
YOU WANT TO BE IN THE UNIT
WHEN IT--
BILL, YOU NEED TO BE--
UP YOU GO.
GIVE ME A BOOST.
I'LL GIVE YOU-- YOU GIVE ME--
NO, YOU GIVE ME-- YOU, ME...
OH, FORGET IT.
NOW HE'S GOT A BEANBAG CHAIR.
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
YOU'LL FILL THAT WITH HELIUM?
I GOT BAD NEWS.
WE SEEM TO BE HITTING
AROUND ZERO
ON THE HELIUM SCALE.
NO PROBLEM?
YOU'VE GOT WHAT?
YOU'VE GOT HELIUM IN THERE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
WHAT HAVE WE GOT?
IT'S PROPANE --
THAT'S PROPANE, BILL.
THAT'S NOT HELIUM.
IT'S NOT GOING TO GO UP.
I THINK PROPANE IS
ABOUT THE SAME WEIGHT AS AIR.
IT'S ABOUT THE SAME.
NO, IT'S HEAVIER.
PROPANE IS HEAVIER THAN AIR.
THAT'S RIGHT, YEAH, YEAH.
BILL'S GONNA EMPTY THE BEANBAG.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HE'S GOT IN MIND.
HE'S GONNA EMPTY THAT OUT.
IT'S BEGINNING TO LOOK
A LOT LIKE TROUBLE
ANYWAY, WE FILLED THOSE
BALLOONS WITH THE PROPANE SO...
DANGEROUS, BUT THEY'RE
NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
HOW DO YOU GO UP IN THE AIR?
YOU'VE SOLVED THE PROBLEM
OF FLOATING AWAY--
MATCHES! OH, MATCHES!
OH, MATCHES, YEAH.
I'M LONG GONE,
AND WHO CAN BLAME ME?
YOU'RE GONNA STRIKE THAT UP.
THAT MAKES PERFECT SENSE.
YOU'RE SITTING ON 400 POUNDS
OF PROPANE.
WELL, YOU WERE SITTING ON THAT.
WONDER WHERE HE IS.
OH, HE'S LOOKING GOOD.
I HOPE YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR THE DOG -- YOU MAY NOT BE
UP THERE TOO LONG.
THERE'S THE LAZY-- WHOA!
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES!
[laughing]
WHAT A PLAN.
STAY TUNED AS HAROLD SAYS
NOTHING MAKES ME LAUGH.
HE'S WRONG.
BAGPIPES WORKED, HAROLD.
I CAUGHT THE MISSING DOG.
YOU WERE JUST LUCKY.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR HAND?
WELL, I THOUGHT...
OK, WHAT WOULD LURE
A BOY SCOTTIE DOG
OFF A GOLF COURSE?
YOU KNOW -- DING!
A BELL WENT OFF IN MY HEAD.
DING!
I THOUGHT,
"OK, A GIRL SCOTTIE DOG."
BUT WE DON'T HAVE ONE.
I THOUGHT, "I'LL DISGUISE
MOOSE THOMPSON'S DOG AS ONE."
MOOSE THOMPSON'S DOG
IS A ROTTWEILER.
IS IT EVER!
DIDN'T SEEM TO MIND
WHEN I PUT THE BAY CITY ROLLERS
SCARF ON HIM, OR THE TAM.
I FIGURE THIS KILT WAS
ABOUT A SIZE TWO SMALL.
[audience laughing]
TOUCHY!
OH, BOY, THOSE ROTTWEILERS --
I THINK THEY'RE OVER-BRED.
YOU SHOULD BE SO LUCKY, HAROLD.
TELL YOU WHAT, THOUGH.
I'LL SPLIT THE REWARD WITH YOU.
OH, OK, ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
LIKE, 100 EACH OR SOMETHING?
WELL, YEAH, AFTER EXPENSES.
WE GOTTA SUBTRACT GAS,
SUPPLIES, BEVERAGES,
BAGPIPE RENTAL AND BAGPIPE
REPLACEMENT, OF COURSE.
SO WHAT?
WE BREAK EVEN?
WE WILL IF YOU CHIP IN
15 BUCKS.
THAT'S NOT BAD!
[laughing and applause]
IT'S "MALE CALL"!
[applause and cheering]
HAROLD.
[laughing]
THAT'S LOUD!
OK, HERE'S A LETTER.
FIRST LETTER GOES AS FOLLOWS,
AND IT'S FROM LOUISE LAKE
FROM HELENA.
NO, THAT'S HELENA
FROM LAKE LOUISE.
ALL RIGHT, UM...
"DEAR RED,
WHAT MAKES YOU LAUGH?"
GOOD QUESTION --
NOTHING, THAT'S WHAT.
[laughing]
HE LAUGHS AT ZIP, NADA.
THAT'S NOT TRUE, HAROLD.
I LAUGH AT LOTS OF THINGS.
NAME ONE THING.
NOTHING, THAT'S WHAT --
NOTHING.
[laughing]
I'M NOT LIKE YOU.
YOU GIGGLE AT AIR.
LOTS OF THINGS I LAUGH AT.
WHAT?
MAYBE NOT THAT SO MUCH...
BUT THERE'S OTHER...
YES?
THERE'S OTHER...
THERE'S SOMETHING I LAUGH AT.
NOTHING.
LET ME THINK.
THERE'S NOTHING.
I KNOW!
WHOA!
THAT'S IT!
YEAH, THAT'S IT!
[laughing]
HERE WE ARE
WITH HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
WHAT ARE WE FISHING FOR?
BASS, RED.
THAT'S WHAT THE BIG T.V.
CELEBRITIES LIKE TO FISH FOR.
[laughing]
COME ON, HAP,
I'M NOT A BIG T.V. CELEBRITY.
I DIDN'T MEAN YOU.
I MEAN PEOPLE I MET WHEN I WAS
A HOLLYWOOD DIRECTOR.
NAMES YOU WOULDN'T REMEMBER,
LIKE THAT KID FROM "RAWHIDE".
EASTWOOD, CLINT.
HE DID THAT ONE SHOW
AND DISAPPEARED.
THERE WAS MY OTHER BUDDY
FROM "HARPER", BURT REYNOLDS.
HE HASN'T MADE IT AGAIN
IN T.V. EITHER, POOR KID.
YOU'RE SAYING THAT
BURT REYNOLDS IS YOUR FRIEND?
WELL, THAT'S WHAT HE'D SAY.
I'M NOT SO FOND OF HIM.
I LIKE SALLY, SALLY FIELDS.
YEAH, REMEMBER HER?
YEAH.
"FLYING NUN" -- WHEN T.V. MADE
THE BIG TRANSITION
FROM BLACK AND WHITE TO COLOUR,
SHE COULDN'T CUT IT.
WONDER WHAT HAPPENED TO HER.
YOU'VE NEVER TOLD ME
YOU WERE A DIRECTOR BEFORE.
YEAH, AND A WRITER.
A WRITER?
ON THE SID CAESAR SHOW.
I STILL FISH WITH A COUPLE
OF THOSE OTHER WRITERS.
NEIL SIMON, WOODY ALLEN.
THEY DON'T DO T.V. EITHER
ANY MORE.
NONE OF US DO.
CLINT, BURT, SALLY, NEIL,
WOODY, OR ME.
WE STILL GO FISHING
EVERY SPRING.
YOU EVER BEEN ON THAT OLD GAME
SHOW "TO TELL THE TRUTH"?
HMM?
THAT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME.
WELL...
HERE'S A PICTURE TAKEN
LAST SPRING.
NOW, HOW DO YOU ACCOUNT
FOR THAT?
SHE LOOKS LIKE A BIT
OF A PASTE-UP, HAP.
BURT'S HEAD IS THE SAME SIZE
AS WOODY'S WHOLE BODY.
THAT'S PERSPECTIVE.
BURT IS CLOSER.
HOW COME YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
IN COLOUR?
EVERYBODY ELSE
IS IN BLACK AND WHITE.
I TOLD YOU, RED.
NONE OF THEM MADE
THE BIG TRANSITION TO COLOUR.
CAN'T BE HARDER THAN
THE BIG TRANSITION TO REALITY.
RAN INTO A BIT OF A WRINKLE
WITH THE LOST-DOG FIASCO.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE,
HAROLD?
A DOG.
A SCOTTIE DOG.
THE SCOTTIE DOG THAT HAS
A $200 REWARD ON HIS HEAD.
WAH-HAHH!
DON'T BE SO SURE
THAT'S THE DOG.
EVERYBODY'S FINDING THEM.
BUSTER HADFIELD DID,
STINKY PETERSON DID.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK
EVEN FOUND ONE.
THEY ALL LOOK
LIKE SCOTTIE?
EXCEPT OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S --
IT WAS A SKUNK.
BUT WE ALL LOSE, HAROLD.
THE REAL SCOTTIE DOG
RAN HOME TO HIS OWNERS,
SCARED OFF
BY ALL THE GUYS
WITH THE CAMP SONGS
AND MUD-WRESTLING
AND EXPLODING CATS AND SO ON.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
HOW DO WE GET THESE DOGS
BACK TO THEIR OWNERS?
IT'S JUST ONE OWNER, HAROLD --
A SCOTTIE DOG BREEDER.
HE'S COMING OVER NOW.
ALL THESE DOGS
FROM ONE PLACE, HUH?
SOMEBODY HAD TO GO THERE
AND OPEN THEIR CAGES.
YEAH, WELL, MORE LIKELY--
THAT'S PROBABLY-- MAKES SENSE--
[possum squeal]
MEETING TIME -- AWAY YOU GO.
AWAY YOU GO -- OFF YOU GO.
UNCLE RED, I AM
SO DISAPPOINTED IN YOU.
WELL, THEN, WE'RE EVEN.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
IF YOU FIND A BLACK HAIR
UNDER MY SHIRT,
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
IT'S JUST PUPPY LOVE.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF HAROLD AND MYSELF
AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
WAVE -- YOU WAVE, TOO.
YOU WAVE --
WAVE TO THOSE PEOPLE.
WAVE TO THE NICE PEOPLE.
[possum squeal]
(Harold): ALL RISE, ALL RISE!
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW...