IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW!"
AND NOW HERE'S THE MAN
WHO LAUGHS AT LIFE,
BUT THE FEELING'S
MUTUAL...
YOUR HERO,
YOUR HOST,
MY UNCLE,
RED GR-E-E-E-N!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
ALL RIGHT. BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE OUR SECOND
ANNUAL SWAMP SKIING COMPETITION.
YEAH, THE WAY THAT WORKS IS WE
GET A GUY WATER SKIING,
WE GO DOWN TO THE BOGGY
END OF THE LAKE THERE,
AND WE CRANK THE BOAT AROUND,
AND THE GUY FIRES INTO
THE SWAMP AREA THERE,
AND WE JUST SEE IF HE CAN
COME OUT THE OTHER SIDE.
I DON'T KNOW, UNCLE RED.
I DON'T KNOW IF THERE'S GOING TO
BE ANY SWAMP SKIING THIS YEAR.
OH, REALLY?
OH, YES, REALLY, 'CAUSE YOU
NEVER GO, DO YOU?
OH, NO, NOT YOU.
YOU JUST SIT IN THE BACK OF
THE BOAT AND LAUGH AT EVERYBODY.
COME ON, HAROLD,
I'VE JUST GOT A GOOD SENSE
OF HUMOUR, THAT'S ALL.
OH, NO, NO, NO, ALL THE GUYS SAY
THEY'RE NOT GOING UNLESS YOU GO
'CAUSE LAST YEAR EVERYBODY
GOT ALL DRAGGED THROUGH
THE SMELLY BOG.
THEY GOT ALL WHIPPED IN THE
FACE WITH THESE STICKS AND
BUSHES AND TWIGS AND STUFF,
AND THEY GOT SLAPPED
OUT THE OTHER END,
AND THEY HAD A FACE FULL OF
MUD AND A MOUTHFUL OF ALGAE.
TOOK TWO WEEKS FOR THE FAT GUYS
TO PRY THE BULRUSHES OUT OF
THEIR BELLY BUTTONS.
I DON'T CARE WHAT
THE WHINERS SAY, HAROLD.
THE SWAMP SKIING
COMPETITION IS A GO.
WE'VE DECIDED.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
'WE'VE' DECIDED?
'YOU' DECIDED.
WELL, THE LODGE -- ME/WE,
IT'S ALL THE SAME.
NO, SEE, THAT'S JUST IT.
NO, IT'S NOT ALL THE SAME.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
SEE, YOU'VE GOT TO BE CAREFUL
NOT TO FORCE PEOPLE INTO THINGS
THAT YOU WANT TO DO.
SOMETIMES YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE
IN TO A HIGHER AUTHORITY.
NOT AT THE LODGE, HAROLD.
I ONLY DO THAT AT HOME.
(APPLAUSE)
[♪♪♪]
TODAY'S SHOW IS
ALL ABOUT ESCAPING.
WE'VE GOT HAP HERE WHO
ESCAPES INTO HIS IMAGINATION;
WE'VE GOT BILL WHO ESCAPES
INTO A TREE...
SOMETIMES;
AND I'M ESCAPING INTO
A LITTLE FREEZER DEN.
MORE ABOUT THAT LATER ON.
WELL, THE SWAMP
SKIING PREPARATION HAS
OFFICIALLY STARTED.
JUST GET THE LODGE MEMBERS
TO SIGN UP, AND THEN WE'LL
SET THE DATE ONCE WE KNOW
WHEN THERE'S GOING TO BE
A DOCTOR VACATIONING
IN THE AREA.
COME ON, HAROLD, WE'VE GOT
A SHOW TO DO HERE.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, SORRY,
UNCLE RED, SORRY.
I WAS JUST OUTSIDE TALKING
TO JUNIOR SINGLETON.
YOU KNOW, HE'S PRETTY
UPSET WITH YOU, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE OF THE WAY, YOU KNOW,
HAVE TO RUN THINGS AROUND HERE.
HE'S VERY UPSET
ABOUT THAT.
HE WANTS TO GET
TOGETHER AND TALK.
BRING HIM IN RIGHT NOW.
WE'LL TALK HERE.
OH, NO, NO, I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T CLARIFY THAT.
WHEN HE WANTS TO GET TOGETHER
AND TALK, YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU SPEAK --
WHEN THEY TALK LIKE THAT --
WHEN HE SAID 'WE'
GET TOGETHER,
HE MEANT WE;
NOT WE.
LIKE ME AND HE;
NOT YOU.
OH, SO YOU'RE GOING TO
BE MEETING WITH JUNIOR.
YES, YES, JUST JUNIOR AND ME --
JUST JUNIOR AND ME...
AND ABOUT FIVE OTHER OF THE
LODGE MEMBERS, MAYBE 10.
WHAT'S THIS
ABOUT, HAROLD?
WELL, YOU ALWAYS GET A SAY
IN WHAT GOES ON AROUND HERE.
YOU KNOW, SOME OTHER PEOPLE
HAVE GOT SOME IDEAS TOO,
AND SOME PRETTY DARN
GOOD ONES SOMETIMES.
BUT YOU ALWAYS
SAY NO, RIGHT?
NO.
SEE, SEE, SEE!
JUST LIKE THAT.
WHAT ABOUT THAT TIME WE WANTED
TO GET LODGE JACKETS,
AND YOU SAID NO?
WHAT ABOUT THAT TIME ALL THE
GUYS WANTED TO GO TO PORT
ASBESTOS AND SEE THE NEW
ASPHALT SPREADER,
AND YOU SAID NO.
WHAT ABOUT THE TIME WE WANTED
TO GET SNACKS WITH BETTER
EXPIRY DATES?
YOU SAID NO.
WELL, JUNIOR GOT THINKING.
HE'S TIRED OF HEARING
YOU SAY NO,
AND MAYBE HE HAS
AN IDEA THAT --
JUNIOR HAD THIS REALLY --
THIS IS MORE JUNIOR
SPEAKING THAN ME.
YEAH.
JUST I'M CHANNELING
AT THIS MINUTE.
HE'S THINKING OF STARTING
UP A RIVAL LODGE,
AND A LOT OF THE POSSUM
LODGE MEMBERS ARE GOING
TO GO WITH HIM.
WELL, GOOD FOR JUNIOR.
REALLY?
YEAH.
CAN WE HAVE OUR
FIRST MEETING HERE?
NO.
OKAY.
♪ OH, YOU'VE GOT YOUR BOOK,
YOU HEAR THE KNOCK ♪
♪ BUT YOU DON'T CARE,
THE DOOR IS LOCKED ♪
♪ LET THEM POUND AND YELL
AND SCREAM AND SHOUT ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WHAT THEY WANT,
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY NEED, ♪
♪ BUT YOU GOT THERE FIRST
WITH SOMETHING TO READ ♪
♪ AND THEY WILL JUST HAVE
TO LEARN TO DO WITHOUT ♪
♪ THE JOHN IS THE ONLY
PLACE  WHERE A MAN CAN
PUT UP HIS FEET ♪
♪ AND TURN ON THE FAN
AND READ A BOOK ♪
♪ AND KNOW WHAT IT'S
ACTUALLY ABOUT ♪
♪ OH, BUT DON'T LET IT GO
TO THE BITTER END ♪
♪ BECAUSE EVERY FIVE MINUTES,
YOU LOSE ANOTHER FRIEND ♪
♪ AND THEY'LL ALL BE WAITING
TO KILL YOU WHEN YOU
FINALLY COME OUT ♪♪
IT'S THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
THIS WEEK Mr. MIKE HAMAR IS
PLAYING FOR THE GRAND PRIZE
OF HAVING HIS CHARGES COMMUTED
TO 30 DAYS OF COMMUNITY SERVICE.
YEAH, YEAH.
GOOD LUCK, MIKE.
ALL RIGHTY, MIKE, YOU HAVE 30
SECONDS TO GUESS THIS WORD
AND --
YOU'RE PEEKING.
DON'T BE PEEKING.
KNOW WHAT, THE WORD IS CHEATER.
CHEATER.
GO.
30 SECONDS, GO.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE, THERE IS
SOMETHING --
CHEATER?
(LAUGHTER)
OKAY, MIKE, YOU PUT A LOT OF
TIME AND WORK INTO THIS,
BUT IT PAYS OFF MONEY
IN THE LONG RUN.
A BANK ROBBERY?
NO, NO, NO,
YOU ALREADY HAVE MONEY.
NO, I DON'T.
WELL, JUST IMAGINE
THAT YOU DO, OKAY?
SO YOU NEED TO MAKE A...
QUICK GET AWAY.
NO, MIKE, THIS ISN'T
MONEY FROM A ROBBERY.
YOU EARNED IT.
OH, LIKE A REWARD WHEN YOU
SQUEAL ON A GUY, RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
SO YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOU HAVE THAT MONEY
WHEN YOU GET OLDER,
SO YOU NEED TO FIND A GOOD...
HANDGUN.
(LAUGHTER)
MIKE, YOU'RE ON PAROLE, OKAY?
YOU CAN'T USE A HANDGUN.
NO, NO, NO, I WOULDN'T
USE IT, Mr. GREEN.
IT'S SORT OF AN INVESTMENT.
OH, BOY!
(FRANTIC BELL RINGING)
YOU KNOW, EVERY MAN NEEDS
A PLACE HE CAN GO TO IN
HIS OWN HOME,
KIND OF A REFUGE WHERE HE
CAN BE ALONE TO DO WHAT
HE ENJOYS THE MOST,
AND WHAT HE DOES THE BEST...
NOTHING.
NO TALKING, NO SHARING,
NO MOVING, NO THINKING.
NOW, SOME GUYS, THEY HAVE A DEN
OR MAYBE A BASEMENT WORKSHOP.
SOME HAVE A GARAGE OR
EVEN A BARN THEY CAN GO TO.
BUT THIS WEEK ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'VE GOT A PROJECT FOR THE
MAN WHO HAS ABSOLUTELY
NO SPACE AT ALL.
EVER NOTICE HOW LAZY PEOPLE
LIVE IN SMALL HOUSES?
THAT'S BECAUSE YOU DON'T NEED
MUCH SPACE WHEN YOU'RE
NOT DOING ANYTHING.
YOU DON'T NEED A WHOLE
ROOM TO GO TO.
ALL YOU NEED IS
AN OLD FREEZER, HUH?
WOULDN'T THAT BE A GREAT
SPOT TO GO TO TO COOL OFF?
YOU GET ENOUGH
ACCESSORIES IN THERE,
AND YOU CAN TURN THIS UNIT
INTO THE DEN OF YOUR DREAMS.
YOU KNOW, CARPENTERS HAVE A
VERY IMPORTANT SAYING...
MEASURE TWICE, CUT ONCE.
THAT'S A GOOD THEORY, ISN'T IT?
YOU'VE NEVER ACTUALLY
DONE IT, HAVE YOU?
WELL, THIS IS NO TIME TO START
BECAUSE THIS IS AN
AIR-TIGHT FREEZER HERE.
IF ALL OF YOUR CUTS
ARE ACCURATE, AND YOUR
MEASUREMENT IS CORRECT,
IT COULD KILL YOU.
SO THROW THAT CUT AWAY.
ALL RIGHT. WHAT YOU WANT TO
DO IS YOU WANT TO CUT A
HOLE YAY BY YAY,
MAYBE A LITTLE MORE YAY
THIS WAY THAN THAT.
ALL RIGHT. THE FIRST THING YOU
WANT TO DO IS DRILL A HOLE IN
THE SIDE OF THE FREEZER,
SO YOU CAN CUT OUT WHERE
THE T.V. IS GOING TO GO.
NO, NO, NO, THAT'S
THE SECOND THING.
FIRST THING YOU WANT TO DO
IS UNPLUG THE FREEZER.
THERE WE GO.
THAT'S A PERFECT FIT.
REMEMBER: NO GAP, NO AIR.
YOU WANT TO HOLD IT SECURELY
IN PLACE THERE, USING THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
BECAUSE IF YOU DROP YOUR T.V.
INTO YOUR FREEZER, IT'S NOT
COVERED BY EITHER WARRANTY.
ALL RIGHT. ONCE YOU'VE GOT YOUR
T.V. MOUNTED ON THERE,
YOU'VE GOT TO START THINKING
ABOUT BEVERAGES AND SNACKS.
SO GET YOURSELF ONE OF THESE
UNITS HERE, SOMETHING
ALONG THIS LINE.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS
MOUNT THAT ON THE SIDE
OF YOUR FREEZER,
SO THEY'LL FEED DOWN
INTO THE DEN AREA.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE THOSE
ARE MOUNTED ON THERE,
YOU PUT YOUR FAVOURITE BEVERAGE
IN THE COOLER, AND IT GOES
DOWN THE TUBE.
YOU PUT YOUR FAVORITE SNACK
INTO THE DUCT, AND IT
GOES DOWN THE CHUTE.
NOW, WE'VE GOT THIS OLD DUSTPAN
HERE TO CONTROL THE SNACKS,
AND WE'VE GOT THE CLOTHESPEG
ON THERE TO GET THE DRINKS
COMING AND GOING.
NOW, FOR THAT EXTRA
TOUCH OF LUXURY,
I'M GOING TO LINE THE DEN
WITH THE FOAM HERE,
AND THEN COVER ALL THAT
WITH THE SHAG CARPETING.
SO IT WILL KIND OF
BE LIKE A VAN,
BUT NO WOMEN.
SO IT'LL BE LIKE MY VAN.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S GOT IT.
NOW, I'VE GOT TO JUST MAKE
A LITTLE ADJUSTMENT TO
THE DOOR SWITCH HERE.
THAT WAY WHEN I RETIRE TO MY
DEN AND I CLOSE THE DOOR,
THE LIGHT WILL STAY ON.
ALL RIGHT. HERE'S ANOTHER
LITTLE RIG THAT I'VE
ADDED TO HER.
I'VE PUT THESE LEGS
ON THE BACK HERE,
AND THIS ALLOWS THE
WHOLE UNIT TO RECLINE.
SHOW YOU HOW THAT
WORKS IN A MINUTE.
OH, MY GOSH, WRESTLING IS ON.
OKAY. SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW RECLINE.
WOW, IT'S LIKE I'M RIGHT
IN THE WRESTLING RING.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU OLDER
GUYS ABOUT SOMETHING YOU HAVEN'T
DONE IN A WHILE...
CHANGE.
PEOPLE SAY YOU'RE OUT OF IT
BECAUSE FOR THE LAST 20 YEARS,
YOU'VE BEEN DRESSING THE SAME
WAY, TALKING THE SAME WAY AND
THINKING THE SAME WAY.
I SAY, GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU STICK WITH IT.
SOMEBODY'S GOT TO STAND
UP FOR TRADITION.
AND HOLD FIRM BECAUSE
TOO MUCH IS CHANGING.
THE PHONE RINGS WEIRD NOW.
RUNNING SHOES LOOK
LIKE SPACESHIPS,
EVEN THE CONTINENTS
ARE SHIFTING...
BUT NOT YOU.
YOU STICK TO YOUR GUNS.
YOU KEEP WEARING THOSE
SHORT-SLEEVED POLYESTER
DRESS SHIRTS.
YOU KEEP SPOUTING YOUR OPINIONS
TO ANYBODY WHO WILL LISTEN.
SOMEBODY'S GOT TO PRESERVE
WHAT'S NORMAL AND SENSIBLE
IN THIS WORLD.
AND WHO KNOWS?
POLYESTER MIGHT COME BACK.
MAYBE YOUR OPINIONS
WILL CATCH ON,
PEOPLE WILL THINK
YOU'RE A GENIUS.
BUT SO FAR, NO CHANGE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, THE SWAMP SKIING IS
GETTING OFF TO A SLOW START.
I'VE GOT THE BOAT GASSED UP,
AND I'VE GOT THE TOW ROPE ON
THERE READY TO YANK SOMEBODY
INTO THE QUAGMIRE DOWN AT
THE FAR END OF THE LAKE.
BUT SO FAR, I'VE GOT
NO CUSTOMERS.
I CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT.
YOU KNOW, UNCLE RED, I THINK
I KNOW WHY YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO HAVE ANYBODY FOR THE
SWAMP SKIING.
THE GUYS' WIVES ALL
FIND OUT ABOUT IT?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S JUNIOR SINGLETON.
ALL THE GUYS ARE
LISTENING TO HIM NOW.
THERE'S LOYALTY
FOR YOU, HUH?
HAS JUNIOR SINGLETON STARTED
ANOTHER LODGE, HAROLD?
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
VERY MUCH SO.
YEAH, IT'S REALLY COOL.
AND HE SAYS IF WE JOIN --
IF WE JOIN, WE CAN GET,
LIKE, LODGE JACKETS,
YOU KNOW, LIKE, MAYBE THE ONES
THE BASEBALL PLAYERS WEAR,
THOSE SILK ONES THE ROCK
AND ROLL STARS WEAR.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
AND WE'RE GOING TO GET,
LIKE, MEMBERSHIP CARDS.
OH, WE HAVE
MEMBERSHIP CARDS NOW.
YEAH, BUT CHEAPY
PLASTIC ONES.
THESE ARE GOING TO BE LIKE
NICKEL ALLOY WITH MY PICTURE
IN THE HOLOGRAM.
HAROLD, YOUR HEAD IS
ALREADY A HOLOGRAM.
SEE, SEE, JUNIOR WOULDN'T
INSULT ME LIKE THAT.
HE SAYS THAT'S THE POSSUM WAY.
THAT'S SO POSSUM.
THE SALAMANDERS ARE GOING
TO DO THINGS DIFFERENTLY.
SALAMANDERS?
THAT'S THE LODGE?
IT'S CALLED SALAMANDERS?
YEAH, WELL SALAMANDERS
ARE COOL TOO.
UH-HUH.
BUT I'M JUST GOING TO GO
TO THAT FIRST MEETING AND
CHECK IT OUT, THAT'S ALL.
I'M JUST, YOU KNOW,
I'LL CHECK IT OUT.
OH, YEAH.
WHAT IS JUNIOR OFFERING
YOU TO JOIN, HAROLD?
A DIGITAL EDITING SUITE,
AND IT IS SO BEAUTIFUL.
I WOULD HAVE EVERYTHING.
HAROLD, HE'S ONLY TRYING
TO BUY YOUR SUPPORT.
YEAH, I KNOW.
DO YOU WANT TO MAKE
A COUNTER OFFER?
I'M A FREE AGENT.
HAROLD, YOU'RE
A FREE WILLY.
WELL, THIS WEEK, WE'RE GOING
BACK TO WHEN WE WERE JUST
KIDS AGAIN.
KIND OF A LAUGH.
I'VE GOT TO GO THROUGH
PUBERTY AGAIN.
OH, BY GOLLY, GOOD START.
GOOD START.
YEP, BILL WANTS TO BUILD
A TREE FORT UP IN THE TREE.
WE'VE GOT THE TREE, AND WE'VE
GOT THE WOOD FOR IT.
BILL, I DON'T THINK YOU'RE
GOING TO BE ABLE TO --
OH, HE'S GOT AN IDEA.
HE'S GOT AN IDEA.
HE'S GOING TO
CLIMB UP ON ME.
I THINK I SAW SOMETHING
LIKE THIS IN ONE OF THOSE
MOVIES ONE TIME.
NO, NO, NO, NO, SORRY.
YEAH, SO HE'S STANDING.
HE'S A HEAVY LITTLE
FELLOW, ALL RIGHT.
HE'S UP.
FINALLY HE'S UP.
I CAN RELAX.
THERE, I LOOK RELAXED.
ALL RIGHT, BILL.
GOT ANOTHER PLAN
TO GET UP THE TREE?
WE DON'T HAVE A
LADDER OR ANYTHING.
BILL, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO, BILL?
ANOTHER IDEA?
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE THAT
2x4 UP AGAINST THE TREE,
AND THEN WHAT?
OH, HE'S GOING TO --
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
HE'S GOING TO MAKE STEPS --
GOING TO CUT IT UP
AND MAKE STEPS.
THERE WE GO.
THERE WE GO,
A SERIES OF STEPS.
OH, OH, MY GOLLY.
ALL RIGHT, BILL, NOW, THIS IS
SOMETHING YOU YOUNGSTERS
CAN PAY ATTENTION TO.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU HAVE BUDGET CUTS.
THAT'S JUST DUMB.
ALL RIGHT. OKAY, OKAY,
THE HIPPETY-HOPPETY.
THERE HE IS.
HE'S UP THE TREE.
OH, MY GOD...
THERE'S THE HAMMER, BILL
BILL, YEAH. SORRY.
LATER THAT DAY, WE'RE
HANDING WOOD UP TO BILL,
AND THESE HAVE ALL BEEN
PRE-CUT TO THE WIDTHS OF
THE TREE FORT HE WANTS,
AND HE'S PUTTING THE SPIKES
TO HIS MOUTH,
STOP HIM FROM TALKING A
LITTLE BIT THERE,
AND START DRIVING.
REALLY DRIVE THAT.
DRIVE THAT.
OH, OH, OH.
OW, OW, OH, OH.
I DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT THE WIND.
ALL RIGHT. SO HE'S KIND
OF CHEWING AND LEANING,
KIND OF PREOCCUPIED.
HE'S CHEWING.
BILL YOU'RE CHEWING
ON THE NAILS.
BILL, YOU'RE
CHEWING ON THE NAILS.
BILL, BILL, YOU'VE EATEN THEM.
THEY'RE GONE.
YOU'VE EATEN THEM.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, THERE.
GETTING A LITTLE IRON IN
THE DIET THERE, ARE WE, BILL?
OH, MY GOSH, COUGHED
UP A NAIL, HUH?
THAT WAS A PARTY --
OH, OH, WELL,
BY GOLLY, I LIKE THIS.
A BOWL OF CHILI AND A CAN OF
NAILS, YOU CAN BUILD A COTTAGE.
OW!
ALL RIGHT, HE'S GOT THE THING
DONE, AND THERE HE'S GOT HIS
PLATFORM AND HE'S ALL SET.
LOOK AT HIM.
THERE'S THE PRIDE OF OWNERSHIP
RIGHT THERE, SITTING THERE.
BILL, OH, OH, OH, OH,
OH, BY GOLLY, IT'S A KIND OF
AMBISWINGSTROUS KIND OF
A TREE FORT.
THE BRANCH IS LETTING GO.
THAT'S GOING TO LEAVE A MARK.
WELL, LET'S SEE IF
THE SAP IS RUNNING.
OH, IT'S MORE OF AN OOZE,
KIND OF AN OOZE.
WHERE'S YOUR NECK?
OH, THERE IT IS.
YOU'RE GOING
TO PAY FOR THAT.
MAN, THIS NEW SALAMANDERS LODGE
IS REALLY THROWING A MONKEY
WRENCH INTO EVERYTHING I'M
TRYING TO DO.
HAROLD, GUESS HOW MANY GUYS
HAVE SIGNED UP FOR THE SWAMP
SKIING COMPETITION?
SURE THING UNCLE RED.
SO I'M GOING TO ADD
A SPECIAL EVENT TO IT.
HAROLD IS GOING TO DO A
CANNONBALL OFF THE TOP
OF ROCK REEF POINT,
SINGING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM,
BUCK NAKED WITH HIS
HAIR ON FIRE.
THAT OKAY WITH YOU HAROLD?
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, WHATEVER.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
I DON'T KNOW THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
SALAMANDER MEETING
TONIGHT, HAROLD?
MAYBE.
UH-HUH.
HAVE YOU LEARNED THE SECRET
SALAMANDER HANDSHAKE YET?
WORKING ON IT.
MEMORIZING THE MOTTO,
ARE YOU HAROLD?
OH, YEAH. YOU KNOW HOW
LONG IT TOOK ME TO MEMORIZE
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI?
WHAT IS THE SALAMANDER
MOTTO HAROLD?
I'LL NEVER TELL.
I'VE BEEN SWORN TO SECRECY.
NO. NO.
IS THAT A SPIDER THERE?
OH, WHAT IS IT?
IT'S A BUG!
(CHUCKLING)
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS
TERRA RETREATUM?
WHEN ALL ELSE FAILS,
CLIMB UNDER A ROCK.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU WAIT HERE.
I'LL GO GET A ROCK.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU TEENAGERS
'CAUSE I KNOW YOUR PARENTS ARE
AFTER YOU AGAIN TO CLEAN UP
YOUR ROOM, HUH?
THEY'RE 'IN YOUR FACE,' EH?
AS YOU WOULD SAY,
BECAUSE THAT PILE OF LAUNDRY
AND JUNK FOOD WRAPPERS AND COMIC
BOOKS IN THE CENTRE OF THE ROOM
JUST DEVELOPED A HEARTBEAT.
OR MAYBE A PAIR OF YOUR GYM
SOCKS GOT TOGETHER AND HAD PUPS.
YOUR DAD, OF COURSE,
IS WARNING YOU
THAT THAT ROOM PROVES YOU
ARE HEADED FOR A LIFE
OF TOTAL FAILURE,
AND YOU'RE THINKING,
HE WOULD KNOW.
HEY, KIDS, INSTEAD OF ARGUING
WITH YOUR PARENTS,
OUTTHINK THEM.
IT'S A LOT EASIER.
TELL THEM THE HOTTEST FIELD
IN SCIENCE TODAY IS YOUR
CHAOS THEORY,
AND YOU'RE ON YOUR
WAY TO A Ph.D.
THOSE AREN'T DUST
BUNNIES UNDER THE BED,
THOSE ARE YOUR PROTOTYPES OF
FUZZY LOGIC AND SCSI DRIVES.
THAT SMELL COMING
OUT OF THE CLOSET,
WHY, THAT'S YOUR ALTERNATIVE
FUEL PROJECT, HUH?
YOU'RE GOING TO
SAVE THE OZONE LAYER,
MAYBE NOT THE
EARTH'S OZONE LAYER,
BUT AT LEAST THE PART
OVER YOUR LAUNDRY HAMPER.
AND THE NEW ANTIBIOTICS,
THEY ALL COME FROM MOULD.
SO YOU'RE NOT A PIG,
YOU'RE A CREATIVE GENIUS.
I OUGHTA KNOW.
I'M A REGULAR EINSTEIN MYSELF.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE EXAMINE THOSE THREE
LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
Audience:  I DON'T KNOW.
AH-HA!
WAY EXCELLENT.
JOINING MY UNCLE RED ON
THE EXPERT PORTION OF
THE SHOW TODAY
IS HIS BEST FRIEND IN
THE WHOLE WIDE ROOM,
WATER TAXI CAPTAIN,
HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
(APPLAUSE)
OKAY, WE HAVE A VIEWER
IN GEORGIA WHO ASKS...
"DEAR EXPERT:  I'M A BIT SELF
CONSCIOUS ABOUT MY HEIGHT.
"I'M NOT SHORT, JUST
VERTICALLY CHALLENGED.
"RECENTLY I READ THAT ASTRONAUTS
ACTUALLY GROW IN SPACE BY
AS MUCH AS AN INCH.
"IS THAT TRUE? AND, IF SO, HOW
CAN I GET INTO SPACE?"
OH, NO, NO, NO, I DON'T
THINK PEOPLE GROW IN SPACE.
I MET THAT WILLIAM SHATNER,
AND HE'S HARDLY TALL AT ALL.
WELL, ACTUALLY, RED, MOST
PEOPLE DO GROW IN ZERO GRAVITY.
I DON'T, BUT MOST
PEOPLE DO.
YOU WERE IN SPACE,
WERE YOU, HAP?
WELL, NO.
SPACE STARTS AT
ABOUT 90 MILES UP.
I ONLY FLEW
88 MILES UP.
AND WHAT WERE
YOU FLYING IN?
A CAPE.
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
A CAPE?
LIKE SUPERMAN, HUH?
NO, NOT LIKE SUPERMAN.
MINE WAS WHITE.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS A BIT OF
A STRETCH EVEN FOR YOU,
I'M FINDING.
WELL, I WAS WITH
THE LOCAL CIRCUS,
HAP THE HUMAN CANNONBALL.
WE WERE PERFORMING
IN PORT ASBESTOS,
AND JUST AS I WAVED GOODBYE,
I SLID DOWN THE TUBE,
A BOLT OF LIGHTENING HIT
THE CANNON AND BOOM!
THE BLAST WAS SO STRONG, THE
WIND WAS SO POWERFUL ALL MY
CLOTHES WERE TORN OFF.
I WAS TOTALLY NAKED.
LUCKILY I WAS 88 MILES UP,
SO NO ONE COULD SEE.
DID YOU KNOW AUSTRALIA'S
IN THE SHAPE OF A DOG'S HEAD?
YOU KNOW, NOT TOO MUCH AIR UP
THERE, I WOULDN'T THINK,
YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW, I KNOW THE AIRPLANES
FLY AT FOUR OR FIVE
MILES UP ONLY,
AND THEY HAVE TO ACTUALLY
PRESSURIZE THE CABINS SO
THAT PEOPLE CAN BREATH.
OH, YEAH, THE AIR IS
VERY, VERY THIN UP THERE.
LUCKILY I WAS JUST TRAVELLING SO
FAST, I JUST OPENED MY MOUTH AND
SCOOPED ENOUGH OXYGEN IN
TO KEEP MY CONSCIOUSNESS.
MY REAL WORRY WAS THE LANDING.
I MEAN, I'M 88 MILES UP EH?
GOING A MILE A SECOND,
SPEEDING HEADFIRST
TOWARDS EARTH.
I GUESS THE IMPACT WOULD
CAUSE YOU TO PRETTY MUCH LOSE
WHATEVER HEIGHT YOU GAINED.
WELL, I GOT LUCKY, HAROLD.
I BLACKED OUT, SO I DIDN'T
TENSE UP FOR THE LANDING.
WHEN I CAME TO, I WAS JUST
OUTSIDE OF TOWN ON TOP OF
A HAYSTACK BUCK NAKED.
WOW! EXCELLENT.
NAKED!
YOU BUY THAT
STORY, HAROLD?
NOT REALLY, NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
NEITHER DID HIS EX-WIFE.
NOW, ALL THE POSSUM LODGE
MEMBERS ARE OVER AT THE
SALAMANDER LODGE
MEETING TONIGHT,
WHICH IS FINE.
YOU KNOW, I CERTAINLY HAVE
NOTHING AGAINST THOSE TRAITOROUS
TWO-TIMING BACKSTABBERS.
NO, SO, NO SENSE
HANGING AROUND, I GUESS.
SO, BERNICE, IF YOU'RE WATCHING
THE SHOW, YOU'RE ABOUT
THE ONLY ONE AROUND.
OH, OH, OH, BY GOLLY.
SALAMANDER MEETING OVER
SO SOON THERE, HAROLD?
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, YEAH, I WASN'T
GOING TO JOIN ANYWAY.
YOU KNOW, JUST FORGET
THE WHOLE THING.
FORGET IT.
OH, YEAH. I JUST WENT IN
TO CHECK IT OUT,
SEE WHAT IT WAS ALL ABOUT.
YOU KNOW, I WAS GOING
TO JOIN TO SHOW MY DISDAIN.
I WAS DOING A
WHOLE DISDAIN THING.
OH, REALLY?
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, I HAD THE
DISTINCT IMPRESSION YOU WERE
GOING TO BE A SALAMANDER,
HAROLD.
YOU'VE ALREADY GOT THE
BEAK AND THE COLD, WET SKIN.
OKAY, OKAY, YEAH, MAYBE
I WAS GOING TO JOIN.
YEAH, MAYBE, MAYBE.
BUT THEN JUNIOR STARTED GOING ON
ABOUT HOW MUCH IT WAS GOING TO
COST TO JOIN THE SILLY LODGE,
YOU KNOW, AND THEN HE STARTED
TELLING US HOW MUCH IT
WAS GOING TO COST
TO BUY THOSE JACKETS AND
ALL THOSE FANCY PANTS
MEMBERSHIP CARDS,
THEN HE STARTS HANDING OUT
DUTIES ABOUT WHO'S GOING TO
BE DOING THE CLEANING,
AND HE'S GOT ETHICS CODES
AND DRESS CODES.
WELL, WE WERE PRETTY MUCH
OUT THE DOOR BY THAT
TIME, PALLY RALLY.
(POSSUM CALL)
HEY, IT'S MEETING TIME.
WE'RE HAVING A MEETING?
OH, YEAH,
EVERYBODY'S BACK.
OH, GREAT.
OKAY, YOU GO AHEAD.
SEE IF YOU CAN GET THE GUYS
TO SIGN UP FOR THE SWAMPS.
I'VE ALREADY PUT MY NAME RIGHT
AT THE TOP OF THE LIST THERE.
OH, UNCLE RED, SEE,
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
THAT IS VERY GOOD.
YOU'VE REALLY LEARNED
SOMETHING FROM THIS EXPERIENCE.
WELL, DON'T GET CARRIED AWAY.
I WROTE IT IN PENCIL.
WAY YOU GO THEN.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
WE'VE GOT NO MONEY
AND NO AGENDA,
SO IT SHOULD BE A QUICK ONE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, WITH ME
SOMETIMES THE QUICK ONES
ARE THE BEST ONES.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTER]
Harold:  HERE HE COMES
TAKE YOUR SEATS!
OKAY, ALL RISE.
Everyone:
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI
Red:  SIT DOWN.
Harold:  OKAY, OUR FIRST
ANNOUNCEMENT...
THE NEXT SECRET SOCIETY
MEETING is a go!
CODE NAME:  AQUA
THERE WILL BE AN OPEN DISCUSSION
OF OPERATION RASH REMOVER.
SPECIAL GUEST SPEAKER:
DEEP WATER.
THE MEETING WILL
BE HELD AT LOCATION A-7.