HERE'S ONE FOR YOU...
HOW MANY MEN DOES IT TAKE
TO CHANGE A LIGHT BULB?
WELL, IT DEPENDS
ON HOW HANDY THEY ARE.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ WHISTLES AND CHEERS ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
NO, NO, DON'T THINK
I DON'T APPRECIATE THAT.
ACTUALLY IT'S TIME FOR OUR
ANNUAL MEN'S FISHING WEEKEND
UP HERE AT THE LODGE.
CATCHING THE FISH
IS THE EASY PART.
GETTING OUR WIVES
TO LET US GO,
THAT'S WHERE THE
REAL SKILL COMES IN.
SO WE'RE TELLING
THEM THAT MIKE HAMAR'S
GOT A TRIAL OUT OF TOWN,
AND WE ALL HAVE TO APPEAR
AS CHARACTER WITNESSES.
ONE OF THE UPSIDES OF
HAVING A KNOWN FELON
AS A PERSONAL FRIEND.
YEAH?
UNCLE RED!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
IS IT INTERNATIONAL
WOMEN'S DAY OR SOMETHING?
OH, I WOULDN'T BE
SURPRISED -- WHY?
WELL, ALL THE TOWN'S
WOMEN ARE ALL LINED UP
LIKE FOR A DEMONSTRATION
OR SOMETHING.
I DUNNO.
IS IT MOTHER'S DAY?
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHEN MOTHER'S DAY IS?
OH, NO.
SURE I DO.
NO.
NOT TODAY, RIGHT?
IT'S, UH --
HEY, GUYS, WHAT ARE
THE WIVES MAD ABOUT?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE, OKAY.
YOU'RE OUR EXCUSE
TO BE ABLE TO
GO FISHING!
THAT CASE IS PUT OFF.
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO!
YOUR CASE
IS POSTPONED;
I'M PUT OFF!
HA! HA!
THAT'S WHY THE
WOMEN ARE SO UPSET.
THEY KNOW
YOU LIED
[ WOMEN CHANTING ]
I DON'T THINK SO.
CONJUGAL VISIT?
IS THIS A
YOU DESERVE THIS.
YOU LIED.
I NEVER LIED
TO A WOMAN.
I KNOW THAT, HAROLD.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE NOT MARRIED.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER WILL
RECEIVE A COUPON
FOR A LARGE BUCKET
OF CHICKEN PARTS
FROM STEVENSON'S
PULVERIZED POULTRY.
WHERE IT'S
GUARANTEED 100% MEAT,
NO BEAKS!
MR. GREEN, YOU'VE
GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET WINSTON TO --
COVER YOUR EARS --
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH,
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
OH, OKAY.
AND... GO!
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON,
WHENEVER YOU START A JOB,
IT'S IMPORTANT
THAT YOU...
PUT ON MY RUBBER GLOVES.
OKAY,  OKAY, BUT AT THE
END OF THE JOB YOU...
HOSE DOWN MY TRUCK?
NO. NO.
OKAY, OKAY,
WHEN YOU RETIRE, OKAY,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO SAY
YOUR CAREER IS AT A...
PHOTOMAT.
THAT'S THE
DREAM, ANYWAY.
YOU KNOW WHEN A GUY
RUNS A MARATHON, OKAY,
THIS IS HIS
FAVOURITE LINE...
"HEY, BABY,
I JUST RAN A MARATHON."
REMEMBER LAST MONTH,
YOU PAINTED YOUR
BEDROOM, EH?
YOU DID THE WHOLE
THING IN A SATIN...
BATHROBE.
YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
TIME, MR. GREEN.
ALMOST OUT OF
WINSTON, LAST THURSDAY
NIGHT YOU WATCHED
ONE OF THOSE
EUROPEAN BORING
FILMS, REMEMBER?
YOU TURNED IT
OFF HALFWAY THROUGH.
WHAT DID YOU MISS?
EVERYTHING.
I DON'T SPEAK FINNISH.
WELL,
THERE WE GO!
[ BELL RINGING ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THIS WEEK ON
TALKING ANIMALS,
LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER, ED FRID, IS
GOING TO TELL US
ALL ABOUT LOBSTERS.
THAT'S RIGHT, RED.
LOBSTERS:
THE RACCOONS OF THE SEA.
WHY RACCOONS, ED?
WELL, BECAUSE THEY'RE
BOTH, UM, SCAVENGERS,
AND THEY B-BOTH
HAVE CLAWS
AND D-DARK RINGS
UNDER THEIR EYES.
YOU EVER SEEN A
LOBSTER UP CLOSE, ED?
WELL, I DON'T SEEK 'EM OUT,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU MEAN.
WELL, NO.
I JUST THOUGHT AS AN
ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER --
THAT WHAT?
THAT I'D GET A LOT
OF CALLS FROM PEOPLE
WHO HAVE LOBSTERS
UP THEIR CHIMNEY?
OR BECAUSE THERE'S
A RABID LOBSTER RUNNING
AROUND AT NIGHT
KILLING ALL THE SHEEP?
[ GROWLING ]
WELL, YOU THOUGHT WRONG.
ED, I JUST THOUGHT --
I'M TELLING YOU,
I HAVE TO RISK MY
LIFE EVERY DAY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT THAT'S LIKE?
WELL, I DRIVE THE
POSSUM VAN, ED, OKAY?
CAN YOU JUST SHOW
US THE LOBSTER?
SURE. SURE.
OKAY.
THERE'S YOUR LOBSTER.
OKAY, YOU HAPPY?
WHERE'D YOU CATCH
THESE LOBSTERS, ED?
POSSUM LAKE.
WELL, THERE'S NO LOBSTERS
IN POSSUM LAKE.
THAT'S FRESH WATER.
IT'S NOT
THAT FRESH.
OKAY, THESE ARE
CRAYFISH, ED.
YOU KNOW, I KNEW YOU'D
WIMP OUT ON ME,
SO I BROUGHT
MY OWN LOBSTER.
WHAT?!
GOTTEN OUT.
WELL, HE MUST'VE
PROBABLY JUST UNDER
THE TABLE HERE.
WELL, I'M GONNA SIT
OVER IN THIS AREA THEN.
WHAT? WHAT?
AHHH! AHHH!
OH! HE'S ON
YOUR BACKSIDE!
ED, HE'S ON
YOUR BACKSIDE.
OH! OH! OH!
I GUESS THEY'RE
BOTTOM FEEDERS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THERE ARE SEVEN WONDERS
IN THIS WORLD,
AND ALL OF THEM ARE GREAT.
BUT BE SURE TO GET
YOUR SEPTICS PUMPED,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
WANNA SEE NUMBER EIGHT.
THIS EVER HAPPEN TO YOU...
YOU'RE DRIVING ALONG,
MINDING YOUR OWN BUSINESS,
AND SUDDENLY IT
COMES TO YOUR ATTENTION
THAT YOU'RE
COMPLETELY LOST,
YOU HAVE NO CLUE
WHERE YOU ARE,
AND LIKE SO MANY OTHER
ASPECTS OF YOUR LIFE,
YOU'RE ON A
DEAD-END STREET?
NOW, THIS WOULDN'T
BE A MAJOR PROBLEM,
IF YOU HAD ROOM
TO TURN AROUND.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY THEY DON'T
ALWAYS BUILD ROADS THAT WAY
AND FOR SURE THEY DON'T
BUILD CARS THAT WAY.
THAT'S BECAUSE OF
THIS DISTANCE RIGHT HERE.
BETWEEN THE FRONT TIRE
AND THE BACK TIRE.
THAT'S CALLED
THE WHEEL BASE.
IF YOU'VE GOT A
LONG WHEEL BASE,
YOU GET A REAL
COMFORTABLE RIDE,
BUT YOU GOTTA GO TO THE
SALT FLATS TO TURN AROUND.
IF YOU GOT A
SHORT WHEEL BASE,
OH, SURE YOU CAN TURN
AROUND ON A DINNER PLATE,
BUT THE RIDE IS LIKE BEING
ON THE TILT-A-WHIRL.
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
IF SOMEBODY INVENTED
A VARIABLE
WHEEL BASE CAR,
LONG WHEN YOU'RE
ON A LONG RIDE,
SHORT WHEN YOU'RE
IN A SHORT TURN?
WELL, DON'T EXPECT THE BIG
THREE TO COME UP WITH
THE ANSWER.
THAT'S WHAT
HANDYMAN CORNER'S FOR.
[ TIRES SPINNING,
ENGINE REVVING ]
ALL YOU REALLY NEED
IS A BOAT TRAILER.
BUT YOU WANNA TAKE
THE WINCH OFF THERE
BECAUSE YOU GOTTA REMOUNT
THAT ON YOUR VEHICLE.
OH, YEAH, AND YOUR VEHICLE
NEEDS TO BE FRONT-WHEEL-DRIVE.
THAT WAY YOU CAN TAKE THE
WHOLE REAR WHEEL AXLE
ASSEMBLY OFF THERE
WITHOUT HURTING
THE DRIVE TRAIN.
AND THEN, AGAIN,
THERE'S NO RULES THERE.
YOU CAN TAKE THAT
REAR AXLE OFF
WITH WHATEVER TECHNOLOGY
IS AVAILABLE TO YOU.
NOW, A WINCH IS
SUPPOSED TO BE
FOR PULLING A BOAT
UP ONTO A TRAILER.
BUT WE'RE GOING TO USE IT
FOR PULLING THE TRAILER
DOWN UNDER THE CAR.
THAT'S WHY HAD TO
TAKE HER OFF THERE
SO I COULD MOUNT
IT ON THE CAR
SOMEWHERE WHERE I COULD
GET AT IT EASILY.
I'M THINKING RIGHT
HERE NEAR THE SUN ROOF.
THE ONLY OTHER
ALTERATION WE NEED
IS SOMETHING TO GUIDE
THE TONGUE OF THE TRAILER
WHEN IT COMES UP
UNDER THE CAR.
SOMETHING TO KEEP
HER GOOD AND SNUG.
LOOSE TONGUES HAVE A WAY
OF GETTING GUYS LIKE ME
INTO TROUBLE.
SO I'M THINKING SOMETHING
KINDA HORSESHOE-SHAPED
THAT I WOULD HANG UNDER
THE MIDDLE OF THE BUMPER.
IN FACT,
I'M THINKING HORSESHOE.
THERE'S NOTHING MORE
HORSESHOE SHAPED THAN THAT.
[ SPITTING DUST
OUT OF HIS MOUTH ]
[ JACK CREAKING ]
[ WINCH WINDING ]
OKAY, ALL'S
I HAVE TO DO NOW
IS ATTACH MY WINCH CABLE TO
THE BACK END OF MY TRAILER.
THEN WE'RE READY
TO GIVE HER A GO.
IF THERE ARE ANY CAR
DESIGNERS WATCHING THIS,
YOU MAY BE GETTING
A FEW PHONE CALLS.
AND EMERGENCY ROOM DOCTORS,
YOU MAY GET A
FEW CALLS YOURSELF.
OKAY, I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR A DEMONSTRATION
OF THE WORLD'S FIRST VARIABLE
WHEEL BASE LUXURY AUTOMOBILE.
BUT BEFORE I DO THAT,
REMEMBER...
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[ WINCH CREAKING ]
[ METAL GROANING ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I WANNA TALK TO
YOU GUYS OUT THERE
WHO HAVE RUN UP A FEW DECADES
ON THE OLD ODOMETER OF LIFE
AND ARE WAY OFF WARRANTY.
YOU KNOW, I HEARD IT SAID
THAT AGE IS A STATE OF MIND.
WELL, SO IS INSANITY.
AGE IS A STATE OF BODY.
BELIEVE ME.
IN OUR SOCIETY
IF YOU'RE NOT YOUNG,
YOU'RE OLD.
YOU BETTER GET
READY FOR THAT.
SOME DAY SOON YOU'LL
BE RIDING A BUS,
AND THAT PRETTY YOUNG THING
YOU'VE BEEN SNEAKING A PEAK AT
IS GONNA GET UP
AND OFFER YOU HER SEAT.
AND YOU BETTER TAKE IT
BECAUSE WHEN THAT HAPPENS,
YOU'RE GONNA NEED ONE.
NOW, DON'T GO NUTS AND
BUY YOURSELF A FERRARI
OR SOMETHING.
IF YOU NEED A CAR AT ALL,
YOU WANNA GET SOMETHING
CONSERVATIVE AND NORMAL.
A FERRARI IS A
MID-LIFE CRISIS.
WHAT YOU NEED IS
A MID-LIFE CHRYSLER.
SO I SAY, JUST EMBRACE THE
AUTUMN OF YOUR LIFE.
IF YOU DON'T,
YOU'LL BE RIDING FOR A FALL.
YOU MAY THINK YOU'RE STILL
BASKING IN THE LAST WARM
RAYS OF YOUTH,
BUT THAT'S EITHER A HOT FLASH
OR LAST NIGHT'S CHILI.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU;
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YOUR BACKYARD SMELLS
LIKE A DINOSAUR GRAVE.
YOU GET MORE LIGHT HEADED
WITH EACH PASSING WAVE.
A GUEST LIT A MATCH
AND IGNITED YOUR LAWN.
YOU'VE BEEN
GOING AND GOING,
BUT WE CAN MAKE IT GONE.
LOOKS LIKE THE MEN'S
FISHING WEEKEND HAS
HIT A SNAG.
THE WOMEN HAVE
FORMED A KIND OF ONE-WAY
BLOCKADE AROUND THE LODGE.
THEY'LL LET THE
GUYS COME IN,
BUT THEY'RE NOT LETTING
ANYBODY GET OUT.
ACTUALLY, DALTON'S TRYING
TO RUN THE GAUNTLET
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S NOT MUCH OF A GAUNTLET,
BUT IT'S DALTON,
SO IT'S NOT MUCH
OF A RUN EITHER.
HEY, HEY,
HAROLD!
WHY DON'T WE JUST
CALL THE POLICE?
I PHONED THE
SHERIFF AT HOME,
BUT HIS WIFE WON'T
LET HIM COME TO
THE TELEPHONE.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
I ALMOST MADE IT.
THERE WERE JUST
TOO MANY KNITTERS.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
I SAID YOU SHOULDN'T
LIE TO THEM.
YOU'RE A REAL
WEINER, HAROLD.
RED, THESE WOMEN
ARE SERIOUS..
YOU KNOW HOW ALL OUR
VEHICLES ARE IN THEIR NAMES
SO WE GET BETTER
INSURANCE RATES?
WELL, WORD IS THEY'RE GOING
TO TRADE IN ALL OUR
CARS AND TRUCKS
FOR SOME SPORTY,
LITTLE, GIRLY JOBS.
MAN WE BETTER
GET OUT THERE,
OR WE'LL ALL
BE DRIVING MIATAS.
HEY! DON'T WORRY, GUYS!
I'VE GOT IT ALL
FIGURED OUT.
BOY, I WISH THIS
WAS GOOD NEWS.
WE'RE GOING TO DIG
OUR WAY TO FREEDOM.
THEY HAVEN'T BUILT THE
LODGE THAT CAN HOLD ME.
I'VE NOTICED THAT THE BASEMENT
WALLS ARE PRETTY SPONGY.
WE SHOULD HIT
DAYLIGHT IN 24 HOURS.
MIKE, MIKE, MIKE,
MIKE, MIKE...
DO ME A LITTLE
FAVOUR...
DIG AWAY
FROM THE LAKE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THANK YOU.
OKAY.
THIS IS OBVIOUSLY A
SYMPTOM OF A LONG-TERM
MISUNDERSTANDING.
IS IT SO HARD FOR YOU GUYS
TO ADMIT THAT YOU MADE
A MISTAKE?
TO YOUR BOSS: FINE;
TO YOUR FRIENDS: OKAY;
BUT WHEN YOU ADMIT
A MISTAKE TO YOUR WIFE,
AND YOUR WIFE JUST HAPPENS
TO BE ANN MARIE HUMPHREY,
THEN THAT IS SOMETHING
YOU WILL REGRET, HAROLD.
MAYBE NOT TODAY;
MAYBE NOT TOMORROW;
BUT SOME DAY AND FOR
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
Red Green [voiceover]:
WALTER HAD ASKED ME TO
MEET HIM OUT BEHIND THE LODGE
BECAUSE HE HAD A
TRAILER ON HIS CAR,
AND HE WANTED A LITTLE HELP
BACKING HER INTO THE GARAGE.
SO I GOT -- HE WANTED ME
IN THE PASSENGER SEAT,
WHICH KIND OF SURPRISED ME.
AND THEN -- OKAY.
SO I THOUGHT, I'LL JUST GO
AROUND AND GET HIM TO
SCOOT OVER,
BUT OF COURSE HE
DIDN'T WANNA SCOOT OVER.
SO SOMETIMES YOU GOTTA DO
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
SO YOU KNOW HAVING A
TRAILER CAN BE DIFFICULT.
LIKE A BOAT TRAILER MIGHT
HAVE A SHORT REACH ON IT,
OR WHAT HAVE YOU.
AND WALTER JUST WANTED
SOMEBODY TO EITHER GUIDE HIM
OR TEACH HIM A LITTLE
BIT ABOUT IT.
BUT HE INSISTED ON TAKING THE
FIRST TRY ON HIS OWN.
SO HE JUST PULLED HER UP,
AND HE GOT FROM DRIVE
INTO REVERSE.
SO THAT IMPRESSED ME,
BUT I THINK THE PROBLEM
HERE -- YEAH, GOOD LUCK.
NOW, HE WAS --
OKAY, YOU'RE OFF TO A --
OKAY, THAT'S A BAD --
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
MY LIFE IS TOO SHORT
FOR A LOT OF THIS.
SO, WALTER,
YOU JUST WATCH,
THEN WHAT YOU DO ON YOUR FREE
TIME IS NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
SO I JUST BRING HER
RIGHT BACK IN.
I'VE DONE A FAIR BIT OF THIS,
SO IT'S NOT A --
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
AND THEN THERE'S YOUR KEYS,
AND WE'RE DONE.
YEP. ALL RIGHT.
NOW, WHAT SURPRISED ME WAS
WALTER JUST WANTED TO
GIVE HER A TRY,
LIKE, RIGHT AWAY.
HE DIDN'T WANNA WAIT.
YOU KNOW, I THINK I MADE
IT LOOK TO DARNED EASY.
AND THAT WAS --
NO, SEE, YOU GOTTA
USE THE MIRRORS.
DON'T JUST --
AND THEN DON'T --
WE'RE OVER HERE.
OH, OKAY, SO WHAT DID I LEAVE
OVER THERE THAT WAS --
I THINK THERE WAS
SOME GARBAGE THERE,
NO, WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT'S WHERE I PARKED
THE VAN, I THINK.
YEAH, THANK YOU, WALTER.
OKAY, SO NOW I'M TRYING
TO CONVINCE HIM --
I PUT SOME TRUCK
MIRRORS ON THERE.
NOW HE CAN JUST --
YOU DON'T WANNA BE LOOKING
BE LOOKING FORWARD.
YOU WANNA LOOK
INTO THE MIRRORS.
AND TAKE IT A
LITTLE SLOWER!
NO! NO! NO! NO!
OH!
HOW WAS THAT
POSSIBLE, WALTER?
AND HE SAYS,
"IT WAS IN MY BLIND SPOT."
OH, MAN!
SO THEN HE GETS THE IDEA
WHAT NEEDS ACTUALLY
IS MORE MIRRORS!
SO HE'S GOT THE
FULL-LENGTH MIRROR;
HE'S GOT THE VAN -- HE'S GOT
EVERY MIRROR FROM THE LODGE
HE'S GOT DUCT TAPED
TO THE FRONT OF CAR.
NOW HE'S GONNA BACK HER UP
STRICTLY USING THE MIRRORS.
THAT'S GONNA
BE BRIGHT, WOW!
THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, JUST TAKE
IT EASY, WALTER.
JUST TAKE IT --
I GOT OUT OF THERE.
AND -- UH-OH.
DON'T LIKE THE LOOK OF THIS.
NO, HE'S ALL RIGHT.
NO, NO, LEFT.
THAT'S GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE GOOD.
SLOW DOWN!
OH, GOSH.
NO, NO, YOU MISSED HER.
YOU MISSED HER.
COME ON BRING HER BACK.
BRING HER AROUND.
OKAY, RIGHT! RIGHT!
NO, LEFT!
HARD LEFT.
THERE YOU GO.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW THEY SAY ORANGE
JUICE IS GOOD FOR YOU.
WELL, NOT IF YOU HAVE A
HEART ATTACK SQUEEZING IT.
AND FOR WHAT?
I CAN GET MORE JUICE THAN
THAT OUT OF A DEAD BATTERY.
AND SPEAKING OF DEAD BATTERIES
AND HEART ATTACKS,
WHAT THIS FORMULA NEEDS IS
A LITTLE BIT MORE POWER.
SO INSTEAD OF SQUEEZING
THE ORANGE BY HAND,
GET YOURSELF ONE OF
THESE BLOOD PRESSURE CUFFS
STICK THE ORANGE
DOWN INSIDE THAT.
YOU CAN ACTUALLY GET THESE
THINGS FOR FREE FROM YOUR
DOCTOR'S OFFICE.
SOME PEOPLE CALL
IT STEALING;
I CALL IT 'PAYBACK'
FOR LEAVING ME ALONE
IN THE EXAMINATION ROOM
WITH NO PANTS ON.
OKAY, SNUG THAT UP
AROUND THE ORANGE.
OKAY, NOW, YES, YOU COULD
PUMP THAT UP BY HAND,
BUT AS I SAID TO YOU EARLIER,
I'M LOOKING FOR
JUST A LITTLE BIT
MORE JUICE.
[ PUMP SQUEAKING ]
JUST THE WAY LIKE IT...
EXTRA PULP.
[ WOMEN CHANTING ]
WELL, WE'VE HIT A BIT
OF A STALEMATE HERE,
WHICH DESCRIBES MOST
OF OUR MARRIAGES.
THE MEN ARE STILL
TRYING TO GO FISHING,
AND THE WOMEN ARE
STILL TRYING TO STOP US.
WELL, I'M WITH THE
WOMEN ON THIS ONE.
NOT A BIG
SURPRISE, IS IT?
WHY? WHY?
BECAUSE I'M
SENSITIVE.
YES. YES.
YOU KNOW IT DOESN'T MAKE
YOU LESS OF A MAN TO BE
SENSITIVE, UNCLE RED.
YOU CAN AFFORD
TO BE MORE SENSITIVE.
WELL, YOU CAN'T AFFORD
TO BE LESS OF A MAN.
HEY,
MIKE'S DOING GREAT
DIGGING THAT TUNNEL.
BOY, YOU CAN TELL
HE'S DONE IT BEFORE.
HEY! THAT'S MY REMOTE!
LOOK, THEY TOOK THE
BATTERIES OUT OF IT.
OH!
LOOK, THERE'S A
NOTE ATTACHED.
WHAT'S IT SAY?
WELL, IT'S A LIST
OF THEIR DEMANDS.
THEY JUST WANT US
TO MAKE A SUGGESTION.
OH, NO!
WE'RE SCUPPERED.
OH! OH!
OKAY! OKAY!
ALL RIGHT, HOW ABOUT
MAYBE YOU INVITE THE WOMEN
TO JOIN YOU ON
THE FISHING TRIP?
HAROLD MIGHT
BE RIGHT, DALTON.
I STILL LIKE
THE TUNNEL IDEA.
HEY, GUYS,
WHAT?
BAD NEWS.
OH!
EW!
I HIT THE
SEPTIC TANK.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME!
YOU GUYS
GO AHEAD.
YOU GO!
YOU GO,
AND I'LL FOLLOW.
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I WOULD JUST LIKE
TO SAY I WAS WRONG.
I APOLOGIZE.
AND I'D BE VERY HONOURED IF
YOU'D ACCOMPANY ME
ON THE FISHING TRIP.
SOMETHING I'VE
ALWAYS WANTED TO DO,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT
THE OTHER GUYS ARE LIKE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Harold: OKAY, HERE HE IS.
EVERYBODY TAKE YOUR SEATS.
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
WE'RE ABOUT TO BEGIN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
OKAY, GUYS, I'VE GOT
SOME GOOD NEWS FOR YOU.
FIRST, THE WOMEN HAVE
CALLED OFF THE PROTEST,
AND WE'RE ALL
FREE MEN AGAIN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
NOW, IN ORDER FOR
THAT TO HAPPEN,
I'VE INVITED THEM
ALL TO JOIN US
ON OUR FISHING TRIP
THIS WEEKEND.
[ WEAK APPLAUSE ]
Harold: OKAY, I'M ALONE THERE.
HERE'S THE SURPRISING
PART OF IT.
THEY WERE REAL PLEASED
THAT WE ASKED THEM TO,
BUT THEY TURNED
US DOWN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]