IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW!"
AND NOW HERE'S A MAN WHO'S A
RIDDLE WRAPPED IN AN ENIGMA
WEARING SUSPENDERS.
YOUR HOST,
YOUR HERO,
MY UNCLE,
RED GR-E-E-E-N!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
I THINK YOU SHOULD ALL
SWITCH BACK TO WATER.
OKAY!
BIG, BIG WEEK UP AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
I'M THINKING ABOUT MAKING A
LITTLE REAL ESTATE INVESTMENT,
GETTING MYSELF A LITTLE
PIECE OF PROPERTY.
I'M THINKING ABOUT BUYING THAT
CHUNK OF LAND THAT FUZZY NORTON
HAS FOR SALE DOWN BY THE
MERCURY CREEK BRIDGE.
UNCLE RED,
THAT'S NOT LAND.
OH, NO,
LAND IS DRY,
AND LAND IS OFTEN
TIMES SQUARE.
THAT'S TRIANGULAR
AND --
WELL, IT'S TRIANGULAR
AND IT'S WET.
IT'S LIKE A BIG DIAPER.
SMELLS LIKE ONE TOO.
YOU GOT TO --
NOW, HAROLD, DON'T
GET EXCITED HERE.
IT'S A FREE MARKET.
FUZZY WANTS TO SELL,
AND I WANT TO BUY.
WHY? YOU CAN'T
BUILD ON IT.
YOU CAN'T EVEN
PARK ON IT.
ANYTHING OVER 200 POUNDS SINKS
RIGHT TO THE BOTTOM.
THERE GOES 90% OF THE LODGE
MEMBERS RIGHT THERE.
AND SO...
WELL, YOU KNOW,
I GUESS THEN, HAROLD,
EITHER I HAVE A
PLAN, OR I'M AN IDIOT.
WELL, GOOD. OKAY.
BECAUSE USUALLY YOU HAVE A PLAN,
AND YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
BUT THIS WAY --
EASY. EASY.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE WORD
"EXPROPRIATION" MEANS, HAROLD?
DID YOU EVER HEAR THAT ONE?
YES, I HEARD OF IT,
AND I DO KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS.
WHAT DOES IT MEAN?
OH, YOU WANT TO KNOW?
OH, OKAY. IT MEANS --
WELL, IT'S, LIKE, IF THE
GOVERNMENT IS GOING TO BUY
YOUR PROPERTY TO, LIKE,
PUT UP A PARK OR SOMETHING
LIKE THAT -- A PARK OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
HOW ABOUT FOR A
HIGHWAY, HAROLD?
OH, YEAH. RIGHT. LIKE, THE
GOVERNMENT IS GOING TO BUILD
A HIGHWAY THAT'S, LIKE,
TRIANGULAR AND FLOODS AND SINKS.
WELL, SOMETHING
LIKE THAT, HAROLD.
BUT, HEY, YOU AND I ARE THE
ONLY ONES IN THE AREA
THAT KNOW ABOUT IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I MEAN?
YEAH.
WELL, I'M WILLING TO
FORGET IT IF YOU ARE.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
HERE'S A FEW SELECTED CLIPS
FROM THIS WEEK'S SHOW,
AND THESE ARE THE
HIGHLIGHTS, FOLKS.
OH, BOY, A LITTLE
BIT OF EVERYTHING.
SOMETHING FOR THE
WHOLE FAMILY HERE.
I'M NOT SURE I WANT
TO MEET THAT FAMILY.
IT'S A GOOD SHOW.
THIS IS PRICELESS!
FOR ANYBODY WHO CAN
REMEMBER WHO HE IS,
WOULD YOU PLEASE ATTEND AND
EXPRESS OUR DEEPEST CONDOLENCES?
OKAY. LOST AND FOUND...
OKAY. HAROLD, I'M GETTING REAL
CLOSE ON THIS REAL ESTATE DEAL.
I'VE GOT FUZZY DOWN TO $400.
WOW! HOW MUCH
WAS HE ASKING?
$400.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I TELL YOU, THE
PLACE HAS BEEN FOR SALE SO LONG,
HE WAS THINKING OF
RAISING THE PRICE.
FUZZY'S NOT TOO SWIFT, YOU KNOW?
WELL, HE WAS SWIFT
ENOUGH TO SELL YOU
A SINKHOLE FOR $400.
OH, NOT JUST ME. I'VE GOT
PARTNERS, HAROLD.
I REALLY COULDN'T COME
UP WITH THE $400
ALL ON MY OWN,
SO THERE'S 85 OF US,
AND WE KICKED
IN $5 A PIECE.
THERE'S 85, AND YOU PUT
$5 IN TO MAKE $400?
BOY, YOU'RE NOT VERY GOOD AT
MATH, UNCLE RED.
OH, NO, NO, HAROLD.
THEY'RE NOT VERY
GOOD AT MATH.
I'M UP $25.
(APPLAUSE)
OH, HAVING RESPECT
FOR NATURE
IS A SPORT THAT'S
ALWAYS IN SEASON
LIKE WHEN SOMETHING
IS CALLED A STINK BUG
THERE'S PROBABLY A
PRETTY GOOD REASON
WHEN YOU STEP
ON A STINK BUG
IT'S NOT LIKE A
SLUG OR SNAIL
THAT'S WHY MY
EYES ARE WATERING
AND THAT'S WHY MY
SHOES ARE FOR SALE
IT'S TIME TO PLAY THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
OKAY, THIS WEEK'S GRAND
PRIZE IS A REAL SPECIAL ONE.
PICTURE THIS:  TWO WEEKS ABOARD
A LUXURY CRUISE LINER,
STOPPING IN VARIOUS PORTS
THROUGHOUT THE WESTERN
CARIBBEAN,
SUNSHINE CAPTURED FOREVER.
AND WHERE IS ALL OF THOSE
WONDERFUL MEMORIES GOING TO GO?
INSIDE TODAY'S GRAND PRIZE,
A PHOTO ALBUM
SUPPLIED BY PHYLLIS'S
PHOTOS AND FLOWERS EMPORIUM.
OKAY, UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30
SECONDS TO GET Mr. ARNIE
DOGAN TO SAY THIS WORD.
PLUG YOUR EARS!
EXCELLENT.
THE WORD IS TALENT.
TALENT.
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT, ARNIE...
SPECIAL ABILITY.
CONTORTIONIST.
NO, ARNIE, BEING A CONTORTIONIST
IS NOT A SPECIAL ABILITY.
I GUESS YOU'VE NEVER MADE OUT
ON A ROOF IN THAT AREA, RED.
(CHUCKLING)
OKAY, WE'RE RUNNING
OUT OF TIME.
OKAY, ARNIE --
OH, I KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU NEED TO
MAKE IT IN SHOW BUSINESS?
BREAST IMPLANTS?
NO, NO, WHEN PEOPLE
FIND OUT YOU'RE A SINGER,
THEY SAY YOU
MUST HAVE...
THICK SKIN.
YOU KNOW THE
GRAMMY AWARDS, OKAY?
THEY GIVE AWARDS TO PEOPLE
WITH THE MOST...
JEWELRY.
THE CLOCK IS TICKING;
CLOCK'S TICKING.
OKAY, ARNIE, YOU'RE
A PRETTY GOOD ROOFER.
WHEN PEOPLE SEE YOUR WORK,
THEY SAY YOU HAVE REAL...
OH, NO,
NOT ME, RED.
THE EMERGENCY ROOM
FRACTURE UNIT,
THEY'RE THE ONES
WITH THE TALENT.
THERE YOU GO!
(FRANTIC BELL RINGING)
THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I WAS GONNA SHOW YOU HOW TO
MAKE A CATAPULT OUT OF ONE
OF THEM HIDEAWAY BEDS
TO HELP GET YOUR TEENAGERS
UP IN THE MORNING.
BUT ON THE WAY OVER HERE,
I WAS PASSED BY A RED
CONVERTIBLE SPORTS CAR,
AND THE WOMAN DRIVING IT
HAD THE TOP DOWN...
ON THE CAR.
AND I SAID, MAN, WOULD I
LOVE TO HAVE ONE OF THOSE --
THE CONVERTIBLE, THAT IS.
OH, YEAH, LOVE THE FEEL
OF WIND IN MY HAT.
BUT I HATE TO GIVE UP THE
ROOMINESS AND SAFETY OF A VAN
TO RIDE AROUND IN SOMETHING THE
SIZE OF ONE OF THEM KIDDIE
RIDES AT THE SUPERMARKET.
SO INSTEAD, THIS WEEK
ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO TURN THE POSSUM
VAN INTO A CONVERTIBLE.
I'M NOT SURE EXACTLY
HOW I'M GOING TO DO IT,
BUT I'LL FIGURE OUT A WAY.
YEAH, I COULD --
NOPE.
I WAS GOING TO MAKE A
CONVERTIBLE OUT OF
THE POSSUM VAN,
JUST CUT THE ROOF
OFF OR SOMETHING.
THEN I THOUGHT, "WAIT A SEC,
"WHAT IF SOMETHING GOES
HORRIBLY WRONG, AND I RUIN
MY FAVOURITE VEHICLE?"
AND THEN I GOT AN IDEA,
A BRAINSTORM.
IT JUST HIT ME.
HEY, PORKY LANSFORD HAS A VAN,
AND HE LOVES CONVERTIBLES,
ESPECIALLY IF HE CAN
GET ONE FOR FREE.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE?
IT'LL BE A SURPRISE.
WHAT I'VE DONE HERE IS
I'VE GOT THIS MODEL.
THIS IS ONE OF
HAROLD'S, ACTUALLY,
AND I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT
I'VE GOT IN MIND.
(MUMBLING)
AND THAT SHOULD WORK GREAT.
NOW TO DO THE CUTTIN',
I WOULD SUGGEST THAT YOU
NEED SOMETHING HEAVIER
THAN A HACKSAW,
UNLESS YOU RECENTLY RETIRED AND
ARE LOOKING FOR SOME WAY
TO FILL UP YOUR DAYS.
BUT I WOULD SAY GO
WITH A TORCH ON THAT,
AND IF YOU DON'T
HAVE A TORCH, WELL...
I'D SAY GET ONE!
JUST GET IT GOOD AND HOT,
AND START CUTTING.
ALL RIGHT. I MADE ALL THE CUTS.
OH! PROBABLY SHOULD HAVE USED
THE HACKSAW ON THIS,
BUT IT WAS JUST A TEST.
IT'LL WORK A LOT
BETTER ON THE VAN.
ALMOST.
ALMOST THROUGH.
ALL RIGHT. NOW, IF YOU
DON'T WANT THE SMOKE,
CLEAN THE VAN OUT FIRST.
ALL RIGHT. WE GOT OURSELVES
A CONVERTIBLE NOW.
JUST TO TURN IT BACK
INTO A HARDTOP,
WE'VE GOT TO CUT THIS UP
A LITTLE BIT MORE AND PUT
SOME HINGES ON THE SIDE HERE.
YOU CAN PUT SOME REGULAR
HINGES ON THERE,
BUT I WOULD RECOMMEND THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT. WE GOT OUR
SECTIONS ALL IN PLACE NOW.
NOW WE NEED SOME KIND OF
A MECHANISM TO RAISE
AND LOWER THE ROOF.
AND FOR THAT YOU
NEED THREE THINGS...
A 2 X 4, A CAR JACK
AND GRADE 10 PHYSICS.
WHAT YOU DO IS YOU TAKE THE
2 X 4 AND YOU LAY IT ON
THE CAR JACK, SEE?
AND THEN WHAT YOU DO IS YOU GET
THE THING NEAR THE CENTRE
OF THE FULCRUM --
OR THE POSITION OF THE FORCE,
AND THEN WHEN YOU JACK UP THE
CAR, THEN YOU'LL RAISE THE ROOF.
LET'S GIVE HER A TRY.
ALL RIGHT. IT LOOKS
LIKE IT'S GONNA RAIN
IN ANOTHER COUPLE OF WEEKS,
SO WHY DON'T WE JUST JACK
IT UP AND RAISE THE ROOF?
OH, LOOK AT THAT BABY GO!
YEP.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
SO, REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
WELL, GET A CONVERTIBLE.
I WONDER WHEN THE
STORM'S GONNA HIT?
I GUESS IT BLEW OVER.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
OLDER GUYS WHO HAVE MORE
MILES ON YOUR ODOMETER
THAN YOU HAVE LEFT
ON YOUR WARRANTY.
MAYBE SOME OF YOU ARE THINKING
THAT ONE DAY SOON,
WELL, YOU'RE GOING TO GO TO
SLEEP AND NOT SNORE...
EVER AGAIN.
NOW, I'M TALKING ABOUT SHUFFLING
OFF THIS MORTAL COIL AND TAKING
THE BIG DIRT NAP.
AND SOME OF YOU
ARE PROBABLY THINKING,
"YOU KNOW, MAYBE I SHOULD START
GOING TO CHURCH AGAIN."
YOU KNOW, KIND OF BUILD UP YOUR
CREDIT AND PAY YOUR ENTRANCE
FEE INTO THE PEARLY GATES,
THAT KIND OF THING.
YOU USED TO GO TO CHURCH
ALL THE TIME.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT THAT THE
BEST GOLFING AND FISHING
TIME IS SUNDAY MORNING.
AND NOW YOU'RE WORRIED THAT
GOD, BEING ALL POWERFUL
AND ALL KNOWING,
MAYBE HE'S NOT GOING TO LET
YOU BACK INTO THE FLOCK
SINCE YOU STRAYED FOR
FIVE DECADES OR SO.
BUT THAT'S THE GREAT
THING ABOUT GOD.
HE'LL FORGIVE YOU.
IT'S NEVER TOO LATE.
IT IS NEVER TOO LATE.
SO NO RUSH TO GO BACK TO CHURCH.
I SAY, WAIT UNTIL YOU'RE
TOO OLD TO GOLF OR FISH.
IT IS NEVER TOO LATE!
PERSONALLY, I'M PLANNING
ON A DEATHBED THING.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
NOW, I GOT THE DEED
ALL SIGNED OVER,
SO THAT LAND IS OFFICIALLY OURS.
WELL, UNCLE RED,
I HEARD THERE IS
NO HIGHWAY COMING THROUGH.
I HEARD THAT YOU DREAMED
THIS WHOLE THING UP.
THIS BIG SCHEME OF YOURS
IS SUPPOSED TO BE WHAT
HAPPENS TO A PERSON
AFTER THEY HAVE 50 YEARS OF
UNATTENDED HEAD INJURIES.
NO, HAROLD, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THAT RUMOUR.
DOESN'T BOTHER ME A BIT.
YOU KNOW WHY?
WHY?
I STARTED IT, HAROLD!
I'M JUST TRYING TO COOL OFF
MY REAL ESTATE PARTNERS.
WELL, IT WORKED.
I HEARD THEY WERE
GOING TO SUE YOU.
THE ONLY REASON THEY BACKED OFF,
THOUGH, IS BECAUSE THEY THOUGHT,
YOU KNOW, THE LEGAL FEES COULD
CUT INTO THEIR $5 CLAIM.
NONE OF THAT MATTERS,
HAROLD, OKAY?
I OFFERED TO GIVE THE
GUYS THEIR MONEY BACK,
AND THEY ACCEPTED, OKAY?
SO FROM NOW ON,
THE PROPERTY,
AND THE PROFIT
WHEN I SELL IT,
WILL BE ALL MINE.
WELL, HOW COME IF YOU CAN
AFFORD TO PAY THEM ALL BACK,
WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST BUY THE LAND
ON YOUR OWN THE FIRST TIME?
BECAUSE I'VE GOT TO PAY
FOR THE LAND TODAY.
THE REFUNDS TO THE
GUYS CAN BE DEFERRED.
THAT'S HIGH FINANCE, HAROLD.
THAT'S BEYOND YOU.
OH, YEAH, I THINK
I GOT IT.
YOU WANT TO SIT AROUND AND DO
NOTHING AND MAKE MONEY,
BUT YOU DIDN'T WANT ANYBODY
ELSE HOARDING IN ON IT.
YEAH, THAT'S PRETTY
MUCH IT. YEP.
HEY, WHERE DID YOU GET
SO SMART ABOUT MONEY?
I WATCH THAT
SHOW "TRADERS."
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
I'M TOTALLY ASHAMED OF YOUR
GREED -- I'M JUST SAYING.
WELL, FINE, HAROLD.
GIVE ME $200, AND I'LL CUT YOU
IN FOR HALF THE PROFIT.
NO, THANK YOU!
THERE'S GOING TO BE NO HIGHWAY;
THEREFORE, THERE WILL
BE NO PROFIT.
WELL, THEN HOW CAN THAT
POSSIBLY MAKE ME GREEDY?
YOU'RE AMAZING, UNCLE RED.
YOU'RE TAKING SELFISHNESS TO
THE POINT WHERE IT ACTUALLY
HELPS PEOPLE.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU TEENAGERS
ABOUT SETTING A GOOD EXAMPLE.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
OH, YEAH. YOU'RE SETTING
AN EXAMPLE FOR A VERY
IMPRESSIONABLE AND
VULNERABLE GROUP
WHO WANT TO DRESS
LIKE YOU AND ACT LIKE YOU;
NAMELY, ADULTS.
NOW, SEE, ADULTS CAN'T ADMIT
THEY'RE OVER THE HILL.
THEY WANT TO BE YOUNG AGAIN.
BECAUSE THEY REALIZE HOW
BADLY THEY BLEW IT THE
FIRST TIME AROUND,
THEY WANT A SECOND CHANCE.
THEY FIGURE AS LONG AS THEY
DRESS LIKE TEENAGERS AND
ACT LIKE TEENAGERS,
NOBODY'LL NOTICE THAT THEY'RE
OLD AND WRINKLED AND OUT OF IT.
YOU GUYS STARTED WEARING THE
SPANDEX; SO DID ADULTS.
YESTERDAY, I SAW A 250-POUND
JOGGER LOOK LIKE A 3-D NEON MAP
OF THE FORMER YUGOSLAVIA,
AND BOSNIA WAS
INFRINGING ON SERBIA.
YOU TEENAGERS STARTED WEARING
THE PLATFORM SHOES AND THE
POLYESTER CLOTHES,
NOW THE ADULTS ARE GETTING OUT
THEIR OLD FLOWER POWER T-SHIRTS
AND BELL BOTTOM JEANS.
AND AT THIS POINT, THE BOTTOMS
ARE A LOT BIGGER THAN THE BELLS.
SO BEFORE YOU DO
OR WEAR ANYTHING,
TAKE A MINUTE, AND THINK ABOUT
HOW YOUR PARENTS ARE GOING
TO LOOK DOING AND WEARING
THE SAME THING.
AND IF NUDITY EVER
BECOMES A TEENAGE TREND,
WE'RE IN FOR ONE UGLY SUMMER.
WELL, THIS WEEK ON ADVENTURES
WITH BILL, HAROLD AND BILL --
LOOK OUT.
LOOK OUT, HAROLD!
I GUESS BILL WAS TRYING
TO PAINT HIM!
THEY'RE OUT IN ONE OF THOSE
PAINT BALL UNITS WE GOT
OUT NEAR THE LODGE.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHETHER THIS
CROSSES OVER FROM A SPORT INTO
AN ARGUMENT OR EVENTUAL WAR.
ANYWAY, THEY'RE GETTING THEIR
COVERALLS ON THERE.
(GUNSHOTS)
OH. OH!
BILL, YOU'VE GOT THE GUN --
OH, MAN!
THERE'S SOMETHING FOR
YOU YOUNGSTERS...
DON'T EVER FIRE A GUN
INSIDE YOUR COVERALLS.
ALL RIGHT, THEY'RE GOING OVER
TO THE PRACTICE RANGE THERE.
THEY HAD THE DUMMIES OF THE
MEN -- YOU KNOW, THE CUTOUTS.
THEY'RE SHOOTING AWAY.
LOOK AT THEM GO!
OH, MY GOSH.
I HOPE THERE'S NEVER ANOTHER
WAR BECAUSE WE WON'T WIN.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
JUST RELAX.
GO SEE HOW YOU DID.
GO CHECK THE TARGETS.
AWAY YOU GO.
HOW DO YOU THINK THIS WENT?
HAROLD, YOU'VE GOT
THEM SURROUNDED.
HOW DID YOU DO, BILL?
WELL, IT'S A MURDER/SUICIDE.
SO THEN THEY GO OUT THERE AND
THEY HAVE THESE WAR GAMES.
OH, LOOK AT THAT.
BILL HAS GOT THE TELESCOPE
LOOKING FOR HAROLD.
AND -- WHERE IS HE?
OH, IT'S BOND.
PLYOBOND.
OH, HOW'D THAT GO,
WOULD YOU SAY, OUT OF TEN?
SO BILL IS WANDERING AROUND.
STRANGE THING HAPPENS NOW.
HE HAS A LITTLE
DISCUSSION WITH A TREE.
OH! AND BILL HAD A COMPLETE
PERSONALITY CHANGE THERE.
AND, UNFORTUNATELY AND
SURPRISINGLY, IT WAS WORSE.
HE GOT VERY VIOLENT AND STARTED
REALLY ARMING HIMSELF FOR A
HUGE ARMAGEDDON --
A PAINT ARMAGEDDON.
HE GOT THE PAINT SPRAY CANS
THERE ON THE -- YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M SAYING.
OH, MY GOSH,
IT'S NOT RAMBO,
IT'S HAMBO.
AND THERE HE GOES
CHASING HAROLD.
OH, MY GOSH, HAROLD,
RUN. RUN.
RUN LIKE THE WIND.
LOOK AT THE NIPPLES
ON THAT THING.
THERE GOES A LITTLE
HAND GRENADE.
WATCH OUT, HAROLD! WATCH OUT!
OH, MY GOSH.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH, BOY, THEY'RE COMING
THICK AND FAST.
OH, MY GOSH! OH, IT'S THE
BOMBING OF BRITAIN.
OH, BOY. OH HE'S GOT
THE PAINTBRUSH DARTS.
LOOK OUT.
OH, MY GOSH, ONE INCH
OR TWO INCH?
HAROLD. HAROLD.
NO, NO, HAROLD, COME BACK!
COME BACK!
HE'S NOT A BAD LITTLE DANCER.
OH, OH! AND THEN BILL
BANGED HIS HEAD,
AND, UNFORTUNATELY,
HE'S BACK TO NORMAL.
YEAH, PEACE LOVING BILL AND
COMING BACK APOLOGIZING
TO HAROLD.
EVERYTHING OKAY, HAROLD?
YEAH. NO HARM DONE, EH?
NO HARM; NO FOUL.
DON'T KNOW WHAT CAME OVER ME.
HAROLD IS VERY,
VERY FORGIVING.
JUST ROLLED RIGHT OFF HIM,
RIGHT, HAROLD?
HEY! WELL, IT DOES NOW.
WELL, UNCLE RED, IT SEEMS
I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY.
YEAH, YOU ALWAYS
DO, HAROLD.
WELL, YOU WERE
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
THEY'RE BUILDING
A BRAND NEW HIGHWAY.
YEP, IT'S GONNA GO FROM
MORTONVILLE TO DINKLEBURG,
RIGHT UP TO MOUNT WALTER AND
STRAIGHT INTO PORT ASBESTOS;
THEREFORE, YES, IT WILL
BE CROSSING YOUR BRAND
NEW PROPERTY.
WHY ARE YOU
TALKING SO WEIRD?
YOU BEEN EATIN' A LOT OF
PLUMS, HAVE YOU, HAROLD?
NO, NO, NO, I'M JUST
SAYING THAT YOU WERE RIGHT.
I WAS WRONG.
YOU RIGHT; ME WRONG.
WHAT'S THE HUNK OF
WIRE YOU GOT THERE?
WIRE? OH, IT'S CABLE.
THIS IS A STRETCH
OF THE NEW HIGHWAY.
PARDON ME?
OUR NEW INFORMATION HIGHWAY.
FIBRE OPTIC CABLE.
YEAH, SEEMS THEY'RE GOING TO
STRING IT FROM TELEPHONE
POLE TO TELEPHONE POLE
ALL THE WAY INTO
PORT ASBESTOS.
SO YOU'RE SAYING THE NEW
HIGHWAY IS AN INFORMATION
HIGHWAY, HAROLD?
OH, YES, FOR YOUR INFORMATION,
Mr. WWW.GREEDY.COM.
WELCOME TO THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW WE CALL
"IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
HAP SHAUGNESSY HAS BROUGHT
SOMETHING FROM HIS HOUSE FOR
ME TO FIX, RIGHT, HAP?
THIS PICTURE FRAME
NEEDS REPAIRING,
BUT IT'S NOT
FROM THE HOUSE.
IT'S FROM THE LOUVRE.
OH, YEAH?
YOU GOT THIS HUNG
IN YOUR BATHROOM, DO YOU?
NOT THE LOO, RED,
THE LOUVRE, IN PARIS.
OH, THE LOUVRE.
OH, YES, IT'S LIKE AN ART
GALLERY OR MUSEUM OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
YEAH, YOU MIGHT
SAY THAT. YEAH!
WELL, I DONATED THIS
IMPRESSIONIST PAINTING
WHEN I WAS LIVING ON
THE WEST BANK THERE.
AND THIS WEEK THEY SHIPPED
IT BACK BECAUSE THE FRAME
IS FALLING APART.
WHAT IS THIS NOW?
IS THIS A VAN GOGH
OR A MONET?
A HAP?
IT'S A HAP?
ONE OF MY
BETTER ONES.
YEAH.
YOU PAINTED THIS,
DID YOU, HAP?
IT'S FROM THE
GREEN PERIOD.
BOY, YOU KNOW, IT SURE SEEMS
LIKE ONE OF THOSE PRINTED
POSTERS.
CAREFUL, RED.
IT TOOK HUNDREDS OF HOURS TO GET
THE PAINT TO LIE FLAT LIKE THAT.
NOW ABOUT THE FRAME --
WHAT ABOUT THE FRAME?
YEAH, YEAH, I'LL FIX THE FRAME.
NO, NO, YOU CAN'T
USE DUCT TAPE.
OH, SURE.
THIS IS PRICELESS!
NO, HAP,
YOU'RE PRICELESS!
I'LL PUT THE TAPE ON THE BACK.
HOW IS THAT?
THERE YOU GO, SHE'S FIXED.
IN THE ART WORLD,
WE SAY RESTORED.
RIGHT.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S AS GOOD AS NEW OR, AS
YOU SAY IN THE ART WORLD,
FAKE!
YOU KNOW SOMETHING? THIS WHOLE
HIGHWAY EXPROPRIATION PROJECT
HAS TAUGHT ME A VERY
VALUABLE LESSON.
WHEN TRYING TO CHEAT YOUR
FRIENDS, MAKE SURE YOU DO
ALL OF YOUR HOMEWORK?
NO, HAROLD. THE LESSON IS LIFE
REWARDS THE RISK TAKERS.
YEAH, RIGHT. YOU'RE OUT
$400, AND YOU OWN A
PIECE OF SWAMP.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
NONE OF THAT IS TRUE.
DID I MISS SOMETHING?
WELL, YOU'RE MISSING SO MANY
THINGS, ACTUALLY, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW, FOR STARTERS,
THE GUY I BOUGHT THE
PROPERTY FROM,
FUZZY NORTON,
HE PASSED AWAY
IN HIS SLEEP DURING
THE SERMON IN CHURCH.
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
IT'S UNFORTUNATE,
ESPECIALLY FOR HIM.
BUT IN HIS WILL,
HE LEFT THE $400
TO THE LODGE,
AND THE LODGE DECIDED TO USE
THAT MONEY TO BUY MY PROPERTY.
OH, REALLY?
YEAH.
WHEN WAS THIS DECIDED?
AT AN EMERGENCY MEETING
WITH AN OPEN BAR.
I MANAGED TO CONVINCE EVERYBODY
THE VALUE OF OWNING A BOG
WHEN SO MANY OF US HAVE
THE OLD APPLIANCES AND
THE CARS AND SO ON.
I FIGURE THAT REAL WET SPOT WILL
SUCK DOWN A FOUR-BURNER STOVE
IN LESS THAN A MINUTE.
IT'S A REAL WIN/WIN SITUATION.
I THINK SO.
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
YOU'RE THE PLANET EARTH.
(POSSUM CALL)
IT'S MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO
AHEAD, HAROLD.
YOU WANT TO COME DOWN?
MAYBE YOU CAN SELL MORE
MISTAKES TO YOUR FRIENDS.
WELL, NO, BUT YOUR PARENTS
MIGHT WANT TO GIVE IT A TRY.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
DIDN'T HAVE QUITE THE PROFIT
MARGIN WE HAD HOPED FOR ON
THE REAL ESTATE DEAL,
SO WE'LL HAVE TO PUT OFF THE
INVESTMENT INTO THOSE BLACK
VELVET PAINTINGS OF ELVIS.
BUT HOPEFULLY THE
PRICE WON'T GO UP.
FOR THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTER]
Harold:  SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
HERE HE IS. TAKE A SEAT.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI
Red: SIT DOWN.
Harold:  I'VE GOT
SOME ANNOUNCEMENTS.
FIRST OF ALL, WITH THE
INFORMATION HIGHWAY COMING
INTO POSSUM LAKE AREA,
A LOT OF THE LODGE MEMBERS
HAVE BEEN ASKING QUESTIONS
AND CONCERNS.
AND FIRST OF ALL, NO, YOU CANNOT
CATCH A COMPUTER VIRUS.
SECOND, THE WORLDWIDE WEB
IS NOT A TOOL OF SATAN
OR ANY ATTEMPT TO IMPOSE
WORLD GOVERNMENT ON YOU.
THIRD, THE INTERNET WON'T
MAKE YOU STERILE.
IT'S OKAY.
AND FINALLY, YES --
YES, I DO KNOW THERE IS
OFFENSIVE MATERIAL ON
THE INTERNET,
AND FOR $10 I WILL SHOW YOU
HOW TO FIND IT. OKAY?