MODERN CAR STEREO IS AN AMAZING THING, ISN'T IT?
DIGITAL EQUALIZATION,
SUPER SURROUND SOUND.
THEY EVEN HAVE A
DETACHABLE FACE PLATE
SO THE SUCKER WHO STEALS YOUR
CAR CAN'T EVEN ENJOY THAT.
WELL, YOU GET THE IDEA.
SO I'M THINKING,
DOESN'T IT MAKE MORE SENSE
IF THEY CAN'T
STEAL YOUR CAR AT ALL?
SO FORGET THE
DETACHABLE STEREO;
WHAT YOU NEED IS A
DETACHABLE STEERING WHEEL.
AND I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT A
NORMAL STEERING WHEEL.
YOU CAN'T WALK AROUND WITH A
STEERING WHEEL IN YOUR POCKET.
YOU'LL LOOK LIKE A DORK.
INSTEAD, GET YOURSELF ONE OF
THESE FOLD-UP VEGETABLE
STEAMERS.
GOT THIS OUTTA
BERNICE'S KITCHEN.
SO NOT ONLY DO I HAVE A
DETACHABLE, COLLAPSIBLE
STEERING WHEEL,
BUT I'VE ALSO
ELIMINATED THE RISK
OF EATING STEAMED
VEGETABLES ANY TIME SOON.
[ APPLAUSE ]
HOW DOES THAT COMPARE
WITH SOGGY BROCCOLI?
IF YOU EVER GET
STUCK IN TRAFFIC,
THIS THING DOUBLES
AS A SNACK BOWL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
YOU'LL ALL HAVE TO
EXCUSE ME A MINUTE.
HAROLD GAVE ME THIS
TEST CARD TO FILL OUT.
IT'S MULTIPLE CHOICE,
SO IT SHOULDN'T
TAKE VERY LONG.
I DON'T PAY ANY ATTENTION
TO THE QUESTIONS, YOU KNOW.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU JUST MARK
THE ANSWERS IN THE SHAPE
OF THE BIG DIPPER,
I FIND I USUALLY PASS.
OKAY, UNCLE RED,
TIME'S UP.
I NEED THE
ANSWER SHEET BACK.
TIME'S UP.
I NEED THE
ANSWER SHEET BACK.
JUST A --
JUST A COUPLE
MORE AND I'M DONE.
WHERE ARE
THE QUESTIONS?
HAROLD, YOU KNOW, THIS IS
A FACE PACED SOCIETY.
NO ONE REALLY CARES
ABOUT QUESTIONS.
THEY JUST
WANT ANSWERS.
IT'S AN I.Q. TEST,
UNCLE RED.
I WAS HOPING TO OPEN A
LOCAL CHAPTER OF MENSA,
AND I NEED
SUITABLE CANDIDATES.
WOULD ANY OF THIS BE
NECESSARY IF YOU HAD
A GIRLFRIEND?
THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
I.Q. TESTS ARE
MEANINGLESS, OKAY?
WHEN A PERSON'S SMART,
THEY KNOW THEY'RE SMART.
WELL, JUST BECAUSE
YOU THINK YOU'RE SMART
DOESN'T MEAN YOU ARE.
YOU THINK YOU'RE LOTS
OF THINGS YOU'RE NOT.
I THINK YOU'RE LOTS
OF THINGS YOU
ARE.
WELL, WHEN WE'RE HAVING
OUR MENSA MEETINGS
DON'T YOU BE UPSET BECAUSE
YOU'RE NOT INVITED.
YOU KNOW, EVEN IF I WAS
INVITED TO YOUR EGGHEAD CLUB,
I WOULDN'T BE DUMB
ENOUGH TO GO.
WELL, YEAH -- YEAH --
I THINK IT'S TIME WE START
RESPECTING PEOPLE FOR
THEIR INTELLIGENCE.
HAROLD, I HAVE A HOME,
I HAVE A VAN AND ALL
MY FINGERS.
AROUND HERE THAT
MAKES ME A GENIUS.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TONIGHT'S WINNER
RECEIVES A THIS COUPON
FOR A FREE SESSION
AT THE POSSUM LAKE
FOOD PACKAGING PLANT
AND BEAUTY CENTRE.
"WHY GO THROUGH THE PAIN
AND EXPENSE OF A FACELIFT
"WHEN WE CAN SIMPLY
SHRINK WRAP YOUR HEAD?"
OKAY, COVER YOUR
EARS THERE, MIKE.
OKAY, RED, YOU'VE
GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET MIKE HAMAR
TO SAY THIS WORD...
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, MIKE, IF SOMETHING
ISN'T CROOKED, IT'S...
OUTSIDE MY EXPERIENCE.
OKAY, LOOK, SAY YOU
GOT A COILED UP ROPE
AND YOU UNROLL
THE WHOLE THING.
NOW YOU'VE MADE IT...
OVER THE WALL!
OKAY, IF YOU HAVE
A FUNNY GUY,
AND THERE'S ANOTHER GUY
WHO'S NOT FUNNY AT ALL,
HE'S CALLED THE
SOMETHING MAN.
HIT MAN.
NO.
OKAY, REMEMBER WHEN
YOU WERE A KID?
ADULTS WOULD SAY,
HOLD YOUR HEAD UP,
SHOULDERS BACK
AND STAND...
IN THE LINEUP.
YOU GUYS ARE
ALMOST OUTTA TIME.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
WHEN YOU'RE IN PRISON,
YOU WANT YOUR
CELL MATE TO BE...
OH! TOTALLY WACKO.
OH, YEAH, 'CAUSE THEN
THEY'LL PUT HIM IN
A STRAITJACKET.
THERE WE GO!
OH, HI THERE,
BOYS AND GIRLS.
RANGER GORD HERE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S REALLY
NO SURPRISE
THAT IN A RECENTLY PUBLISHED
SURVEY OF THE WORLD'S
BEST JOBS,
FOREST RANGER JUST SNATCHED
THE COVETED 257th SPOT,
RIGHT BEHIND TELEMARKETER
AND PART-TIME KEYBOARDIST
IN A JAZZ FUSION QUARTET.
WHY?
WELL, IT'S BECAUSE
WE FOREST RANGERS
BEAR WITNESS TO SOME OF THE
MIRACLES OF MODERN NATURE
THAT YOU PEOPLE ONLY
GET TO SEE ON TV
OR SOME SLAPDASH
EDUCATIONAL FILM.
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
IT'S TIME FOR MY LATEST
EDUCATIONAL FILM.
SO SIT BACK AND ENJOY.
BUT REMEMBER,
MY JOB IS NOT AVAILABLE.
I DON'T CARE WHAT THE PARKS
DEPARTMENT TELLS YOU.
HERE WE GO.
[ CHEERY MUSIC ]
HEY, EVERYONE.
TODAY I'M GOING TO TEACH
EVERY MAN, WOMAN AND CHILD
THE ONLY SURE WAY TO DETERMINE
IF AUTUMN IS ABOUT TO ARRIVE.
THE LEAVES
CHANGE COLOUR?
OH! KIDS GO
BACK TO SCHOOL?
THE AIR GETS A
BIT NIPPY?
YOU'RE BOTH IDIOTS.
IN FACT, THE ONLY
WAY TO TRULY KNOW
IS TO OBSERVE
FLYING SQUIRREL DAY.
"NOT UNLIKE GROUNDHOG DAY
IN THE SPRING,
"FLYING SQUIRREL DAY IS
THE DAY THE FLYING SQUIRREL
"EMERGES FROM HIS
HOLE TO SEE --"
OH! OH! OH! OH!
I KNOW! I KNOW!
TO SEE HIS SHADOW?
CLOSE, HAROLD.
TO SEE THE GHOST OF
MATINEE IDOL, TONY CURTIS.
I DON'T THINK
TONY CURTIS IS DEAD, GORD.
DON'T INTERRUPT THE LORE.
"WHEN THE SQUIRREL
SPOTS MR. CURTIS,
"HE GOES TO NEST TO WINTER
IN HIS THICK LUSTROUS
HEAD OF HAIR."
DOESN'T TONY CURTIS
WEAR A TOUPEE?
WELL, ENOUGH BACK STORY.
LET'S GET STARTED.
THE FIRST THING WE NEED
TO DO IS ROUSE THE
FLYING SQUIRREL.
GENTLEMEN,
SHAKE THIS TREE.
OH, LOOK AT THAT,
MY BADMINTON SHUTTLECOCK.
MY BICYCLE!
OH, MY ANVIL!
THERE'S NOT SQUIRREL
IN THIS TREE, GORD.
I KNOW THAT.
I JUST NEEDED SOME HELP
GETTING A FEW THINGS DOWN.
ACTUALLY, THE ONLY WAY TO
STIR THE FLYING SQUIRREL
IS WITH A MIGHTY
BLAST OF THIS HORN.
[ NO SOUND ]
[ SMALL SQUEAK ]
LOOK!
UP THERE!
LOOKS LIKE WE'VE SUMMONED
AN ENTIRE SQUADRON.
OH, NO.
RUN, HAROLD.
THEY THINK YOU'RE MATINEE
IDOL TONY CURTIS!
WELL, THAT'S GOTTA
BE A FIRST.
WE NEED TO
DISTRACT THEM, RED.
DO YOU SEE ANY NUTS?
NOTHING BUT.
THIS IS NO TIME
FOR LEVITY, MAN!
SCROUNGE! SCROUNGE!
HEY, YOU SQUIRRELS,
DOWN HERE.
LOOK, IT'S PRECIOUS SUSTENANCE
FOR THE COLD MONTHS AHEAD.
[ HORN BLASTING ]
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S
GOING TO BE AN EARLY
AUTUMN AFTER ALL.
SO FROM ALL OF US
TO ALL OF YOU,
[ HAROLD SCREAMING ]
HAVE A NICE FALL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
ISN'T IT A PAIN WHEN YOU'RE
DRIVING BY YOURSELF
YOU HAVE TO REACH OUT THE
OTHER WINDOW FOR SOMETHING?
WELL, WHAT ABOUT THIS...
WHAT IF YOU COULD BE
THE DRIVER AND THE PASSENGER
AT THE SAME TIME?
WOULD THAT BE
GREAT OR WHAT?
SO TODAY ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW YOU CAN ADD
DUAL CONTROLS TO YOUR CAR
SO YOU CAN DRIVE
FROM THE RIGHT-HAND SIDE.
THAT WAY YOU CAN BE THE
PASSENGER IN YOUR OWN CAR.
BECAUSE THE PASSENGER
NEVER HAS TO ORDER THE LUNCH
OR WORK THE A.T.M. MACHINE
OR BLOW INTO
THE BREATHALIZER.
OKAY, I'VE GOT MY SECOND
STEERING WHEEL IN PLACE HERE.
ACTUALLY, I GOT THIS
FREE FORM MOOSE THOMPSON.
IT HAD RIPPED OUT OF HIS CAR
WHEN HE SLAMMED ON THE BREAKS.
GUESS HE GAVE IT...
NOW I JUST NEED SOME WAY
OF CONNECTING THAT ONE
TO THE REAL STEERING WHEEL.
I'M THINKING OF USING ONE OF
THE INNER TUBES OUT OF
THIS BICYCLE.
YOU KNOW, THIS HERE
IS CALLED A KICKSTAND.
OKAY, THAT WENT
PRETTY WELL.
THE NAP HELPED.
NOW I'VE GOT DUAL CONTROLS
AND STYLISH WHEEL COVERS.
JUST NEED SOME WAY
TO HOOK UP THE PEDALS.
OH.
IF THERE ARE
KIDS WATCHING,
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
GET THEM OUT OF THE ROOM.
OKAY, NOW, THE HOCKEY
STICKS ARE PERFECT FOR THIS
BECAUSE THE BLADE IS STRONG,
AND IT'S SHAPED LIKE A PEDAL.
SO NOW ALL I GOTTA
DO IS ATTACH THESE TO
THE FLOOR OF MY VEHICLE.
AND MY REAL FEET
ON THE FAKE PEDAL
IS GONNA ACTIVATE THE
FAKE FEET ON THE REAL PEDAL.
NOW, IF YOUR VEHICLE HAS THE
FLOOR COMPLETELY ROUNDED
OUT OF HER,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO ABANDON
THIS PROJECT ALL TOGETHER.
INSTEAD, YOU COULD
BUILD A GLASS BOTTOMED BOAT.
OKAY, NOW TO HOOK UP THE GEAR
SHIFT AND TURN SIGNALS
AND WHAT HAVE YOU,
I RAN A FEW BUNGEE CORDS UP
OVER THE REAR VIEW MIRROR
DOWN THROUGH
THE SEAT BELT CLIPS.
NO REAL SET RULE ON THAT,
BECAUSE EVERY CAR IS
DIFFERENT, OF COURSE.
SO YOU PRETTY MUCH HAVE TO
USE YOUR OWN BRAIN POWER.
YOU MAY WANNA ALLOW A FAIR
EXTRA BIT OF TIME THERE.
OKAY, OTHER THAN THAT WE'RE
PRETTY WELL SET HERE.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW THINGS LIKE
GETTING THE MAIL
OR PARALLEL PARKING
ARE A BREEZE.
AND THE DUAL CONTROLS
MAKE THIS VEHICLE
AN EXCELLENT
DRIVER TRAINING TOOL,
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T FORGET
WHO'S TEACHING WHO.
I WANNA TALK TO
YOU GUYS OUT THERE
THINKING ABOUT
CHANGING CAREERS.
MAYBE AFTER TEN YEARS
OF WEARING A PAPER HAT
AND ASKING PEOPLE IF
THEY WANT FRIES WITH THAT,
HEY, MAYBE IT'S
TIME TO MOVE ON, HUH?
BUT I'LL TELL YOU THE JOB
MARKET IS TOUGH OUT THERE.
IF YOU WANNA COMPETE,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO GET SOME
EDUCATION AND TRAINING.
I SUGGEST THE
CORRESPONDENCE SCHOOLS
BECAUSE IT'S SOMETHING YOU
CAN DO IN YOUR OWN HOME,
IN YOUR OWN PACE,
IN YOUR OWN UNDERWEAR.
YOU CAN EVEN PLAY HOOKY BY
MAILING IN AN EMPTY ENVELOPE.
BUT, SEE, AT THE
CORRESPONDENCE SCHOOLS
YOU CAN LEARN A TRADE,
BECAUSE YOU WANNA
BE CERTIFIED IN SOMETHING.
BEING CERTIFIABLE
IS REAL IMPORTANT IN
THE BUSINESS WORLD.
YEAH, BECAUSE IF YOU'VE
GOT A CERTIFICATE,
IT DOESN'T MATTER IF YOU
DON'T HAVE ANY EXPERIENCE
OR EVEN ANY IDEA WHAT IT IS
YOU'RE TRYING TO DO,
BECAUSE WHEN YOU SCREW UP
YOUR BOSS'LL BE ABLE
TO BLAME IT ON
WHOEVER GAVE YOU
THE CERTIFICATION.
KIND OF LIKE PASSING
THE BUCK, EH?
YOU DON'T WANNA BE CAUGHT
WITH THE HOT POTATO.
YOU'LL BE RIGHT BACK ASKING
PEOPLE IF THEY WANT
FRIES WITH THAT.
SO GET YOURSELF
SOME TRAINING.
AND IF THAT DOESN'T WORK OUT,
WELL, JUST TELL
ANY PROSPECTIVE EMPLOYER
THAT YOU DO EVERYTHING
RED GREEN SAYS,
AND THAT'LL PROVE
YOU'RE CERTIFIABLE.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
announcer: THIS SUMMER
TERROR COMES TO POSSUM LAKE.
WHAT IS THAT?
AND IT SUCKS.
IS IT A BUS?
NO, NO,
IT'S A TRUCK,
A SEWAGE TRUCK!
WHO'S DRIVING IT?
THERE'S NOBODY
DRIVING IT!
announcer:
SOME MEN ARE BORN TO SEWAGE.
OTHERS HAVE IT
THRUST UPON THEM.
IF THAT UNIT HITS DEADMAN'S
CURVE AT OVER 55,
IT'S GONNA BE A
BLOOD BATH.
WELL, SOME KIND OF BATH.
announcer: THIS SUMMER,
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD FACES
EVERY SEPTIC PROFESSIONAL'S
WORST NIGHTMARE...
THE DEVASTATING POWER OF
A RUNAWAY SEWAGE TRUCK.
I'M GOIN' IN!
Harold:
OH, COME ON, UNCLE RED.
WE CAN OPEN
THEM TOGETHER.
COME ON, I DON'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE NOT INTERESTED
IN THE RESULTS
OF THE I.Q. TEST.
COME ON
HAROLD, THERE'S NOTHING
IN THAT ENVELOPE
THAT'S GONNA
CHANGE MY LIFE.
THERE'S SOMETHING IN MY
ENVELOPE THAT'S GONNA
CHANGE MY LIFE.
COME ON.
HERE'S YOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANYTHING,
WE'RE NOT KEEPING IT.
[ SCREECHING ]
158! 158!
THAT IS SO GOOD!
I'M THE MOST GIFTED.
I'M LIKE TWO
POINTS AWAY.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
THAT MAKES ME?
I SURE DO,
HAROLD.
OKAY,
IT'S YOUR TURN.
OPEN YOURS.
AND REMEMBER, THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH BEING OF AVERAGE
INTELLIGENCE.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
SO?
HOW'D YOU DO?
I DUNNO.
YOU TELL --
IS 160 MORE
THAN 158?
NO WAY!
THERE'S LIKE A
MISTAKE OR SOMETHING.
HAROLD, HAROLD,
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH BEING OF AVERAGE
INTELLIGENCE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU SAID SO
YOURSELF.
THESE TESTS ARE
MEANINGLESS.
YEAH, BUT I SAID THAT
BACK WHEN I WAS DUMB.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WAIT!
Red (voice over): WALTER ASKED
US TO COME OUT THE BACK.
HE HAD HIS KITE
STUCK UP A TREE.
WE WERE GONNA HELP HIM.
I DIDN'T ACTUALLY
SEE THE STRING.
SO NOW WE HAD
THE KITE UP THE TREE
WITH A VERY SHORT
STRING ON IT.
SO I FIGURE, YOU KNOW,
THERE'S A BUNCH OF ROCKS.
USUALLY ROCKS EVERYWHERE.
JUST PICK UP A
ROCK AND THROW --
BE CAREFUL WHERE
YOU GO, WALTER.
THERE'S SOME ROCKS
YOU MIGHT TRIP ON THERE.
WALTER'S GOT A
PRETTY GOOD ARM,
BUT IT'S NOT
CONNECTED TO ANYTHING.
AND HE KNOCKS
THE BIG NEST -- OH!
AND THEN THE -- OH!
THEN THE NEXT COME
DOWN OUT OF THE TREE.
NOW, WALTER HAD AN UNU --
HE THOUGHT THIS WAS
SOME KIND OF TRANSCENDENTAL
RELIGIOUS EXPERIENCE.
IT'S NOT THE
MAHARISHI HUMPHREY.
THEN A BIG BIRD --
OKAY, I SEE.
WE'RE MESSING AROUND WITH A
PRETTY BIG BIRD'S NEST.
I THINK THE BEST THING,
GET THE NEXT BACK UP
INTO THE TREE.
WE DON'T -- LET'S NOT WORRY
ABOUT THE KITE RIGHT NOW.
SO DALTON AND I CAME OVER
TO GIVE HIM A BOOST UP.
NEVER SURE HOW YOU
DO THAT WITH THE ARMS.
LIKE YOU HOLD ONE WRIST --
AND WE GOT INTO A --
WE HAD A BIT OF
AN ARGUMENT.
LUCKILY, THE POSSUM LODGE
OATH COMES IN REAL
HANDY THERE.
THEN WALTER COULD JUST --
YOU WANNA GET UP THERE.
JUST GET THE NEST
BACK IN PLACE,
WALTER, GET THE KITE
WHILE YOU'RE UP THERE.
BUT THE BIRD STARTS
COMING BACK
AND DOESN'T QUITE UNDERSTAND
WHAT WE'RE DOING,
AND THEN -- OKAY, WE HAD
NO PLAN FOR THIS.
BOY, THEY GET A LOT OF
LIFT OUT OF THOSE WINGS.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE THEY HAVE
A CRANE OR SOMETHING.
MAYBE THAT IS A
CRANE, THAT BIRD.
AND THEN HE
DROPPED THE NEST.
THERE, WALTER'S GOT THE NEST
RIGHT BACK IN PLACE.
PERFECT.
BIRD'S GOTTA BE HAPPY NOW.
THE BIRD'S HAPPY.
WE'RE HAPPY.
NICE JOB.
NICE JOB, WALTER.
TAKE A BOW.
AND THE BIRD
I GUESS IS HAPPY
BECAUSE IT DROPPED WALTER.
WE GOT YOU
OH, NO. OH, NO.
I GUESS THE WIND
TOOK HIM THERE.
BUT HE'S OUT IN THE -- WHAT
WE FIND AROUND THE LODGE
IS IF YOU GIVE TO NATURE,
NATURE WILL GIVE BACK TO YOU.
SO WE GAVE WALTER
A SORE BACK,
AND WE GAVE THE
BIRD THE NEST,
AND THE BIRD GAVE
US THE KITE.
WHAT A GREAT DAY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, WHEN THE
WEATHER WARMS UP,
A LOT OF PEOPLE LIKE TO HANG
THEIR LAUNDRY OUTSIDE.
IT'S CHEAPER THAN
USING THE DRYER,
AND IT'S A REAL NICE WAY TO
BLOCK OUT THAT RUSTY K-CAR
YOU'VE HAD UP ON
BLOCKS SINCE 1985.
THE PROBLEM WITH MOST
CLOTHES LINES IS THE
WORK INVOLVED.
YOU EITHER HAVE TO WALK THE
LENGTH OF HER AS YOU GO,
OR YOU GOTTA HORSE THE
LINE AROUND THE PULLEYS.
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT IF YOU
COULD MOVE YOUR CLOTHES LINE
WITH JUST A TOUCH
OF A BUTTON?
WELL, YEAH.
ALL IT TAKES
IS A LITTLE CREATIVITY
AND YOUR TRUSTY
BETAMAX VCR.
MAKE THAT YOUR DUSTY
OKAY, I JUST STUCK
AN OLD TAPE IN THERE
AND I WOUND THE OTHER END
AROUND MY FAR PULLEY
SO I COULD USE
IT AS A CLOTHES LINE.
AND YES, YOU COULD
DO THIS WITH A VHS,
BUT EVERYBODY KNOWS
BETA'S A LOT BETTER, EH?
AND YOU CAN USE
ANY TAPE YOU WANT.
I THOUGHT GONE WITH
THE WIND WAS A GOOD CHOICE.
NOW, TO MOVE MY
CLOTHES OUT,
ALL I DO IS PRESS FORWARD.
AND WHEN I WANT THE
CLOTHES TO COME BACK,
I JUST HIT REWIND.
AND IF I NEED THE CLOTHES
TO DRY IN A HURRY,
I GO INTO SHUTTLE MODE.
BOY, HAROLD'S HAVING
A LOT OF TROUBLE
DEALING WITH ME BEATING
HIM ON THE I.Q. TEST.
HE MAY EVEN BE ACTING WEIRD
AND NOT MAKING ANY SENSE,
BUT WITH HAROLD
YOU NEVER REALL KNOW.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
(imitating Red)
HOW YOU DOING?
HAROLD,
YOU LOOK GOOD.
(imitating Red)
THANK YOU. APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
OH, COME ON, HAROLD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
(normal voice)
WELL, MY SOCIAL
PSYCHOLOGY CLASS TAUGHT ME
PEOPLE CAN CHANGE
THROUGH EMULATION.
SO I'M GOING TO RAISE MY
I.Q. BY TRYING TO BE
MORE LIKE YOU.
DO YOU REALISE HOW
DIFFICULT THAT IS,
HAROLD?
WASN'T EVEN THAT
EASY TO SAY.
YOU CAN'T BE ME.
BESIDES, WE ALREADY
HAVE A ME.
WHAT WE DON'T
HAVE IS A YOU.
AH, YOU'RE GONNA
MISS ME THAT MUCH?
DON'T GET CARRIED AWAY,
HAROLD, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, YOU HAVE A
HIGHER I.Q. THAN I DO.
THAT GOES AGAINST ALL
SENSE OF FAIR PLAY
AND LOGIC.
OKAY, OKAY.
ACTUALLY, HAROLD,
I DON'T HAVE A
HIGHER I.Q. THAN YOU.
I SWITCHED THE RESULTS.
YEAH.
WHAT?
LIKE YOU JUST OPENED THE
ENVELOPES AND SWITCHED 'EM?
THAT'S WHAT I DID.
THEN YOU RESEALED
THE ENVELOPES?
YOU'RE ONTO ME.
YOU COULDN'T POSSIBLY THINK
YOU WERE GONNA GET AWAY
WITH THAT.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
I'M NOT AS SMART AS YOU.
AND THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE ASHAMED OF.
YEAH, THANK YOU,
HAROLD.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, MEETING TIME.
BOY, YOU'RE AS SHARP
AS A TACK AREN'T YOU?
JUST KEEPS COMING.
YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN
IN A MINUTE.
OKAY.
160! 160!
[ APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, SO IF MY
WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
NOW, I TOLD HAROLD I SWITCHED
I.Q. RESULTS WITH HIM
AND THAT'S HOW
I BEAT HIM.
NOW, HE'S ACCEPTED THAT,
AND I'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU DIDN'T MENTION
THAT I SWITCHED
RESULTS WITH YOU FIRST.
NO HUSBAND NEEDS AN I.Q. TEST
TO FIGURE OUT WHO THE
SMART ONE IS.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND THE GENIUS HAROLD,
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, EVERYBODY.
YEAH, SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT MEN, I UNDERSTAND
HAROLD HAS A BRIEF
ANNOUNCEMENT.
YES, VERY MUCH SO.
OKAY, YES, ALL THE
I.Q. TESTS ARE BACK NOW,
AND WE'RE DEFINITELY
GOING TO HAVE
OUR LOCAL CHAPTER OF MENSA.
NOW, THE THING IS YOU HAVE TO
HAVE A MINIMUM I.Q. OF 150.
SO MOST OF YOU ARE GOING
TO HAVE WORK IN PAIRS.