You know, as you get older
you're faced with
two choices...
either take down your
full-length mirror,
or buy a fitness machine.
See, the beauty
of a treadmill is
when you get
tired of walking,
you don't have to worry about
making it back home.
You just stop walking.
And start snacking.
But after a
week or so now,
your wife and you have
given up on lookin' good
and you're stuck
with the unit.
Can't even give it away,
because everyone you know
already has one
they're
trying to unload.
That's why they advertise it
as "stores under the bed,"
because that's all you
ever do with it...
unless, of course, you can
turn it into something useful.
First thing you have to
do is remove the handle.
Okay, next you
wanna cover the belt
with the handyman's secret
weapon, duct tape,
but you put it on
sticky side out,
so it's more like the
handyman's secret flypaper.
Oh, and get yourself one of
these sand-filled ashtrays.
They're kinda
hard to come by
with all the anti-smoking
legislation.
But you can usually find a
couple of them
in the hospital
waiting room.
Or maybe if you
live near the beach
you can get some
sand from there.
It'll probably have more
cigarette butts in it.
And there
you have it...
your very own
industrial-sized belt sander.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
All right.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, I appreciate that.
Bit of a situation this
week up at the lodge.
The flagpole fell down.
Well, okay,
it was knocked down.
I knocked it down.
But she went down easy.
I mean, I couldn't have
been doin' over 50.
Anyway, the pole flies across
the lake like a javelin,
and it hits
Old Man Sedgwick's car,
which, ironically,
is also a Javelin,
and the flag wraps
around him like a diaper.
Or, I should say,
like another diaper.
So what I've done is
I've made a claim
on the insurance company
for a new flagpole.
It was like 37 bucks!
Which would use up
the whole lodge kitty,
plus we'd have to
borrow another 30.
Uncle Red!
Yeah?
I just got the response
from the insurance
company.
Doesn't look like
a cheque, Harold.
No.
They're not going
to pay the $37,
because it doesn't
exceed our deductible.
Well, what is
our deductible?
$10,000.
$10,000
deductible!?
Well, what's
The Lodge worth?
Well, the land's worth
about $100,000,
you know --
Wow!
Yeah, oh, yeah.
Then we've got the lodge
and all the out buildings,
and of course plus all the
work that you've put
in around here.
And that brings it down
to about $9500.
Well, why would
we have $10,000 deductible,
on something that's
only worth $9,500?
Well, it's the only
way we could get
insurance.
Well, we're not gonna
do that anymore,
Harold.
Oh, no, no, no!
Don't tell me we're
getting out of the
insurance business.
No, I'm gonna get into
the insurance business.
I'm gonna start my
own insurance company.
Yes, I'll insure
the lodge.
What the heck, eh,
$10,000 deductible,
I'll be making
a fortune.
And I'll tell
you what else...
I'll charge 10% less
than the insurance
company does now,
so everybody's
a winner.
Wow!
I'm a winner!
No, no, no.
No, you're
the deductible.
[ APPLAUSE ]
It's time for the
Possum Lodge word game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Today's prize
is this coupon
for a hot air
balloon ride
over the Port Asbestos
archery range.
"Duration of
ride varies with...
"competence of archers."
All right, Blair,
cover our ears there.
Red, you've
got 30 seconds
to get local snowmobile
aficionado, Blair Cobden,
to say this word...
All right,
Winston.
And... go!
Uh, okay, Blair, remember
you did that stunt
where you took your
snowmobile over the
edge of Rock Reef point,
caught the upside
of the boathouse
and landed
on the toolshed,
and everybody who saw it
wanted to know, who's...
Next.
No, no, no, no.
But you didn't try
to blame anybody else.
You said you
were completely...
Loaded.
No, okay, no, but
the machine was wrecked,
the boathouse
was on fire,
but you went right up to that
cop and you said, "I am..."
Canadian.
[ LAUGHTER ]
Okay, okay, but...
but you were accountable,
you did it.
you were...
The man.
All right,
let's go another way.
Let's say your girlfriend
announces that she's pregnant.
But you do
the right thing.
You go right to her dad
and you tell him
that you are...
Gay.
[ LAUGHTER ]
Almost outta time,
here, Red.
Yeah.
Okay, Blair, when you
train new snowmobilers,
you teach 'em
to be smart and...
Plan your escape route.
That way when
you smash stuff,
no one knows
who's responsible.
There we go!
Before we tried it,
our lives
were a mess.
The idea of even
having company over
sent me into a panic.
I was so anxious
I had to use the
bathroom all the time.
But I couldn't.
It was hurting
our marriage.
It was hurting us!
BOTH: Thank you,
Winston Rothschild.
Now we entertain,
barbecues.
Even chili!
It's been
pointed out to me
that for one
reason or another,
a lot of the viewers
are not exactly like me.
Seems they don't have the
wherewithal or the desire
to do projects like making a
reclining chair out
of a stove.
Does that make
them useless drones
who have no
reason to live?
Well, according to our
public relations people,
it's not for me to say.
So this time on
Handyman Corner,
we're not gonna build
something from scratch,
'cause apparently some of you
aren't that itchy.
Instead, we're gonna
show you how to assemble
a beautiful coffee table.
It's from one of
those stores
where they make you
do most of the work
and then charge you
for the privilege.
I think it's
from the same guy
that invented
self-serve gas.
But it's a simple job,
because all the
pieces and hardware
come in the one box.
Maybe two or three boxes would
have been a better move.
Okay, now don't
get upset
if the furniture gets a few
nicks and scratches
during the
unpacking process.
Distressed furniture
is very popular.
Like I said, though,
this is a simple project,
because all the
pieces come pre-cut
and pre-drilled.
You even get all
the necessary hardware.
Heck, it comes with
detailed instructions.
I believe this will be a
Swedish-style coffee table
because it was
a Swedish store.
I don't know why
all the Swedish stores
sell their stuff
in kit form,
rather than
make it for you.
Maybe with the free love,
the Swedish furniture
makers all go home early?
Okay, we're ready
to start assembling it.
Just check the pre-drilled
holes in the pre-fab pieces
until you get
a few to match up.
There, that's better.
Okay, now, just make
sure that the screw
isn't longer than
the hole it's going into.
Otherwise, the point will
come out the other side,
and that can
be a real pain,
especially if you're
building a loveseat.
Once you get the first
two pieces together,
just keep adding on
until you run out of parts.
If you run out
of hardware,
that's never a problem.
Well, I got nothing
to worry about.
I got hardware left over.
You know,
that happens to me
every time I put
furniture together.
But I got the coffee table
put together no problem.
Kind of an
odd looking unit.
It's that modern style
of furniture
that Swedish
people go for.
Not really my taste,
but then,
I don't drive a Volvo.
And it's just that easy.
So remember, if the women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you put together.
Oh!
And if you ever
need spare parts
or have any problems.
They usually put the company
phone number and address
on the bottom of
the instruction sheet.
Huh!
Says here this is
a bunk bed.
[ APPLAUSE ]
The other day I went
to the mall with Bernice.
Let's just say
I lost a bet
and leave it at that.
Anyway, we're walkin'
by this store
and I see a pair
of jeans for sale
that were already
faded and dirty
and runnin' ragged
at the cuff.
And this wasn't a
used clothing store,
you understand.
These were 100 bucks
worth of brand new.
I couldn't
figure this out.
I mean, imagine
buying a new car
with rust and dents
and bullet holes in it --
that'd be kinda cool...
Anyway.
So I stopped the
first teenager I saw,
and I asked her
to explain it.
Well, I learned
two things...
number 1: kids in malls
talk like merchant marines;
number 2: these same kids
will pay more for stuff
that has that
"lived-in" look,
because lookin'
"lived in" is cool.
Well, that made me
feel real good.
I realised, hey,
I'm not out, I'm in.
Here's all of us
middle aged guys
checking out these teenagers
with their smooth skin
and full heads
of purple hair
and feeling jealous,
when they should
be jealous of us.
We're the ones with
that lived-in look.
And we don't even need to
wearin' clothes to
pull it off!
Heck, most of us are
so lived in we're worn out.
Remember,
I'm pullin' for you.
We're all in this together.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Call Rothschild's when
you have the right stuff...
in the wrong place.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Well, it's all done.
I'm officially the
insurer of the lodge.
"Red Green Insurance...
"you're in
calloused hands with RGI."
Uncle Red!
Yeah?
Are you sure you've
thought this through?
No time for that
at my age, Harold.
You know,
the $10,000 deductible
will only save you from
paying property damage.
You know, there's personal
injury and accidental death
that you're gonna
have to worry about.
Oh, no, Harold,
when a guy makes a
decision to join
the Lodge,
he's already an
accident.
If somebody dies,
they're not gonna come
lookin' for a cheque.
No, no, they won't,
but their lawyers will.
That's why insurance
is so expensive.
Well, I don't have
to worry about that.
Oh, no?
Yeah. Yeah.
You know, Uncle Red,
lawyers are smarter
than you.
Yeah, okay, well,
when you're not smart
enough to be a lawyer,
you become a judge.
And my judgment was
to get all the guys
to sign this waiver
that guarantees they
will never take
legal action
against me
or the Lodge.
I need you to
sign this too.
You mind if
I read it first?
It never ends with you,
does it, Harold?
Mr. Green, uh, I have
an insurance claim.
Oh, yeah?
The outhouse door slammed
against my knee.
Well, that's
what you get for
sittin' down.
Look, this is a
serious accident here.
I can't even
do this, look.
What's that worth?
A little smile.
Here it comes.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red: IT WAS A
BEAUTIFUL SUNNY DAY,
SO HAROLD AND WALTER
HAD DECIDED TO
TAKE A LITTLE TRIP
TO THE BEACH,
GET THAT TAN
THING GOIN' THERE.
NO PROBLEM WITH THE U.V.,
BUT HAROLD WAS SOCKING
THE OLD CREAM ON THERE
PRETTY GOOD.
AND THEN, UH, WALTER
HIT A BUMP OR SOMETHING,
AND, UH --
THAT WAS UNFORTUNATE.
IT WAS ACTUALLY -- I BELIEVE
THAT WAS A BEACH UMBRELLA,
WHICH THEY HAD FORGOTTEN
TO PUT IN THE TRUNK.
AND, UH, WALTER WAS UPSET,
A LITTLE BIT ANGRY.
HAROLD,
HE'S NEVER ANGRY,
BUT SOMETIMES
HE PRETENDS TO BE.
THEN HE PAYS THE PRICE.
SO WALTER OPENS
THE TRUNK,
AND THERE'S A LOT
OF STUFF IN THERE.
SO HE STARTS CHUCKING --
EASY.
LOOK OUT, HAROLD.
LOOK OUT. LOOK OUT.
HAROLD... INCOMING!
THERE YOU GO.
BUT WHAT HE DOESN'T
FIND IS A JACK,
SO -- WELL, HE'S GOT A PRETTY
HEAVY DUTY SUITCASE HERE.
MAYBE THE SUITCASE COULD
ACTUALLY SUPPORT
THE WEIGHT OF THE CAR.
SO HE ASKED HAROLD IF
HE WOULD LIFT UP THE CAR,
AND WALTER WILL SLIDE
THE TRUNK UNDERNEATH.
SO HAROLD IS
PRETTY STRONG --
UH, STRONGER THAN
HIS PANTS, FOR EXAMPLE.
SO NOW WALTER DECIDES
TO CHANGE JOBS.
OH, THERE'S
THE PROBLEM THERE.
HEH-HEH, GIRLY ARMS.
SO WALTER'S GONNA
PICK UP THE CAR,
AND HAROLD WILL SLIDE THE
SUITCASE UNDER --
NO, HAROLD --
OKAY, NO, OKAY.
HAROLD, HAROLD,
HE'S HOLDING THE CAR UP.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
ABOUT THE CLO --
YOU DON'T NEED
TO FOLD THEM, HAROLD!
JUST GET --
HAROLD, GET THE SUIT --
HAROLD, THE SUITCASE!
GET THE SUITCASE!
OKAY, THEY'VE GOT
THE SUITCASE IN THERE,
AND OH, IT'S ON HIS FOOT.
OH, IT'S OKAY.
OF COURSE, HAROLD
WANTS TO APOLOGIZE.
JUST GET THE SUITCASE
UNDER THE CAR!
OKAY, BUT NOT THERE.
NOT THERE.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
UP ON ITS END.
THERE WE GO.
LOOKIN' GOOD.
LOOKIN' GOOD, YEP.
NOW JUST SET THE
CAR DOWN ON THE SUITCASE,
SHOULD BE GOOD,
SHOULD BE GOOD.
DOWN SHE GOES,
DOWN, DOWN, DOWN.
AND GOOD.
NOW, OF COURSE,
THE PROBLEM IS,
WHAT ARE WE GONNA
USE FOR A SPARE?
HAROLD HAS A SUGGESTION...
HMM.
I DON'T THINK SO.
OKAY, WHAT CAN
THEY USE AS A SPARE?
GOTTA IMPROVISE.
AND HE REMEMBERS THERE WAS A
FIRE HOSE THERE ON THE WALL
AND MAYBE IF HE TOOK
THE WHOLE REEL AND
EVERYTHING OFF,
THAT WOULD PROBABLY
FIT RIGHT ON THERE.
UH, HAROLD'S NOT USED TO
STEALIN' STUFF.
SO THEY GOT IT ON THERE
AND NOW ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS
FILL THE HOSE WITH WATER
THAT'LL ACTUALLY
CREATE THE TIRE,
BUT YOU WANNA TURN THAT
NOZZLE OFF THERE, HAROLD.
OKAY, THERE'S A LOT
OF PRESSURE THERE.
EASY NOW,
EASY, EASY, EASY.
HEH-HEH, GREAT
TO BE YOUNG, ISN'T IT?
SO HE GETS THAT ON THERE,
FULL OF WATER,
GETS HER ALL SECURED.
AND WALTER SAYS, OKAY,
JUST PUSH HER OFF THE JACK,
AND AWAY WE'LL GO.
SO HAROLD'S ALL SET.
AND THEN GIVE HER A PUSH.
OH!
OKAY, YEAH.
AWAY YOU GO, HAROLD
AWAY YOU GO.
CATCH UP TO HIM.
YOU CAN CATCH HIM.
AWAY YOU GO.
ENJOY YOUR DAY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
You know, one mark of
a real creative person
is the ability to take an
unfortunate mistake
and turn it into an
incredible opportunity.
Your wife knows
what I'm talkin' about.
So today I'm gonna
show you how a handyman
can turn a minor mishap
into something
the whole family
can enjoy.
Now, I know what
you're asking.
What mistake could
you possibly have made?
Drivin' without
your glasses, right?
Nope, I don't even
wear glasses.
The problem was
building the garage
ten feet too far forward.
Okay, first step in
creating an opportunity...
start up the car.
Now you just drain the rad
into the water gun here,
and then just
wait a few minutes
for the engine
to overheat.
I don't see a mistake;
I see your
very own home sauna.
It would be even better
if it was a Swedish car.
Then we'd have a
real Saab [sob] story.
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
Yes, I did!
I did!
I told you something
like this would happen.
But oh, no!
You know everything
about insurance.
You're like
Mutual of Brouhaha.
Just find me the
Lodge charter, okay.
I got this covered.
Ha!
You have nothing covered,
from the Lodge
to your own butt.
Well, you can't
buy butt insurance.
Tell them.
Go ahead, tell them.
Okay, apparently
an insurance claim
has been launched
against the Lodge.
And you personally.
And me personally.
For $11,000.
We had some kind of
barbecuing mishap apparently.
Yeah, the Lodge propane
safety sticker,
it expired in 1973.
I thought you
wanted me to tell this.
Well, it's too big a
story for just one
narrator.
So Mr. Insurance
Underwriter
is about to become
Mr. Under Arrest.
You're gonna
need a lawyer.
No, I don't!
I don't need any more
legal mumbo jumbo, Dumbo.
All I gotta do is find
out who's behind this
and then I can
deal with them.
Oh, okay.
DALTON: Hey, Red!
How's the insurance claim
coming, huh?
You know what, I bet that guy
would settle out of court
for $10,000.
Uh-huh.
How would you
know that?
My lawyer --
um, um, um --
A lawyer.
I talked to somebody.
You know, I watch
"Law and Order."
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Meeting time!
We'll settle this
in a minute, Dalton.
I'll be right down.
Okay, if my wife
is watching,
I'll be coming straight home
after the meeting.
I have an insurance claim
against me,
so I'm liable
to do anything,
but I'll certainly
check your policy first.
And to the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself
and Harold
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge,
keep your stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Sit down, take your seat.
Meeting's coming to order.
Everybody sit down.
All rise!
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
RED: Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the man's prayer.
I'm a man, but I can change,
if I have to...
I guess.
Okay, men, I was looking up
in the Lodge charter
on this insurance
claim business,
and apparently whenever the
Lodge has a financial problem
like this $11,000,
each member is personally
responsible to pay it.
But the way it works is it's
pro-rated to your net worth.
And the guy with the
most net worth around here
is Dalton.
So Dalton, you're actually
responsible for 95%
of the 11 grand.
And then there's
an additional $1500
for my company to
do all the paperwork,
so I'm thinking it might
be in your best interest
to find out who's
behind this
and make this go away.
I'll talk to Ann Marie.
Uh --
I mean, I'll talk to
whoever it is.
Great. Great.
Thank you.
Where does it
say that?
Never mind.