And now it's time for the show that answers
the questions who, what, where, when and why,
what you ask and I'll say the red green show
where you ask, Well, right here, where else
and why?
Because we like you.
And of course, you know, we need the money
and the time slot was available.
And who, while only the greatest human being
who ever walked through that door at the back
of the lodge there, you know, sort of to a
left by the by the snowshoe right there.
Here he is, the star of my show and my
uncle, Mr.
Red Green.
It's about how, Howard, what the hell?
Thank you. Welcome to possum, Elijah.
It's a pleasure for me to be here.
That doesn't mean I wouldn't be happier
someplace else.
And speaking of someplace else, you've
already met my nephew on a more personal
note, my producer and director Harold.
Hello. I'm the guy who makes the buttons in
the show.
Go do this.
Oh, sure, blame it on the buttons.
Now the guys are pretty edgy up at the lodge
this week, I don't I don't know what it is,
but I tell you I don't like it.
You think maybe it's just everybody starting
to get on each other's nerves.
Sometimes people do that when they get on
each other's nerves, it starts to bug other
people. I think that would. It could be.
What do you think, Uncle Red?
Well, Harold, when
That happens, you can't even control where
you live or stuff.
He just starts to bug you and you don't even
know why.
Yeah, I imagine it's a
Great idea, right? That's the big thing.
It's it's great. It's great to know why
people keep doing the same thing again and
again and again and again and again and
again and again and again and again and again
and again and again and again and again.
And then what? They do it again.
Oh, well, that's a theory.
May have to kill him someday.
Anyway, I think what the guys need is a
vacation.
I mean, I know they come up here to get away
from it all, but sometimes they start
bringing it with them.
You know, like this morning. I asked, Well,
man, Sedgwick to pass me the salt, right?
So I said, OK, no, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that. I didn't mean I had a
cup of coffee about a week ago.
Kind of jangle my nerves and I feel bad.
No, I didn't mean it. Go ahead.
Go on. Go on, go on. This morning I asked
Asshole man Sedgwick, pass me the salt,
right?
He says, Oh, well, what's in it for me?
Well, I meant at that time.
And you see this month's edition of Humongous
Fish.
No, no, I haven't seen that dog.
Well, I'm not going to get real column.
They say the Marlin are biting off the
Florida coast Gulf side.
Oh, that's good fishing buoys.
I'll tell you, I was there about 10 years
back.
Did you catch anything he just did?
Well, as a matter of fact, on my last day
there, my son was just dipping down below the
horizon. I was just coming back up from the
bathroom after throwing up my Dramamine.
As soon as I sat down in that chair bang,
something hit my bait and that line went up
from between my legs so fast you couldn't
see it.
You could hear that real squealing, Hey,
that much those ball bearings heating up.
She was one hundred and seventy two thousand
degrees kelvin.
Luckily, fear helped me cool it down.
That's what happens when you hear a line
cutting the prop.
Talk to one of my ladies in the blanket.
No. So OK, so yourselves.
He actually was the biggest Marlin you ever
saw.
But four men and a small boy that landed 17
tons of fish.
Oh, that muscle. And how would you clean
something like that now?
Hmm. Well, he tossed it on a boat trailer
and told it to the nearest car wash and went
at it with a buck sock. The manager refused
to honor our gas coupons.
That's a nice tumblers, though.
Anyway, I'm thinking about mounting another
expedition to the Sunshine State.
No way. Oh, Disney World.
Oh, come on, we can't afford to go.
The airfares are too much. And besides, you
guys should all want to bring your fish back
as carry on.
Oh, now we happen to know somebody who owns
an RV.
No, but the RV, you want to take the RV to
Florida?
Yeah, I was thinking how nice that RV would
look parked on a Florida beach?
Oh, sure. Can you just see it?
I could just I could see it, huh?
And the bumper sticker?
Oh yeah. I visited Disney World Busch
Gardens.
We saw SeaWorld, the one man.
I could just see it, you know, I could just
see it.
So the the RV is going to Florida.
Absolutely. Oh, it's so totally awesome.
Oh, Busch Gardens, Disney World.
The girls on the beaches, you know, with
their teeny weeny microscopic bikinis.
You know, I got my
Binoculars, you know, my suntan lotion and
all real
High number two, you know, because you can
use those.
And of course, you know, fishing for Marvin,
for Marlin, Marlin, you know, whoever is
around.
Well, I'm up for it. I'm in you, Eddie.
You hate fishing? Well, I'm going.
All right, Bill.
Ok, that's all right.
I'll go up to the RV. I got I got all the
new maps.
I just got them from the RV Gypsy Road club.
Oh yeah, they got all all these little
symbols where they marked out, where you can
get like fat parking spots and you get cheap
gas, huh?
We can just jump on that I-75 right through
Tennessee.
Oh, what? You know, I'd be up for it too.
You know, anybody asks me or not red.
How about one?
No. Thanks, Eddie. Not if here is going to be
out of town.
But I think your boy should realize, you
know, Ben likes going places and he likes
coming back, but he really doesn't like
being there.
Well, that's because nobody likes
Him being there. Well, how are we going to
get to Florida if we don't take Glenn's RV?
I mean, you know, I mean, how are you guys
Going to get to Florida without his RV?
Is what, man? Well, we have Glenn's RV.
I never said anything about Glenn.
Oh boy. Well, what do you hold?
He hold it right there. And oh, that's
that's subversive.
That's manipulative.
No way. Count me out.
That is wrong. No.
Of course, if you chip in for gas, Harold, we
could see our way clear to dropping you off
at Disney World.
Ok, I'm in.
Oh boy, I got a real bad feeling about this.
Even though it would do Harold Hero a world
of good to meet the real goofy.
It'll be a piece of cake.
Not your cake, of course.
Yay. See Gleno.
You're feeling all right. Look a little in
there.
You're not coming down with anything, are
you?
No, I don't think I can watch this.
See you guys later. Hey, this will be great,
Glenn.
The good for the R&B too.
To get on this long run like this under your
belt, you're doing a world of good.
Oh, great.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I can see the RV now parked underneath those
swaying palm trees, huh?
Yes, their lawn chairs out front.
I'm in the hammock and he's at the barbecue.
I can't see the barbecue, of course.
Harold's out front row and his frisbee
herald of the kid's got his heart set on
shaking Pluto's paw, you know.
Oh, okay, sure.
I can't ask you not to go.
It's a trip of a lifetime.
Oh yeah, yeah.
The Sun's beaming down and Bill's gathering
up coconuts.
And what am I doing, Doug?
Run on your marina. I kid you.
I can't run my marina from Florida.
Well, we'll send you a postcard, then duck.
It's my RV. See the thing I go where the RV
goes?
Well, now, Glenn, there's not room enough
for all.
Well, then, honey, you can't go.
Well, that's not the way it works, Glenn,
though.
You see, with all the stuff, it's it's all
of us or none of us.
Oh, well, grab a chair then, because
nobody's going in, huh?
I went away a humbug, no.
That's the song you sing with a hornet in
your shorts.
This week on
Handymen Corner, we're going to show you what
you can do with all that crap your wife makes
you bring in every winter.
You know, first of all, there's the picnic
table.
She doesn't want that in the backyard
because she wants to get it out of the
weather. And also, it stops the snowmobilers
from running into the clothesline and letting
you have the lawn edging.
I just want you to bring that in.
You know, it goes between the garden and the
lawn.
She doesn't want you to run over that with a
snow blower again.
And now this, I can understand the croquet
said, OK, fine.
You don't want to be playing croquet when
the balls are all frozen and spit like cooked
peas. On the other hand, the indoor outdoor
carpeting is a bit of a stretch because to
me, the word outdoor is right in the name,
you know, along with odor.
I guess it's part of outdoor and shouldn't
this be outdoors?
But apparently not.
And finally, my work socks, which have been
added on the line since around Lent.
But you know, rather than accept us as a as
a storage problem, the true handyman accepts
this as a challenge, and I happen to be
packing my staple gun when I'm packing my
staple gun. I'm ready for any challenge.
Oh, sorry, Harold.
All right. Step one is to wet everything off
the table except for the the carpeting, and
we're going to attach the carpeting and then
we're going to attach the lawn edging to the
table using the staple gun, just like re
upholstery in a chair.
Come see, come saw, and all we do is put the
croquet hoops in where the gaps are and then
cover them over with the work socks using
the handyman secret weapon duct tape.
So there you have it. Let the winner stay as
long as it wants.
I'll be inside here playing croquet pool.
And you know, if you wanted to build some
sort of a ball return system here, you could
use the downspouts from your eavesdropping
or even your toilet drainpipes.
Ok. Yellow ball in the side pocket.
Oh, remember, if the women don't find you
handsome, they should at least find it handy.
Nice break.
It is winter, the snow is plowed and piled
deep at the side of the road here and there,
sticking out of the giant mounds, the hands
or feet of snow pedestrians.
Brett O'Gara, what do you do when you left
school?
Well, Harold, usually I'd go home and empty
the pigsty, you know, except Thursdays,
Thursdays, I hose down the horses.
I hated Thursdays.
No, no. I mean, like after you graduated
school, would you do then?
Well, after grade seven, I went right into
the army.
They take them. They take you into the army
grade seven.
Well, they do that. If you're 19 years old
now, why don't you join the army here in a
career, huh?
No, no, I don't think so.
I don't think marching in step is a big plus
on anybody's resume anymore.
I'll go and join the army.
No, wait. You got to get up early.
Go marching around, wear uniforms, live in
Spartan quarters, eat lousy food, carry guns.
Get killed, be killed.
Oh no, no.
All for minimum wage.
I can do that here.
I just don't like it.
I'll tell you, this Florida trip has been on
and off again more times than old man
Sedgwick's toupee.
Now, Glenn says he's going to make it a solo
run.
Thirty two hours of thunder straight down
there, 40 hours, actually, if he sticks to
the speed limit. But the guys are holding
fast with that all for one and one size fits
all thing, at least publicly.
I have a feeling a few of them are trying to
cut side deals, you know, on the side deals.
It's funny. Isn't that a guy?
Nobody likes? Glenn sure gained a lot of
popularity.
But, you
Know, read, he's got the power.
You know what they say? Power and personal
popularity.
They go hand in hand.
Well, yeah. Well, how come nobody can stand
the guy who produces and directs this show?
Well, they're jealous, aren't they?
Oh, that must be it. Well, anyway, everybody
is kind of looking forward to going down in
Florida. Even Harold here.
I think he's dying to go down to Disney
World and ride on one of them big, huge
teacups.
That'd be so neat.
Oh, do you think it's like you sit in a big
teabag?
Like I say, everybody's got their own reasons
for going.
Except Eddie, I don't know why he's gone.
And of course, myself, there's nothing for
me there.
Oh yes, there is. What about the fountain of
youth?
You know, you remind me of Ponce de Leon.
You got the beard and you can ever find
anything.
Just take us into the next segment, Harold.
Oh, I struck a nerve.
No, but I'm going to.
Oh, OK.
Oh, right. Bed look, I'm glad you're here.
I need your advice. Yeah, you do.
Do you know what's in Florida swamp Disney
World?
Do you know what's in Disney World?
Mgm Studios and now they've got backstage
studio tours when I see Mr.
Spielberg. I'm going to leap from the bus.
I'm going to jump up on that stage and I'm
going to sing and dance my way into his
heart. I'm going to get noticed red.
Wow by the security guards.
At the very least, you've got something in
the oven there, ready.
Everything is under control.
Tucker, what do you think I should do?
Should I? Should I sing and play clarinet?
Tap dance with a mannequin, juggle
telephones and tell jokes.
What's really popular
Talent?
I'm going to knock their socks off red.
I got what they need.
Well, unless they need a cook, Eddie, have
you got raw, unpeeled potato sitting right on
the heat there?
It doesn't matter.
This is my career.
Yeah, you're right. Those are large potatoes.
This is my moment red.
And I'm going to seize my moment.
Shabu, shabu.
Everyone's a critic.
I've got a real book when I want to say
those, I've got a real special adventure with
Bill today, he's going up to all our friends
down in Australia.
First of all, the stables for sale and what
we wanted to do today was Bill had an idea to
do something on boomerangs.
He'd bought this boomerang down at a max max
max boomerangs.
I think it's called anyway.
Oh gosh, there goes the wrapper.
Look at that. Look at that.
Holy mackerel.
Well, I guess they've been left out.
Got it. Nice catch.
I don't know how that worked, but by golly,
Bill's got the touch.
So he gets a boomerang.
The ideas, you know that you're trying to
use this as a well, maybe didn't quite get
the grip just just right on that and give it
another go.
Give another call. All right, I'll try
Harrisville.
I'll try. I've never done this before.
I think I did the other way.
But by golly, I can't believe this kervin
ran around by the barn and coming up, Oh,
nice, 'cause I'm kind of proud of myself
there.
So now Bill says, OK, before you go hunting
or whatever with a boomerang, you got to sort
of do a little target practice.
So luckily, I had these empty bottles in the
back of the van.
Purely coincidental, I'm sure.
Oh, I'll take a little bit longer to
Set those up than what we'd planned, but we
got nothing but time here on the red green.
Joe and I give her a try and not bad.
Not bad. I'm bad, Bill.
Give her a shot. Let's see how this goes.
Oh, I'll I'll.
Yeah. Wow.
Oh, I told him to
Have that bunion removed.
Get that out there. Oh, oh my gosh.
Oh, that was going to affect the flight.
Just outside.
Oh, thank you, Bill.
All right, we're going to try her again on
this one.
He fires them up, she goes, and you're
looking up into the sun there and you can't
see it values.
Forget about that one. Bill's got Bill's got
a couple more.
So here come on.
Yeah. Oh, all right.
Let her go. Let her go.
Oh oh my lucky hat.
Oh my gosh. Bill, what have you done to my
hat?
I don't care how it happened.
You did it. All right, all right, settle
down, settle down, settle down, settle down.
Look at that. Look.
Oh, my gosh.
This is for bringing down the big game like
elephants or or even I would say humans.
Well, she's out of control there to turn the
other way back.
Get out. Ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow.
They shot their. Well,
by golly, this Florida trip has gotten real
complicated.
Now Glenn is charging everybody five hundred
dollars to go to Florida in his RV.
I mean, that's more than the airfare.
But then you can't have beer parties and
food fights on an airplane.
So it looks like everybody's going to go
except Glenn, which means no one's going to
go except Glenn.
Apparently, that all gets explained at
tonight's Lodge meeting.
I think it'd be simpler. Florida came here.
Oh yeah, wouldn't that be great?
We could sure use some fresh orange juice.
Can you not just picture me lying in the
white sand?
Yeah. You blend right in, Harold.
The cry of the wild possum.
It's meeting time.
Now we get to find out who gets to go to the
Sunshine State and who doesn't.
Yeah, I'm beginning to understand why there
are so many old people in Florida.
Takes your whole life to make the travel
arrangements.
All right. Why are?
All right.
You know,
Flora is writer Ingrid
Matlin, gentlemen of both this Florida.
Forget it. Oh no, no, no.
You see, Glenn, we all want to go with you
guys.
But yeah, yeah, we feel really bad, Glenn,
we want you to go, we really do.
It wouldn't be any fun without, you know,
what's the catch, what I'm supposed to fly
down or something? No, no, no.
You see again.
Yeah, look OK.
Yeah. All right. Here we go.
The Nine Amigos are forward about, oh god.
There's only room for eight on the RV.
Yeah, that's what we're towing a boat.
I mean, someone can just ride in the back.
Well, right in that boat, all the way to
Florida this summer.
It's like riding the convertible mountain.
Now we're going to draw to see who goes in
the book.
All right. No, now we've all put our names,
these little pieces of paper here, Glenn.
So paper pencil good.
And just put your name out there.
Drop in the bucket.
And now we'll commence with our own lucky
draw.
Oh.
Watch out there.
Thanks largely to the drawing, seeing how
you're uninvolved and unbiased
And not interested, OK?
You're a lucky loser, is Glenn Brock's.
Huh. But I'm guessing oh, one and nine.
Right? Well, I'll get to see the RV rolling
down the highway.
Well, I better go pack a windbreaker.
We're even done. Yeah.
Yes. I don't know about the.
Oh, what a guy like that.
No. You know, this is kind of interesting.
Now look how much Glen Braxton's handwriting
looks like yours.
Isn't that weird? Oh, you'd probably say, Oh,
Gypsy?
And he spelled his last name wrong.
That's unusual, isn't it?
Well, well, he was nervous. Read, you know.
Bill, Gwen Braxton, right, oh.
Most got it wrong. Braxton Glen Braxton
Braxton, you.
You won't tell them, will you read
And give up two weeks of peace and quiet?
Go to your mind now.
All right. Our large business bill.
Ok, I'm going to call on the Eddie.
Eddie, go get some entertainment.
Yes. Well, I'd like to do the the audition
piece that I plan to use at the MGM studio
when we arrive there at the Cotton Center
there, that special thing.
It's a mind piece. It's a mind piece and
I've entitled it quite simply, man in the
wind, in a box that's shrieking while doing
a tug of war.
Smiling.
Well, Gwen has to be about the saddest, most
desperate guy I've ever met around here.
That's going somewhere. I. Still, the votes
got a windshield, so we won't be too bad off.
He can take off a couple of his coats after
they hit North Carolina.
Anyway, my wife is watching.
I'll be coming straight home after the
meeting and I thought maybe we could have our
very own stay at home vacation.
I'll bring a quart of orange juice and a sun
lamp, and maybe we could go to Adventureland
unless the roller coaster is closed.
So until next time, on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole gang up here in Possum
Lodge. Keep your stick on the ice.
It sounds like it's a book movie.
Watch your trust there it.
I listen. How should we help?
My employees in the blanket, oh, how easy
fellas come on.