(Medieval melody plays)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW".
HERE'S THE MAN WHO'S
AS MUCH A PART OF THE NORTH
AS TREE SAP AND MOOSE DROPPINGS,
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE,
RED GREEN.
(Cheering)
WOO!
(Applause)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
MY WIFE DRAGGED ME TO
THE POSSUM LAKE LITTLE THEATRE.
THEY WERE DOING "CAMELOT".
IT'S SMART TO DO A MUSICAL.
WHILE YOU'RE SITTING THERE
THINKING THEY CAN'T SING,
YOU FORGET THEY CAN'T ACT.
"CAMELOT", I LOVE THAT!
(Singing) CAMELOT
I KNOW IT MAY SOUND
A BIT BIZARRE
YOU DON'T JUST SOUND BIZARRE,
HAROLD.
BUT YOU KNOW,
WHILE I'M SITTING THERE,
I'M THINKING, IN A WAY
POSSUM LODGE IS
KIND OF OUR CAMELOT.
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
TO DRESS UP
AS KNIGHTS OF THE ROUND TABLE
AND FORCE PEOPLE
TO BECOME CHRISTIANS?
YEAH, YEAH, BECAUSE THEY WORE
ARMOUR AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
THEY HAD, LIKE, CHAIN MAIL.
I GOT A CHAIN LETTER ONCE,
BUT THAT'S A LOT DIFFERENT.
JUST IGNORE HIM. IT'S NOT RUDE.
IT'S SAVING HIS LIFE.
STAY TUNED AND WATCH
MIDDLE-AGED GUYS
RECREATE THE MIDDLE AGES.
(Singing) IF EVER
I WOULD LEAVE YOU
DON'T TEASE
ME, HAROLD.
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): IF I HAVE TO
EXPLAIN THIS,
WE'LL BE HERE ALL EVENING.
WE DO HAVE EDGAR MONTROSE
TRYING TO HEAR.
I'LL LAY A LITTLE PEACE SIGN
ON BUZZ SHERWOOD.
I'LL BUILD A CROSSBOW
THAT PUTS HAIR ON YOUR CHEST.
OLD LADY BENKMAN,
PRINCIPAL OF THE SCHOOL,
HAS OFFERED US
THEIR OLD SPORTS EQUIPMENT.
SHE'S HOPING TO PARTICIPATE
IN OUR MEDIEVAL DAY.
SHE WANTS TO PLAY GUINEVERE.
SHE'S A LIGHT ON THE GUINE,
BUT SHE'S HEAVY ON THE VERE.
I DON'T THINK
USED SPORTS EQUIPMENT
IS THE BEST IDEA TO
REPRESENT THE MIDDLE AGES,
UNLESS I'M MISSING SOMETHING.
YOU'RE GONNA BE, HAROLD.
HOW ABOUT PURPLE HORSES?
DO YOU THINK WE COULD USE
PURPLE HORSES AT ALL?
PURPLE HORSES?
THE SCHOOL BOARD
HAS PURPLE HORSES?
THAT WOULD EXPLAIN
THE MEAT IN THE CAFETERIA.
THAT SAYS "POMMEL HORSES,"
UNCLE RED.
WE COULD USE THAT.
WHAT ABOUT THIS
THE LONG POLE VAULT THING?
PARALLEL BARS.
THAT'S HOW I SPRAINED
MY ARMPITS.
YEAH.
I HATE GYM.
(Red): IN KEEPING WITH
OUR MEDIEVAL TIMES THEME,
BILL WILL HAVE
A LESSON ON FENCING.
KIND OF
A DELICATE FRENCH THING.
UH-OH! -- VERY GOOD.
ALMOST LIKE A BALLET.
VERY, VERY DIGNIFIED.
UNFORTUNATELY,
I'M NOT FROM FRANCE.
HERE WE ARE WITH BUZZ SHERWOOD
TO PLAY
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
IS THIS THE PART WHERE
I FILL UP THE SHOPPING CART?
NO.
TODAY'S PRIZE IS
THREE BOTTLES OF
POSSUM HILLS DRINKING WATER
AND A PAIR OF RUNNING SHOES.
HAROLD, GIVE ME THE WORD.
I'LL SHOW THE FOLKS AT HOME
WHAT IT SAYS.
BUZZ, YOU GOT 30 SECONDS
TO SAY THIS WORD.
LET'S DO IT.
UH, HARMONY.
BAD MUSIC!
TRANQUILLITY.
OO, OO, AH, HIDING PLACE!
WAR AND...
COMMISSION.
COMMISSION?
THE WARREN COMMISSION --
IT WAS SUCH A CROCK.
OSWALD
COULDN'T HAVE BEEN ALONE!
TWO BEERS.
CLOSING TIME!
LIVE LONG AND PROSPER,
MR. SPOCK.
WHAT DOES THE MINISTER
SAY TO YOU?
ADULTERY IS A SIN.
REMEMBER ABOUT A MONTH AGO,
THE COPS PULLED YOU OVER.
WHAT DID THEY SAY?
YOU CAN CALL FLYING YOUR PLANE
THROUGH A MALL
FREEDOM OF EXPRESSION,
BUT WE CALL THAT
DISTURBING THE PEACE.
THAT'S THE ONE!
(Strums acoustic guitar)
LIFE IS LIKE A RIVER
IT WINDS AND EBBS
AND FLOWS
IT CARRIES YOU ALONG
FOR QUITE AWHILE
THEN IT SHOOTS WATER
UP YOUR NOSE
LIFE IS LIKE A RIVER
NOTHING SCHEDULED
NOTHING PLANNED
YOU CRUISE ALONG
AS FAR AS YOU CAN
AND AT THE END
YOU'RE PROBABLY DAMMED
WITH THE LODGE INTO
A MIDDLE-AGES FRAME OF MIND,
I'LL TAKE HANDYMAN CORNER
AND BUILD SOMETHING APPROPRIATE
FOR THE AGE OF CHIVALRY.
REMEMBER THAT SHOW "ROBIN HOOD"?
YOU KNOW WHAT I LOVED?
THE WAY THEY'D SEND MESSAGES
BY ATTACHING THEM TO AN ARROW
AND SHOOTING THEM
INTO A TREE OR A PEASANT'S BACK.
WHY DON'T WE USE
THAT TECHNOLOGY
TO SEND PACKAGES
THROUGH THE WOODS?
SORT OF A COURIER DE BOIS.
IF THAT MAKES YOU BLANCH,
THEN MAYBE YOU'RE
A BLANCHE DUBOIS.
OR A T.V. CRITIC.
FIRST THING YOU NEED
IS A POLE VAULT POLE
TO USE AS YOUR BOW.
I GOT THIS FROM
THE POSSUM LAKE SCHOOL,
BUT YOU CAN GET ONE FOR FREE
BY STANDING NEXT TO
THE POLE VAULT EVENT.
AS THE GUY GOES OVER,
HE'LL LET GO OF THE POLE.
YOU'LL BE MILES AWAY
BY THE TIME HE COMES TO,
WHEN HE LANDS ON THE GROUND,
'CAUSE THE CUSHION GOT MOVED,
YOU KNOW, BY SOMEBODY.
YOU'LL NEED SOME KIND OF
A BOW STRING.
YOU COULD USE A ROPE
OR A GARDEN HOSE.
BUT I SUGGEST FAN BELTS
OUT OF YOUR CAR.
OR BETTER YET, FAN BELTS
FROM YOUR FRIENDS' CARS.
SURE, THEY'LL BE TICKED
WHEN THEIR CARS ARE
BOILING OVER ALL THE TIME.
BUT VEHICLES DON'T BELONG
IN THE MIDDLE AGES,
EXCEPT MAYBE BUSTER'S EDSEL.
WE'LL NEED AN ARROW
FOR THIS RIG.
I SUGGEST A SHOVEL,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'LL BE
SENDING GOVERNMENT DOCUMENTS.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
"HOW WILL ONE GUY BE ABLE TO
WORK THIS HUGE BOW AND ARROW
ALL BY HIMSELF?
WELL, THAT'S A LITTLE SURPRISE
I'VE BEEN SAVING FOR YOU.
I'M NOT JUST BUILDING A BOW.
(Squeaking)
I'M BUILDING A CROSSBOW.
NOW, WITH A BOAT TRAILER,
YOU GET THE PERFECT ANGLE
FOR LAUNCHING.
WITH HER MOUNTED ON WHEELS,
YOU HAVE THE FULL
390 DEGREE RANGE FOR AIMING.
NOW, WHAT YOU DO IS
GET YOURSELF A PIECE OF ROPE,
TIE IT TO THE BOW LINE,
AND THEN JUST HOOK YOUR WINCH
RIGHT ON THERE.
AND CRANK HER BACK.
(Humming)
(Groaning)
THERE WE GO.
WE HAVE TO ADAPT THE HANDLE
SO THAT SHE'LL HOOK ONTO
THE BOW LINE.
JUST PULL THAT OUT
NO, NO.
WE'VE GOT TO ATTACH SOMETHING
TO THE SHOVEL
TO CARRY THE PARCELS.
YOU COULD USE A LUNCH PAIL,
A BREAD BOX.
I PREFER A BEDPAN.
IT'S LIGHT, AERODYNAMIC,
AND IT PREPARES THE RECEIVER
FOR BAD NEWS.
NO NEWS IS GOOD NEWS.
ALL RIGHT, JUST GOING TO AIM
THIS UP TO BRAXTON'S MARINA,
'CAUSE I'VE GOT THIS
ELECTRONIC IGNITION
THAT I HAVE TO RETURN
OR PAY FOR IT.
NOW, TO SEND OUR PACKAGE,
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
CUT THE TWINE.
YOU COULD TIE A SPOOL OF THREAD
ONTO THE SHOVEL
AND YOU COULD
TRACE YOUR PACKAGE.
THERE WE HAVE IT.
THE POSSUM LAKE
MEDIEVAL COURIER SERVICE,
WHEN IT ABSOLUTELY HAS TO
GET THERE OVER WATER.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
AND I'M GUESSING THEY DON'T,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
FORE!
(Crashing)
SORRY!
AH.
(Red): BE THERE
WHEN RANGER GORD DISCOVERS
ANOTHER PHOBIA.
SOMETIME YOU'LL BE
AT A SOCIAL FUNCTION
WHEN ONE OR TWO YOUNGER WOMEN
WILL START FLIRTING WITH YOU.
THEY'LL PAT YOUR BALD HEAD,
LAUGH AT YOUR CORNY JOKES,
MAYBE PLAYFULLY SIT IN YOUR LAP
OR GET YOU ON THE DANCE FLOOR.
MAKE YOU FEEL ALIVE?
MAKE YOU FEEL LIKE
A PISTOL AGAIN?
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU ARE OFFICIALLY
AN OLD GEEZER.
(Laughing)
YEAH, YOU.
I'M TALKING TO YOU.
THAT'S THE FIRST SIGN.
THOSE WOMEN ARE FAWNING YOU
BECAUSE THEY THINK IT'S CUTE
TO SEE SOMEONE YOUR AGE
DOING THE FRUG.
THINK OF WHO ELSE WAS THERE.
A BUNCH OF YOUNG GUYS WITH
TESTOSTERONE IN THEIR EYES,
AND ONE THING ON THEIR MIND.
WHEREAS YOU ARE OLD
AND FUN AND SAFE.
IT'S NOT BAD
BEING AN OLD GEEZER.
DID YOU HAVE FUN?
DID YOU ENJOY BEING
THE CENTRE OF ATTENTION?
SURE YOU DID.
WHILE YOU'RE RUBBING
LINIMENT INTO YOUR JOINTS,
YOU'VE GOT THE MEMORY.
I'M PULLING FOR YOU 'CAUSE
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER,
YOU OLD GEEZER!
(Applause)
ON BEHALF OF OUR VIEWERS
AND MANKIND IN GENERAL,
WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU
DOING HERE, RANGER GORD?
HERE'S MY IDEA.
AFTER A RAIN,
THE FIRE DANGER IS LOW.
SO I'M BUILDING
A SPRINKLER SYSTEM
FOR THE FOREST.
IN THE FOREST.
IT'S MANDATORY
IN MOST BUILDINGS,
ñ WHY SHOULDN'T IT BE
IN THE FOREST.
I'M DRILLING OUT
THESE OLD BRANCHES
TO USE AS PIPES
TO CARRY THE WATER ALONG.
I'M USING PINE CONES
AS SPRINKLERS.
GORD, DID YOU EVER THINK
THERE'S A TIME LIMIT
ON HOW LONG A PERSON
SHOULD BE A FOREST RANGER?
NO, NO WAY.
NOT FROM ME, RED, BECAUSE
AS SMOKEY THE BEAR ONCE SAID,
"ONLY YOU CAN PREVENT
FOREST FIRES."
HE SAID THAT TO ME ONE DAY.
I REMEMBER THE DAY
LIKE IT WAS YESTERDAY.
I WAS IN THE BASEMENT.
I TURNED ON MY 26-INCH ADMIRAL
AND THERE WAS SMOKEY THE BEAR,
LOOKED ME STRAIGHT IN THE EYE
AND SAID
"ONLY YOU CAN PREVENT
FOREST FIRES."
I SAID, "YES, SIR."
IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN A BURDEN
TO LAY ON A 9 YEAR OLD,
ESPECIALLY SINCE I DIDN'T WANT
TO PREVENT FOREST FIRES.
I WANTED TO STUDY MEDICINE.
BUT WHEN A BEAR SENDS
A PERSONAL MESSAGE TO YOU,
YOU'D BETTER DARN WELL LISTEN.
GORD, I THINK THAT'S
MORE OF A SLOGAN, ACTUALLY.
SORRY, WHAT?
SMOKEY THE BEAR SAID "ONLY YOU
CAN PREVENT FOREST FIRES"
IN EVERY COMMERCIAL
HE EVER DID.
IT WAS HIS SCHTICK.
SO IT WASN'T A MESSAGE TO ME?
OH, GOSH NO.
NO, NO.
WHAT, WHAT?
I COULD HAVE STUDIED MEDICINE.
YEAH, UH...
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, GORD, WAIT A MINUTE.
COME ON BACK.
THINK ABOUT IT THIS WAY.
YOU'RE SAVING A LOT MORE LIVES
AS A FOREST RANGER
THAN YOU EVER WOULD HAVE
AS A DOCTOR.
BUT I HAVEN'T SAVED
A SINGLE LIFE HERE.
BUT YOU'RE STILL AHEAD.
YEAH.
THIS MEDIEVAL DAY
IS TURNING INTO
THE MOST EDUCATIONAL EVENT
WE'VE EVER HAD AT POSSUM LODGE,
WHICH ISN'T ALL THAT HARD.
WHERE'S YOUR ARMOUR?
THE PAINT'S
DRYING.
THOSE HOCKEY PADS
REALLY SOAK UP THE PRIMER.
I HOPE THE HORSES AREN'T HURT.
WE'RE NOT USING HORSES.
WE BOLTED POMMEL HORSES
TO K-CARS.
HORSES WERE GOOD ENOUGH
FOR KNIGHTS OF THE ROUND TABLE.
WE NEED MORE HORSEPOWER.
THE WIVES ARE DOING UP
A GROANING BOARD,
BUT, NOBODY KNOWS WHAT THAT IS.
OH YEAH,
IT'S A GROANING BOARD.
SURE, I KNOW, YEAH.
IT'S A BOARD AND IT GROANS.
YOU GOT A GROANING
AND A BOARD.
IT'S A GROANING BOARD.
AS I SAY,
NOBODY KNOWS WHAT THAT IS.
I FIGURE ANYTHING THAT
USES FOOD AND INVOLVES
THE WORD "GROANING"
SOUNDS GOOD.
I NEVER THOUGHT HISTORY
WAS THIS EXCITING.
I THOUGHT HISTORY WAS
JUST DEAD PEOPLE.
WELL, IT'S EARLY YET.
YOU KNOW, RANGER GORD,
YOU LIVING, EATING AND SLEEPING
UP IN THE TOWER FOR 16 YEARS,
YOU EVER SUFFER FROM
ACROPHOBIA AT ALL?
WHAT'S THAT, RED?
FEAR OF HEIGHTS.
HEIGHTS?
OH NO --
I'M NOT REALLY THAT HIGH HERE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
OH, OH.
HELP ME.
IT'S TOO HIGH.
NO, NO, ONLY 200 TO 300 FEET.
I'M TOO HIGH.
NO, YOU'RE FINE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I'M TOO HIGH.
WE'RE ON TELEVISION.
WE'RE ON TELEVISION HERE.
YOU'RE CRYING ON MY SHOE.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S FINE.
WHEN YOU LOOK BACK INTO
MEDIEVAL HISTORY,
THERE'S A LOT OF POMP
AND CIRCUMSTANCE.
THAT'S WHAT WE WANTED TO
RECREATE.
THIS IS A NORMAL WAY
OF STARTING...
OF STARTING A...
THAT WOULD GET ON YOUR NERVES,
WOULDN'T IT?
MM-HMM.
UH-HUH, YEAH.
THAT'S MY WAY OF
THROWING DOWN THE GAUNTLET.
THIS SETS UP A SWORD FIGHT
OR A DUEL OF SOME KIND.
WE USED TO DO MORE FENCING
AT THE LODGE
BEFORE THE POLICE CRACKDOWN.
YOU GET THE MASK ON.
THAT'S ME BEHIND THERE.
WHEN YOU HIT A GUY,
YOU WON'T HURT HIM.
I PUT MY HAT ON
SO I'D KNOW WHO I WAS
IN CASE I GOT LOST.
BILL'S GOT A LITTLE BEEPER
ON HIS, TOO.
HE ACTUALLY GOT
THE PRESCRIPTION SCREEN.
DIDN'T WANT TO STRAIN HIS EYES.
(Creaking)
COME OUT OF YOUR CORNER,
AND DOSIE-DO.
FOR GOSH SAKES!
THAT IS A BIT FRIGHTENING.
NOW WE GET INTO
THE MAJESTY OF IT ALL.
ALL RIGHT, SEE, NORMALLY
YOU HOLD ON TO THE SWORD.
IT'S A GOOD ONE ON BILL.
OH, IT'S A GOOD ONE
ON ME, I GUESS.
OH, WELL,
I GOT THREE OTHER WHEELS.
DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT IT,
BILL.
AND...
BACK TO THE SWORD FIGHTING.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
THRUST, PARRY, THRUST, THRUST,
THRUST, THRUST, THRUST, THRUST,
THRUST, THRUST, OUCH.
WHY DON'T YOU RUN
AND CATCH THAT, BILL?
LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT.
(Laughing)
THE VAN KIND OF
GOT BACK AT HIM.
TAKE THE MASK OFF.
IT'S OVER THERE.
GET THAT SWORD.
CHASING A SWORD,
THAT'S BRIGHT, ISN'T IT?
GRAB IT.
YOU MISSED IT.
OH, YOU'RE FINE.
IT'S JUST THROUGH YOUR SHOE.
THERE'S NO PROBLEM THERE.
AT LEAST NOW I KNOW
WHERE BILL IS.
MIGHT AS WELL FINISH THE FIGHT
THOUGH.
(Laughing)
I LOVE THE MIDDLE AGES.
(Red): STAY TUNED FOR
"JASON OF THE ROUND TABLE".
(Applause and cheering)
(Red): OK, BLOW ME A HERALD,
HAROLD!
PARDON ME?
BLOW ME A HERALD, HAROLD!
WHAT'S A HAROLD HAROLD,
UNCLE RED UNCLE RED?
YOU KNOW, THE WAY THEY WOULD
HERALD THE TRUMPETS
TO BRING THE KING IN.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, OK, OK.
(Fanfare)
HERE HE COMES!
(Applause)
(Laughing and applause)
THE OLD KING RED,
THE CONQUEROR.
HA HA!
WOW!
YOU LOOK PSYCHOTIC, UNCLE RED.
YOU SAUCY-TONGUED MINSTREL.
I COULD HAVE YOU BEHEADED.
THAT'S BETTER THAN DYING OF
EMBARRASSMENT -- LOOK AT ME!
THAT'S YOUR OWN FAULT, HAROLD.
I TOLD YOU YOU COULD BE
THE WIZARD IF YOU WANTED.
WIZARD?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID WHIZZER.
WHAT'S ALL THAT TALK ABOUT
THE ROYAL WEE ON THE THRONE?
YOU'VE COME HOME
IN THE BEST MOOD OF YOUR LIFE.
YOU WALK IN AND HEAR
THOSE WORDS THAT MAKE
YOUR BLOOD RUN COLD.
"WE NEED TO TALK."
MEN SHOOT THE BREEZE,
MEN CHEW THE FAT.
MEN DON'T TALK.
SHE WANTS YOU TO DO
SOMETHING ELSE MEN DON'T DO,
SHARE YOUR FEELINGS.
MEN ONLY HAVE THREE EMOTIONS.
MILD ANXIETY,
FULL-BLOWN PANIC...
I MAY HAVE MISCOUNTED.
NO, THERE'S THE ONE
WHEN YOU'RE DRIVING.
PRIMAL RAGE.
WHEREAS WOMEN HAVE
A HUGE RANGE OF EMOTIONS
WITH THE SUBTLE GRADATIONS
OF AN F.M. RADIO DIAL.
IF EMOTIONS WERE COLOURS,
A WOMAN'S EMOTIONS
WOULD LOOK LIKE
THAT WALL OF PAINT CHIPS
AT THE HARDWARE STORE,
WITH NAMES LIKE
MISTY RIVER GREEN.
WHEREAS MEN ARE STUCK WITH
RUSTOLEUM RED
AND SAFETY YELLOW.
HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
DON'T TALK, JUST LISTEN.
CLAMP DOWN ON THE INSIDE
OF YOUR MOUTH WITH YOUR TEETH.
THAT GIVES YOU A SOULFUL LOOK.
IT MAY BRING TEARS TO YOUR EYES
WHICH YOU CAN DAB AWAY
WITH YOUR MANLY FIST.
SCORE BIG POINTS.
SHE'LL THINK YOU'RE SWIMMING IN
A DEEP WELL
OF EMOTIONAL RICHES.
WHEREAS YOU'RE WADING IN
THE SHALLOW END
OF CLUELESS WONDERMENT.
SO REMEMBER, BIDE YOUR TIME.
AND BITE YOUR TONGUE.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW.
THIS WEEK WE HAVE
EXCELLENT EXPERTS:
MY UNCLE RED AND HIS FRIEND,
MR. EDGAR MONTROSE.
(Applause)
OK,
THIS LETTER GOES AS FOLLOWS.
IT'S FROM A VIEWER
IN MADISON, WISCONSIN.
OH, HO, HO.
"DEAR EXPERTS, I AM RESTORING
A 1963 RAMBLER.
"AT 2 A.M. LAST NIGHT
"I WENT INTO THE HOUSE
FOR A BANDAGE
"AND I FOUND A NOTE
FROM MY WIFE
"SAYING THAT
SHE WAS LEAVING ME.
"HER CLOTHES WERE GONE,
"AND I THINK SHE TOOK
MOST OF THE FURNITURE.
"IS SHE KIDDING
"OR WHAT?
"SIGNED, CONFUSED."
WELL, THANKS FOR WRITING,
CONFUSED,
RATHER THAN SHOWING UP
IN PERSON.
OK, NOW, THE HARDEST THING
ABOUT THESE SITUATIONS
IS GETTING RID OF THE STOVE.
MR. MONTROSE,
THIS GENTLEMAN HERE,
HE'S GOT A RAMBLER.
HIS WIFE IS GONE.
ONCE A MAN STARTS COOKING,
THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
HE THINKS HE CAN
LIVE WITHOUT WOMEN.
AND THAT WAY LIES MADNESS.
AND BELIEVE ME, I'M NOT JUST
GUESSING ABOUT THIS.
YOU GOTTA GET RID
OF THE STOVE.
NOT THAT EASY TO DO, EDGAR.
THE ENVIRONMENTALISTS
WON'T LET YOU
JUST THROW 'EM INTO THE LAKE
ANYMORE.
I'D PUT HER UP
ON TOP OF THE VAN,
GO FOR A DRIVE --
WHATEVER HAPPENS HAPPENS.
PARTS PER MILLION,
THAT'S THE SECRET.
LOWER THE PARTS PER MILLION.
REDUCE THE DENSITY.
BREAK THAT BABY DOWN
INTO TINY LITTLE PIECES
SO IT CAN BE
ABSORBED BY THE EARTH.
PUT A TRIPLE CHARGE
OF NUMBER SEVEN DYNAMITE
IN THE OVEN DRAWER AND KABOOM!
(Applause)
YOU KNOW, THAT WOULD BE
KIND OF FUN TO WATCH.
SOUNDS INCREDIBLY DANGEROUS.
EXACTLY.
DON'T HAVE A MAGNET
IN YOUR POCKET
OR YOU'LL WIND UP WITH
200 POUNDS OF IRON FILINGS
IN YOUR SHORTS...
... AGAIN.
(Laughing)
BLOW UP A STOVE AND ROMANCE
COMES BACK INTO YOUR LIFE.
QUITE POSSIBLY THE STUPIDEST
ADVICE I'VE EVER HEARD.
WELL, OF COURSE IT IS, HAROLD.
WE'RE JUST KILLING TIME HERE.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
ANYONE WHO'S RESTORING
A RAMBLER
IS BEYOND HELP ANYWAY.
(Laughing)
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
TWO GUYS IN HOME-MADE ARMOUR
CARRYING WOODEN LANCES,
HEADING AT EACH OTHER
ON A COUPLE OF POMMEL HORSES
BOLTED TO K-CARS
WOULD BE DANGEROUS?
I GUESS IT WAS ROUGH BEING
A KNIGHT OF THE ROUND TABLE.
COURSE, IN THOSE DAYS
THEY DIDN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT A TIE-ROD BREAKING.
THERE WAS CARS
SWERVING EVERYWHERE.
WHEN STINKY PETERSON'S
MONK ROBES
GOT STUCK IN THAT BUMPER,
HE WENT FROM BEING FRIAR TUCK
TO LADY GODIVA.
IT MADE US APPRECIATE
THE THINGS WE HAVE TODAY.
AMBULANCES, STRETCHERS,
X-RAY MACHINES.
MEETING TIME.
(Squealing)
YOU GO AHEAD.
I WANT TO GET THIS OFF.
I'M GETTING METAL FATIGUE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M NO LONGER KING RED.
I'VE RENOUNCED MY THRONE.
I'M GOING BACK TO BEING A SERF
AND "SERF'S UP".
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
HERE'S HERE.
UP AND AT 'EM.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): WELL, HERE WE ARE.