YOU CAN TELL A
LOT ABOUT PEOPLE
BY WHAT THEY TEND TO
HANG ON TO OVER THE YEARS:
THE WEDDING ALBUM,
THE HIGH SCHOOL YEARBOOK,
THE CAR SEAT COVERS FROM
THAT LUCKY PROM NIGHT.
IT SEEMS THAT EVERYBODY
HAS A DRESSER
WTH A DRAWER WITH
A BUNCH OF STUFF IN
THE BACK OF IT.
WOMEN TEND TO KEEP THINGS THAT
REMIND THEM OF PEOPLE:
LOCK OF HAIR,
BABY BOOTIES.
AND MEN KEEP THINGS THAT
REMIND THEM OF EVENTS:
MAYBE A BROKEN LIGHTER,
PERHAPS A BULLET CASING.
ONE OF THE MAIN DIFFERENCES
BETWEEN MEN AND WOMEN
IS WHAT THEY HAVE
IN THEIR DRAWERS.
IT'S NOT SMART OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF THOSE
THINGS THAT MAKES US
WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
RED GREEN:
ON TODAY'S SHOW SPECIAL
GUEST DAVE THOMAS
WATCHES HIS BROTHER GET
SOMETHING OFF HIS FINGER,
I MAKE A POLITICAL
STATEMENT,
BILL TRIES HIS HAND
AND HIS FOOT AT FOOTBALL,
WE CATCH GLEN BRACKSTON
IN THE MIDDLE OF A BUSY DAY
AND I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW TO SWING THROUGH
YOUR PUBLIC SCHOOL DAYS.
AND NOW HERE IS THE MAN
WITH MILLIONS OF VIEWERS,
THOUSANDS OF FOLLOWERS,
HUNDREDS OF FRIENDS,
DOZENS OF INLAWS AND
ONLY ONE NEPHEW,
MR. RED GREEN
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
THINGS ARE VERY GOOD
UP AT POSSUM LODGE
THIS WEEK,
NOT PERFECT BUT
VERY GOOD.
AND HERE'S THE REASON
THEY'RE NOT PERFECT,
MY NEPHEW, HAROLD.
OH, BOY.
WELL, WE GOT A BIG
THING GOING ON HERE,
WE'RE ALL GOING TO MEET
DOWNTOWN AND FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO FIX UP
THE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
OH, WE'RE GOING
TO LYNCH THE MAYOR?
NO, NO, HAROLD, WE'RE
GOING TO SAVE THE OLD
ONE-ROOM SCHOOL HOUSE.
A COUPLE OF YUPPIES
PUT AN OFFER IN ON
IT TO BUY IT
AND TURN IT INTO ONE
OF THOSE QUAINT
COUNTRY STORES.
MAN I HATE
THOSE PLACES.
YOU KNOW WHERE
YOU HAVE THE
LITTLE JELLY JARS
WITH ENOUGH JAM IN THERE
FOR ONE SLICE OF TOAST
OR THEY GOT THE CANADIAN
SOUVENIR FRIDGE MAGNETS
MADE IN TAIWAN?
OR THAT YUPPIE ICE
CREAM THAT COSTS A FORTUNE
AND GOT NAMES
LIKE DUGANSNER
OR SQUEEZENBAJORNAN OR
SOMETHING, YOU KNOW.
AND OF COURSE
NO VANILLA.
NO, NO, THEY GOT
SINFULLY DECADENT
CHOCOLATY MOCHA CRAPPOLA.
I DON'T KNOW.
SO WE'RE GOING TO NIP
THIS THING IN THE BUD
BEFORE THIS QUAINTNESS
CAN GET A TOEHOLD.
WE'RE GOING TO TRY TO
GET THE SCHOOLHOUSE
TO BE TAKEN OVER
BY THE TOWNSHIP AND THEY
CAN PAY FOR GETTING
IT FIXED UP.
YOU KNOW I THINK THAT
BUILDING IS CONTAMINATED
WITH LIKE LEAD OR
ZIRCONIUM OR SOMETHING.
IT'S GOT BAD AIR,
YOU KNOW.
IT JUST DRAINED ALL
THE INTELLIGENCE
RIGHT OUT OF US
LIKE THOSE ALIEN SPACE
POD PEOPLE DID IN
THOSE OLD MOVIES.
OH, YEAH.
IT'S 150 YEARS OLD
AND IT'S FULL OF
HISTORY THERE, TOO.
JUNIOR SINGLETON
INVENTED THE WEDGY
DURING RECESS ONE DAY.
HI, THIS IS WINSTON
ROTHCHILD, REMINDING YOU,
YOUR SEWAGE IS
OUR BREAD AND BUTTER.
OH, WE'RE HEADING FOR
THE COTTAGE AT THE
BREAK OF DAWN,
GOT OUR SEAT BELTS
BUCKLED AND OUR
HELMETS ON.
DADDY'S IN A BAD MOOD,
MOMMY'S IN A FUNK,
GOT THE BOAT ON THE ROOF
AND THE DOG IN THE TRUNK.
OH, WE'RE HEADING
TO THE COTTAGE AND THE
TRAFFIC'S GETTING TIGHT,
THE CAR'S GETTING HOT
AND THERE'S GOING
TO BE A FIGHT.
SO I'M STARING OUT
THE WINDOW BEING
AS QUIET AS I GET
CAUSE I DON'T WANT MY
LAST WORDS TO BE
ARE WE THERE YET.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU HAD A FAMILY
GET TOGETHER ON
THE WEEKEND
AND YOU REALIZE
THAT YOUR GRANDSON IS
BEING RAISED BY A MORON.
IMBECILE SON-IN-LAW,
IT'S KIND OF AN
INFLICTION.
WELL, HE MARRIED YOUR
DAUGHTER, THERE WAS
A TIP OFF.
AND NOW IT'S SERIOUS
BECAUSE THERE'S
OFFSPRING INVOLVED.
THE LITTLE RASCAL NEEDS
A DAD, NEEDS KIND A
FIRM HAND, TRADITION.
YEAH, AND YOU'RE
AFRAID THAT YOUR
KNEE JERK SON-IN-LAW
IS NOT GOING TO RAISE
THE KID THE WAY YOU WOULD.
MAYBE NOT GOING TO
LET HIM PLAY WITH GUNS,
NOT EVER GOING TO LET
HIM THROW THE FIRST PUNCH
OR EVEN THE
SECOND.
PREFERS SOCCER
TO BASEBALL,
VERY EUROPEAN.
DON'T WORRY, THE KID'LL
PROBABLY GROW UP,
TOUGHEN UP AND STOP
LISTENING TO HIS DAD.
LIKE WE DID.
ABSOLUTELY.
MAYBE GET ARRESTED A
COUPLE OF TIMES,
YOU KNOW,
NOTHING SERIOUS,
JUST ENOUGH TO
MAKE HIM A MAN.
WORTH FIVE YEARS
IN UNIVERSITY.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH.
MY DAD NEVER HUGGED ME,
NEVER HELD MY HAND,
AND I TURNED
OUT ALL RIGHT.
MEN SHOULD
NOT TOUCH MEN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
SO JUST GIVE IT TIME.
HOPEFULLY THE KID'LL
COME AROUND.
WE DID.
OH YEAH.
THIS ATTEMPT TO SAVE
POSSUM LAKE SCHOOLHOUSE
FROM DEMOLITION
HAS GOT ME THINKING ABOUT
ONE OF THE MAIN THINGS THAT'S
WRONG WITH THE SCHOOLS.
LOOK AT THIS DESK.
NO WONDER I SPENT
SO MANY YEARS
IN GRADE 6.
THIS DESK ISN'T BUILT
FOR A 17 YEAR OLD KID.
AND WHAT ABOUT THE
KID OF TODAY, HUH?
WHERE IS HE GOING
TO PUT HIS COMPUTER?
UP HERE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
OR HOW ABOUT
A SEMI-AUTOMATIC?
NO WAY.
SO HE ENDS UP SITTING
THERE IN SCHOOL BORED
OUT OF HIS MIND
WHILE HE WAITS
FOR RECESS.
SIX HOURS OF DRUDGERY
FOR TEN MINUTES
OF ENJOYMENT.
SORT OF LIKE
A HONEYMOON.
WELL, I SAY YOU GO
INTO THE PLAYGROUND
THERE AT THE SCHOOLYARD,
TAKE THE SWINGS DOWN
AND BRING THEM INSIDE
AND START MAKING SCHOOL
FUN FOR THE KIDS.
WELL, THIS MAKES A LOT
MORE SENSE, DOESN'T IT?
THE KID DOESN'T
HAVE TO SIT STILL.
HE CAN MOVE AROUND.
GO OVER AND GET
SOMETHING IN
THE CLOAKROOM
OR GO UP AND CHECK
WHAT'S ON THE BLACKBOARD
OR HE CAN SNEAK UP
BEHIND ANOTHER KID
AND CHECK HIS ANSWERS.
AND IF THE TEACHER SAYS
COME ON UP TO THE
FRONT OF THE CLASS,
WELL, HEY, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO WAIT.
OH BOY.
[ CRASH ]
ALL RIGHT, THIS
GIVES ME ANOTHER IDEA.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
SOME TYPE OF A
FLAT SURFACE
TO USE AS A DESK,
WHAT ABOUT A DOOR?
MORE SPECIFICALLY
THIS DOOR.
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO PUT LONGER
ROPES ON THE SWING
AND YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO CUT A SQUARE HOLE IN
THE BOTTOM OF THE DOOR.
I ALREADY MADE A PILOT
HOLE WITH MY LEG.
SO YOU TAKE THE EXTRA
ROPE THAT'S MOUNTED
TO THE SWING
AND YOU TIE ONE TO
EACH SIDE OF THE DOOR,
THAT WAY THE KID CAN
BE SITTING THERE
SWINGING HIS WAY
THROUGH HIS A, B, CS,
AND SUDDENLY THE
TEACHER SAYS OKAY
TIME FOR DESK WORK,
NO PROBLEM.
AND IT'S 100 PERCENT
ADJUSTABLE TO WHATEVER
HEIGHT YOU WANT
DEPENDING ON HOW MUCH
WEIGHT YOU PUT
ON THE SEAT.
YOU CAN EVEN MAKE
YOURSELF INVISIBLE,
THAT WAY YOU CAN MAKE
FACES AT THE TEACHER.
FINALLY A DESK THAT
REFLECTS THE ATTITUDE
OF TODAY'S TEENAGERS.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OR ON A HOT SUMMER'S
DAY HOW ABOUT THIS?
IT'S A NICE BREEZE
BUT IT SMELLS FUNNY.
RED GREEN:
STAY TUNED.
BILL IS GOING TO TURN
HIMSELF INTO AN 18-WHEELER
AS PART OF HIS FUN
WITH RUBBER HOBBY
AND HAROLD IS GOING
TO GIVE ME A LIFT
INTO TOWN.
I KNOW A LOT OF YOU
YOUNG PEOPLE ARE STUCK
IN SOME LOUSY JOBS OUT THERE
AND YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE TURNING 40
STILL ASKING PEOPLE IF
THEY WANT FRIES WITH THAT.
BUT THE PATH TO A
BETTER CAREER
IS NOT TO SCREW UP
THE JOB YOU HAVE NOW.
FOR EXAMPLE, I WAS IN
ONE OF THEM FAST FOOD
PLACES THE OTHER DAY
AND AFTER I PLACED MY
ORDER FOR THE THIRD TIME,
IT STRUCK ME THAT THAT
KID BEHIND THE COUNTER
WAS PROBABLY NEVER GOING
TO BE RUNNING THE COMPANY.
THEY EVEN HAD THE
MANAGER HELPING HIM.
I COULD TELL SHE WAS
A MANAGER BECAUSE SHE
WAS 18 MONTHS OLDER
AND DIDN'T HAVE TO
WEAR THE PAPER HAT.
I MADE THE MISTAKE
OF HANDING THEM
A $20 BILL
JUST AS THE COMPUTER
WENT DOWN,
WHICH MEANT THEY HAD
NO IDEA HOW MUCH
CHANGE TO GIVE ME.
I JUST KNEW I WAS
LOOKING AT TWO KIDS
WHO HAD SAT IN GRADE 7
MATH CLASS THINKING,
HEY, WE'RE NEVER
GOING TO NEED TO
KNOW THIS STUFF.
THEY STARED AT THAT TWENTY
LIKE THEY WERE LOOKING FOR
OPERATING INSTRUCTIONS.
MY POINT IS, IF YOU
WON'T OR CAN'T DO
THE JOB YOU HAVE,
NO EMPLOYER IS GOING
TO PROMOTE YOU TO THE
BETTER JOB YOU WANT.
I MEAN, HAROLD HAS
BEEN MY PRODUCER
AND DIRECTOR
FOR FIVE YEARS IN A ROW,
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU?
I'M WINSTON ROTHCHILD
REMINDING YOU,
IF THE NEIGHBOURS
ARE COMPLAINING
BETTER START
DRAINING.
CALL 1-800-555-SUCK.
WELL, THIS PROJECT TO
HAVE POSSUM LAKE
PUBLIC SCHOOL
DECLARED A HISTORICAL
SITE HAS BROUGHT OUT
THE COMMUNITY
SPIRIT IN EVERYBODY.
I'M ON THE COMMITTEE
TO ORGANIZE THE
SCHOOL REUNION.
WE'RE GOING TO GET
EVERYBODY BACK WHO'S
EVER WENT THERE BEFORE
AND WE'RE HOPING THAT
THE FIVE WHO ACTUALLY
GRADUATED CAN MAKE IT, TOO.
HOW ARE YOU
GETTING IN TOUCH
WITH EVERYBODY?
WELL, WE FIGURE THE PAROLE
BOARD IS THE BEST SOURCE
OF INFORMATION.
SO I GUESS YOU'RE SENDING
OUT INVITATIONS MAINLY TO
NO FIXED ADDRESS, ARE YOU?
NO. YOU KNOW WE FIGURE
ANYONE WHO WENT
TO THAT SCHOOL,
THEIR READING COMPREHENSION,
YOU KNOW, MIGHT BE
IN DOUBT.
SO I'M ACTUALLY
I'M GOING TO PHONE
EVERYBODY DIRECTLY.
IT'S SCARY THE TYPE
OF PEOPLE THEY ALLOW
TO HAVE PHONES.
BUT, ANYWAY, I JUST TOLD
THEM MEET AT THE SCHOOL
NEXT SATURDAY
YEAH, I HOPE WE CAN
FIGURE OUT WHERE THE
SCHOOL IS GOING TO BE
BECAUSE YOU KNOW
WE GOT TO MOVE IT.
AND OF COURSE ONCE THAT
WORD GOT OUT THAT WE'RE
MOVING THE SCHOOL,
EVERYBODY WANTED TO
COMPETE FOR THAT JOB,
SO GOT THEY GOT THEIR TRUCKS
OUT AND THEY STARTED
SHOWING OFF, YOU KNOW.
AND JUNIOR SINGLETON
THREW A CHAIN AROUND
THE POST OFFICE
AND PULLED HER RIGHT
OFF THE FOUNDATION.
AND BUSTER HADFIELD
DRAGGED THE TOWN CLOCK
FROM ONE END OF THE
STREET TO THE OTHER.
MADE PERFECT
TIME ON THAT, TOO.
SO WHO GOT THE HONOURS
OF MOVING THE SCHOOL?
WELL, I THINK IT WENT
TO JUNIOR SINGLETON
BECAUSE HE HAD PULLED
THE DRUGSTORE TWO
AND A HALF MILES.
EVERYBODY WAS PRETTY
IMPRESSED WITH THAT
EXCEPT FOR THE
DRUGGIST OF COURSE.
SO NOW THE NEXT
MAJOR DEAL IS
WHO GETS TO KEEP
ALL THE TREASURES
THAT ARE IN THE BASEMENT
UNDERNEATH THE SCHOOL?
OH, HAROLD, THERE'S GOT
TO BE A TON OF STUFF
UNDER THERE, EH?
OLD PENS, INK WELLS,
SHOES, BUTTONS,
GLASS EYES,
LOST MARBLES, HAROLD.
A LOT OF THE TEACHERS
LOST THEIR MARBLES
IN THAT SCHOOL.
ANY OF YOUR STUFF
GOING TO BE UNDER
THAT SCHOOL?
A LOT OF HOMEWORK.
I USED TO JAM THAT DOWN
THROUGH THE HOLES IN
THE FLOORBOARDS.
I TOLD THE TEACHER
THAT THE DOG ATE
IT, YOU KNOW.
BUT IF MY DOG HAD EATEN
AS MUCH HOMEWORK AS
I SAID HE DID,
HE'D BE PASSING
FIRE LOGS.
DON'T ADJUST YOUR SET,
THE SHOW'S SUPPOSED
TO LOOK LIKE THIS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU
DON'T GET A BETTER
VEHICLE UNCLE RED,
YOU KNOW LIKE ONE OF THOSE
NEW KIND OF VANS THEY'RE
BUILDING THESE DAYS,
YOU KNOW THE KIND
THAT ACTUALLY RUN.
CAN'T AFFORD
IT, HAROLD.
JUST BORROW THE MONEY
FROM THE BANK.
YEAH, BUT ONCE YOU ADD
ON THE INTEREST AND
THE SERVICE CHARGE
AND THE HUMILIATION
OF HAVING TO TELL SOME
DOLT WHY YOU'RE BROKE,
THAT COULD BE A
NEGATIVE EXPERIENCE.
YEAH, I GO THROUGH THAT
EVERY WEEK TRYING TO
GET MY ALLOWANCE.
YOU KNOW, BUT YOU'D ALWAYS
HAVE THE NEW VEHICLE
TO BORROW AGAINST,
YOU KNOW, YOU'D ALWAYS
HAVE THAT AS BACK UP.
THE BANK DOESN'T
WANT MY VAN, HAROLD.
THEY'RE IN THE MONEY
BUSINESS, NOT THE
VEHICLE REPO BUSINESS.
CUSTOMERS DON'T GO INTO
THE BANK TO WITHDRAW A
DOOR FROM A HYUNDAI PONY.
THEY WON'T REPOSSESS
IT IF YOU KEEP THE
PAYMENTS UP.
YOU CAN DO THAT.
MAYBE I CAN,
MAYBE I CAN'T,
BUT WORRYING ABOUT
IT WILL CRAMP
MY LIFESTYLE.
YEAH, BUT YOU'D BE
RIDING AROUND IN A
LOT NICER VEHICLE.
WITH THE HITCHHIKING I CAN
BE IN A NICER VEHICLE
EVERY COUPLE OF HOURS
AND IT'S FREE.
YEAH, I GUESS SO, YEAH.
I SUPPOSE IF YOU
DON'T COUNT THE
LOSS OF SHOES,
LOSS OF DIGNITY,
SUNSTROKE AND
OTHER RELATED INJURY.
DROP IT, HAROLD, OR
YOU'LL BE A RELATED
INJURY
GONNA BE?
WELL, HERE WE ARE WITH
THIS WEEK'S BOATING TIP
WITH GLEN BRACKSTON OF
BRACKSTON'S MARINA.
HOW ARE YOU
TODAY, GLEN?
NOT BAD AT ALL, RED,
FOR A GUY WHO'S HAD
TWO HEART ATTACKS,
BLOWN OUT GALL BLADDER,
DOUBLE HERNIA,
PLUS I GOT THESE
BAD ANKLES, TOO.
I FIND THEY CAN BE
LIFE-THREATENING
IF, YOU KNOW,
I COULDN'T GET
TO A PHONE OR A
RESTAURANT OR SOMETHING.
HOW ABOUT THE BOATING
TIP TODAY, GLEN?
WELL, ACTUALLY, RED,
IT'S A SAFETY TIP.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
YEAH.
THE PROPER WAY TO
REFUEL YOUR BOAT.
SO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO
FIRST IS SHUT DOWN
THE ENGINE.
YEAH, YOU'VE
DONE THAT, YEAH.
AND THEN NEXT
YOU'VE GOT TO TAKE
OFF THE GAS CAP.
STICK THE NOZZLE
IN THERE AND
LET HER GO.
YEAH.
CAN YOU
GET THAT?
WELL, IT'S YOU'RE
DEMONSTRATION.
WELL, I KNOW RED
BUT I'M ALLERGIC
TO THE SMELL OF GAS.
OH, YEAH, MY EYELIDS
WILL JUST BLOW UP
LIKE BALLOONS.
IT'S HORRIBLE.
AND I GET THESE
BIG BLISTERS.
ALL RIGHT, GLEN,
SPARE US THE DETAILS.
MAN, OH MAN, OH MAN,
OH MAN, OH MAN.
THAT'S IT.
JUST GET THE
CAP THERE, RED.
THANK YOU.
THAT'S IT.
THERE WE GO.
OKAY.
STEP THREE.
EXTINGUISH ALL
OPEN FLAMES.
I GUESS THAT COULD
ACTUALLY BE STEP ONE
OR TWO, COULDN'T IT?
I THINK SO.
I'M SORRY, I SHOULD
HAVE KNOWN THAT.
NOW WHAT DO I DO,
EASE OFF ON THE NOZZLE
WHEN I HEAR IT
FILLING UP THERE?
WELL YOU CAN, RED,
BUT THAT'S IF THE OWNER
OF THE BOAT IS AROUND.
IF HE'S GONE, THEN YOU
JUST KEEP'ER GOING
'CAUSE YOU MAKE A COUPLE
EXTRA BUCKS EVERY FILL UP.
THERE'S A GOOD TIP FOR
YOU MARINA OPERATORS
OUT THERE.
WELL, THAT'S
A NICE TOUCH,
YOU'RE USING OUR SHOW
TO GIVE RIP
OFF ADVICE.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
PEOPLE WANT TO KNOW
THIS STUFF, RED.
I GOT TO BE A FULL
SERVICE BUSINESS
IF I'M GOING TO COMPETE
WITH THE INFORMATION
SUPER HIGHWAY.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M DONE.
THAT'S AS MUCH GAS
AS I CAN TAKE.
BILL HAD ASKED ME TO
MEET HIM OUT ON
THE GRIDIRON
FOR ONE OF HIS FAVOURITE
SPORTS, FOOTBALL.
OH, YEAH, YOU
LOOK GREAT, BILL.
WHAT AN ATHLETE.
HE WAS ASKING FOR THAT.
AND NOW HE TOOK
ME OVER TO THE
BLOCKING DUMMY.
ACTUALLY THEY
GOT AT LEAST TWO
TO CHOOSE FROM THERE.
WANTED ME
TO TRY THAT.
ONE THING I DIDN'T
REALIZE IS THAT I REALLY
WASN'T WEARING THE PADDING.
BILL IS GOING
TO SHOW OFF AGAIN.
BACKS WAY UP, TAKES
A FULL RUN AT 'ER
AND IN HE COMES.
WOW.
WATCH THE AIM
THERE, BILL.
OH, GOT 'ER RIGHT
ON TOP OF THE HEAD.
NOW, LUCKILY I HAD
TAKEN THAT ST. JOHN'S
AMBULANCE COURSE
SO I KNEW EXACTLY WHAT
TO DO WITH THIS TYPE
OF A SITUATION.
OH, IT'S A BOY.
AND NOW WE TRY
RUNNING THROUGH
THE TIRES HERE.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
YOU DO SO THAT YOU WILL
BE ABLE TO RUN THROUGH TIRES.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
A FOOTBALL PLAYER
ACTUALLY RUN THROUGH TIRES,
THAT'S A TOTAL
WASTE OF TIME,
BUT YOU GOT KNUTE
ROCKNEY HERE, WELL,
YOU DID IT YOURSELF.
AND THEN HE COMES.
OH MY GOSH.
LOOK AT THAT STYLE.
LOOK OUT.
WATCH OUT.
OH, OH, OH, AND HE
GOT HIMSELF ALL WOUND
UP IN THE DARN TIRES.
THERE HE GOES.
TAKE HIM OVER
TO THE BIG HILL,
HAVE SOME FUN.
THAT WAS A PRETTY
NICE KICK IF I DO
SAY SO MYSELF.
UNFORTUNATELY IT'S
NOW BILL'S TURN.
YEAH, GOT THE POINTED-TOED
RUNNING SHOES
WHICH ARE NOT THAT
GREAT FOR THIS SPORT
BUT THEY'RE OKAY
FOR KILLING BUGS IN
THE CORNER I SUPPOSE.
AND BILL JUST HAD
A BIRTHDAY WHERE HE
GOT ALL THESE FOOTBALLS
SO HE WAS PRETTY
DARN EXCITED.
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT
ONE WAS THE CAKE.
ALL RIGHT, BILL, HERE
IS A NORMAL FOOTBALL.
SEE IF YOU CAN PUT THIS
THROUGH THE UPRIGHTS.
REALLY LET 'ER GO.
REALLY HIT IT.
OH, NICE KICK,
BEAUTIFUL KICK.
WRONG BALL, BILL.
DON'T THINK THAT
DIDN'T HURT.
TELL YOU WHAT, BILL,
WHY DON'T I HAVE
ONE LAST KICK,
ALL RIGHT?
YOU HOLD IT FOR ME.
NO, NO, NO, NOT
JUST THE FINGER,
WRAP YOUR HAND,
I'M GOING TO REALLY --
WRAP YOUR HAND.
AND LEAN RIGHT OVER IT, BILL,
LEAN RIGHT OVER IT,
CLOSE YOUR EYES
AND MAKE A WISH.
CHALK ONE UP FOR
THE HOME TEAM.
RED GREEN:
STAY TUNED.
DOUGIE FRANKLIN IS
GOING TO LAY OUT
A BIG THEORY
AND WINSTON ROTHCHILD
IS GOING TO SUCK IT ALL UP.
HAROLD, YOU MISSED OUT
ON THE EXCITEMENT.
NO SOONER DID WE LIFT
UP THE SCHOOLHOUSE,
YOU LOOK DOWN UNDER
THERE, A SKELETON
IN THE FOUNDATION.
IT'S PROBABLY JUST ONE
OF THOSE GANGLY
WHITE SKELETONS
THAT USED TO HANG
IN THE CORNER OF
THE CLASSROOM.
YOU SHOULD TALK.
ANYWAY, THE BIG QUESTION
NOW IS WHERE ARE WE GOING
TO PUT THE SCHOOLHOUSE.
SOME SAY DOWN AT THE
PARK, SOME SAY UP AT
ROCK CREEK POINT.
MAYBE WE COULD KEEP
IT HERE AT THE LODGE.
NO, THEY'RE AFRAID
WE'LL WRECK IT BY
FIXING IT UP.
WE'RE HERE WITH
SMALL BUSINESSMAN
WINSTON ROTHCHILD
FOR MORE OF HIS
HANDY HINTS FOR
THE ENTREPRENEUR.
LISTEN, FIRST OF ALL,
I RESENT BEING CALLED
A SMALL BUSINESSMAN.
OH, NO, I DIDN'T
MEAN YOUR HEIGHT,
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE
SIZE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
I KNOW.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH MY HEIGHT?
NO, I'M SAYING YOU'RE NOT
EXACTLY A MULTINATIONAL
CORPORATION HERE, WINSTON.
YOU'RE THE ONLY EMPLOYEE.
WELL, LISTEN,
MR. POSSUM,
I MEAN JUST BECAUSE MY
CASH FLOW HAS RESTRICTED
MY EMPLOYMENT
ACQUISITION
TIMETABLE,
RESULTING IN
A JOB SHARING
SITUATION, I MEAN,
THAT DON'T MEAN I'M
NOT THINKING BIG.
BECAUSE AFTER ALL,
THINKING BIG,
THAT'S THE SECRET TO
SUCCESS RIGHT THERE.
I LEARNED THAT FROM
ONE OF THEM INSPIRATIONAL
TAPES, THINK BIG BY ED BIG.
AND, YOU KNOW,
THROUGH ED I REALIZED
THAT EVENTUALLY SOMEDAY
I COULD OWN LIKE
MY WHOLE FLEET OF
SEPTIC TANK TRAINS,
SEPTIC SUPER TANKERS,
SUPER SONIC SEWAGE PLANES.
SEPTIC SPACE SHUTTLES?
YOU SEE, I PLAN
ON EXPANDING INTO
OTHER BUSINESSES
THAT ARE SORT
OF SIMILAR IN
NATURE, EH?
SORT OF, I
DON'T KNOW,
CAPITALIZE ON MY
EXPERIENCE AND
EXPERTISE, EH?
COME ON!
THAT ONE JUST DID NOT
WANT TO LET GO, EH?
LIKE, FOR INSTANCE,
WHEN THESE GUYS
ASKED ME TO BRING MY
TRUCK OUT EARLIER TODAY,
YOU KNOW, TO MOVE
THE SCHOOLHOUSE.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
A LOT OF BUSINESS
PEOPLE WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT THAT THAT
WAS JUST AN INCONVENIENT
ANNOYING IMPOSITION, EH?
OH, YEAH, BUT TO ME
IT'S OH SO MUCH
MORE THAN THAT.
I LOOK AT THAT
AS A BUSINESS
OPPORTUNITY, EH?
SEE THE WAY
I SEE IT,
IF YOU GOT A BIG
SCHOOLHOUSE LIKE THAT
THAT YOU WANT TO MOVE.
NO ONE HAS MOVED
SOMETHING LIKE
THAT BEFORE, RIGHT?
SO IF IT WORKS FOR ME,
ALL OF A SUDDEN I GOT
A NEW BUSINESS.
I'M INTO RENOVATIONS
AND RESTORATION, EH?
I SUPPOSE, YEAH.
WELL, ARE YOU KIDDING?
I MEAN, THEY SAVE
OLD BUILDINGS, RIGHT?
MAY AS WELL MOVE
OLD OUTHOUSES, TOO.
YEAH, YEAH, I
GUESS SO, YEAH.
YOU KNOW SOMETHING,
WE COULD BE SITTING
ON A FORTUNE.
OKAY.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THIS WEEK CLAIMING
TO BE EXPERTS WITH
MY UNCLE RED
ARE THE FRANKLIN
BROTHERS, DOUGIE
AND BEN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
HERE IS THE
FIRST QUESTION:
DEAR EXPERT, IF YOU
WERE WASHED UP ON
A DESERT ISLAND,
WHO WOULD YOU WANT
TO HAVE WITH YOU?
BOY, THAT'S A
TOUGH ONE, HAROLD.
YOU WOULD WANT SOMEBODY WHO
WAS GOOD WITH SURVIVAL
STUFF, YOU KNOW?
YEAH, AND HAD
WILDERNESS SKILLS.
THAT WOULD BE GOOD.
OR SOMEBODY WHO WOULD
KEEP A COOL HEAD
IN WHAT I CALL YOUR
CSS OR YOUR CRISIS
SITUATION SCENARIO.
WELL THEN I WOULD
HAVE TO GO WITH
GILLIGAN
BECAUSE LIKE HE WAS ON
THAT ISLAND FOR LIKE
THREE YEARS AND --
AND -- AND LIKE HE
BUILT ALL THEM SHELTERS
AND THERE WAS LIKE --
YOU KNOW, IT WAS LIKE
A BAMBOO SUB-DIVISION.
EXCUSE ME, THAT WAS JUST
A TV SHOW THOUGH,
MR. FRANKLIN.
I MEAN, GILLIGAN REALLY
DIDN'T BUILD ALL
THOSE SHELTERS.
YOU ARE SOME
KIND OF IDIOT.
THE PROFESSOR
BUILT THEM.
YEAH, I GOT TO GO --
I GOT TO GO WITH
DOUGIE ON THIS ONE.
EVERY TIME THEY
TRIED TO ESCAPE,
GILLIGAN ALWAYS WAS
THE ONE SCREWING IT UP.
I WOULD THINK
THE GUY YOU WOULD
WANT ON YOUR TEAM
WHEN YOU'RE IN ONE OF
YOUR CRISIS SITUATION
SCENARIOS
WOULD BE SOMEBODY
LIKE THE PROFESSOR.
I MEAN, HE WAS CLOSE
TO A MECHANICAL GENIUS
THAT FELLOW, YOU KNOW.
REMEMBER THAT RECORD
PLAYER HE BUILT?
IT HAD -- WELL,
REMEMBER IT?
IT WAS BETTER THAN THE
ONE THEY HAD ON THE
FLINTSTONES,
YOU KNOW, THAT HAD
THAT BIRD WITH THE
BEAK THAT WENT DOWN
AND AFTER THE RECORD
WAS DONE IT DID THAT
"IT'S A LIVING."
REMEMBER THAT?
IT WAS MUCH
BETTER THAN THAT.
I AM NOT AN IDIOT.
IT WAS GILLIGAN'S
ISLAND, OKAY,
IT WAS ABOUT
GILLIGAN.
NOW HE WAS ALWAYS
COMING UP WITH
THESE CRAZY PLANS
AND EVERYTHING
WOULD GO WRONG
AND THEN EVERYBODY
WOULD FEEL SORRY FOR HIM.
AND THAT'S WHAT YOU
WANT IN THE WILDERNESS
IS SOMEBODY DUMB THAT
YOU CAN FEEL SUPERIOR TO.
THAT WOULD GIVE
YOU A WILL TO LIVE.
SO I'LL PICK GILLIGAN.
THESE ARE
ALL MYTHICAL
CHARACTERS
WELL, SO WHAT
HAROLD, IT'S A
HYPOTHETICAL QUESTION.
HANG ON ONE
SECOND HERE.
LET'S SAY, OKAY,
YOU'RE OUT THERE
ON YOUR THREE HOUR
TOUR, ALL RIGHT?
SOMETHING HAPPENS,
WHAMO, HERE YOU ARE
STRANDED ON A
DESERT ISLAND FOR
SAY THREE SEASONS.
I'M TELLING YOU,
I GOT TO GO WITH
THE PROFESSOR.
WELL, I'D GO WITH
GILLIGAN BECAUSE
HE HAD ALL THE IDEAS.
I WOULD GO WITH
EITHER GINGER
AND/OR MARY ANN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
I DIDN'T KNOW THEY
WERE IN THIS.
OKAY, I'LL
PICK GINGER.
MRS. HOWELL FOR ME.
SHE WAS GOOD.
WAIT A SEC.
OH, UNCLE RED, WHAT
ABOUT YOUR WIFE?
WOULDN'T YOU
TAKE YOUR WIFE?
AND HAVE BERNICE
STRANDED ON A DESERT
ISLAND FOR THREE YEARS?
I LOVE HER TOO MUCH
TO PUT HER THROUGH
THAT, HAROLD.
WELL, THE OLD POSSUM
LAKE SCHOOLHOUSE HAS
BEEN RE-LOCATED.
DID IT GO
WITHOUT A HITCH?
WELL, IT WENT WITHOUT
A PROPER ONE, HAROLD.
WE TRIED TO USE MOOSE
THOMPSON'S CLASS THREE
HOMEMADE HITCH
THAT HE MADE OUT OF
A STOVE LEG AND
A DOORKNOB.
THE WHOLE THING
PACKED IT IN JUST
AS WE CRESTED THE HILL
AND THE TRAILER WITH
THE SCHOOLHOUSE ON IT
ROLLED ALL THE WAY
DOWN THE HILL,
ACROSS THE TOWN DOCK
RIGHT INTO POSSUM LAKE.
OH, GREAT, SO
WHAT NOW WHAT WE CAN
OFFER SUBMARINE RIDES
TO SEE THE
HISTORIC SCHOOLHOUSE?
WELL, IT FLOATS HAROLD.
THE SCHOOLHOUSE
IS MADE OF WOOD.
WOOD FLOATS.
I THOUGHT YOU WOULD
NOTICE THAT EVERY TIME
YOU WASHED YOUR FACE.
[ LAUGHING SARCASTICALLY ]
SO DID YOU GET IT
OUT OF THE LAKE?
NO, WE'RE JUST
GOING TO LET HER
DRIFT THERE, HAROLD.
DURING THE SUMMER IT
CAN BE A FLOATING CHURCH
OR A BOAT SCHOOL
OR MAYBE ONE OF
THEM MARINAS
THAT COMES RIGHT
UP TO YOUR DOCK.
IN THE WINTER WE'LL
JUST LET HER FREEZE
IN THERE SOLID.
YOU GOT YOURSELF AN ICE
FISHING HUT WHERE EVERYBODY
GETS THEIR OWN DESK.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A
LITTLE WHILE.
WELL, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING
AND I HAVE A PICTURE OF ME
SITTING BEHIND YOU
IN GRADE 4 AT
POSSUM LAKE SCHOOL,
THAT ONE WHERE I
WAS DIPPING YOUR PIG
TAIL INTO THE INK WELL.
I KNOW YOU NEVER
FORGAVE ME FOR THAT,
BUT YOU'LL SEE IN THE
PICTURE THE PIG ISN'T
UPSET AT ALL.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
AND ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND WISBANG THERE
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
RED: ALL RIGHT,
HAROLD, GET 'EM UP.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
CAREFUL, UNCLE RED,
AUNT BERNICE SENT THIS OVER.
SHE SAID YOU SAID YOU
WOULDN'T TOUCH HER
COOKING --