IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
IF IT WALKS, TALKS,
AND ACTS LIKE A DUCK,
AND IS CARRYING
A SEIZED-UP CHAINSAW,
YOU'D BETTER DUCK BECAUSE
IT'S PROBABLY YOUR HERO,
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU.
(Cheering and whistling)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
VERY EXCITING DAY HERE.
I GOT THIS FROM
THE INCOME TAX DEPARTMENT.
WE'RE LOOKIN' AT A REFUND.
YEAH,
RIGHT, UNCLE RED.
YOU HAVE TO PAY TAX
BEFORE YOU GET A REFUND.
NOT IF YOU GOT
A GOOD ACCOUNTANT.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
YOU GOTTA PAY IN BEFORE
YOU CAN GET ANYTHING BACK.
YOU'RE CONFUSING THE WORD
"FILING" WITH "CHEATING".
"NEPHEW" WITH "WHO CARES?"
STICK AROUND, FOLKS.
I'M GONNA SHARE THIS
WITH YOU -- THE NEWS, THAT IS.
OHHH...
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MAIN MESSAGE BEING,
FOR GOSH SAKES,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
YOU WANNA MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
THAT'S GOOD, HAROLD.
(Grunting)
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH...
LOOK WHAT WE GOT.
THERE'S A REFUND CHEQUE.
LOOK AT THAT --
THAT'S A REFUND CHEQUE,
EXACTLY AS I PREDICTED.
YOU GOTTA PAY INCOME TAX
BEFORE YOU CAN EXPECT A REFUND.
IT'S A GREAT COUNTRY, ISN'T IT?
LET'S SEE HOW GREAT.
GIVE ME A HAND.
THERE WE GO, THERE WE GO.
$11.43 -- NOT BAD, NOT BAD.
THAT'S A FLY DROPPING.
TRY THAT AGAIN.
$1,143?!
WHAT?! NO!
OH, MAN!
WHOA! WHOA!
THAT'S WRONG! THAT'S A MISTAKE!
THAT'S A MISTAKE,
THAT'S A MISTAKE!
I'M PHONING THE TAX DEPARTMENT.
WE'LL GET THIS
STRAIGHTENED OUT.
WE'RE NOT PHONING ANYBODY.
I'M THINKIN' THAT
I MAY HAVE MADE COMMENTS
ABOUT THE GOVERNMENT,
TAX DEPARTMENT, OVER THE PAST--
COMMENTS?! THEY WERE THREATS.
I HEARD THEM -- THREATS.
BUT I'LL TELL YA,
WHEN YOU TAKE A MAN
WHO'S BARELY MAKIN' ENDS MEET,
THEREFORE NOT ABLE
TO GENERATE ENOUGH INCOME
TO PAY THE INCOME TAX,
WHICH IS A PRIVILEGE --
THAT'S A PRIVILEGE.
WE'RE ONE OF THE WORLD'S
MOST PRIVILEGED COUNTRIES.
AND YOU HAND THAT MAN $1,143...
I'M TELLING YA,
THIS IS A GREAT GOVERNMENT!
IT'S A GOOD DEAL!
(Red): LATER ON, WE'LL
BE MAKING A BIT OF WINE
ON "ADVENTURES WITH BILL".
I HAD DRIVEN OVER
TO THE VINEYARD
IN THE POSSUM VAN...
THAT WOULD BE ME ARRIVING.
UH, LOOK AT THAT BEAUTIFUL
VINEYARD OUT THE BACK, THERE.
LOOKS LIKE A BEAUTIFUL
BACKDROP.
BILL IS LOOKIN'
FOR THE WHEELBARROW.
GONNA PUT THE GRAPES IN THERE.
HE'S GONNA START
BY CRUSHING HIS MELON.
OHHH!
OH, BOY.
THAT WOULD, UH... YEAH.
NO HARM, NO FOUL, HUH?
ALL RIGHT, SO AROUND WE GO,
BECAUSE APPARENTLY
THE WHEELBARROW HAD WEDGED IN.
WE HAVE THE HEAVY-DUTY
SUSPENSION ON THAT,
WHICH WAS BUILT
TO CATCH WHEELBARROWS.
SHE'S LOOKIN', UH,
A LITTLE ROUGH, BILL.
AND I'M SUSPECTING THIS UNIT
IS OFF WARRANTY -- OOP!
I'LL TAKE OUT A ROLL
OF DUCT TAPE.
IT'S NOT QUITE AS GOOD AS NEW.
HARD TO BELIEVE ONE WHEEL
COULD BE OUT OF ALIGNMENT.
WE SEEM TO HAVE MANAGED IT.
BILL'S APPARENTLY SPOTTED
SOME GRAPES.
THESE ARE THE, UH, I BELIEVE,
THE CONCORD... MALLARD...
THEY'RE RIPE... WE DON'T KNOW
THEY'RE RIPE.
BILL'S GONNA...
PUT THIS GRAPE IN YOUR MOUTH.
BILL?
OH, GOSH -- I'LL TRY ONE.
BILL NEEDS A HAT.
WHAT'S THIS? OH!
KIND OF THE BULK APPROACH.
AND HE'S ALL SET.
THROW IT IN THE WHEELBARROW.
THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
OH, NOW, LOOKING
IN THE CAMPFIRE
TELL ME WHAT YOU SEE
A PILE OF LOGS
AND KINDLING
THE ARTIST
FORMERLY KNOWN AS "TREE"
OR DO YOU SEE THE SPIRIT
CALLING YOU LIKE A BROTHER
IF THAT SPIRIT LOOKS
LIKE AN AEROSOL CAN
I SUGGEST
YOU RUN FOR COVER
(Laughing)
WELCOME TO THE POSSUM LODGE
WORD GAME!
TONIGHT'S PRIZE IS
A YEAR'S SUPPLY
OF UNMARKED PHARMACEUTICALS
FROM THE CRANKHOUSE PHARMACY.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. MIKE HAMAR
TO SAY THIS WORD.
"ADDRESS".
(Quietly): "ADDRESS".
GO!
(Audience laughing)
ALL RIGHT, MIKE,
THE PLACE YOU CALL HOME.
THE BIG HOUSE.
WHERE YOU LIVE.
IN MY CAR.
OK, YOU GOTTA PARK YOUR CAR
SOMEWHERE.
THE PLACE YOU
PARK IT IS...
... THE LIQUOR STORE.
(Audience laughing)
OK, LET ME TRY ANOTHER WAY.
WHEN YOU WRITE TO YOUR MOTHER,
YOU WRITE
TO HER...
... CASE WORKER.
(Audience laughing)
I'M TALKIN'
ABOUT HER HOUSE, MIKE.
PICTURE THE FRONT DOOR.
THIS IS BESIDE IT OR ABOVE IT
AND IT'S
CALLED...
... UH, THE RED LIGHT.
(Audience laughing)
NO, NO, MIKE, THIS IS A NUMBER.
OH, 666.
OK, AND THAT'S CALLED...
... GRAFFITI.
I DID IT MYSELF.
IT'S FOR
MOTHER'S DAY.
REMEMBER THAT TIME
THEY MENTIONED YOUR NAME
ON THE RADIO?
ON THE NEWS, EH?
THEY SAID THE COPS
HAVE ARRESTED MIKE HAMAR OF...
... NO FIXED ADDRESS.
THERE WE...
(Applause and cheering)
SCIENCE HAS PUT A MAN
ON THE MOON,
CURED A BUNCH OF DISEASES,
AND EVEN DEFINED
THE ORIGIN OF THE UNIVERSE,
BUT AS YET, THEY HAVE FAILED
TO SOLVE THE ULTIMATE MYSTERY:
HOW TO MAKE A HALF-DECENT
AMPHIBIOUS CAR.
TODAY ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
I'M GONNA SOLVE THE QUESTION
THAT HAS PLAGUED MANKIND
SINCE...
WELL, THE LATE '50's, I GUESS.
ANYBODY WHO'S MADE
AN AMPHIBIOUS CAR HAS FAILED
BECAUSE THEY STARTED
WITH A CAR
AND TRIED TO MAKE IT SEAWORTHY.
I'LL START WITH A BOAT
AND MAKE IT ROADWORTHY.
I GOT THIS BOAT.
SHE ALREADY FLOATS,
GOT A MOTOR ON 'ER.
ALL I NEED TO MAKE IT
INTO A CAR IS WHEELS.
BUT WAIT A MINUTE!
THIS BOAT ALREADY HAS
A SET OF WHEELS...
ON THE TRAILER!
ALL I GOTTA DO IS
HOOK UP THE MOTOR
SO IT WILL DRIVE THE WHEELS.
SOUNDS HARD, RIGHT?
(Grunting)
WRONG! ALL YOU NEED IS
ONE MORE OUTBOARD MOTOR,
SO YOU GOT ONE FOR EACH SIDE.
ALL YOU DO IS
REMOVE THE PROPELLER.
THERE'S A COTTER-PIN ON HERE.
OH, NO, NO.
YOU GOTTA REMEMBER, OUTBOARD
MOTORS ARE WATER-COOLED.
WE'RE GONNA COMPENSATE FOR THAT
BY GOIN' REALLY FAST.
ALLS YOU GOTTA DO IS
RE-MOUNT THIS
SO THAT THIS SHAFT RUBS UP
AGAINST THE TIRE,
AND LET FRICTION DO THE REST.
(Grunting)
THERE WE GO --
DROP 'ER INTO GEAR.
I'M THINKIN' BELT DRIVE.
(Grunting)
FOR MAKIN' THE BELT,
I SUGGEST SOMETHING STRONG,
FLEXIBLE, AND WATERPROOF...
THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT, JUST LAY THAT
IN THERE.
THAT WOULDN'T BE ANY MORE SNUG
IF I'D ACTUALLY TAKEN TIME
TO MEASURE IT.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GIVE 'ER A TRY.
(Grunting)
JUST... START UP THE MOTOR.
I DID THAT TO SHOW YOU
WHAT HAPPENS
IF YOU DON'T CUT A GROOVE
IN THE TIRE FOR THE BELT.
YOU WEREN'T THINKIN', WERE YOU?
(Grunting)
YOU WANT TO BE CAREFUL, 'CAUSE
RUBBER DOESN'T GROW ON TREES.
ALL RIGHT, YEAH, IT DOES,
BUT BE CAREFUL IS WHAT I'M--
BE CAREFUL.
OHH...
AHHH...
ALL RIGHT, THERE'S OUR GROOVE.
WE GOT OUR BELT IN IT.
THEY SAY NECESSITY'S
THE MOTHER OF INVENTION.
DON'T KNOW WHO THE FATHER IS.
PROBABLY REMORSE.
I'VE DONE THE SAME THING
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
GOT ANOTHER MOTOR THERE.
GOT THE GROOVE IN THE TIRE
AND THE BELT ON.
THE ORIGINAL OUTBOARD MOTOR'S
ON THE BACK.
SHE'S GOT THE PROP AND THAT'S
HOW WE'LL DRIVE OUR BOAT.
WE STEER THE SAME WAY THEY
STEER BULLDOZERS AND TANKS,
BY SPEEDIN' UP ONE SIDE
OR THE OTHER.
TO TURN LEFT,
SPEED UP THIS MOTOR.
TO TURN RIGHT,
KEEP 'EM THE SAME SPEED,
YOU'RE GOIN' STRAIGHT.
THE BEAUTY OF THIS IS IF YOU
WANT TO MAKE A SHARP CORNER,
JUST FIRE ONE
INTO REVERSE, HUH?
HERE'S SOMETHING
TO THINK ABOUT.
THE BOAT FLOATS
BUT THE TRAILER DOESN'T.
YOU MUST ATTACH ONE
TO THE OTHER.
SPEND A LITTLE EXTRA
AND MAKE 'ER SOLID.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
LET'S GO DRIVIN'
OUR AMPHIBIOUS CAR!
(Motor backfiring)
(Grunting)
CHOKE...
COME ON, BABY --
OH, BOY! OH, BOY!
I'M GONNA GET SEASICK
ON DRY LAND!
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
WANT TO TALK TO YOU GUYS
ABOUT SOMETHING THAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN TO YOUR WIFE
THAT WILL AFFECT YOU
TREMENDOUSLY --
WHEN A WOMAN GETS INTO
THOSE MIDDLE YEARS
AND HAS THIS BIOLOGICAL URGE
TO HAVE ONE MORE CHILD.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE
HER BABIES ARE GROWN
OR MAYBE SHE SEES
A YOUNGER WOMAN EXPECTING,
OR MAYBE SHE REALIZES
THAT ONCE THE KIDS MOVE OUT,
SHE'LL ONLY HAVE YOU.
(Audience laughing)
BUT BELIEVE ME,
PARENTHOOD AT YOUR AGE
IS NOT A GOOD IDEA.
AS YOU'RE SLIPPING
INTO YOUR SECOND CHILDHOOD,
YOU DON'T NEED SOMEBODY WHO'S
JUST STARTIN' THEIR FIRST.
YOU DON'T WANT SOMEBODY ELSE
WHO GOES TO THE BATHROOM
MORE OFTEN THAN
YOU
DO.
SO HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
BORROW A BABY FOR THE WEEKEND.
FIND SOME NEW PARENTS
AND BABYSIT.
GIVE THEM A LITTLE BREAK.
BY THE TIME YOU HIT
THE ONE A.M. FEEDING,
YOUR WIFE WILL BE HAVIN'
SECOND THOUGHTS.
THEN THE 3 A.M. COLIC FIT,
SHE'LL BE ASKING YOU
TO PHONE THE PARENTS,
AND BY THE 4 A.M.
DIAPER CHANGE,
SHE'LL BE PRAYIN'
FOR HOT FLASHES.
JUST LET NATURE
TAKE ITS COURSE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Laughing and applause)
YEAH, IT'S ALL HERE.
YOU EVER SEE $1,143
IN ONE PLACE BEFORE, HAROLD?
YUP.
ON "BAYWATCH NIGHTS".
LIKE, THEY HAD
THESE DRUG DEALERS.
NOT LIKE PHARMACISTS.
THESE WERE
WERE ILLEGAL DRUG DEALERS.
THEY HAD THIS DRUG DEAL,
SO THEY HAD ALL THIS MONEY.
THEN THEY THOUGHT
"LET'S GO FOR A SWIM."
LUCKILY, THEY HAD THEIR SPEEDOS
UNDER THE DRUG-DEALER CLOTHES.
SO THEY GO IN THE WATER.
THEY LEFT THEIR MONEY
UP ON THE BEACH.
SOMEONE STOLE THE MONEY!
SO THEY'RE FREAKIN' OUT.
THEY'RE BLAMING EVERYBODY,
PARTICULARLY THE LIFEGUARDS.
WHO ELSE BUT
PAMELA LEE ANDERSON GETS BLAMED?
THEY WANTED TO FRISK HER!
YOU COULD TELL BY
THE BATHING SUIT SHE HAD ON --
SHE DIDN'T HAVE ANY LUMPS
SHE WASN'T SUPPOSE TO HAVE.
THE LUMPS SHE HAD
WERE WORTH MORE
THAN $1,100.
WHY DO I ASK?
I GOT THE CHEQUE MADE OUT
IN CASH.
THAT WAY IT'S UNTRACEABLE
AND COMPLETELY LIQUID.
I MAY USE PART OF IT
TO BUY SOMETHING
THAT'S COMPLETELY LIQUID.
UNCLE RED, THIS IS DISHONEST.
YOU'RE AN HONEST PERSON.
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN HONEST
WITH ME.
THIS ISN'T DISHONEST.
THE GOVERNMENT SENT ME A CHEQUE
AND I CASHED IT.
END OF STORY.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO --
MIDDLE OF STORY.
END OF HAPPY PART.
GOVERNMENT FINDS THEIR MISTAKE.
GOVERNMENT NAILS UNCLE RED.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD,
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF YOU WERE ME?
I'D INFORM THEM
OF THEIR MISTAKE
AND RETURN THE MONEY.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE NOT ME.
DITTO!
(Siren)
9-1-1.
HOW CAN WE HELP YOU?
(Growling)
WHAT IS THAT?
THAT'S A BEAR!
THAT'S A RABID BEAR!
THAT'S A RABID BEAR IN HEAT!
SOUNDS LIKE A WOLF
WITH A WEDGIE!
WHAT IS THAT?
MAN, HAROLD, I'M GLAD I'M NOT
IN THE ROOM WITH THAT THING!
SOMEBODY'S IN THE ROOM!
HOW ELSE DID THEY CALL?
OH, BOY --
HOUSTON, WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
WE GOTTA CALM THE DOG DOWN.
TALK TO IT.
WHAT WOULD YOU NAME A DOG
THAT SOUNDS LIKE THAT?
KILLER, KILLER, KILLER.
(Snarling)
TERMINATOR.
DEADLY FORCE.
MURDE-- CLARK.
FLUFFY --
FLUFFY, FLUFFY, FLUFFY, FLUFFY!
FLUFFY?
IT COULD BE.
YOU DON'T KNOW THIS DOG.
THIS SOUNDS SO FAMILIAR.
I CAN PICTURE MYSELF
HEARING IT.
I'M RUNNING DOWN THE STREET.
"CALL YOUR DOG, CALL YOUR DOG,
MR. WINSLOW!"
IT'S THE WINSLOW DOG.
JASON, JASON!
(Panting)
GOOD BOY, GOOD DOG.
YOU CAN SAY THAT NOW.
WAIT TILL HE'S CHASING YOU.
MR. WINSLOW, MRS. WINSLOW,
ANYBODY THERE?
HELLO?
THANK-- THANK YOU, GUYS.
THE DOG WAS STOPPING ME FROM
TAKING OUT THE TELEVISION SET.
WELL, THAT'S OK, MR. WINSLOW.
WHY WERE YOU TAKING OUT
THE T.V.?
'CAUSE I'M NOT MR. WINSLOW.
(Audience laughing)
WELL, AS PROMISED, THIS WEEK
ON "ADVENTURES WITH BILL"
WE'LL MAKE SOME WINE.
GOT THE WHEELBARROW FULL OF
GRAPES.
BILL, BILL!
MAN, HEAVY.
BILL HAD GONE TO GET--
OH, HE GOT A CARD TABLE.
WATCH THAT.
YEAH, THE LEGS FOLD UP--
THAT ONE FOLDS UP
THE SAME AS
THE FIRST ONE DID.
OW!
I'M BEGINNING TO THINK
HE ENJOYS THIS.
I WOULD SAY DEFINITELY.
ANYWAY, THAT'S ALL THE LEGS.
SO, PUT HER DOWN THERE.
KIND OF HEAVY HERE, BILL.
WE'RE SET TO SEE WHAT WE GOT.
BILL SAYS YOU GOTTA SEE
HOW MUCH JUICE
YOU CAN GET OUT OF THEM.
THAT'S ONE WAY OF TESTING.
A LOT OF ACID IN THOSE GRAPES.
THIS IS ANOTHER WAY OF, UH...
OH, MAN!
BILL!
THAT WAS A LITTLE BETTER.
BILL, THERE'S A MACHINE
THAT GOES WAY BACK IN TIME.
AHA!
THE WINE PRESS.
YOU DON'T NEED THAT.
OH.
I GUESS I DON'T NEED THAT.
WE PUT THE GRAPES
INTO THE WINE PRESS.
DUMP 'EM IN,
DUMP 'EM IN, DUMP 'EM IN.
THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED YOU TO DO.
OW!
NOW HE PUTS THAT PLATE ON
TO PRESS THEM DOWN.
THEN HE PUTS THE HANDLE ON.
THIS IS A TRADITION.
THE WAY OF SQUEEZING GRAPES
GOES BACK TO THE DAYS
OF SOCRATES PROBABLY.
I BELIEVE HE DRANK
HIS SHARE OF WINE.
HE MUST HAVE.
HAVE YOU READ HIS STUFF?
BILL'S FINDING THAT
THIS IS TEDIOUS.
SO HE'S GOT AN IDEA
OF HOW TO SPEED THE PROCESS.
THIS TECHNIQUE DATES BACK TO
THE DAYS OF HENRY FORD.
HE'S HOOKED UP
A PULLEY SYSTEM
FROM THE WHEEL
OF THE POSSUM VAN.
HE'S GOT ANOTHER HUB ON THERE.
JUST BY STARTING HER UP
AND GOING IN VARIOUS GEARS,
WE CAN RAISE OR LOWER, UH...
WE CAN RAISE OR LOWER
THE, UH, THE UH...
WELL, YOU KNOW.
WE PUT IT IN REVERSE.
THAT SPINS THAT.
AND THEN WHAT THAT WOULD DO
IS LOWER THE PLATE,
AND THAT WOULD
CRUSH THE GRAPES.
NOW WE CAN STOP HER.
THAT STOPS HER.
WE PUT HER INTO DRIVE.
THIS REVERSES EVERYTHING.
THAT WOULD RAISE THE PLATE.
I WAS SO ENTHUSED THAT --
WE SHOULD HAVE WORKED OUT
OUR HAND SIGNALS
'CAUSE I THOUGHT THAT MEANT
PUT HER INTO REVERSE.
THIS IS UNFORTUNATE.
DON'T WATCH THIS.
BUT,
WE GOT OURSELVES SOME WINE.
MAYBE NOT AS CLEAR AS
WHAT IT COULD HAVE BEEN,
BUT WE MADE UP FOR THAT
IN QUANTITY.
AND BILL IS
REALLY NOT FEELING THAT GREAT
RIGHT NOW.
BUT A GOOD ATTITUDE.
HE DIDN'T COMPLAIN.
HE JUST LET OUT A LITTLE WHINE.
HERE'S TO YOU, BILL.
HERE'S SOMETHING SENT
BY A VIEWER.
IT'S THE POSSUM LODGE OATH
IN OLD ENGLISH.
THIS WILL MAKE YOU HAPPY.
I'M GONNA GIVE MY REFUND BACK
BY DIVIDING IT AMONG
THE 20 GUYS THAT HAVE BEEN TO
THE MOST MEETINGS
IN THE LAST FIVE YEARS.
EACH GUY GETS $57.
YOU CALL THAT
GIVING THAT BACK?
THESE GUYS AREN'T SAVERS.
THE MONEY WILL
BE INTO THE ECONOMY
IN A COUPLE OF DAYS.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
TILL THE GOVERNMENT GETS IT.
ANYWAY, I WON'T BE
THE ONLY ONE GOING TO JAIL.
THERE WILL BE 20 OTHER GUYS
THAT I KNOW THERE.
I'M SURE THERE ALREADY ARE.
TELL THE TAX DEPARTMENT
THEY MADE A MISTAKE.
DON'T GIVE THEM YOUR NAME.
THEY'LL TRACK ME DOWN.
THEY'LL SAY SOMETHING
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO HEAR.
THEN THEY'LL KILL ME
'CAUSE I KNOW TOO MUCH.
UNCLE RED KNOWING TOO MUCH.
(Laughing)
NOTHING.
NOW WE FOCUS ON
THE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY,
(All): I DON'T KNOW!
OK, EXCELLENT.
TO JOIN MY UNCLE RED
IS THE PRESIDENT OF
ROTHSCHILD SEPTIC AND
SEWAGE SUCKING SERVICES,
MR. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD!
(Applause)
THIS WEEK'S LETTER COMES FROM
A LADY IN CINCINNATI.
"I'VE BEEN TRYING TO START
MY OWN CAR RENTAL BUSINESS,
"IT'S BEEN A DISASTER.
"I ONLY RENTED ONE CAR
LAST YEAR.
"THE GUY
NEVER BROUGHT IT BACK.
"SO TECHNICALLY,
THAT'S CAR THEFT.
"WHAT CAN I DO?"
SIGNED "THE NUMBER TWO
CAR RENTAL COMPANY.
"WE'RE NOT NUMBER TWO,
BUT WE FEEL LIKE IT."
(Laughing)
YOUR PROBLEM IS
MARKET POSITION.
YOU GOTTA BE FIRST
AND YOU GOTTA BE BEST.
IF YOU CAN'T BE BEST,
BE FIRST.
IF YOU CAN'T BE FIRST,
IT'S NOT ENOUGH TO BE BEST.
IS THAT TRUE ALSO IN ROMANCE?
THESE DAYS
IT'S HARD TO BE FIRST.
(Laughing)
HAROLD'S HAVING TROUBLE
JUST GETTING IN LINE.
(Laughing)
THIS LADY WASN'T THE FIRST
TO GET INTO
THE CAR RENTAL BUSINESS.
SHE SHOULD HAVE PICKED
A DIFFERENT BUSINESS,
SOMETHING A LITTLE MORE UNIQUE.
I WOULD LEAN TOWARD SEWAGE.
CINCINNATI IS A BIG CITY.
MAYBE IT DOESN'T RUN ON
SEPTIC TANKS.
THAT'S TOO BAD --
IT'S A GROWTH BUSINESS.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
IT'S THE LAST THING
PEOPLE STOP DOING.
(Laughing)
WELL,
THAT'S ALL DONE.
TWENTY GUYS SHARED
MY TAX REFUND.
THE REACTION
WAS PRETTY CONSISTENT.
BIG SMILE, THEN
THE CREEPING REALIZATION
THAT THEY OWED ME BIG-TIME.
UNCLE RED,
I PHONED THE TAX DEPARTMENT.
PARDON ME,
HAROLD.
IT'S GOOD NEWS.
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE THIS.
THIS IS SO GOOD.
THIS IS GREAT.
OVER THE YEARS --
THIS IS SO GOOD --
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE IT.
OVER THE YEARS,
YOU'VE EXCEEDED THE LIMIT
TO YOUR MEDICAL EXPENSES.
SO YOU'RE ENTITLED TO
A REBATE OF $1,143.
ISN'T THAT GREAT?!
ARE YOU -- ARE YOU TELLING ME
MY TAX REFUND WAS OK, HAROLD?
OH NO, NO, NO.
FINE.
IT'S NOT A REFUND,
IT'S A REBATE.
THE MONEY WAS ALL YOURS --
IT'S ALL YOURS.
THE WAY THEY PHRASE THINGS
UP THERE, EH!
WOO-OO!
THOSE GUYS.
(Laughing)
THOSE-- THOSE GUYS.
HAROLD, YOU MADE ME GIVE
MY REFUND AWAY TO ALL THE GUYS.
NO, NO,
NO, NO.
YES, YES.
NO, I DID NOT.
I SUGGESTED THAT
WE PHONE THE GOVERNMENT
AND STRAIGHTEN THIS OUT.
BUT YOU CHOSE TO
GIVE THE MONEY AWAY.
I WOULD NEVER CHOOSE TO DO
SUCH A THING.
PERSONALLY, I WOULD SAY
THAT'S STUPID.
YOU KNOW HOW SOMETIMES
PEOPLE NEED TIME ALONE?
YES, I UNDERSTAND,
YOU NEED SOME TIME ALONE.
NO, YOU NEED TIME
AWAY FROM ME.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
NOW, HAROLD.
OK, POINT TAKEN.
I AM RECEIVING
WHAT YOU'RE SENDING OUT.
(Squealing)
I'LL MEET YOU AT THE MEETING.
YOU'LL BE IN YOUR ROOM,
I THINK.
I'LL BE IN MY ROOM.
THAT'S WHERE I'LL GO.
IT'S BETTER FOR ME TO BE AWAY
IN MY ROOM.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M NOT REALLY
GONNA HURT HAROLD,
BUT, AS YOU SAY,
IT'S THE THOUGHT THAT COUNTS.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND EVERYBODY AT--
(Squealing)
KEEP YOUR... ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
TAKE YOUR SEATS, EVERYBODY!
I GOT NO HAROLD HERE.
EVERYBODY STAND UP.
HAROLD'S NOT COMING.
HERE WE GO.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN, GUYS.
YOU PROBABLY HEARD WE HAD
A GAME OF SUNFISH BASEBALL.
IT'S JUST LIKE BASEBALL
EXCEPT YOU USE A SUNFISH.
THEY NOW HAVE A RULING
ON THAT HIT BY MOOSE THOMPSON.
IT'S A HOMER, A GROUNDER
AND A FOUL BALL.