IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW."
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
AND NOW HERE'S A
LEGUME IN HIS OWN TIME,
YOUR HOST,
YOUR HERO,
BUT MY UNCLE,
RED GR-E-E-E-N!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
HEY, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
I WAS ALMOST LATE FOR
THE SHOW, THERE, TODAY.
BUNCH OF KIDS, THERE, BLOCKING
THE WAY UP AT THE TOP
OF CARDIAC HILL.
WELL, THEY WERE ON
THE SIDEWALK, WEREN'T THEY?
YEAH, BUT I WAS TAKING MY
SHORTCUT, YOU KNOW?
YEAH, I FIGURE,
WHEN I'M DRIVING,
EVERYTHING BETWEEN THE FIRE
HYDRANTS IS MY TERRITORY,
YOU KNOW?
WHAT THE HECK WERE THOSE KIDS
DOING UP THERE, HAROLD?
WELL, THOSE ARE
THE LITTLE GUYS.
YOU KNOW? FROM THE BIG GUY
LITTLE GUY CLUB.
IT'S, LIKE, WHERE A MAN
VOLUNTEERS HIS TIME TO BE
WITH A LITTLE BOY WHO DOESN'T
HAVE A FATHER AVAILABLE.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
I'M THEIR SECRETARY.
I'VE ASKED YOU TO
JOIN A MILLION TIMES.
OH, NO, I CAN'T RELATE, HAROLD.
I FIND THE YOUNG PEOPLE WANT TO
DO THINGS FAST AND OFTEN.
THAT'S NOT
REALLY MY STYLE.
WELL, REALLY, WHEN YOU THINK
OF IT, THAT'S PART OF THE
CHALLENGE, ACTUALLY.
YOU KNOW, DEFINING COMMON
INTERESTS AND ACTIVITIES
TO SHARE WITH THE YOUNG BOY.
WELL, THAT'S WHY
WE'RE HAVING THE
SOAP BOX DERBY.
SOAP BOX DERBY?
OH, NOW, I LOVE
THE SOAP BOX DERBIES.
IF YOU WERE TO BECOME A BIG GUY,
AND WE FOUND YOU A LITTLE GUY,
YOU COULD BE IN THE DERBY.
WELL, I DON'T WANT
TO MAKE A BIG COMMITMENT.
MAYBE I COULD BE A
24-HOUR BIG GUY.
OKAY. BUT I'D HAVE TO
RUN YOUR NAME THROUGH
THE COMPUTER.
HOW COME?
TO FIND OUT IF YOU'VE
EVER BEEN IN TROUBLE
WITH THE POLICE.
WELL, IF YOU'RE
GOING TO NITPICK...
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
HERE'S A FEW SCENES
FROM THIS WEEK'S SHOW.
THE USUAL STUFF.
THERE'S A NEW GUY THERE;
NEW GUY FOR YOU TO MEET.
AND, OF COURSE, YOU'VE GOT AN
ADVENTURE FILM, AS PER USUAL.
OH, DON'T WORRY. WE'RE STILL
SPINNING OUR WHEELS HERE.
WELL, THEY'RE GETTING
CARDIAC HILL ALL SET FOR
THE SOAP BOX DERBY THERE.
THEY'VE GOT THE BALES OF
STRAW RUNNING DOWN THE SIDES.
THEY'VE GOT THE SKIN GRAFT UNIT
DOWN AT THE FINISH LINE.
OH, I SEE YOU'VE GOT THE
RESULTS OF YOUR URINE TEST.
NO. NO. THIS IS A LIST OF
YOUR COMMUNITY INFRACTIONS.
VERY IMPRESSIVE.
OH, YES,
INDEEDY DOODY.
LOOK AT THAT... WE'VE GOT AIR
POLLUTION, NOISE POLLUTION,
LITTERING,
PROPERTY DAMAGE.
THAT'S NOT TOO BAD, HAROLD.
THERE'S NO FATALITIES THERE.
OH, JUST ONE:
MOTHER NATURE.
WHY WOULD YOU CARE?
SHE'S NO FRIEND OF YOURS.
YOU BETTER START BEING
NICE TO ME, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE I WAS JUST CONSIDERING
BENDING THE RULES TO LET YOU IN
THE BIG GUY LITTLE GUY CLUB.
YEAH, BUT, HAROLD, I ONLY
WANT TO JOIN IF I CAN GET
INTO THE SOAP BOX DERBY.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
BUT WE'VE GOT TO
DO THE PLEDGE.
PUT ONE HAND
OVER YOUR HEART
AND THE OTHER ONE
ON YOUR WALLET,
AND REPEAT AFTER ME.
I PROMISE TO BE A BIG GUY
TO A LITTLE GUY
UNTIL THE LITTLE GUY
BECOMES A BIG GUY.
I PROMISE TO BE A BIG GUY
TO A LITTLE GUY
UNTIL THE END
OF THE RACE.
OKAY. YEAH.
CLOSE ENOUGH.
ALSO -- ALSO -- ALSO -- ALSO
THERE'S THE CLUB SONG.
YOU HAVE TO DO THE CLUB SONG.
SONG?
IT'S LIKE THIS...
BA-BA-BIG GUY
DON'T CRY, LITTLE GUY.
I'LL BE YOUR BIG, BIG,
BIG, BIG, BIG GUY!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
OKAY?
SO, NOW YOU GO.
OKAY. GO.
BA-BA-BA-BIG GUY!
BA-BA-BA?
BA-BA-BA-BIG GUY.
BA-BA-BA
BIG GUY?
D-D-D-DON'T CRY
LITTLE GUY,
DON'T-UH-,
I'LL BE YOUR --
I'LL BE --
NOT YOU, ME.
I'LL BE -- I'LL BE --
I'LL BE -- I'LL --
YOUR BIG GUY --
I'LL BE YOUR --
BIG GUY --
BIG GUY.
LITTLE GUY.
I'LL BE YOUR
BIG GUY -- LITTLE GUY.
MY GUY.
YO!
YO.
(CHEERES AND APPLAUSE)
WAS THAT
GOOD ENOUGH?
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST MADE THE SONG UP.
OH, MY UNCLE JOE WAS
A HANDSOME MAN
WITH HIS ICY COLD BLUE EYES
BUT THE THING THAT
MADE HIM DIFFERENT
MY UNCLE JOE WAS
COVERED WITH FLIES
OH, UNCLE JOE HAD LOTS OF
FLIES ZOOMING ROUND HIS HEAD
I'VE SEEN OTHER THINGS WITH
MORE FLIES ON 'EM
BUT MOST OF THEM WERE DEAD
OH, UNCLE JOE WAS
A WILD, WILD, MAN
HE'D DRINK HOMEMADE
BEER BY THE DOZEN
DOES HE ACT THAT WAY
BECAUSE OF THE FLIES
OR IS UNCLE JOE THE
ONE WITH THE BUZZ ON?
OKEYDOKEY DOO!
WELCOME BACK TO THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
AND, THIS WEEK, Mr. MIKE HAMAR
IS PLAYING FOR A FABULOUS PRIZE:
AN ENTIRE CAR ALARM SYSTEM
BROUGHT TO YOU BY THE
PEOPLE OF CAR SAFE.
OH, I KNOW THOSE.
THOSE ARE GOOD ONES.
REMEMBER, CAR SAFE
STOPS THIEVES COLD.
UNLESS YOU HAVE A HAIRPIN
AND A BENT KNIFE.
OKAY. FINE!
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET Mr. MIKE HAMAR TO
SAY THIS WORD...
PURCHASE.
30 SECONDS AND GO!
ALL RIGHT, MIKE, YOU GO INTO A
STORE, AND YOU SEE SOMETHING
THAT YOU WANT AND YOU NEED,
SO YOU...
STEAL.
NO.
SWIPE.
GRAB.
NO.5
SNATCH.
NO.
BOOST.
PAWN.
NO.
HOLSTER.
MIKE! MIKE!
MIKE, FOR STARTERS,
YOU HAVE MONEY TO PAY
FOR THIS THING.
OH! OH! OH!
OKAY. DIFFERENT STORY, RIGHT?
SO YOU GO INTO
THE STORE AND YOU...
RIP OFF?
NO-O-O-O.
PILFER?
NO.
FILCH?
MIKE, ARE YOU NOT GETTING THIS?
ALL RIGHT, THINK ABOUT
IT THIS WAY.
YOU HAVE A WALLET IN
YOUR POCKET, OKAY?
THAT WALLET IS
FULL OF MONEY.
FULL OF CREDIT CARDS.
SO YOU GO RIGHT UP TO
THE COUNTER AND YOU...
MIKE, YOU GO
RIGHT UP THERE.
WHAT YOU DO IS YOU
TAKE IT, AND YOU...
RETURN IT?
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
HEY. HEY. HEY. HEY. HEY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS IS $50 SHORT.
YEAH, I HAD TO
MAKE A FEW PURCHASES.
(FRANTIC BELL RINGING)
CONGRATULATIONS.
THAT'S MARVELOUS.
WAY TO GO!
ALL RIGHT. SO YOUR VAN HAS BLOWN
A GASKET, AND YOU'RE ABOUT
TO DO THE SAME.
BUT YOU'RE LOOKIN' AT A TOW
TRUCK CHARGE THAT'S GONNA
BE MORE THAN THE DARN
VEHICLE'S WORTH.
SO I THOUGHT THIS WEEK ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'D SHOW YOU A WAY TO AVOID
THOSE ENDLESS TOW TRUCK CHARGES.
BASICALLY, NOW, YOU'VE
GOT TWO CHOICES.
ONE:  YOU COULD BUILD
YOUR OWN TOW TRUCK;
BUT, OTHERWISE, YOU COULD TAKE
BETTER CARE OF YOUR VEHICLE.
GET THAT MAINTENANCE DONE
ON A REGULAR BASIS.
ALL RIGHT. HERE'S HOW
TO BUILD YOUR OWN TOW TRUCK.
FIRST THING YOU NEED
IS A BOAT TRAILER.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE
A BOAT TRAILER,
JUST GO DOWN TO YOUR LOCAL
MARINA AND YOU CAN PICK
ONE UP CHEAP.
OR, IF YOU'RE REALLY
ON A BUDGET,
GO DOWN TO YOUR LOCAL BOAT RAMP
AND JUST PICK ONE UP.
ALL RIGHT. NEXT THING
YOU NEED IS A TRUCK.
UNFORTUNATELY, MY TRUCK
IS THE VAN.
SO I BOUGHT THIS CAR
OFF BUSTER HATFIELD.
I GAVE HIM $100 FOR IT,
AND I KNOW THAT'S A LOT
TO PAY FOR A CAR,
BUT I WANTED SOMETHING
THAT WOULD LAST.
SO NOW I'M GONNA
MAKE A TOW TRUCK.
WELL, I SHOULD SAY A TOW CAR.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS LIFT THE
TONGUE OF THE TRAILER UP HIGH
ENOUGH AND GET THE BACK
END UNDER THERE.
AND THEN YOU WANT TO
GET IT A LONG WAY IN.
OTHERWISE, IT COULD
BE DANGEROUS.
OKAY, NOW YOU WANT TO ATTACH
THAT TO THE BACK OF THE CAR
AS FIRMLY AS POSSIBLE.
AND THOSE OF YOU WHO HAVE SEEN
THE SHOW BEFORE KNOW WHAT I'M
GOING TO SAY NEXT.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE
WE'RE MARRIED.
ALL RIGHT. THAT'S GOT HER.
NOW WHAT YOU DO IS YOU TAKE
YOUR CABLE OFF THE WINCH THERE,
AND YOU TAKE THAT DOWN,
HOOK HER RIGHT ON TO VEHICLE
THAT NEEDS TO BE TOWED,
AND THEN YOU JUST WINCH THE
TRAILER DOWN SO THE HITCH FITS
RIGHT ON TO THE BALL.
ALL RIGHT.
AND THAT'S GOT HER.
ALL RIGHT. JUST CLAMP
HER DOWN HERE.
AND, GUYS, IF YOU HAVE
A TWO-INCH HITCH, USE A
TWO-INCH BALL NOT A 1 7/8TH.
YOU'VE GOT A TON OF METAL UP
IN THE AIR HELD TOGETHER TO
YOUR CAR WITH DUCT TAPE.
LET'S NOT BE STUPID.
SAME THING WITH
THE SAFETY CHAINS.
NOT SOMETHING YOU
USE A WHOLE LOT,
BUT, YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE
EVER GOING TO USE 'EM,
THIS MIGHT JUST BE THE TIME.
NOW I JUST GOT TO ADD SOME
WEIGHT TO MY TOW TRUCK,
AND WE'RE DONE.
BOY -- OH, THIS SHOULD DO IT.
AND THAT'S GOT HER.
SO, REMEMBER, IF WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
AND NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I REALLY MUST BE TOWING.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU OLDER GUYS
ABOUT SOMETHING THAT WOMEN
DO BETTER THAN US --
OTHER THAN SHAVE THEIR LEGS --
AND THAT IS TALK.
YOU KNOW, WHEN A GUY GETS MAD,
HIS VOCABULARY WILL SHIFT DOWN
TO THE FOUR LETTER WORDS...
DANG, SHUCKS, GOSH,
AND EVEN WORSE IF
THE KIDS AREN'T AROUND.
BUT WHEN A WOMAN
GETS TICKED OFF,
MAN, SHE COMES UP WITH PHRASES
AND EXPRESSIONS THAT WOULD PUT
SHAKESPEARE TO SHAME.
NOW, SCIENTISTS TELL US THAT
WOMEN ACTUALLY HAVE MORE
SPACE IN THEIR BRAIN
FOR VERBAL SKILLS.
BUT, GUYS, I GOT
THE GREAT EQUALIZER.
TWO WORDS THAT WILL STOP ANY
ARGUMENT COLD IN ITS TRACKS...
"YES, DEAR!"
OH, YEAH, IF SHE SAYS A SENTENCE
THAT KIND OF GOES UP AT THE END,
TWO OUT OF THREE TIMES,
"YES, DEAR" IS THE
PERFECT ANSWER.
OR YOU GET A LONG PAUSE...
IN A CONVERSATION,
YOU JUST DROP "YES, DEAR"
RIGHT IN THERE.
BUT LISTEN, NEVER USE
"YES, DEAR" IF HER
SENTENCE STARTS,
"YOU KNOW WHAT YOUR PROBLEM IS?"
NOW, I KNOW SOME GUYS PREFER
TOTAL SILENCE AS A RESPONSE,
BUT I DON'T RECOMMEND IT,
BECAUSE TO HAVE TOTAL SILENCE,
YOU HAVE TO BE ALL ALONE.
AND THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENS.
SO, "YES, DEAR" IS BAD
ENOUGH IN PERSON,
IT'S MUCH WORSE OVER THE PHONE,
AND A LOT MORE EXPENSIVE
THROUGH YOUR LAWYER.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(APPLAUSE)
HERE'S A TIP FOR YOU
RACING GUYS OUT THERE.
WHEN YOU'VE BEEN TO
THE SOAP BOX DERBY,
GET THE BIGGEST WHEELS
YOU CAN GET.
I TELL YOU, MOOSE THOMPSON, HE
USED GROCERY CART WHEELS.
THEY GOT SO HOT THEY BURNED ALL
THE HAIR OFF HIS LEGS.
NOW, LUCKILY HIS NATURAL BODILY
FUNCTIONS PUT OUT THE FIRE
BEFORE IT SPREAD TO HIS BACK.
SO I'M GOING TO USE
BICYCLE WHEELS ON MINE.
HEY, WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA.
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE IN
THE BIG GUY LITTLE GUY CLUB
DOESN'T MEAN YOU GET TO
BE IN THE DERBY RIGHT AWAY.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE
A LITTLE GUY.
AND, SO FAR, NO KID IN THE
POSSUM LAKE AREA WANTS
TO BE WITH YOU.
WELL, HOW COME,
HAROLD?
WELL, SOMEONE SAID THAT
YOU'RE TOO BOSSY,
AND YOU DON'T THINK,
AND YOU DON'T LISTEN,
AND YOU DO DANGEROUS STUFF.
WHO TOLD 'EM THAT?
THAT'S NOT THE POINT, REALLY.
COME ON. THERE'S GOT TO
BE SOME KID THAT WOULD
DO IT, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW WHAT
WE'LL DO?
WE'LL SWEETEN THE POT
A LITTLE BIT.
LET THE GUY JOIN THE LODGE,
AND HE CAN FIX THE BOATS,
WASH THE CARS.
KIDS LOVE DOING
THAT KIND OF --
WELL, HOW ABOUT SPENDING
A LITTLE TIME WITH THE
LITTLE GUY, HUH?
MAYBE DO THINGS THAT
HE'S INTERESTED IN,
LIKE PLAYING SPORTS OR
GOING TO ROCK CONCERTS.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, WHEN
I WAS A KID, I HAD TO DO
WHATEVER THE ADULTS WANTED.
AND NOW THAT I'M AN ADULT,
YOU WANT ME TO DO WHAT
THE KIDS WANT.
FORGET IT. YOU'RE NOT CHANGING
THE RULES ON ME NOW, BUDDY.
WELL, I'M SORRY,
UNCLE RED,
BUT YOU HAVE TO HAVE A
LITTLE GUY TO BE IN THE DERBY.
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
I TELL YOU WHAT,
I'LL PAY HIM $10.
I DON'T KNOW.
$10 MIGHT NOT DO IT.
WELL, I'LL PAY MORE
IF HE'LL TAKE A CHEQUE.
(APPLAUSE)
THIS IS THE ONLY RADIO STATION
IN THE WHOLE POSSUM LAKE AREA;
OWNED, OPERATED, HOSTED, BUILT
AND PARTIALLY PAID FOR
BY SPARKY HOOVER.
HE LETS THE LODGE ADVERTISE FOR
FREE, AND THAT'S WHY WE'RE HERE.
SO HOW'S
IT GOING, SPARK?
OH, OH, SORRY, SORRY.
AND THAT WAS 'SMOOCHY
AND THE WET ONES' SINGING
"I NEVER SEEN A GIRL
WITH ONE OF THOSE."
(SOUND OF TYPEWRITER)
(IN 'REPORTER' VOICE)
TIME NOW FOR THE HOOVER REPORT
WHERE YOUR HOST SPARKY HOOVER
TACKLES THE TOUGH POLITICAL AND
CONTROVERSIAL ISSUES OF THE DAY.
JOINING SPARKY TODAY IS RED
GREEN, LOCAL LODGE LEADER
AND A BIT OF AN ODD BALL,
BUT AT LEAST HE'S
NOT ONE OF "THEM"!
SPARKY.
(NORMAL VOICE)
HEY, YEAH, THANKS A LOT, JASON.
AND HELLO TO RED GREEN.
HOW ARE YOU?
WELL, I'M A LITTLE CONFUSED,
I GUESS, SPARKY.
HOW'S THE SCHOOL BUS
DRIVING GOING?
OH, IT'S FINE.
MAINLY IT KEEPS "THEM"
FROM GETTING ME!
YOU KNOW, THEY'D NEVER BLOW
UP A BUSLOAD OF KIDS
JUST TO GET TO ME.
FIGHT THE POWER!
HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN
THAT THERE, SPARK?
MAYBE IT'S TIME TO CLEAN
THE REAR VIEW MIRROR.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
Sparky:  WELL, YEAH.
WELL, THAT'S BRIAN.
I DIDN'T HAVE TIME
TO TAKE HIM HOME.
I'LL DO IT LATER.
RIGHT.
NOW I'VE GOT
THE SHOW TO DO.
YOU KNOW, RED,
THIS ISN'T JUST RADIO,
IT'S HAM RADIO!
THAT'S A MARRIAGE MADE IN
HEAVEN, I WOULD THINK.
ALL RIGHT, ALL YOU
HAM OPERATORS OUT THERE,
I WANT YOU TO JOIN
US ON THE AIR.
HIT YOUR TALK BUTTONS,
AND LET'S RAP ABOUT
POLITICS AND WHATNOT.
YEAH, LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
NUMBER ONE ISSUE THAT
PLAGUES US ALL.
U.F.O.s!
Male voice:  YEAH,
HELLO, SPARKY?
THIS IS, SPARKY.
Male Voice:  LISTEN, CAN YOU
TURN YOUR SIGNAL DOWN?
I'M GETTING YOUR
SHOW ON MY FILLINGS,
AND YOUR TOWER JUST
MICROWAVED MY COW.
AND, OH, BY THE WAY, SPARKY,
COULD YOU BRING BRIAN HOME?
HE'S GOT FATHER AND SON
CHESS CLUB TONIGHT.
IT'S THE C.I.A.
YEAH?
A TRICK TO GET ME
OFF THE AIR.
OH, YEAH?
JUST ACT NORMAL.
YOU CAN DO THAT?
OBVIOUSLY A NATURE-ORIENTED
ADVENTURE WITH BILL THIS WEEK.
HE'S OUT THERE TRYING TO GET
HIMSELF A BUTTERFLY,
AND I JUST JOINED HIM.
I'M HERE, BILL.
I'M HERE.
I MEAN, THE VAN IS RIGHT HERE.
KIND OF HARD TO BELIEVE THAT
HE'S GOING TO CATCH A BUTTERFLY
IF HE CAN'T SEE A VAN.
HERE HE COMES.
YOU OKAY, BILL?
YEP, HE'S FINE.
YEP, I KNOW. OH!
BOY, I'M SO GLAD I CAME.
WELL, THERE'S A BUTTERFLY
SITTING RIGHT THERE.
BILL, SNEAK UP.
WELL, THAT'S A BIGGER NUT,
ISN'T IT, BILL?
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT. I GUESS
HE KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
OH, BOY! OH, LOOK.
I'M NOT TOUCHING HIM.
OKAY, THERE YOU GO.
THE BEST THING TO DO HERE
IS JUST KIND OF WAIT
THIS OUT, I THINK.
BOY, MAYBE I'LL TAKE HIM BACK
TO THE LODGE AND MIX
SOME PAINT.
OH, THERE IT IS.
OH, HE GOT IT.
YOU GOT -- BILL, YOU GOT IT.
YOU GOT HER. YOU GOT HER.
ALL RIGHT. GOOD. EXCELLENT.
OH!
OKAY. YOU'VE
GOT THE BUTTERFLY,
AND WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO NOW?
OH, THAT'S ETHER.
ETHER.
HE'S KIND OF THE ETHER BUNNY.
PUT THAT ON THE BUTTERFLY,
AND ADD IT TO -- DON'T PUT IT
UNDER THERE, BILL.
NO, NO, YOU DON'T WANT
YOUR ARMPIT GOING TO SLEEP.
OH! OH, A LITTLE BIT OF
THAT ON THE BUTTERFLY.
OH! OH! ALL RIGHT.
KIDS, DON'T TRY THIS AT HOME.
LATER THAT DAY...
I PUT THE MIRROR BACK ON THE
VAN AND HERE COMES THE
BUTTERFLY AGAIN.
OH!
FLY'S NOT EVEN ON
THAT SIDE OF MY PANTS.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GETTING
OUT OF THERE.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
THANKS, BILL.
NOT REALIZING THE BUTTERFLY
WAS ON MY TRAILER HITCH,
AND, IN ONE FELL SWOOP,
BILL GRABS IT.
OH, I GUESS I DIDN'T NOTICE.
GEE, I FEEL BAD
ABOUT THIS.
OH, MY GOSH, THERE'S A LOG.
I'LL JUST STRADDLE THAT.
OH, LOOK, BILL HAS
A KNOT IN HIS HAIR.
OH, I BETTER GO BACK AND MAKE
SURE HE'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW HOW HE GETS.
YOU'RE FINE.
OH, SURE, YOU'RE FINE.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO GET
THAT SHOE ON.
LOOK, BILL, I'VE GOT SOME
GREAT NEWS FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW, YOU THOUGHT
YOU HAD GIVEN UP.
YOU THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T
GOING TO CATCH IT.
THAT SAYS DODGE,
BUT THE BUTTERFLY FORGOT TO.
WELL, YEAH, YEAH.
HE NEEDS A LITTLE
GUY RIGHT AWAY
BECAUSE HE WANTS TO BE
IN THE SOAP BOX DERBY.
WELL, YEAH! WELL, YEAH, OF
COURSE, HE'S IN THE BIG GUY
LITTLE GUY CLUB.
YEAH, RED GREEN.
THAT'S RIGHT. YEAH, RED GREEN
OF THE POSSUM LODGE.
(DIAL TONE)
HELLO? HELLO?
I DON'T LIKE TO BRAG,
BUT I THINK I MAY HAVE BUILT
THE ULTIMATE SOAP BOX
LITTLE UNIT THERE.
UNBELIEVABLE.
SHE'S AERODYNAMIC,
ALMOST FRICTIONLESS.
SHE'S LIGHT, AND SHE IS QUICK!
I TELL YOU, WHEN THEY FIRE THAT
STARTER PISTOL AT THE TOP OF
CARDIAC HILL,
THAT LITTLE CAR IS GOING TO GO
DOWN FASTER THAN A LARGE DRAFT
AT CLOSING TIME.
SO, HAROLD, WHO'S THE LUCKY
LITTLE GUY WHO'LL JOIN ME
IN THE WINNER'S CIRCLE?
WELL, THAT'S THE INTERESTING
THING BECAUSE SO FAR --
WELL, NOBODY.
DID YOU TELL THEM
I'D PAY THEM $10?
YES, I DID. BUT MOST OF THEM
PUT A MUCH HIGHER VALUE ON
THEIR LIFE THAN THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, HAROLD?
YOU GOT ME INTO THIS,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO BE MY LITTLE GUY.
NO! NO WAY! NO! NO!
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S GONNA WORK.
I DON'T PAY
YOU TO THINK.
YOU DON'T PAY ME.
THEN IT WILL
SAVE ME $10.
(APPLAUSE)
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU TEENAGERS
OUT THERE WHO PLAY THE VIDEO
GAMES AND THE COMPUTER GAMES
BECAUSE YOU MAY BE READY FOR
THE ULTIMATE 3-D EXPERIENCE.
IT'S CALLED REALITY. HUH?
REALITY COMES WITH ITS OWN
HARDWARE AND SOFTWARE,
AND IT'S FULLY
COMPATIBLE WITH YOU.
NOW, SEE, THE IDEA OF THE GAME
IS YOU WORK YOURSELF AROUND THIS
PLACE CALLED EARTH,
HOPING THAT YOU DON'T SCREW
UP SO BAD THAT YOU EMBARRASS
YOURSELF AND YOUR FRIENDS.
AND TAKE IT FROM ME,
IT'S A LOT HARDER
THAN IT SOUNDS.
ANYWAY, I THOUGHT I WOULD
GIVE YOU A FEW TIPS;
MAYBE HELP YOU GET TO THE
ADVANCED LEVELS, ALL RIGHT?
YOU KNOW WHEN THOSE VIDEO
CHARACTERS IN THOSE VIDEO GAMES,
WHEN THEY GET BLOWN TO BITS,
THEY JUST KIND OF BOUNCE
RIGHT BACK?
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE TRYING
THAT IN REALITY, OKAY?
MAKES FOR A SHORT GAME.
AND YOU KNOW ON THE VIDEO GAMES,
IT'S EASY TO RECOGNIZE
THE BAD GUYS?
WELL, SEE, NOW, IN REALITY,
SOMETIMES THE BAD GUYS ARE
GOOD AND THE GOOD GUYS ARE BAD,
SO DON'T BE SHOOTING OR
LASER BLASTING ANYBODY
BECAUSE YOU MAY NEED THEIR
HELP BEFORE THE GAME IS OVER.
OF COURSE, NOW, YOU CAN SAVE THE
VIDEO GAMES, CAN'T YOU?
TRY AGAIN.
REALITY DOESN'T HAVE
A SAVE BUTTON.
ALTHOUGH IT DOES HAVE A LITTLE
WRINKLE CALLED CONSEQUENCES.
REALITY IS A GOOD GAME.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
TRY IT SOMETIME.
BUT LET ME WARN YOU,
IT'S EXPENSIVE.
WELL, HOW DO YOU SUPPOSE WE
DID AT THE SOAP BOX DERBY?
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
BY GOLLY. OH! WHAT A MACHINE!
BOY, DID THAT BABY --
I'VE GOT TO GIVE HAROLD
A LOT OF CREDIT.
HE DROVE A HECK OF A RACE
DESPITE THE FEAR.
YOU KNOW, I NEVER REALIZED
THE HUMAN EYEBALL COULD
OPEN THAT WIDE.
OH, NOW, HAROLD --
HAROLD, HAROLD,
THAT WAS REALLY SMART
USING POSSUM LAKE TO STOP
YOURSELF LIKE THAT.
HEY, LOOK. WE WON!
I DON'T WANT TO BE
YOUR PARTNER ANYMORE.
COME ON, NOW, HAROLD,
THAT WAS GREAT.
THAT TOOK A LOT OF
NERVE TO GO THAT FAST.
OH, WELL, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY, IT WAS
QUITE EASY CONSIDERING THE
VEHICLE HAD NO BRAKES.
BUT I HAD TO KEEP
THE WEIGHT DOWN.
OKAY. FINE. BUT HOW HEAVY
CAN STEERING BE?
WELL, NOW THAT WAS --
WE HAD A HARD FIGHT
ON THAT ONE.
WE HAD A LOT OF COMPETITION
IN THAT RACE...
BUSTER HATFIELD
PRETENDING HE WAS A KID.
AND JUNIOR SINGLETON WAS HIDING
DOWN IN HIS CAR PUMPING ON THE
PEDALS TO MAKE IT GO FASTER.
WERE THEY THE ONES
THAT HIT THE FENCE?
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, RIPPED ALL
THEIR CLOTHES OFF.
YOU COULD SURE TELL
THE BIG GUY FROM
THE LITTLE GUY.
(POSSUM CALL)
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A SEC.
I THINK I
ALREADY WENT.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I'M COMING HOME A WINNER.
NOT TOO MUCH ON THE
FAME AND FORTUNE.
BUT IF YOU'RE LOOKING TO GO DOWN
HILL IN A HURRY, I'M YOUR MAN.
TO THE REST OF YA,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
NOW, FOR MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG HERE
AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTER]
Harold:  TAKE YOUR SEATS PLEASE.
EVERYBODY, SIT DOWN.
HE'S HERE NOW.
OKAY, TAKE YOUR SEATS.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUKUS MORITATI.
Red:  SIT DOWN.
Harold:  OKAY. THERE'S NO
ANNOUNCEMENTS TONIGHT.
JUST A COUPLE OF
LOST AND FOUNDS.
LOST:  SHORT-HAIRED, MIX BREED
DOG VERY AFFECTIONATE
WITH PEOPLE,
DISTINCTIVE COLOURING,
HEALTHY APPETITE.
THAT'S A LITTLE PICTURE THERE.
AND FOUND ALMOST BALD,
A REAL MUTT DOG,
CONSTANTLY TRIES TO RUB AGAINST
PEOPLE, BLOTCHY COLOURING,
EATS LIKE A PIG.
CALL BUSTER HATFIELD.
A LITTLE PICTURE THERE.
AND... OH, THAT'S IT. OKAY.
YEAH! I THOUGHT IT WAS
A CAT FOR A MINUTE.
WELL, THERE'S ONE CASE SOLVED.
SO THERE ARE NO
ANNOUNCEMENTS TONIGHT.