YOU EVER SEEN ONE
OF THESE?
IT'S CALLED A G.P.S.,
WHICH STANDS FOR --
WELL, WHO CARES?
THE POINT IS THIS
THING USES SATELLITES
TO TELL YOU WHERE YOU ARE,
WHICH MEANS THAT EVERY MAN
CAN HAVE A $500 REASON
NOT TO ASK FOR DIRECTIONS.
BUT THAT ISN'T NEARLY AS GOOD
AS WHAT I'VE COME UP WITH.
I GOT MYSELF ONE OF
THESE ANIMAL TAGS
THAT HAVE THE LITTLE
TRANSMITTERS IN THEM
THEY USE TO
TRACK ANIMALS.
YOU'VE PROBABLY SEEN THEM ON
THOSE NATURE SHOWS
WHERE SOME ANIMAL LOVERS ARE
TRYING TO PROTECT THE SPECIES,
BUY SHOOTING THEM WITH A
TRANQUILIZER DART
AND THEN STAPLING ONE
OF THESE IN THEIR EAR.
WELL, HERE'S WHAT
I'VE DONE.
I'VE MADE EARRINGS
AND PUT ONE OF THOSE
TRANSMITTERS INTO EVERY PAIR.
BUT HERE'S THE BEST PART...
I MADE A WHOLE WHACK
OF THESE EARRINGS,
AND I GAVE THE PRETTIEST
PAIR TO MY WIFE BERNICE.
SHE'S OUT RIGHT NOW,
BUT I'M SURE
SHE'S WEARING THEM.
THAT'S WAY BETTER
THAN G.P.S., EH?
'CAUSE G.P.S. ONLY
TELLS ME WHERE I AM.
HEY, IF I'M HAVING
A GOOD TIME,
I DON'T CARE WHERE I AM!
BUT WITH THESE
TRANSMITTING EARRINGS,
EVERY TIME BERNICE
COMES HOME EARLY
OR SAUNTERS OUT
TO THE GARAGE
TO SEE WHERE THE
SMOKE IS COMING FROM,
THIS BABY STARTS BEEPING,
WHICH GIVES ME TIME
TO HIDE THE DAMAGE
OR AT LEAST COME UP
WITH AN EXCUSE.
[electronic beeping]
OH, MAN.
SHE WASN'T DUE BACK
FOR A COUPLE HOURS.
HI, HONEY!
[beeping continues]
[beeping slowly dies]
[cheers and applause]]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
ALL RIGHT. THANK YOU.
WELL, I HAD QUITE AN
EXPERIENCE LAST NIGHT,
AND WHEN I GOT HOME,
BERNICE WAS STANDING THERE,
WEARING HER COAT
AND I COULDN'T SMELL DINNER
COOKING OR ANYTHING.
I NOTICED THAT THE
POWER WAS STILL ON.
AND THEN IT STRUCK ME...
IT'S OUR ANNIVERSARY.
SO I DECIDED TO TAKE HER
OUT TO THE DINNER THEATRE
UP IN PORT ASBESTOS,
BECAUSE...
SHE'D ALREADY BOUGHT
TICKETS FOR THAT.
UNCLE RED!
[cheers and applause]]
YOU WENT OUT
LAST NIGHT.
HOW WAS THE
DINNER THEATRE?
OH, MY GOSH,
I'LL TELL YOU,
THAT CHEZ RALF,
IT'S A RIP-OFF.
THIRTY BUCKS, YOU GET
THREE LITTLE POTATOES;
YOU GET A DINNER ROLL
LIKE A GOLF BALL --
AND I'M TALKING
WITH THE BACKSPIN.
AND THEY GIVE YOU SOME
SORT OF A CORNISH
CHICKEN THING
THAT HAD THE MUSCLE
MASS OF A CHIUHUAHUA.
WELL, YOU KNOW
WHAT THEY SAY...
A FOOL AND HIS MONEY
EAT AT RALF'S.
AND THE PLAY,
OH, MAN, BRUTAL.
YEAH, IT WAS CALLED
"THE MOUSETRAP".
SO I'M WAITING
AND I'M WAITING.
THE ONLY MOUSE I SAW
COME OUT OF THE KITCHEN.
IN FACT, I THINK
THEY KEEP MICE IN THERE,
IN CASE SOMEBODY
ORDERS RIBS.
OH! OH! OH!
YOU KNOW WHAT
WE COULD DO?
KNOW WHAT WE COULD DO?
WE COULD OPEN OUR
OWN DINNER THEATRE.
YEAH, THAT PORCH BEHIND
THE LODGE THERE,
IT HOLDS, LIKE,
100 PEOPLE.
YEAH, AND AT 30 BUCKS
A PLATE, THAT'S...
A LOT.
OH, WE'RE GONNA
NEED A PLAY.
WELL, WE'LL JUST TAKE
AN EXISTING PLAY,
AND WE'LL CHANGE IT
JUST A LITTLE BIT.
NOBODY AROUND HERE WILL
NOTICE, THAT'S FOR SURE.
OH, OKAY, WELL, WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO ABOUT ACTORS?
HAROLD, WHENEVER
YOU HAVE MARRIED MEN,
YOU HAVE ACTORS.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]]
TODAY'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FOR 200 AIR SICKNESS BAGS.
IDEAL FOR CARRYING
YOUR LUNCH BEFORE
OR AFTER YOU EAT IT.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
EARS, HAROLD.
UH, MR. GREEN,
YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET HAROLD
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH,
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND... GO!
OKAY, HAROLD, WHAT DO YOU
CALL PEOPLE WHO COME
OVER TO YOUR HOUSE?
MY DUNGEONS AND
DRAGONS CLUB.
OKAY, THAT'S MY FAULT.
OKAY, WHAT DO YOU CALL PEOPLE
WHO COME OVER TO MY HOUSE?
EXTERMINATORS.
NO, OKAY, NO.
A GROUP OF ACTORS
TOGETHER FORM...
AN UNEMPLOYMENT LINE.
NO, OKAY. OKAY.
IF YOU HAVE LIKE MAYBE
20 GUYS IN THE ARMY,
THAT'S CALLED...
THE CANADIAN MILITARY.
[applause]
YOU'RE ALMOST
OUTTA TIME, MR. GREEN.
OKAY, HAROLD, LET'S SAY THE
DAY COMES WHEN YOU'RE
GONNA GET MARRIED.
SO YOU WOULD SEND OUT
INVITATIONS...
"HAROLD GREEN REQUESTS THE
PLEASURE OF YOUR..."
DAUGHTER.
TO ACCOMPANY ME
UP THE AISLE.
THERE YOU GO.
GOOD BOY.
[applause]
[quirky upbeat music]
AND NOW WE COME TO THE EXPERTS
PORTION OF THE PROGRAMME,
WHERE WE ADDRESS THOSE
THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
[giggles]
OKAY, TODAY'S LETTER
READS AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"WE WENT ON A LONG TRIP
RECENTLY AND MY WIFE
WAS DRIVING,
"SO I GOT A CHANCE TO
LOOK OUT THE WINDOWS.
"I NOTICED THAT WHEN YOU HAVE
TWO COUPLES IN THE SAME CAR
"THERE IS A LOT
OF SEATING CHOICES.
"CAN YOU TELL ANYTHING
ABOUT THE COUPLES
"BASED ON WHERE
THEY SIT IN A CAR?"
WELL, YOU GOTTA LOOK AT THE
LEVEL OF CONVERSATION
THAT'S GOING ON.
LIKE, UH, IF THE MEN
ARE DOING THE TALKING,
THEY'RE DATING.
IF THE WOMEN ARE
DOING THE TALKING,
THEY'RE MARRIED.
RIGHT.
AND WHAT IF NOBODY'S
DOING ANY TALKING?
THEY'RE MARRIED.
WELL, WHAT IF
EVERYBODY'S YELLING?
MARRIED.
THEY'RE MARRIED.
NOW, IF YOU'VE GOT THE
TWO GUYS IN THE
FRONT SEAT
AND THE WOMEN IN
THE BACK SEAT,
THEY ARE DEFINITELY
MARRIED.
AND IF YOU'VE GOT THE
TWO WOMEN IN THE FRONT SEAT
AND TWO GUYS IN
THE BACK SEAT,
THEY'VE BEEN
MARRIED A WHILE.
WELL, WHAT IF EVERYBODY'S
IN THE BACK SEAT?
DATING.
[applause]
YOU KNOW, WHEN HAROLD HAD
HIS FIRST BUSINESS TRIP
LAST YEAR,
THE GUYS AT THE LODGE WERE SO
HAPPY HE WAS GOING AWAY,
THEY ALL CHIPPED IN AND GOT
HIM ONE OF THESE LAPTOP
COMPUTERS.
THE PROBLEM IS THE
NAME LAPTOP SCARES ME
BECAUSE HAROLD'S LAP IS NO
PLACE FOR ANYTHING VALUABLE.
WHICH GOT ME THINKING...
IF THEY CAN MAKE
A PORTABLE COMPUTER,
WHY CAN'T SOME GOOFBALL
MAKE A PORTABLE DESK.
WELL, GUESS WHAT...
SOME GOOFBALL HAS.
NOW, THIS MAY LOOK LIKE A
REGULAR GARMENT BAG,
BUT IT'S ACTUALLY A BUSINESS
TRAVELLER'S DREAM.
IF YOU DO A LOT
OF BUSINESS TRAVEL,
IT MIGHT BE A
RECURRING DREAM --
OR A RECURRING NIGHTMARE,
DEPENDING ON
WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
NOW, INSIDE, ON TOP,
WE HAVE OUR NEATLY
FOLDED SUITS.
AND UNDERNEATH WE HAVE OUR
NEATLY FOLDED DESK.
TV TRAYS: THEY'RE NOT JUST FOR
PATHETIC BACHELORS ANY MORE.
AND OF COURSE, YOU'VE GOTTA
HAVE A FLASHLIGHT
AND A CLOTHES HANGER.
THOSE ARE ESSENTIALS
FOR ANY EXECUTIVE.
WHO WANTS A DESK
WITHOUT A DESK LAMP?
NOW, THE REST IS UP
TO YOUR IMAGINATION.
THE GARMENT BAG ITSELF
BECOMES MY MODESTY PANEL.
AND I'VE ADDED A PANT HANGER
WITH THE METAL CLIPS
TO MY DESK LAMP.
OF COURSE, YOU'RE NOT GONNA
HANG YOUR PANTS ON THERE,
UNLESS YOU WORK
FOR THE GOVERNMENT.
INSTEAD, YOU'RE GONNA HANG
THE BEST PART OF YOUR PANTS,
YOUR WALLET,
OR AS IT'S ALSO KNOWN...
YOUR ROLODEX.
AND OF COURSE,
YOU CAN'T TRAVEL WITHOUT
TRAVELLING MUSIC.
TRANSISTOR RADIO OUGHTA
TAKE CARE OF THAT, HUH?
[signal not tunning in]
[country music plays]
OKAY, NOW ALL WE NEED IS ONE
OF THOSE FANCY NAME PLATES,
TO ADD THAT FINAL
TOUCH OF SOPHISTICATION
AND THERE'S OUR
PORTABLE DESK.
IT'S QUICK,
IT'S SIMPLE,
AND IT'S READY
TO HIT THE ROAD.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD --
[quirky upbeat music]
I WANNA TALK TO YOU
OLDER GUYS OUT THERE
ABOUT THE DANGERS OF
SHOPPING FOR YOUR WIFE.
MOST IMPORTANTLY, I'M TALKING
ABOUT HER REACTION
TO THAT GIFT
YOU JUST BOUGHT HER.
NOW, I KNOW SOME OF YOU HAVE
BEEN BUYING HER GIFTS
FOR 25 OR 30 YEARS,
AND YOU THINK YOU'RE
GETTING PRETTY GOOD AT IT.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT.
THE TRUTH IS THAT MEN
RUN OUT OF GOOD GIFT IDEAS
AFTER ABOUT THE
FIFTH YEAR OF MARRIAGE.
THAT'S WHEN THE PHRASE,
"OH, I LOVE IT HONEY.
"IT'S JUST WHAT I WANTED."
IS REPLACED WITH,
"DID YOU KEEP THE RECEIPT?"
I KNOW WE'VE
ALL BEEN THERE.
THAT TIME YOU BOUGHT HER THE
PICTURE OF THE DOGS
PLAYING POKER.
OR THE YEAR YOU
ENROLLED HER
IN THE BARBEQUE SAUCE
OF THE MONTH CLUB.
REMEMBER WHEN
YOU GOT HER
THAT HILARIOUS FISH THAT SINGS
WHEN YOU CLAP YOUR HANDS?
[chuckling]
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT
THE GOOD NEWS IS, EH?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GET
TOO UPSET ABOUT IT,
BECAUSE ALL YOU GOTTA REMEMBER
IS ONE IMPORTANT THING
WHEN YOU'RE SHOPPING
FOR YOUR WIFE...
MEN ARE FROM MARS;
WOMEN HAVE TASTE.
SO THE NEXT TIME YOU'RE
SHOPPING FOR A GIFT
FOR YOUR WIFE,
LOOK AROUND THE SHOP.
IF YOU SEE SOMETHING KINDA
SPECIAL, SOMETHING UNIQUE,
SOMETHING YOU WOULD HONESTLY
LIKE TO HAVE YOURSELF,
GET THE HECK OUTTA THERE,
BECAUSE, BUDDY, YOU'RE
IN THE WRONG STORE!
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, BUSTER HADFIELD
WROTE UP THE SCRIPT
FOR OUR DINNER
THEATRE PLAY.
REHEARSALS START TODAY.
I'M NOT ACTUALLY IN IT
BECAUSE I'M ALLERGIC
TO VEGETABLES,
ESPECIALLY WHEN PEOPLE ARE
WINGING 'EM AT ME.
UNCLE RED!
[wolf whistles and applause]
[louder wolf whistles]
IT'S NOT A
BALLET, YOU KNOW?
THIS IS AN ACTING
TECHNIQUE.
WE HAVE TO DIVEST OURSELVES
OF OUR OWN PERSONAS
SO WE CAN TAKE ON
A NEW CHARACTER.
AND IN YOUR CASE,
IT'S PROBABLY A GOOD IDEA.
THERE'S A TYPO
IN THE SCRIPT, RED.
BUSTER CALLED IT
"THE MOOSE TRAP",
INSTEAD OF
"THE MOUSETRAP".
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S NOT A TYPO.
IT'S "THE MOOSE TRAP".
OKAY, IT'S LOOSELY BASED
ON "THE MOUSETRAP".
IT'S IDENTICAL!
SAME PLOT,
SAME CHARACTERS.
NO, NO, SEE?
OURS IS CALLED
"THE MOOSE TRAP".
THAT WAY WE DON'T HAVE
TO PAY ANY ROYALTIES.
"THE MOUSE TRAP" HAS BEEN
RUNNING FOR 50 YEARS.
WE'RE NOT GONNA
FOOL ANYBODY.
DON'T BE SO SURE, HAROLD.
THE MAYOR OF POSSUM LAKE HAS
BEEN RUNNING FOR 60 YEARS,
AND HE STILL
FOOLS EVERYBODY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE NEED YOU TO REHEARSE THIS.
ANN MARIE IS GONNA
BE IN THE AUDIENCE,
AND I GET ENOUGH
BAD REVIEWS AT HOME.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
LET'S DO, UH,
ACT THREE, SCENE FOUR,
"THE BLOODY
AFTERMATH".
NOW, UNCLE RED,
AS AN ACTOR,
I'M NOT SURE OF MY
MOTIVATION IN THE SCENE.
I WAS HOPING MAYBE YOU
COULD HELP ME WITH THAT.
YES. YES,
I CAN, HAROLD.
SO YOUR MOTIVATION
IS TO DO WHAT IT SAYS
IN THE SCRIPT.
OR WE GET SOMEBODY
ELSE TO PLAY THE PART.
OKAY, SEE,
I NEEDED THAT.
YES. YES,
I DID TOO.
ALL RIGHT, DALTON, GO AHEAD.
YOU'VE GOT THE FIRST LINE.
IT'S JUST THAT I'M
NERVOUS, YOU KNOW.
AND I DON'T WANT WANNA BE
THE WORST ONE UP THERE.
YOU'VE GOT SOME
NERVE, LITTLE MAN,
BUT MAYBE IF WE...
WORK TOGETHER...
WE COULD FIND A COPY
OF THE OLD LADY'S...
WILL!
LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE SAFE.
I THINK SO!
Red: I WAS KILLING TIME
OUT BEHIND THE LODGE
WAITING FOR WALTER.
HAD SOME DRUM STICKS.
YOU KNOW, YOU GET
DRUMMING AWAY THERE,
AND YOU GOTTA GET
A BEAT GOING.
WALTER HAD KIND OF
A CHINESE THING GOING,
WHICH IS PERFECT
I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
IT AT FIRST,
BUT APPARENTLY HE'D GOTTEN
HIMSELF SOME NEW LITTLE TOY
THAT HE WANTED TRY,
HE WANTED ME TO BE
THE GUINEA PIG ON.
THEY USE THESE THINGS NOW IN
SOME OF THE BIG CITIES.
NOT JUST IN CHINA,
BUT EVERYWHERE.
I THINK IT'S CALLED
A RICKSHAW.
BOY, THEY PACK UP PRETTY
SMALL FOR THE SIZE OF IT.
SO WALTER WANTED ME
TO GET IN THERE,
SO, ALL RIGHT,
I'LL GIVE THAT A CHANCE.
GONNA FEEL LIKE THE
SHAW (Shah) OF SOMEWHERE.
I'M SITTING THERE,
AND HE TAKES HER --
DON'T EXACTLY UNDERSTAND
THE PHYSICS OF THIS,
AND I'M QUESTIONING IT --
OH! OH!
THAT HAS GOTTA HURT.
SO APPARENTLY I WASN'T
SITTING FAR ENOUGH BACK.
YOU'VE GOT TO PUT
THE WEIGHT BACK,
LIKE IT IS ON MY AUNT.
AND THERE, LOOK AT --
THE WAY HE RUNS
SCARES ME.
BUT AS WE STARTED
GOING UP A HILL,
AGAIN, I GUESS MY WEIGHT
WAS TOO FAR FORWARD,
AND HE STARTED TO DIG
IN A LITTLE BIT,
SO HE ASKED ME IF
I WOULD MOVE BACK.
AND YOU KNOW, I PROBABLY
OVER CORRECTED.
AND I KNEW THIS
CAN'T BE GOOD.
OH! OH!
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S ENOUGH FUN
FOR ME FOR ONE DAY.
WHY DON'T YOU GET
IN THERE, WALTER,
AND I'LL TRY?
YES, I'LL TRY.
BUT I'M NOT ACTUALLY
GONNA PULL IT MANUALLY.
SEEMS LIKE A BETTER
IDEA TO ME.
NOW, MY PLAN WAS TO TAKE
HIM UP ONTO THE FOUR-LANE,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY, I HAD
TO GO UP A HILL FIRST,
AND SOME OF THE HILLS AROUND
POSSUM LODGE
ARE NOT ALL THAT SMOOTH,
AND I HIT A POTHOLE.
I PROBABLY SHOULD HAVE
HAD SOME KIND OF A HITCH
BECAUSE, UH --
SOME --
WE DECIDED WE SHOULD JUST
PUT THE RICKSHAW AWAY
FOR THE DAY.
AND I CAME IN THERE,
HOPING WALTER WAS OKAY.
AND IT WAS LIKE
GOING TO THE VET,
LIKE THOSE DOGS WEAR.
THAT WAS JUST HIS HAT.
I TOOK THAT OFF,
AND THAT DAMAGED HIS EARS.
THEN I COULD YELL AT HIM.
IT WAS A GREAT HAT.
IT WAS A GREAT DAY.
AND WE'LL PROBABLY
NEVER DO IT AGAIN.
[quirky upbeat music]
OH, HI, EVERYBODY.
RANGER GORD HERE,
WITH ANOTHER ONE OF MY
ANIMATED EDUCATIONAL SHORTS.
NOW, THIS PARTICULAR ONE
IS ALL ABOUT POLLUTION.
AND MORE SPECIFICALLY,
I'M AGAINST IT.
YOU KNOW, WHEN I'M
IN THE GREAT OUTDOORS,
I ALWAYS HARKEN BACK
TO THAT OLD ADAGE...
TAKE NOTHING BUT PHOTOS,
LEAVE NOTHING BUT FOOTPRINTS.
UNLESS, OF COURSE, YOU'RE
DOING SOMETHING WEIRD,
IN WHICH CASE, THOSE THINGS
WILL BE USED AGAINST YOU
AS EVIDENCE LATER ON.
[chuckles]
SERIOUSLY.
ANYWAY, ENJOY THE FILM.
[quirky upbeat music]
HI, FOLKS.
TODAY I'M GONNA TEACH
THE WHOLE WORLD
TO CLEAN UP ITS ACT.
BUT FIRST,
WE NEED A MASCOT.
WHY, HERE'S A
CUTE LITTLE FELLOW.
CAN YOU SAY,
GIVE A HOOT, DON'T POLLUTE?
CAN YOU SAY
TRADEMARK INFRINGEMENT?
UH, RIGHT THEN.
LET'S BEGIN OUR LESSON
WITH NOISE POLLUTION.
[rock music blasting]
NOW, OBVIOUSLY, WE CAN'T
HAVE THIS KIND OF NOISE
IN THE FOREST.
IT'S IMPOLITE,
IRRESPONSIBLE
AND INCREDIBLY DANGEROUS.
SO IS THE MUSIC!
AND HERE COMES
THE HIBERNATING BEAR
WE JUST WOKE UP
TO FINISH THE JOB.
OHH-AWW!
WHAT DO WE DO, GORD?
I KNOW.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE THIS
MOTORCYCLE TO SAFETY?
GOOD IDEA.
HEY, SWEET RIDE.
YEAH, SWEET NITROUS OXIDE
RIDE, YOU MEAN.
GREENHOUSE GASES ARE A
CONSTANT THREAT TO US ALL.
BUT FORTUNATELY, YOU CAN'T
DO TOO MUCH DAMAGE...
WITH A POTATO IN
YOUR TAILPIPE.
I'M GONNA PUT A POTATO
IN YOUR TAILPIPE, GORD.
WELL, THERE'LL BE PLENTY
OF TIME FOR RECREATION
LATER, RED.
NOW, LET'S FLY THIS CHOPPER!
Red: I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE
MAKING US PICK UP LITTER
IN THE DARK.
Gord: THE POLLUTION SOLUTION
IS A 24/7 JOB, RED.
NOW YOU KNOW WHAT
I GO THROUGH EVERY DAY.
Harold: WOW! IT'S AMAZING
HOW MUCH GARBAGE
PEOPLE LEAVE AROUND
A CAMPSITE.
Gord: ACTUALLY, IT'S NOT A
CAMPSITE AT ALL, HAROLD.
YOU'VE BEEN CLEANING MY
PLACE FOR THE PAST HOUR.
[laughing]
AH! THIS ISN'T
YOUR APARTMENT, GORD.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHO'S PLACE IS THIS?
[screaming]
WELL, FOLKS, WE'VE HAD
A LOT OF FUN TONIGHT.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
FUNNY ABOUT POLLUTION.
YOU SAID IT, PAUL
THE POLLUTION BEAR.
WHEW!
SO HE WAS YOUR
MASCOT ALL ALONG.
I THOUGHT HE WAS
GOING TO ATTACK US.
OH, PAUL'S STILL
GOING TO ATTACK YOU.
GIVING ENVIRONMENTAL
TIPS IS HIS JOB.
EATING YOU IS JUST --
WELL, IT'S JUST A PERK.
AH! WAIT A SECOND, PAUL.
YOU DON'T WANNA EAT ME.
I'M, UH, POLLUTED.
OH, UH,
IT'S TRUE!
[laughing]
[applause]
[loud booing]
WELL, THE DINNER THEATRE
THING SEEMS TO BE GOING
PRETTY WELL.
WE DECIDED TO SERVE
HAMBURGERS.
WE ALREADY HAD LOTS
OF HOT DOGS ON STAGE.
[lood booing]
GEEZ!
OKAY! OKAY!
IS THE PLAY OVER?
WELL,
FOR US IT IS.
THAT IS THE WORST
AUDIENCE I HAVE EVER SEEN.
THEY DO NOT KNOW HOW TO
APPRECIATE GOOD TALENT.
WE DON'T KNOW THAT, HAROLD.
THEY WERE THROWING
FRENCH FRIES AT US.
IT WAS HUMILIATING.
WELL, LOOK AT THE
BRIGHT SIDE.
AT LEAST WE DIDN'T
GIVE THEM CUTLERY.
[loud pounding]
WE CAN'T GO BACK OUT
THERE, UNCLE RED.
WELL, HOW FAR INTO
THE PLAY WERE YOU?
WE WERE AT THE
MURDER SCENE.
WINSTON WAS DYING.
WE ALL WERE.
[loud booing]
WELL, THAT'S ENOUGH
OF THAT!
THAT AUDIENCE HAS NO
RESPECT FOR THE DEAD.
RIGHT NOW THEY ENVY
THE DEAD, WINSTON.
IT WAS AWFUL.
I'M LAYING THERE
ON THE STAGE,
AND THEY PELT ME WITH
MUSTARD AND HOT PEPPERS
AND TOBASCO SAUCE!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON?
YEAH,
I'M OKAY.
A LITTLE HEARTBURN,
BUT --
[possum squealing]
Harold:
MEETING TIME!
YEAH, YOU GUYS GO
AHEAD, ALL RIGHT?
I'LL BE DOWN
IN A MINUTE.
[whimpering]
LISTEN, THE BUTLER
DID IT, OKAY?
[applause]
I'LL BE DOWNSTAIRS.
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
UH, THE DINNER THEATRE
THING DIDN'T GO SO GOOD.
WASN'T REALLY BROADWAY,
NOT EVEN OFF-BROADWAY.
IT WAS JUST OFF,
WHICH, COINCIDENTALLY,
PART OF THE PHRASE
THE AUDIENCE WAS YELLING.
[tentative laughter,
then laughter]
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheers and applause]]
SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY GOTTA SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, EVERYBODY.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, THE
WHOLE DINNER THEATRE THING,
THAT'S ALL OVER WITH.
AND WE HAVE SOME
FOOD LEFT OVER.
WE'VE GOT 40 POUNDS
OF GROUND BEEF,
65 POUNDS OF FRENCH FRIES,
AND I'M NOT EXACTLY
SURE HOW MUCH HAM.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS WEIGH?