ONE OF THE DIFFERENCES
BETWEEN MEN AND WOMEN
IS THAT MEN FEEL THEY
HAVE TO DOMINATE THINGS.
IT'S NOT ENOUGH TO ENJOY
NATURE OR A JOB OR EVEN
A CONVERSATION.
MAN HAS TO DOMINATE.
I THINK THAT'S WHY
WE EAT SO MUCH MEAT.
I MEAN, THERE'S DOMINATION
FOR YOU, MAN AGAINST ANIMAL,
WHO'S GOING TO EAT WHO?
MOST MEN THINK VEGETARIAN
IS AN INDIAN WORD MEANING
LOUSY HUNTER.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT MAKES
US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
RED GREEN:
HERE ARE A FEW SCENES
FROM THIS WEEK'S SHOW:
HAROLD TELLS ME ALL
THE BIG SHOWS DO THIS,
SHOWS LIKE LAUGH-IN
OR CAROL BURNETT.
I KNOW MARLIN PERKINS
DOES THIS KIND OF THING.
I SHOULD ALSO MENTION
THAT WE GOT SPECIAL
GUESTS HERE,
DAVE THOMAS AND
GRAHAM GREENE.
BILL'S GOING TO JUMP UP
AND DOWN UNTIL HE
HURTS HIMSELF.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND NOW HERE IS THE
MAN WHOSE CAREER HAS
DONE FOR PLAID
WHAT MUSIC VIDEOS
DID FOR LINGERIE,
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
AND HERE IS THE MAN
WHO HAS DONE FOR
MY TV CAREER
WHAT PIGS HAVE DONE
FOR AIRPLANES,
MY NEPHEW, HAROLD.
GOT SOME BAD NEWS UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK,
GROUCHY RADCLIFF
HAS PASSED AWAY.
OH, NO.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
GROUCHY'S GONE?
YES.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
OH, WE SHOULD DO SOMETHING.
WE SHOULD SEND
FLOWERS OR SOMETHING.
NO, A CARD, A CARD.
WE'LL SEND A CARD.
A SYMPATHY CARD, YEAH.
OH, I SAW A LOVELY
ONE THE OTHER DAY.
IT HAD A SQUISHED
WORM ON THE PAVEMENT,
YOU KNOW, AND WHEN YOU
OPEN IT UP THE MESSAGE
INSIDE IT SAID
"SORRY TO HEAR THAT
YOU HIT THE ROAD."
WE COULD SEND THAT.
WE SHOULD DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
IF WE DID SOMETHING LIKE
THAT, WE SHOULD DO THAT,
THAT WOULD BE --
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
TWO MINUTE SILENCE
ABOUT A HUNDRED TIMES.
IT'S NOT THAT HIS
PASSING WAS THAT
UNEXPECTED.
GROUCHY HAS GOT TO BE
THE OLDEST FARMER IN
THE WHOLE AREA.
HE WAS LIKED.
HE WAS A VERY
COLOURFUL CHARACTER.
ESPECIALLY HIS LANGUAGE.
YOU KNOW, I THINK HE
WAS A LOT FRIENDLIER
THAN HE SEEMED
BECAUSE HE WOULD
STAND THERE ON
HIS FENCE,
YELLING OUT OBSCENITIES,
THROWING BRICKS AT PEOPLE.
WELL, HE COULD
BE GROUCHY.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S HOW
HE GOT HIS NAME, GROUCHY.
HE WAS...
HE WAS DIFFICULT.
CRANKY.
HARD TO GET
ALONG WITH.
OBNOXIOUS.
HE WAS INSANE.
I HATED HIM.
EVERYONE DID,
HAROLD.
AND THE STRANGE
THING IS...
THAT WHEN GROUCHY DIED,
HE WAS VERY, VERY RICH,
AND THERE'S NOW NO
FRIENDS AND NO RELATIVES
TO GET THE INHERITANCE.
I DIDN'T REALLY
HATE HIM, YOU KNOW.
I THINK ADMIRE IS
A BETTER WORD.
FORGET IT, HAROLD.
THE ONLY GUY WHO
HAS A CHANCE IS
JUNIOR SINGLETON.
HE WENT UP THERE EVERY
DAY, MADE FRIENDS
WITH GROUCHY,
DID ALL THE CHORES
AND EVERYTHING.
I THINK HE'S LOOKING
PRETTY SMART NOW
HE'S GOING TO INHERIT
THE WHOLE DARN THING.
HE'S GREAT.
YOU ARE
PATHETIC, HAROLD.
WHEN I GO YOU'RE NOT
GETTING WHAT I GOT.
WELL, WHEN YOU
GO I WILL HAVE
EVERYTHING I WANT.
HI, YOU'RE WATCHING
THE RED GREEN SHOW.
[ SOBBING ]
YOU'RE LUCKY.
OH, THERE'S HOLES
IN MY PANTS
AND THE WATER'S
DRIPPING IN,
IT'S FALLING ON MY HAT
AND DRIPPING ON MY CHIN.
ALWAYS REMEMBER CAMPING
LESSON NUMBER ONE...
IF YOU GOT BUGS
IN YOUR TENT,
DON'T SHOOT THEM
WITH A GUN.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE SITTING AT
THE KITCHEN TABLE,
STIRRING YOUR COFFEE,
MINDING YOUR OWN BUSINESS,
SUDDENLY YOU LOOK UP,
SHE'S STARING RIGHT AT YOU.
YEAH.
YOU REALIZE YOUR WIFE
HAS BEEN TALKING TO YOU
AND YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN PAYING ATTENTION.
AND HERE'S THE CAPPER,
SHE JUST SAID, WELL,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, SHE'S GOT
YOU CORNERED.
YOU CAN'T SAY YOU
WEREN'T LISTENING
AND YOU CAN'T SAY
SOMETHING LIKE, OH,
GEEZ, I DON'T KNOW DEAR,
WHY DON'T YOU DECIDE.
I MEAN, THAT'S
A LAME EXCUSE,
SHE'D KNOW YOU WEREN'T
LISTENING, RIGHT?
AND SHE'S GOING
TO GET MAD.
OH, YEAH.
THE BEST THING TO DO
IN A SITUATION
LIKE THIS,
DON'T LOOK AT HER.
NO.
WHEN SHE SEES THAT
BLANK LOOK IN YOUR EYES,
SEES YOU'RE BREATHING
THROUGH YOUR MOUTH,
YOU'RE A DEAD DUCK.
THE BEST DEFENCE
IS A GOOD OFFENCE.
CHANGE THE SUBJECT
RIGHT THEN AND THERE.
WANT TO KNOW A
GREAT SUBJECT, HER.
TELL HER HOW
GREAT SHE LOOKS.
SAY HOW LONG HAS
IT BEEN SINCE
I TOLD YOU
HOW MUCH I APPRECIATE
EVERY LITTLE THING
YOU DO.
OR JUST SAY WHEN
WAS THE LAST TIME
WE WERE OUT TOGETHER
ON A NICE EVENING?
OH, OH, OH, BE
CAREFUL WITH THAT ONE,
THAT SHOULD ONLY BE
USED BY A PROFESSIONAL.
YEAH.
THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING IS WHILE YOU'VE
GOT HER DISTRACTED
IS TO GET OUT OF THE
ROOM FAST BEFORE
SHE REMEMBERS
WHAT SHE WAS
TALKING ABOUT.
HOPEFULLY SHE WASN'T
PAYING ATTENTION.
YEAH, LIKE YOU.
I THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO NOTICE A LITTLE
MORE SENSITIVITY
IN THIS WEEK'S
HANDYMAN CORNER,
CAUSE WITH GROUCHY
RADCLIFF PASSING AWAY
AND NOT HAVING ANY RELATIVES
TO CELEBRATE OR ANYTHING,
A BUNCH OF US HAVE KICKED
IN VARIOUS CAR PARTS
AND ASSORTED
FLOTSAM AND JETSOM.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE
GROUCHY SOME KIND
OF A HEADSTONE
OR A MAUSOLEUM
OR SOMETHING
SO THAT EVERY TIME
WE GO BY THE CEMETERY,
WE'LL BE REINFORCED WITH THE
COMFORTING THOUGHT THAT HE
REALLY IS DEAD.
NOW, EVERYTHING MEANS
SOMETHING, YOU KNOW,
WITH THIS TYPE OF THING.
FOR EXAMPLE, THESE
CAR AXLE STANDS,
WHAT THEY WILL SAY TO US
IS THAT EVERY ONCE
IN A WHILE
IT'S A GOOD IDEA
FOR A MAN TO SPEND A
WINTER UP ON BLOCKS.
RADIATOR, THAT MEANS
IT'S OKAY TO BLOW OFF
A LITTLE STEAM.
WHEEL DISKS, WELL
THEY'RE MAINLY DECORATIVE.
NOW WE'RE ABOUT TO CROSS
THE LINE BETWEEN BEING
AN ARTISAN
AND BEING A HANDYMAN,
BECAUSE I'LL TELL YOU,
THIS PROJECT REQUIRES
AS MUCH TASTE
AND ARTISTIC ABILITY AS
IT DOES A BIG HAMMER
AND THE ATTITUDE TO
MAKE IT EFFECTIVE.
AND THE THING WITH ART IS
THERE'S NO RIGHT WAY
AND NO WRONG WAY.
[ EXPLOSION ]
ALL RIGHT, MAYBE THERE
STILL IS A WRONG WAY.
I DECIDED TO GO INSTEAD
WITH THE HANDYMAN SECRET
WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
AND DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THE DAMAGE TO THAT
ACETYLENE TORCH,
IT WAS A RENTAL.
SO NOW WHAT WE HAVE IS
NOT ONLY AN ATTRACTIVE
ART DECO HEADSTONE,
IT'S ALSO EXTREMELY
FUNCTIONAL.
FOR EXAMPLE, I'VE INSTALLED
THE TURN SIGNALS
TO HOOK THEM UP TO SOME
CHRISTMAS LIGHTS THERE
AND SO NOW THE DECEASED
CAN SIGNAL HIS TURN,
RIGHT OR LEFT,
UP OR DOWN, YOU KNOW.
BUT WITH GROUCHY I
THINK WHAT I'LL DO
IS PUT THE FOUR-WAY
FLASHERS ON TO KEEP
HIS OPTIONS OPEN.
ACTUALLY WHERE HE'S GOING
HE'S GOING TO WISH I PUT
IN AIR CONDITIONING.
MAYBE THE LUCKY DICE WILL
MAKE ALL THE DIFFERENCE.
YOU KNOW WHEN SOMEBODY
FAMOUS DIES
LIKE A PRESIDENT OR
ELVIS OR SOMETHING,
THEY ALWAYS HAVE
THE ETERNAL FLAME,
SO WHAT I'VE DONE IS I'VE
TAKEN THE GAS TANK OUT
OF GROUCHY'S CAR
AND WE'LL JUST
FIRE THAT UP.
BOY THAT SMELLS BAD.
THERE WE GO.
THERE'S YOUR FLAME.
THE ETERNAL PART WILL
DEPEND ON HIS GAS MILEAGE.
AND ALSO I PUT AN
ASHTRAY IN HERE
JUST IN CASE GROUCHY
GETS HIMSELF CREMATED.
AND I'VE HOOKED UP THE
WINDSHIELD WASHER,
DOWN THROUGH THIS
GAS NOZZLE,
THEY GO INTO HERE AND
SO ON AND GO DOWN AND
WATER THAT PLANT,
BECAUSE I FIGURE GROUCHY
PROBABLY IS NOT GOING
TO GET A LOT OF FLOWERS
WITH HIS PERSONALITY.
LET'S SEE HOW THAT WORKS.
THERE WE GO.
BOY, THAT BRINGS ON A LOT
OF FEELINGS FOR ME,
HOW ABOUT YOU?
ANYWAY, THERE'S THE KIND
OF THING THAT YOU CAN DO
THE NEXT TIME SOME DISTANT,
FAR AWAY DISTANT RELATIVE
OF YOURS PASSES AWAY.
UNTIL THEN REMEMBER,
IF WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
HONK IF YOU LOVE
INHERITANCES.
[ CAR HORN HONKS ]
SPEAKING OF HONKING,
STAY TUNED FOR DAVE THOMAS,
AND WE'LL CHECK OUT AND
SEE HOW BILL'S DOING
IN THE SMOKE HOUSE.
I WANT TO TALK TO ALL
YOU MIDDLE-AGE GUYS
AND I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
I'M ONE OF YOU.
AND EVERY WEEK MORE AND
MORE OF US ARE COMING
OUT OF THE TOOL ROOM
AND ADMITTING IT.
ADMITTING THAT WE HAVE
NOTHING TO SAY TO ANYONE
ABOUT ANYTHING.
I KNOW THAT FEELING,
YOUR WIFE PROBABLY
UNDERSTANDS.
YOU'VE SAID IT ALL TO
HER BEFORE, YOU'RE
STILL WITH HER,
YOU HAVE NOTHING
TO ADD.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
UNFORTUNATELY THERE ARE
SOME GUYS WHO HAVE NOTHING
TO SAY BUT KEEP TALKING.
IF YOU FIND YOURSELF
RANTING ABOUT HOW PEOPLE
ARE PARKING THEIR CARS
ON YOUR STREET,
YOU HAVE NOTHING TO
SAY, STOP TALKING.
IF YOU FIND YOURSELF
GOING ON AND ON ABOUT
HOW JEOPARDY IS WAY BETTER
THAN WHEEL OF FORTUNE
OR HOW HARD THESE NEW
ORANGE JUICE CANS
ARE TO OPEN
OR THE HIGH PRICE OF
HAMMERS, YOU HAVE
NOTHING TO SAY.
IF YOU FIND YOURSELF
TELLING A HILARIOUS STORY
THAT YOU READ IN
READER'S DIGEST,
STOP TALKING.
NO ONE IS
LISTENING TO YOU.
THE PERSON YOU'RE TALKING
TO HAS GLAZED OVER
AND IS NODDING THEIR
HEAD WHILE THEY MAKE
UP A GROCERY LIST
OR PLAN THEIR
WINTER VACATION
OR VOW NEVER TO GET AS
OLD AND BORING AS YOU ARE.
SO DON'T JUST KEEP
TALKING UNTIL YOU THINK
OF SOMETHING, YOU MAY NOT.
REMEMBER, I'M
PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
HI, WINSTON ROTHCHILD
HERE FOR ROTHCHILD SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES
REMINDING YOU, DON'T
GET HOSED SOMEWHERE ELSE.
CALL 1-800-555-SUCK.
WELL, WE HAD THE READING
OF GROUCHY RADCLIFF'S WILL.
JUNIOR SINGLETON WAS
REAL EXCITED BECAUSE
THE LAWYER HAD CALLED HIM
AND TOLD HIM SPECIFICALLY
TO GET DOWN THERE.
I'LL TELL YOU, JUNIOR HAD
DOLLAR SIGNS DANCING
IN HIS HEAD.
SOMETHING TELLS ME THOSE
DOLLARS DIDN'T DANCE
INTO HIS WALLET.
WELL, BEING OF SOUND
MIND AND BODY,
GROUCHY BEQUEATHED HIS FARM
AND ALL HIS PROPERTIES
AND ALL HIS INVESTMENTS
AND HIS DOMESTIC AND
INTERNATIONAL BANK
ACCOUNTS
TO THE HARMONIOUS CHURCH
OF MARS UNDER AUSPICES OF
THE RIGHT REVEREND LARRY.
OH MAN.
HE DID REMEMBER US,
THOUGH, HAROLD.
GROUCHY LEFT HIS ENTIRE
MANURE PILE TO
POSSUM LODGE.
SO WE DON'T COME OUT
OF IT EMPTY-HANDED.
WE ARE THE HEIRS
OF MANURE.
HAVE YOU EVER SMELLED
THE AIR OF MANURE?
SO DID JUNIOR INHERIT
ANYTHING FOR ALL
HIS EFFORTS?
YES, SIR.
GROUCHY LEFT HIM
HIS PRIZE STEER,
WANDA THE
WONDER COW.
AND I THINK JUNIOR
WAS PLEASED.
HE HAD A ACCEPTANCE SPEECH,
WHICH HE YELLED FOR
SOME REASON.
AND DURING THAT HE VOWED
TO MAKE THAT COW A
TRIBUTE TO GROUCHY
BY HAVING IT BUTCHERED
AND EATEN BEFORE THE SUN
SET ON RADCLIFF'S GRAVE.
LET'S MEET
OUR CONTESTANTS.
OUR CONTESTANTS STARTING
ON THE FAR END IS
MY UNCLE RED
AND OF COURSE DOUGIE FRANKLIN
AND HIS BROTHER BEN FRANKLIN.
9WELCOME TO THE SHOW
ONE AND ALL.
TODAY'S CATEGORIES ARE:
ATOMIC PHYSICS,
THE LIFE OF MONET THE
IMPRESSIONIST ARTIST,
DIFFERENTIAL EQUATIONS,
POST FEMINIST POETRY,
I PICKED THAT ONE,
PALINDROMES OR CARS.
WELL, THAT POST FEMINIST
POETRY SOUNDS TEMPTING,
BUT I THINK I'LL GO
WITH THE CARS, HAROLD.
ALRIGHTY, THEN.
OKAY AND REMEMBER PLEASE
TO PHRASE YOUR ANSWER
IN THE FORM
OF AN ANSWER.
ALL RIGHT.
QUESTION ONE:
WHAT DRIVER SAFETY DEVICE
WAS MADE MANDATORY
IN ALL PASSENGER
VEHICLES IN 1962?
[ LAUGHTER ]
ANYONE AT ALL.
OH, BEN.
YES, BEN,
WHAT MANDATORY
DRIVER SAFETY DEVICE
WAS MADE MANDATORY
BECAUSE IT WAS
MANDATORY --
THEY INSISTED
UPON IT IN 1962?
HE OPENED A NEW ROAD
TO LANDSCAPE PAINTING
BY APPLYING SCIENTIFIC
PRINCIPLES DEDUCED FROM
THE LAWS OF LIGHT.
NO.
CAN YOU REPEAT THE
QUESTION, HAROLD?
MAY I?
YES.
WHAT DRIVER SAFETY DEVICE
WAS MADE MANDATORY
IN ALL PASSENGER
VEHICLES IN 1962?
YES, DOUGIE?
I WOULD HAVE TO SAY
IT WOULD BE THE
FIRE RETARDANT,
ASBESTOS-LINED FIRE SUIT.
NO.
UNCLE RED?
THE REALLY BIG CAR.
NO!
THE SEAT BELT.
SEAT BELTS WERE MADE
MANDATORY IN 1962.
OKAY.
NEVER THOUGHT
OF THAT ONE.
TIME FOR ANOTHER VISIT
WITH OUR PAL, RANGER GORD.
HI RED.
HI HAROLD.
YEAH.
NICE TO SEE YOU UP
HERE AT THE FIRE TOWER.
ALWAYS NICE TO SEE
YOUNG PEOPLE UP AT
THE FIRE TOWER.
I'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR YOU.
WELL, WE CAN'T
STAY LONG, GORD,
JUST CAME FOR THAT BOOK
THAT YOU SAID YOU
WOULD LEND ME.
OH, RIGHT.
THERE YOU GO,
"FROM STEER TO STEAK
"THE DO IT YOURSELF
HOW TO SLAUGHTER BOOK."
GREAT.
THAT'S TERRIFIC.
DO YOU WANT A COFFEE?
I KNEW YOU WERE COMING,
I MADE A POT.
IT WILL ONLY TAKE ME ABOUT
15 MINUTES TO RUN UP TO
THE TOP TO GET YOU A CUP.
NO, NO, NO, NO, GORD.
NO, NO.
COME ON BACK.
COME ON.
I'M NOT GOING TO
INTERRUPT YOU FOR
THAT LONG.
I SEE THAT YOU'RE IN
THE MIDDLE OF RESEARCHING
SOMETHING IMPORTANT HERE.
OH, YEAH, I'M LOOKING
FOR A PET, RED.
OH, BOY.
YOU'RE GOING TO TRY
AGAIN ARE YOU GORD?
OH SURE, YEAH.
THERE MUST BE A PET
FOR ME OUT THERE
SOMEWHERE.
IT SEEMS LIKE EVERY
DOG YOU GET RUNS
AWAY ON YOU.
YEAH.
THE LAST ONE
STAYED TWO DAYS.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
THEN THE TRANQUILIZER
WORE OFF, HE WAS GONE.
BOY.
WHAT ABOUT CATS?
YOU EVER TRIED CATS?
YEAH, FOUR OF THEM.
YEAH, THE LAST ONE
I WAS SURE WOULDN'T
GO FAR, HE WAS BLIND.
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU NEED, GORD,
YOU NEED AN ANIMAL THAT
DOESN'T MOVE, LIKE MAYBE
CORAL OR MOSS
OR SOMETHING.
NO.
I NEED AN ANIMAL WITH
A SENSE OF DUTY.
ONE THAT WILL STAY WITH
ME UP IN THE FIRE TOWER
JUST LOOKING OUT OVER
THE FOREST FOR
YEARS ON END,
NEVER QUESTIONING WHY,
JUST KNOWING THAT IT'S
HIS ROLE IN LIFE.
BOY, ANIMALS THAT DUMB
ARE PRETTY MUCH EXTINCT.
YEAH.
THANKS, GORD.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS STILL ANYBODY'S GAME
BECAUSE NO ONE'S SAID
ANYTHING EVEN CLOSE
TO RIGHT YET.
ALRIGHTY.
IN SOME STATES
AND PROVINCES
IT IS STILL ILLEGAL
TO DO WHAT AT A
RED LIGHT?
I'M ASSUMING BEN.
THE MOST POPULAR OF
THE SERIES ARE THE HEYREX,
THE POPLAR, THE CLIFFS
OF ETRETAT AND THE --
WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
WHAT DO YOU GOT THERE?
COME ON, LET ME SEE.
COME ON, COUGH IT UP.
COUGH IT UP.
MONET, MONET.
LOOK AT THAT, MONET.
WE'RE DOING
CARS, OKAY?
AND WHAT ARE THESE,
YOUR CHEAT SHEETS?
YOU KNOW, I HAVE NEVER
BEEN SO HUMILIATED IN
MY ENTIRE LIFE.
YOU'VE
HUMILIATED ME.
YOU'VE LET DOWN THE
ENTIRE FAMILY
HERE TONIGHT.
NOW, LOOK, LET'S
TRY THIS ONCE AGAIN.
HAROLD, ASK HIM
THE QUESTION AGAIN.
YOU PLAY THE GAME
BY THE RULES.
TRY'ER AGAIN.
OKAY, BEN, IN SOME
STATES AND PROVINCES
IT IS STILL ILLEGAL TO
DO WHAT AT A RED LIGHT?
[ BEEPING HORN ]
PEAL RUBBER.
NO.
SORRY BEN.
OH, YOU IDIOT.
YOU ARE AN IDIOT.
OKAY, WE NEED A
TIE BREAKER.
SO PICK A NUMBER
BETWEEN ONE AND TEN.
HAROLD:
DOUGIE?
SEVEN.
HAROLD:
BEN?
I'LL GO WITH
SEVEN TOO.
WE MAY BE A
WHILE, ALRIGHTY.
UNCLE RED, CAN YOU
PLEASE PICK A NUMBER?
YOUR SALARY, HAROLD.
WE GOT A WINNER.
THAT'S A WINNER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
UNCLE RED WINS AGAIN.
WELL, BILL IS IN FOR BIG
FUN TODAY ON ADVENTURES
WITH BILL
BECAUSE HE GOT HIMSELF ONE
OF THESE NEW FANCY
TRAMPOLINE THINGS.
A LOT OF THE CORPORATIONS
AND SO FORTH
ARE HAVING THE EXERCISE
ROOMS AND IT'S KIND OF
A STRESS THERAPY THING.
AND YOU GET ON --
YOU JUST GET ON THERE
LIKE THAT I GUESS.
I GUESS BILL HAS THE
PROFESSIONAL TECHNIQUE.
I JUST KIND OF --
YOU KNOW I'M JUST AN
AMATEUR AT THESE THINGS.
THAT'S A VERY INTERESTING
MOUNT YOU GOT THERE, BILL.
ANYWAY, UP HE COMES.
NOW, THE BEAUTY OF THIS
IS APPARENTLY THE MORE
YOU BOUNCE AND JUMP
THEN THE MORE STRESS
IS RELIEVED FROM YOU.
AND, OF COURSE, I DON'T
THINK YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO LEAVE YOUR SHOES
RIGHT ON THE
EDGE LIKE THAT.
THAT TO ME IS NOT RELIEVING
ALL THAT MUCH STRESS
AT THIS POINT
SO I'M SAYING I'VE HAD
ABOUT AS MUCH STRESS
TAKEN OUT OF ME
AS I REALLY CAN STAND
AND STILL BE ALIVE
SO I WILL JUST
LET BILL DO IT.
AND BILL SEEMS PRETTY
STRESSED TO ME,
SO I'M THINKING PROBABLY
THE BIGGER THE BOUNCE, THE
MORE STRESS RELEASE,
THAT ONLY MAKES
SENSE TO ME.
SO I'M HELPING HIM.
I'M PUTTING A LITTLE
EXTRA WEIGHT ON THERE
AND LOOK AT THE
FUN HE'S HAVING.
HE'S HAVING A
REAL GOOD TIME.
I'M THINKING IF WE CAN
GET HIM JUST ONE
GOOD JUMP,
EH BILL, JUST
ONE BIG ONE,
SOMETHING YOU CAN
TALK ABOUT FOR
YOUR WHOLE LIFE.
OH, THIS COULD BE IT.
MAYBE THAT WAS HIS
WHOLE LIFE.
OH, NO, HERE HE IS.
OH, HE'S GOT A WHEEL RIM
AND A WHEEL RIM, BILL,
IS SORT OF LIKE LIFE,
YOU KNOW THAT, WHAT
GOES AROUND COMES AROUND.
RED GREEN:
STAY TUNED.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS
WHAT WE GOT PLANNED
FOR THE COW
OR OUR SPECIAL GUEST,
GRAHAM GREENE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, AS SOON AS JUNIOR
GETS HERE WITH WANDA
THE WONDER COW,
WE WILL BE UP TO OUR
RUMP ROAST IN STEAK.
OH, NOW I FEEL
LIKE K.D. LANG.
HAROLD YOUR LOOK
ANYWAY, STINKY IS
BRINGING THE COW OVER
IN THE BACK SEAT OF
HIS '69 CADILLAC.
HE'S GOT TWICE AS MUCH
LEG ROOM THERE,
WHICH IS GOOD BECAUSE THE COW
HAS TWICE AS MUCH LEGS.
STINKY IS PUTTING
A FARM ANIMAL IN THE
BACK OF HIS CADILLAC?
WHAT ABOUT THE SMELL?
THE COW DIDN'T
SEEM TO MIND.
SO ALL THE GUYS ARE
BRINGING DIFFERENT
POWER TOOLS OVER
DEPENDING ON WHAT KIND
OF MEAT WE'RE CUTTING.
I'M USING THE BABY
FOR THE DELMONICOS,
WE GOT A SKILSAW
FOR THE RIBS
AND WE'RE USING A
ROUTER ON THE
FILET MIGNON.
OH, I DON'T EVEN WANT
TO HEAR ABOUT THE
HAMBURGER.
BUSTER IS BRING
A ROTATILLER.
I HEARD, OHH.
NOW I KNOW WHY PEOPLE
BECOME VEGETARIANS.
HAROLD, THE COW IS NOT
AN ANIMAL IN THE WILD,
IT'S LIKE A CROP.
IT'S LIKE THAT
APPLE, ALL RIGHT?
THIS IS HARVEST
TIME, THAT'S ALL.
THERE IS NO COMPARISON.
I DIDN'T HAVE TO
MURDER THIS APPLE
FIRST BEFORE I EAT IT.
NO, WITH THE STEAKS
WE'RE DOING THE
HUMANE THINGS
AND KILLING
THE COW FIRST.
YOU'RE EATING
THAT APPLE ALIVE.
THIS WEEK'S LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS:
DEAR EXPERTS, A LOT
OF MY ROOF SHINGLES ARE
CRACKING AND CURLING UP
AND I'M HAVING TROUBLE
KEEPING THE PAINT ON THE
INSIDE AND OUTSIDE WALLS,
NOT THAT MY WIFE
LIKED THE COLOUR ANYWAY.
CAN YOU TELL
ME WHAT TO DO?
WELL, SOUNDS LIKE YOU'VE
GOT WATER LEAKING IN
THROUGH THE SHINGLES
IN YOUR ROOF.
I'LL SAY SO.
YOU KNOW, IF THIS GUY
IS FROM ALBERTA,
LIKE IT SOUNDED,
HE PROBABLY HEATS
HIS HOUSE WITH OIL.
SO WHAT I RECOMMEND
IS THAT YOU TAKE A
PIECE OF ROPE
AND YOU PUT ONE END
OF THE ROPE IN
THE OIL TANK
AND YOU THREAD THE
OTHER END OF THE
ROPE OUT
THROUGH THE BASEMENT WINDOW.
WHAT'S THE ROPE FOR?
THAT'S YOUR WICK.
YOU SEE, THEM 250-GALLON
TANKS OF OIL
ARE THE CHEAPEST DYNAMITE
YOU'RE GOING TO FIND.
KABOOM!
YOU'RE GOING TO BLOW
THE GUY'S HOUSE UP JUST
BECAUSE HIS ROOF LEAKS?
OH, IT'S GOT TO
BE DONE, HAROLD.
IT'S GOT TO BE DONE.
ONCE YOU GET WATER
IN THE WALLS, YOU GET
MOLD, YOU GET FUNGUS.
IF SOMEBODY WITH A
WOODEN LEG COMES
OVER TO VISIT
AND CATCHES UP A
CASE OF DRY ROT,
YOU'RE LOOKING
AT A LAWSUIT.
YEAH, HAROLD, AND HE
ALREADY SAID HIS WIFE
DOESN'T LIKE THE
COLOUR OF THE HOUSE.
ONCE YOU'RE INTO
THAT STUFF, IT'S EASIER
JUST TO FLATTEN THE PLACE.
YEAH, IT'S LIKE
I ALWAYS SAID,
IT'S CHEAPER TO BUILD
A NEW HOME THAN IT IS
TO FIX THE OLD PLACE.
AND THAT'S THE GREAT
THING ABOUT THE
CRAPPY WAY
THEY BUILD HOUSES
THESE DAYS,
JUST LIGHT THE
WICK AND KABOOM!
A LOT OF OUR VIEWERS
WOULD LIKE TO KNOW
HOW TO START UP AND RUN
THEIR OWN BUSINESS
AND WE GOT A FELLOW
HERE WHO'S DONE JUST THAT.
WINSTON ROTHCHILD OF
ROTHCHILD SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT, RED.
WELL, I'M LIVING
THE CANADIAN DREAM.
FIND A CAREER THAT
SUITS YOUR TEMPERAMENT.
TAKE JUNIOR SINGLETON,
FOR INSTANCE,
I MEAN HE LOVES
HUNTING, RIGHT?
YEAH.
SO HE'S GOING TO ENJOY
KILLING AND SLAUGHTERING
THAT NEW COW
HE JUST INHERITED.
YEAH, IT WILL PROBABLY
BE SLOW ENOUGH THAT HE
CAN ACTUALLY HIT IT.
NO, NO, RED, YOU
DON'T SHOOT A COW.
TAKE IT FROM ME, EH,
I WORKED IN A SLAUGHTERHOUSE
FOR A WHOLE SUMMER.
SLEDGEHAMMER,
RIGHT HERE.
BOOM.
INSTANT DIRT NAP.
OH, HAROLD,
STOP CRYING.
YOU KNOW WHAT, MY DAD
GAVE ME SOME GOOD
ADVICE ONCE.
LISTEN TO THIS.
IF YOU'RE SEARCHING
FOR A CAREER, LOOK AROUND
AND SEE WHAT YOU DO IN
YOUR SPARE TIME FOR FUN.
THAT'S GOOD ADVICE.
YOU SUCK OUT SEPTIC
TANKS IN YOUR SPARE
TIME WINSTON?
NO, NO, NO, BUT GEEZ
I LOVE TRAVELLING.
I LOVE MEETING
PEOPLE.
I LOVE THE
GREAT OUTDOORS.
I LIKE PUMPS.
I GUESS YOUR DAD HAS
GOT A JOB HE ENJOYS
TOO, DOES HE?
OH, ABSOLUTELY.
HE'S THE HAPPIEST,
DRUNKEN, GAMBLING
GIGOLO YOU EVER MET.
SO YOU SHOULD JUST
DO WHAT YOU ENJOY, RIGHT?
THAT'S THE SECRET.
BECAUSE IN THE
SEPTIC BUSINESS,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TAKE
A BACK SEAT TO NOBODY.
JUST FOLLOW YOUR NOSE.
YOUR DREAMS.
YEAH, RIGHT.
I HAVE AN OPEN INVITATION
HERE FROM RANGER GORD.
IT'S FROM RANGER GORD.
WE ALL KNOW RANGER
GORD, RIGHT?
HE'S BEEN UP IN THE TREE
WATCHING FOR FIRES
FOR THE PAST 16 YEARS
OVER POSSUM LAKE.
AND, OH, HE'S HAVING
A PAJAMA PARTY.
I'M HAVING A PAJAMA PARTY,
BRING YOUR ABBA ALBUMS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
HAROLD, IF THE PEOPLE
OF THIS COMMUNITY
EVER FIND OUT WHAT WE DID
IN THAT PARKING LOT
TO THAT COW,
I WILL NEVER BE ABLE
TO HOLD MY HEAD
UP HIGH AGAIN.
YOU ACTUALLY DID
IT UNCLE RED?
YOU DID THE WHOLE TEXAS
CHAINSAW MASSACRE-THING
TO THAT POOR, LITTLE,
DEFENSELESS MILK MAKER?
WE CHICKENED
OUT, HAROLD.
EVERY LAST ONE OF US.
THERE WASN'T ONE GUY
WHO COULD LOOK INTO
THOSE BIG BROWN EYES
AND THEN NAIL HER
WITH A SLEDGEHAMMER.
GUYS WERE SOBBING.
THEY GOT MISTY EYED.
AT ONE POINT MOOSE
THOMPSON ASKED THE
COW TO MARRY HIM.
THIS IS A DARK DAY
FOR THE IMAGE OF
POSSUM LODGE
WELL I FOR ONE AM
VERY PROUD OF YOU,
UNCLE RED.
DON'T MAKE IT
WORSE, HAROLD.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MANY
VEGETARIANS THERE ARE
IN THIS COUNTRY
BUT I BET MOST OF THEM
WORK IN SLAUGHTERHOUSES.
YOU KNOW, EATING MEAT
IS LIKE HAVING KIDS,
THE LESS YOU KNOW ABOUT
IT THE MORE LIKELY YOU
ARE TO GO AHEAD.
WELL, I HOPE YOU APOLOGIZED
TO WANDA, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE THAT COW HAS
HAD A VERY STRESSFUL DAY.
OH, YOU COULD TELL THAT
BY THE BACK SEAT OF
STINKY'S CADILLAC.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
IT'S MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO
AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN
A LITTLE WHILE.
OKAY.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND AFTER WHAT I'VE
BEEN THROUGH TODAY,
I DO NOT WANT TO HAVE
ANY MEAT FOR DINNER.
LET'S HAVE HOT DOGS.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
UNTIL NEXT TIME, ON BEHALF
OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS & APPLAUSE ]
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.