So I’m coming home from the
lodge the other night
and this guy's heading at me
with his high beams on.
So I flick my high beams
a couple of times,
but he keeps drilling
into my eyeballs like
laser surgery.
I couldn't see where
I was going.
Luckily,
nobody was hurt...
except the
postal system.
I figure that guy didn't
dim his lights
because he wasn't affected
by my puny high beams.
So I'm going to fight fire
with a flame thrower.
I'm going to add these
babies to the possum van.
I got them from the
Port Asbestos Arena.
Now that hockey's
on strike,
all they got going on
is line dancing
and they're afraid
if it's too bright
it'll just look like a bunch
of old, fat people
playing hopscotch.
You just mount those on
a piece of waterproof plywood.
I got this one
just up the road.
Now, these lights take
a while to warm up
so you just leave
them on all the time
and then swing them into
place when you need them.
To do that, I used a himmelman
hinge on the front edge
and mounted the whole unit
on a hockey stick.
The blade hangs
down inside.
All's I have to do
is pull down on it
when some idiot's coming
at me with his high beams.
The bulbs'll swing up,
shoot right at him
helping him
see the light.
Oh sure, the arena lights
are shooting up at the
sky all the time,
but that's not dangerous.
We're nowhere
near the airport.
[ APPLAUSE]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
All right.
Thanks very much.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
Big, big week up at
the lodge this week.
Harold's been pushing
us all to get these
fancy cellular phones
so I found a deal
and got enough
for everybody.
I don't know if I'm too excited
about having a cell phone,
but I figure if
it gets annoying,
it's small enough that
I can throw it
farther than
my ears can hear.
Uncle Red!
Did the cell phones come?
Is that the cell phones?
Yes, Harold, yes.
I wanted to call you
but then of course
I couldn't, could I?
Did you get the
one I wanted?
Yeah, pretty much.
With the caller I.D.
and the call forwarding
and the call waiting
and the personalized ring
and the text messaging
and the video capabilities,
did you get that?
Pretty much, yeah.
Pretty much that, yeah.
Did you not get the
exact make and model
that I specified?
No, I didn't, Harold.
Ohhhh!
Harold, 300 dollars
for a phone?
I can get a station wagon
for that kind of money,
and then I wouldn't have
to call anybody,
I'd just drive over.
Do you want to know
what I paid for these
babies, Harold?
Nothing.
Zero.
Nice catch.
It's a box of cereal.
Yeah, all different
kinds of cereal.
Every one comes with
a free cell phone inside.
Nut Flakes.
You should talk.
You're so naive it's
embarrassing sometimes.
Uncle Red, of course
the cell phone's free.
It's the activation fee
and the time rate
that they're going
to charge so much on.
There's going
to be no savings.
I'm not going to activate
my phone, Harold.
Instead of using their
cellular towers to
relay my calls,
I'm just going to boost
my phone signal
by using stronger
batteries.
Now let's see, what kind
of cereal should I get?
Well, you have trouble
making outgoing calls,
maybe you should
try the All Bran.
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Tonight's winner
will receive
a complimentary
dinner for two
at the Nurk & Fingle Pub.
Enjoy traditional
English fare
such as Fish 'n' Chips,
made with real
English fish,
Sausages 'n' Chips,
made with real
English sausage;
and Shepherd's Pie,
made from
real shepherds.
Real English shepherds?
No, German shepherds.
Okay, cover
your ears, Ed.
Okay, Mr. Green, you've got
30 seconds to get Ed Frid
to say this word...
Yeah, all right, Mike.
Okay, and GO!
Okay Ed, as an animal
control officer
you know that large
animals are most dangerous
when they're in...
My tent.
Okay, no but
in the spring,
animals are dangerous
because they're in...
... sane.
You know what,
that's right.
And what makes
them that way?
That's just the way
they are, Red.
No, okay, okay.
You can tell if a female
is ready to mate
because she's in...
A singles bar.
No.
Okay, okay, Ed,
when you need to get
people to do what you want,
you say, "it's time
to turn up the..."
Guilt.
Okay, no, no, okay.
On a cold winter's day,
your furnace pumps out
a lot of...
Smoke.
Okay, there's
an expression,
"Get out of the kitchen,
if you can't stand the..."
Smell of cauliflower.
We're almost out
of time, Mr. Green.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I know, an NBA team,
the Miami...
Dolphins.
No, no, no, basketball.
The Miami Basketballs.
Man, Ed you're not very good
at this, you know.
Me, your clues suck.
Why should
I take the heat?
There we go!
It's time for Harold's
Hobby House
where we examine
more than the hobby,
more importantly
the hobbyist.
And tonight's guest
is Mr. Edward Montrose.
And Edgar, I understand
that you are a hobbyist.
Oh no, Harold,
I'm Presbyterian.
No, I mean a hobby.
You know, what you do
in your spare time.
And I certainly hope it has
nothing to do with explosives
because I know you've
had some bad experiences
with those.
Yeah, well, sometimes
I get carried away.
Sometimes buildings
get carried away.
But not my hobby.
I have a gentle,
creative hobby.
Oh excellent.
Oh, that's perfect.
That's exactly what
I was hoping for.
You know, an example
of a hobby that shows
the balance in one's life.
Gosh, I wish that
was interesting.
I love trains,
Harold.
Oh, trains,
and what is it,
specifically,
that you love
about trains?
I love the way
they flatten stuff.
Yes, yes, oh yeah,
like coins and stuff
like coins
and stuff, right?
Oh, tut-tut, Harold,
coins are for amateurs.
How about...
a wristwatch?
Now, this is art.
I call it
"'A' Train On Time."
Very rare.
That's cool, Edgar.
I also tried
other items...
like a stapler.
Wow, that's --
that's a stapler.
I tried one without
opening it up
but it was too tall
and tapered,
so when the big
steel wheel hit it,
it shot out like a bullet
right through the windshield
Hey, I saw that
on the news!
Yeah?
Uh, everybody's fine
as far as I know.
Oh yeah, yeah...
but Edgar, do you
notice any similarities
between your chosen
profession
and the hobby
you've selected?
Oh, yes I do,
Harold.
They both take
place outdoors.
Even if I start my
explosive work indoors...
well, it doesn't
stay there very long.
No, not really.
No, no.
But you know,
I was talking more about
the destructive
component of each.
I find it
very disturbing.
It's a small world, Harold,
and it's getting smaller.
I create space.
Edgar, I'm just a little
concerned about the message
we're sending out
to our viewing audience,
you know, particularly
our younger viewers
because you do
dangerous things.
Oh, all right.
All you kids out there,
don't be blowing stuff up,
and don't be
putting things on
the railroad tracks.
It's very dangerous...
especially if you
stand too close.
You ever seen
these hot rod magazines
with pictures in them
that are supposed to
make you jealous?
Now, there are other kinds
of men's magazines
that have pictures
in them
but they're supposed to
make your wife jealous.
Neither one works,
except for pictures
like this.
Some guy doing
a massive burnout
with smoke pouring
off the tires
really gets my attention.
And if it doesn't,
your testosterone
may be down a quart.
to pull off a
stunt like that.
The only major peeling
I've ever done
involves an unplanned
nap on the beach.
But maybe we can look like
we're peeling rubber,
even though we're not,
'cause when a car does
a massive burnout,
it's not going fast,
it just creeps along
with the tires squealing
and the smoke fuming.
Maybe there's another
way to do that.
I mounted a fire
extinguisher
with the nozzle pointing
down through the floor
right at the wheel.
And I can turn the unit on
from the driver's seat
using that cable.
That'll provide
the smoke.
I didn't even have
to cut a hole in the floor,
as she's rusted out
in exactly the right spot.
Another reason
to buy domestic.
And as for the sound
of the squealing tires,
I've got no pads left
on these brakes
so I just put the
brakes on a little,
and she'll scream like
a parrot sitting on
a jalapeño.
And you don't have to worry
about the brakelights
giving the trick away...
they burned
out years ago.
Got to love domestic.
Okay, maybe doing a fake
peel out isn't exactly honest,
but for men my age,
truth is a last resort.
And the beauty
of this system,
it doesn't wear
out your tires.
[ BRAKES SQUEALING ]
You know, after
39 years of marriage,
I've learned one thing,
which puts me ahead
of most guys.
If you and your wife want
your marriage to survive
the long haul,
you've got to argue.
I don't mean yelling
and screaming
and acting
like a big baby,
leave that to your
elected representative.
I mean the simple act of
actually telling your spouse
what's bugging you,
rather than laying on
a thick layer of sarcasm.
For instance, instead of
your wife asking you
not to leave your stuff
on the floor, she'll say,
"Hey now,
"there's an interesting
place to keep your underwear."
Or like instead of asking for
your help with the dishes,
she'll say, "Are you sure
you can hear the ball game
"over all this
running water?"
But guys are no better
except men tend to do it with
actions rather than words.
A guy won't say
"I'd rather be golfing
than visiting your mother,"
he'll just carry his
golf bag around on his back
the whole trip.
Hey, do yourself
a favour,
lay off the sarcasm
when you're talking
to your spouse.
You may just find
yourself saying,
Gee, Red, that was
really good advice...
for once.
Remember,
I'm pulling for you.
We're all
in this together.
Don't put off getting
your septics pumped.
You can pay me now...
or you can pay me
through the nose later.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I love this cell phone.
I don't have
to remember anything.
If I think of something,
I just phone the person,
tell them right
then and there.
And I'm not really
bothering anybody
'cause I hardly
ever think of anything.
The only problem is
reception is not very good.
It's almost like when they
invented these things
they weren't targeting
markets like Possum Lake.
[ CELL PHONE RINGS ]
Excuse me.
Hello?
Hellooo?
Can you hear me?
Hey, Red?
Is that you, Winston?
No, Red, it's me,
Winston!
Hang on a sec.,
you're breaking
up a little bit.
There, that's better.
Red... Red,
where are you?
Good thanks.
Are you
at the lodge?
No, I'm fine,
it was just gas.
Red, listen,
I can't hear you.
I can't hear
you, Winston.
So how are those new
cell phones working out?
I tried to call you
but I couldn't get through.
Well then,
they're working perfectly.
Can you hear me now?
How about now?
What?
I said, how about now?
Now?
Can you hear me now?
[ MIKE FALLS DOWN STAIRS ]
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
Well, look at
the bright side.
That's the only phone
he's ever had
where he's allowed to
make more than one call.
[ PHONE VIBRATING ]
I'm getting a call!
Oh, my gosh.
I thought the ice cream
truck had pulled up.
Hello?
What? What?
What?
It's Dalton,
I think he said there's
an emergency.
What? Dalton? What?
Okay, okay, yeah.
Okay, I got it.
What was it?
Not sure.
He either said he knows
there's a meeting and
he has to beg off,
or his nose is bleeding
and his leg fell off.
Oh look, look,
he's sending you
a text message.
S - H - I,
don't like where
this is going.
R - T, "shirt."
"Shirt on fire."
What?
Shirt's on fire!
His shirt's on fire!
C'mon Uncle Red,
let's go!
Let's go!
We'll go out there
and help him.
Yeah, okay,
that's good.
He must be down
at the store.
The whole store could
be burning, you know.
Should we get another
fire extinguisher?
Yeah, yeah.
No, I think
we're good.
Sorry! Sorry,
my bad.
Sorry, my bad!
RED:
Dalton had asked Ed and Mike
to meet him out
behind the lodge.
He'd put some mats out.
I don't know,
some kind of exercise
or some sort of a spiritual
experience he had...
I wasn't quite
sure what he --
There, it looks more like
a fitness thing
and not a
minute too soon.
But Dalton has something going
on under that shirt and I --
You know, you see
stuff like that
and you don't know
whether to comment or --
You figure he's got to be
aware of it, you know.
But of course, Ed felt
he had to point out
that there was some sort of
an aberration there,
but Dalton seemed --
and then they see
what's happening.
This is the
instructor arriving
and boy, things are
looking up, aren't they?
Yeah, the guys look great and
Dalton's happy to meet her.
Oh boy, I don't know
if I want to -- oh, okay.
Just -- yeah, okay.
Oh boy,
oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
So apparently what this is
is a yoga lesson.
She's going to get them to be
all flexible and relaxed.
So okay guys,
just do that,
just do that.
Just do --
oh boy, oh boy,
oh boy, oh boy, okay.
All right, let's try
something that you can do.
I say, let's try
lying on our back.
Very good, excellent,
excellent, perfect.
Now, legs up,
over and...
and this is something
the guys found very easy
to watch.
And then up into some kind
of a stand and...
again, fascinated.
So now this is a flexibility
on the spine
and you turn your head right
around like that and...
Well, they're willing
to meet her halfway,
but that's about it.
And oh, good.
Yes, very good.
And the other side...
And perfect.
Okay, now they move on
to where you work in couples
as they do in yoga,
which is why so many
yoga people have kids.
And so she
sits Dalton down.
So Ed and Mike
have to duplicate
what they're doing,
and that's...
I don't --
I don't think --
You might want to --
Well, Dalton's suddenly
enjoying the day and...
They lean right back over
on the person
and relax totally
on them and so...
Mike's in for
a rough go here.
Now, this is an
interesting position.
You put your toes together
and then you bring your feet
up in between your arms,
and it's a
very elegant look,
and isn't that great, eh?
Now, that doesn't
go so well --
Oh, oh, oh.
This is -- this is almost
like a Cirque du Soleil thing,
where you get up and support
the weight of your partner,
and she arches her back
and... I don't --
Look out.
This is why we have
socialized medicine
in this country.
So they're trying --
Can't seem to break them up
and, you know, you do
what you got to do
when you get...
There we go.
Okay, okay.
That's good.
What were you
guys thinking?
Anyway, I guess that
pretty much brought
the yoga lesson
to a close,
and I don't
think you guys
are going to see
her anytime soon.
Just relax.
Well, we rushed over
to Dalton's store
'cause we thought
his shirt was on fire,
but it wasn't.
No, see, we thought Dalton
typed us a message that said,
"shirt on fire."
Whereas, in truth,
he was advertising,
"all shorts, half off."
But it wasn't an
emergency at all.
Well, not until
we got there.
No, no.
And in retrospect,
probably not a good idea
to burst in to a retail
establishment
with your fire extinguisher
going full blast.
Took that one lady customer
over an hour for her
leg to thaw.
Yeah.
But hey, she won't be
catching on fire
anytime soon.
No, so that's good.
And the really
good news is...
I got a new
pair of shorts!
Oh boy.
Aren't they hot?
They're hot!
Not anymore.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Meeting time.
Yeah, you go ahead,
Harold.
You might want
to slip those on,
may do you
a world of good.
If my wife is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting
and I learned
something this week.
I learned that no matter
what your message is,
you've got to say it
simply and clearly.
I have no plans
for this evening,
there is nothing worth
watching on television,
and I have a tremendous
amount of energy.
[ YELPS AND APPLAUSE ]
And no...
I don't feel
like moving furniture.
To the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself
and Harold
and the whole gang up here
at Possum Lodge,
keep your
stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Sit down, everybody!
Everybody sit down!
Sit down, c'mon sit down!
You got to sit down now!
C'mon, sit down!
Sit down!
All rise.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
RED: Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the man's prayer.
I'm a man,
but I can change,
if I have to...
I guess.
All right, men,
Harold apparently
has something to say.
Harold?
You know, as men,
oftentimes,
you don't communicate
as well as you should
so I was hoping that perhaps,
this side of the room,
all the men would stand...
just stand.
Now, think of something
personal and important
you'd like to say
to the gentlemen
on this side of the room.
And please do that now.
[ CELL PHONES RINGING ]
Hello?
I can't hear you?
Can you hear me?