[quirky upbeat music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> WELL, COME ON.
NEXT TIME, TELL ME OR SOMETHING.
THOUGHT YOU GUYS WERE
PROFESSIONALS.
OKAY, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, IT'S
TIME AGAIN TO WELCOME THE
WORLD'S GREATEST WOODSMAN.
WELL, OKAY.
UNLESS, OF COURSE, YOU'RE
COUNTING FESS PARKER, BUT HE'S
THE GREATEST STORYTELLER SINCE
WILL ROGERS DIED.
THAT'S FOR SURE, AND HE'S LIKE
THE WORLD'S BEST UNCLE.
NO OFFENSE, UNCLE JERRY.
BUT ANYWAY, HERE HE IS, THE STAR
OF THE RED GREEN SHOW,
RED GREEN.
>> THANK YOU, HAROLD.
THANK YOU, AND WELCOME.
AND THANK YOU, HAROLD, FOR SUCH
A NICE INTRODUCTION.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, TV DEMANDS
HYPE.
>> WELL, I WOULDN'T SAY I WAS
THE BEST STORYTELLER SINCE WILL
ROGERS DIED, BUT I'M CERTAINLY
GLAD SOMEONE DID.
BUT YOU KNOW, IT'S EASY TO BE A
STORYTELLER UP HERE AT THE LODGE
BECAUSE SO MANY THINGS ARE
HAPPENIN' ALL THE TIME.
LIKE YESTERDAY, MOOSE THOMPSON
DECIDED HE WAS GONNA MAKE SALT
AND PEPPER SHAKERS OUT OF A
COUPLE OF OLD SHOTGUN SHELLS.
>> THAT SURE IS A GREAT STORY,
UNCLE RED, BUT LET'S JUST MOVE
ON TO THE NEXT SEGMENT, OKAY?
HERE WE GO.
>> JUST A MINUTE, HAROLD.
BACK OFF ON THE ELECTRONIC
HISTRIONICS FOR A SECOND.
I HAVEN'T FINISHED THE STORY
YET.
SO ANYWAY, MOOSE MADE THE SALT
AND PEPPER SHAKERS OUT OF THE
SHOTGUN SHELLS, BUT SOMEWHERE
BETWEEN THE WORKSHOP AND THE
DINING ROOM, EVERYTHING GOT KIND
OF MIXED UP.
>> WELL, YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT SURE WAS WORTH LISTENING TO
THE WHOLE THING.
THE WAS WAY BETTER.
>> THAT WASN'T THE END, HAROLD.
>> WELL, THERE'S NO SENSE
WAITING FOR THE FAT LADY TO SING
HERE.
NO OFFENSE, AUNT MARY.
JUST I CAN HEAR CHANNELS
CHANGING ALL OVER THE PLACE.
CLICK, CLICK, CLICK, CLICK,
CLICK, CLICK.
YEAH, WE'RE IN A NEW SEGMENT.
>> [strumming guitar] ON A WARM SUMMER'S DAY
WHEN WE'RE NOT AFTER BASS
WE GET OUT THE VAN
FILL HER UP WITH GAS
PULL IN BEHIND A CAR
HEADIN' DOWN THE ROAD
PULL UP SO DARN CLOSE
YOU THINK WE'RE BEING TOWED
TAILGATIN', TAILGATIN'
KINDA LOOKS LIKE
THE VEHICLES ARE MATIN'
TAILGATIN', TAILGATIN'
JUST MAKE SURE YOUR BRAKES
ARE OKAY
IN RETROSPECT
THAT WAS AN OVERSIGHT
ON OUR PART
>> THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
WE'RE GONNA GO OUTSIDE AGAIN AND
SHOW YOU HOW YOU CAN FIX A DENT
IN YOUR CAR.
HOW MANY TIMES HAVE YOU DENTED
YOUR FENDER OR BANGED IN YOUR
BUMPER OR WHAT HAVE YOU OVER THE
LAST WEEK?
TOO MANY TO COUNT, I'M SURE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, BODY WORK IS
PRETTY EXPENSIVE IF YOU WANT IT
DONE HALF DECENT, AND THIS WEEK,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW YOU CAN
ACTUALLY DO YOUR OWN BODY
REPAIR, HOW YOU CAN FIX A DENT
IN YOUR FENDER.
NOW, YOU MIGHT SAY, "OKAY," YOU
MIGHT ASK ME, "HOW COULD I FIX A
DENT LIKE THIS?"
WELL, THERE'S NO DENT.
HANG ON.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW YOU MIGHT SAY, "HOW CAN YOU
FIX A DENT LIKE THIS?"
WELL, YOU GET YOURSELF
A BALL-PEEN HAMMER,
WHICH IS A--I GUESS A BALL ON
ONE END AND A--I GUESS THAT'S A
PEEN ON THE OTHER, AND JUST--YOU
OPEN THE TRUNK UP.
AND THEN YOU JUST GENTLY
TAP--TRY TO TAP OUT THE DENT
FROM THE INSIDE.
[grunting]
OKAY.
ACTUALLY, I MAY HAVE GONE A
LITTLE--A LITTLE TOO FAR
HAMMERING THAT OUT.
HANG ON.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S--THAT'S BETTER.
NOW, WE CAN JUST--THAT'S A
LITTLE BIT DENTED, BUT WE CAN
FILL THAT UP WITH--WE GOT
THE--THIS IS KIND OF A BODY
FILLER, A BONDO BODY--BONDO
FILLER.
WE JUST PUT THAT ON AND WE HAVE
FIBERGLASS HERE THAT WE ADD ON.
THIS IS THE APPLICATOR.
AND WELL, IT'S JUST SOMETHING
THAT'S NOT ALL THAT DIFFICULT TO
DO.
THAT SMELLS GOOD.
OKAY, JUST FINISH THAT UP THERE
AND JUST DRY HER OFF.
AND NOW SHE'S READY FOR THE
GRINDING.
I GOT A POWER GRINDER HERE, AND
WE JUST START HER UP, AND THEN
BRING HER RIGHT DOWN ONTO THE
METAL ITSELF.
[whirring]
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, THAT'S--IT'S NOT PERFECT,
BUT IT'S CERTAINLY GOOD ENOUGH
FOR OUR PURPOSES.
AND SO I'M READY TO PRIME, PUT
THE PRIMER COAT OF PAINT ON
THAT.
AND YOU'VE GOT TO JUST SHAKE
THAT UP A LITTLE BIT.
KIND OF SLIPPERY.
SLIPPERY.
LAY THAT ON THERE.
YOU WANT A NICE EVEN COAT OF
PRIMER ON THERE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
THE PAINT RUNNIN' OR NOTHIN'.
ALTHOUGH IF YOU'RE A REAL FUSSY
GUY, YOU COULD PUT THE CAR UP ON
ITS SIDE, BUT HERE WORKS GOOD.
TRY TO SEE WHAT YOU'VE DONE SO
THAT YOU DON'T MISS ANY SPOTS.
THIS COLOR'S GOOD FOR THAT,
ISN'T IT?
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GOT HER PRIMED THERE.
NOW YOU JUST WAIT FOR IT TO DRY,
AND THEN PUT ON THE FINISH COAT.
OKAY, I PRETTY WELL EMPTIED THE
WHOLE CAN INTO THERE.
THOSE DRIPS'LL WEAR OFF.
AND I THINK THIS IS--IT'LL FADE,
AND IT'LL BLEND IN.
AND ANYWAY, THERE YOU GOT IT.
YOU'VE DONE IT ALL YOURSELF.
A HECK OF A JOB.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME, REMEMBER.
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
HAROLD! HAROLD! HAROLD! HAROLD!
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE
WOODSMAN LORE, A SPECIAL GUEST,
THE SALT SHAKER STORY, AND OUR
REGULAR RED GREEN FEATURES.
>> AND SOME REALLY COOL SPECIAL
EFFECTS.
BONUS!
[laughs]
>> IT IS SPRING.
TADPOLES SWIM IN A STAGNANT POND
SURROUNDED BY FLOATING LILIES
AND WATER SNAKES.
YOU'RE TEMPTED TO DESTROY THEIR
WORLD WITH MEN AND EQUIPMENT,
TO DRY UP THE SWAMP
AND KILL THE ANIMALS.
BUT WHAT THE HELL?
YOU DON'T GO DOWN TO THE
BASEMENT THAT OFTEN ANYWAY.
WELL, AS I WAS SAYING BEFORE I
WAS SO RUDELY SPECIAL EFFECTED,
MOOSE THOMPSON DECIDED TO MAKE
THE SHOTGUN SHELL SALT AND
PEPPER SHAKERS WHEN HE COME HOME
FROM THE DUCK HUNT WITH A WHOLE
BOATLOAD OF EMPTY SHOTGUN SHELLS
AND NO DUCK.
BUT ANYWAY, WE ALL KIND OF LIKED
THE IDEA 'CAUSE SHOTGUN SHELLS
KIND OF GO WELL WITH THE DECOR
HERE AT THE LODGE, WHICH IS MORE
OR LESS A WOODSMAN'S MOTIF UNDER
A LAYER OF GRIME AND FUZZ.
OR AS WE CALL HIM, OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK.
>> OH, THAT'S A REALLY
INTERESTING STORY, UNCLE RED,
BUT I THINK, YOU KNOW, THE
CERTAIN CROSS SECTION OF OUR
AUDIENCE MIGHT FIND IT, LIKE,
BORING.
WELL, YOU KNOW.
YOU KNOW, LIKE CROSS SECTIONS
CAN BE--YOU KNOW.
AND WELL, IT'S ONE OF THE FIRST
THINGS I LEARNED AT TV
PRODUCTION SCHOOL, IS THAT TV IS
ABOUT SHOWING, NOT TALKING,
RIGHT?
THAT'S THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN TV
AND RADIO.
WELL, THAT AND THE PAY.
>> WELL, MAYBE I SHOULD BRING A
COUPLE OF SHOTGUN SHELLS OUT
HERE.
WE'D HAVE TO KEEP THEM AWAY FROM
THE HOT LIGHTS THOUGH.
>> WELL, YEAH.
YEAH, WE COULD DO THAT.
OR I WAS THINKING INSTEAD WE
COULD JUST, LIKE, YOU KNOW, MOVE
RIGHT ON TO SOMETHING ELSE, AND
THAT'D BE BEST FOR ALL PARTIES.
>> WHAT ABOUT MY STORY?
>> WHAT STORY IS THAT?
>> I FORGET.
>> OH.
WELL, WHILE YOU'RE TRYING TO
REMEMBER, WHY DON'T YOU DO ONE
OF THOSE NEAT SEGUE THINGS YOU
DO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S SOMETHING ELSE.
OH, I REMEMBER NOW.
IT WAS THE SALT AND PEPPER
SHOTGUN SHELL THING.
>> OH, YEAH.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
OH, BOY.
>> I'M OUT HERE WITH ONE OF THE
GREATEST MONSTER TRUCKS YOU'RE
GONNA SEE, AND I GOT THE OWNER
HERE WITH ME, MY GOOD BUDDY,
DOUGIE FRANKLIN.
DOUGIE, THIS IS SOME KIND OF
VEHICLE YOU'VE GOT HERE.
>> YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN, RED.
YOU KNOW, SHE DOES KIND OF CATCH
YOUR ATTENTION, DON'T SHE?
>> I'LL SAY.
>> WOMEN TOO.
[laughs]
NOW, I'M NOT SAYIN' THAT I GOT
HER TO ATTRACT THE WOMEN.
I'M NOT SAYIN' I DONE NOTHING
THAT CHEAP.
I ACTUALLY--I GOT THESE PANTS TO
ATTRACT THE WOMEN, BUT SHE'S
JUST--SHE'S A HUMDINGER.
SHE--YOU KNOW, THIS--IT'S LIKE A
MAGNET, THIS VEHICLE.
THIS IS LIKE A MAGNET TO WOMEN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> AND THEY COULD BE, YOU KNOW,
A COUPLE OF MILE AWAY AND JUST
SENSE THIS THING WAS THERE AND
[whistles]
THEY'D BE RIGHT UP THERE, JUST
LIKE A MAGNET AND A BIT OF STEEL
FILINGS OR SOMETHING.
>> OH, FOR GOD'S SAKE.
YOU HAVE TO BEAT 'EM OFF WITH
A STICK, I GUESS, EH, DOUG?
>> NO, NO.
NO, NOTHIN' THAT--NOTHIN' THAT
GOOD, RED.
BUT, YOU KNOW, THEY TALK TO ME,
AND, YOU KNOW, THEY SAY YOU CAN
TELL A LOT ABOUT A MAN BY THE
KIND OF CAR HE DRIVES.
WELL, YOU KNOW, REMEMBER, THE
OPPOSITE SEX SEES ME SITTIN' UP
HERE IN THIS MONSTER TRUCK.
SHE UNDERSTANDS,
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
SHE UNDERSTANDS.
>> OH, YEAH.
AND THEY--THEY KINDA THROW
THEMSELVES AT YOU, I GUESS, EH,
DOUG?
>> NO, NO.
NOTHIN' THAT GOOD, BUT THEY TALK
TO ME, AND, YOU KNOW, I--SO I
TELL 'EM ABOUT THE TIRES, YOU
KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> I TELL YOU, YOU SIT A WOMAN
NEXT TO THAT MUCH--NEXT TO THAT
MUCH RUBBER, BOY, SHE GETS A
LOOK OF RAPTURE OVER HER FACE.
I'LL TELL YOU, THEY--THEY LOVE
THAT.
COURSE, UH, THEY LIKE TO COME UP
AND SIT IN THE CAB, AND THAT
WORRIES ME A MIGHT, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE I DON'T LIKE TO HAVE
STRANGERS GETTIN' TOO CLOSE TO
MY INSTRUMENT CLUSTER, YOU KNOW?
MIND YOU, IF IT'S SOMEBODY I
KNOW, AND I APPROVE OF 'EM, MY
TYPE OF WOMAN, I DON'T MIND HER
SITTIN' UP THERE.
>> OH, YEAH?
WHAT IS--WHAT IS YOUR TYPE OF
WOMAN, DOUG?
>> WELL, RED, I'LL TELL YOU.
SHE'S GOTTA BE BETWEEN THE AGES
OF 15 AND 55.
I HAVE A FEW DEMANDS, BUT ONE OF
'EM IS THAT SHE HAVE HER OWN
HAIR, AND, UH, IT DOESN'T MATTER
TO ME IF, YOU KNOW, THERE'S SOME
BODY PARTS COURTESY OF MODERN
SCIENCE THERE.
I MEAN THAT'S QUITE ACCEPTABLE,
BUT, YOU KNOW, THEY JUST LOVE
TO--THEY LOVE TO GET UP HERE IN
THE CAB ON--ON A NICE HOT DAY
AND FEEL MY FUN FUR SEAT COVERS.
THEY'RE OUT AT THE CLEANERS
RIGHT NOW, ACTUALLY, BUT THEY
JUST LOVE THAT.
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW, DOUG, IT
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE THIS TRUCK HAS
CHANGED YOUR WHOLE SEX LIFE,
HUH?
>> [laughs]
OH, RED.
YOU HIT THE NAIL ON THE HEAD
THERE, I'LL TELL YOU, MY FRIEND.
[laughs]
[coughing]
>> WELL, THAT IS GREAT.
DOUGIE FRANKLIN, LADIES' MAN.
>> [gagging]
>> WAY TO GO, DOUGIE.
>> OH, THAT'S THE LAST TIME I'M
TOUCHIN' THAT TUNA SALAD.
>> [strumming guitar] I'M NOT A MALCONTENT
IN ANY WAY
I DON'T BELIEVE IN DREAMING
YOUR WHOLE LIFE AWAY
BUT IF I HAD ONE WISH
FOR THE GOOD LORD TO GRANT
I'D WISH TO TAKE A WET TOWEL
TO A NUDIST CAMP
>> [laughs]
>> SMACK, SMACK, SMACK
OH, SORRY
DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE
DRIP, DRIP, DRIP
THEY DON'T CALL IT ICE WATER
FOR NOTHIN'
SLAP, FOOF, AH!
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SPEND
MONEY TO HAVE FUN
THAT'S THE TRUTH, ISN'T IT,
HAROLD?
>> [laughs]
YOU SAID "NUDIST."
[laughs]
OH, UNCLE RED, EXCELLENT.
THIS IS GREAT.
IT'S ANSWER THE LETTER TIME.
THIS IS MY FAVORITE PART OF THE
SHOW, YOU KNOW.
I LOVE THIS PART 'CAUSE IT'S--
IT'S AN EXCHANGING OF IDEAS.
I LOVE THAT ASPECT TO IT, YOU
KNOW?
IT'S EXHILARATING TO ME.
I THINK IT'S JUST THE BEST PART
OF THE WHOLE PROGRAM.
[laughs]
>> JUST READ THE LETTER, HAROLD.
>> OH, OKAY.
JUST--I'M JUST SO EXCITED.
THIS IS SUCH A GREAT LETTER.
"DEAR RED, I'VE SEEN YOUR SHOW A
FEW TIMES NOW, AND I FORCE MY
CHILDREN TO WATCH IT UNLESS
THEY'VE BEEN GOOD.
I ENJOY THE PROGRAM, BUT IT--I
THINK IT WOULD BE A LOT BETTER
IF IT WAS MORE LIKE THE OLD
DICK VAN DYKE SHOW."
>> WELL, ALL RIGHT, HAROLD, YOU
KNOW HOW HAPPY WE ARE TO GET A
LETTER OF THIS TYPE, ESPECIALLY
WHEN IT CONTAINS A TERRIFIC
SUGGESTION LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW, THE DICK VAN DYKE
REFERENCE IS INTERESTING, AND WE
WEREN'T REALLY TRYING TO DO
EXACTLY THAT KIND OF A SHOW.
WE WERE THINKING MORE ALONG THE
LINES OF BEWITCHED OR MR. ED.
>> OH, WELL, UNCLE RED, I DON'T
THINK SARCASM'S IN ORDER.
NOTHING CAN BE ACCOMPLISHED WITH
THAT.
THE VIEWER JUST HAD A
SUGGESTION.
I THINK IT'S VALID.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
[mutters]
>> WELL, MAYBE I'M WRONG,
HAROLD.
MAYBE WHAT WE SHOULD DO IS GET
OURSELVES A NEIGHBOR NAMED
MILLIE, AND I'LL GET MARY TYLER
MOORE TO RUN THE BAIT SHOP, EH?
AND WE CAN IMITATE EVERY OTHER
SHOW ON TELEVISION.
>> YEAH, BUT UNCLE RED, YOU'RE
FORGETTING THAT IMITATION IS THE
SINCEREST FORM OF FLATULENCE.
>> I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT,
HAROLD.
THIS IS NOT A SITUATION COMEDY.
THIS IS A MAGAZINE SHOW FOR
SPORTSMEN.
>> AND WOMEN.
>> YEAH, WELL, THAT'S FINE.
THAT'S FINE.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT.
I'M JUST SAYING THAT I WANT--I'D
RATHER BE UNIQUE AND DO MY OWN
KIND OF SHOW AND NOT TRY TO
IMITATE SOMEBODY ELSE JUST FOR
THE SAKE OF GETTIN' BETTER
RATINGS.
>> "OH, ROB."
[laughs]
MARY TYLER MOORE.
SORRY.
>> I ALWAYS LOOK FORWARD TO
ADVENTURES WITH BILL 'CAUSE YOU
NEVER KNOW WHAT HE'S GONNA PULL
OUT OF HIS PANTS, AND THIS WEEK,
IT'S A COUPLE OF SLINGSHOTS.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT WE USED
TO DO WHEN WE WERE KIDS.
I'M NOT GONNA GET INTO
EVERYTHING THAT WE USE TO DO
WHEN WE WERE KIDS, BUT THESE ARE
KIND OF FUN, JUST THE FEELIN'.
THOSE ARE GREAT.
IT'S GREAT.
NO, NOT SO GREAT FOR BILL,
MAYBE.
>> OOH!
>> OH, BOY.
YEAH, I'LL BET THAT SMARTS, HUH?
YEAH.
WELL, BILL JUST DID THAT TO SHOW
ME THINGS THAT CAN GO WRONG WITH
THE SLINGSHOT.
GOT HIMSELF A LITTLE TARGET.
WATCH YOUR FOOT.
OH, GOOD.
YEAH, YEAH.
SO HE'S IMPROVING, ISN'T HE?
NOW, HE GIVES ME A LITTLE--ONE
OF THESE ROUNDED STONES, KIND OF
A LIGHT STONE THING, AND THEN
WE'RE JUST GONNA FIRE OFF.
KIND OF FELT GOOD.
IT'S FUN. IT'S FUN. IT'S FUN.
BILL HAD A--WELL, A COUPLE OF
PROBLEMS, AND WE BOTH MISSED THE
TARGET.
OH, WELL.
OH, NO, HE'S GOT ANOTHER ONE.
YEAH. YEAH.
AND A LITTLE MORE AMMO.
I MUST ADMIT, I WAS HAVING--I
WAS HAVING A GOOD TIME, JUST
FIRE UP INTO THE AIR THERE,
AND--OH!
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYBODY DO THAT,
BUT THAT'S BILL.
I'M SURE HE'S GOT A COUPLE MORE
SLINGSHOTS IN HIS PANTS THERE.
THIS IS KIND OF AN UNUSUAL--NO,
WAIT A--BILL.
BILL, BILL, BILL.
RIGHT.
WHAT ELSE?
OH, ANO--THIS IS A--NOW, THAT IS
A MAJOR PIECE OF WORK, THAT ONE
THERE.
AND YEAH, HE HAD THE AMMO.
YOU WANT TO SHOOT THE WHOLE BOX
IN ONE GO?
BILL, COME ON, NOW.
THIS IS A--WE'RE INTO TIMES OF
DISARMAMENT.
AND THE AMMO WAS--THESE ARE
ACTUALLY STEEL BALLS, AND THEY
COULD--THEY COULD TAKE YOUR EYE
OUT.
AND HE'S REALLY GOING FOR IT.
OH.
WELL, WE'RE JUST NOT GONNA TELL
MOOSE THOMPSON ABOUT THAT.
NOW, WE SET UP THESE MASON JARS
AS TARGETS AND ARE GONNA TO WORK
ON OUR AIM, BUT BILL GOT
CREATIVE HERE AND MADE WHAT I
WOULD CALL A NUCLEAR SLINGSHOT.
NOW HE'S LOOKIN' FOR SUITABLE
AMMO FOR IT.
NOT BIG ENOUGH, NOT BIG ENOUGH.
THAT SEEMED TO STRIKE HIS FANCY.
AND I'M GETTING A LITTLE WORRIED
AT THIS POINT, 'CAUSE THIS
THING'S GOT A LOT OF TORQUE ON
IT THERE, AND HE'S GONNA FIRE
THAT BRICK, AND MAYBE TAKE MY
HAT OFF,
AND KINDA LOST A BIT OF HIS
GRIP AND THEN SLIPPED, AND OH--
>> [yelling]
>> OH!
PERFECT.
>> IT IS WINTER.
DASHING THROUGH THE SNOW
IN A ONE-HORSE OPEN SLEIGH
JUST LIKE YOUR GRANDPARENTS DID,
ONLY IT'S COSTING YOU
100 BUCKS AN HOUR.
>> UNCLE RED, WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THE WAY OUR GOVERNMENT'S
RUNNING THIS COUNTRY?
YOU KNOW, SAY WITH THE ECONOMY?
>> IN WHAT AREA?
>> OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW, JUST SAY MINIMUM WAGE
FOR STARTERS.
YEAH.
>> YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, THE--I LIKE MINIMUM WAGE.
>> ME TOO.
ME TOO, WITH A QUALIFIER, OF
COURSE.
YOU KNOW, MANY OF MY FRIENDS AND
SEVERAL OF MY GRANDPARENTS ARE
WORKING FOR MINIMUM WAGE.
>> YEAH, MOST OF THEM ARE
FLIPPING HAMBURGERS, HAROLD.
>> GRANTED, TRUE.
AND YES.
OKAY, YES, GRANDMA GREEN IS NOT
THE FASTEST BURGER FLIPPER.
BUT OTHER PEOPLE ARE IN
POSITIONS OF RESPONSIBILITY, AND
I THINK THEY SHOULD BE MAKING
MORE THAN MINIMUM WAGE.
I.E., PEOPLE IN THE COURIER
INDUSTRY OR THOSE PRODUCING AND
DIRECTING A TELEVISION SHOW.
>> THINK I JUST SAW A RED FLAG
GO BY THERE, HAROLD.
>> WELL, I'M JUST SAYIN', UNCLE
RED, THAT PRODUCING AND
DIRECTING A SHOW LIKE YOURS DOES
NOT STRIKE ME AS A JOB THAT
SHOULD BE PAYING MINIMUM WAGE.
>> WELL, IT'S EITHER THAT OR
NOTHING.
>> WELL, I'M OPTING FOR THE
STATUS QUO.
CAN I CHOP THAT WOOD FOR YOU?
THERE'S NO INSTRUCTIONS.
>> WE'RE GONNA TAKE THIS LITTLE
COMMERCIAL BREAK SO THAT I CAN
REMEMBER THE SALT SHAKER STORY.
>> BUT HE MIGHT NOT, SO STAY
TUNED.
>> I KNOW A LOT OF YOU HAVE JUST
TURNED 16, AND YOU'VE ALREADY
SMASHED UP THE FAMILY CAR
SO NOW YOU'RE FORCED TO STAY
HOME AND WATCH THIS SHOW.
I WANT YOU TO THINK ABOUT BEING
OLD ENOUGH TO VOTE.
IT'S JUST AROUND THE CORNER, YOU
KNOW.
SO WAS THE TAVERN, BUT OF
COURSE, THAT'S NOT OPEN ON
ELECTION DAY.
IF THEY KEPT THE BARS OPEN, THE
POLITICIANS WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO
STAND FOR THE OFFICE THEY JUST
RECEIVED.
WHEN IT COMES TO YOUR FIRST
VOTE, I WANT YOU TO FIND
SOMEBODY THAT YOU LIKE AND USE
YOUR VOTE TO VOTE THEM IN THERE.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO WITH YOUR
FIRST VOTE.
AFTER THAT, YOU JUST FIND
SOMEBODY YOU CAN'T STAND AND USE
YOUR VOTE TO GET THE BUGGERS
OUT.
JACK!
JACK, COME ON UP HERE.
I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE, JACK.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> OH, NOTHING.
I JUST COME BY TO SEE HOW YOU
WERE DOIN'.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING DOWN THERE,
JACK?
>> NOTHIN'.
I WASN'T COOKIN' DOWN HERE JUST
NOW.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
DON'T GET EXCITED.
I JUST DROPPED BY TO SEE IF
YOU'RE OKAY NOW THAT YOU'VE
TURNED INTO A, YOU KNOW, A
CAVEMAN.
I MEAN...
[laughs]
WHAT'S THAT LIKE?
>> LOOK.
I DON'T HAVE ANY EXTRA FOOD,
OKAY?
I'M SORRY.
I TOLD THEM THIS WOULD HAPPEN
WHEN THEY BROUGHT IN THAT
CAPITAL GAINS TAX, YOU KNOW.
PEOPLE ARE GONNA COME RUNNIN' TO
OLD JACK TO OFFSET THE
SHORTFALL, BUT I DON'T HAVE ANY
EXTRA FOOD.
I'M SORRY.
>> WELL, IT'S--AND, JACK--
JACK, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I ACTUALLY--I STOPPED ON THE WAY
UP HERE.
I HAD A CHEESEBURGER.
I HAD A LARGE FRIES.
>> OKAY, LOOK.
ALL RIGHT, I WAS COOKING DOWN
THERE JUST NOW, R--SO WHAT?
YOU KNOW, THIS--IT'S MY CAVE,
AND IF THEY CAN TAX MY DIVIDEND
EARNINGS, THEN I THINK I SHOULD
BE ABLE TO COOK IN MY CAVE.
THAT'S FAIR, I THINK.
>> NO, I AGREE.
I AGREE, JACK.
NOW, DON'T TAKE THIS THE WRONG
WAY, OKAY.
BUT A BUNCH OF US UP AT THE
LODGE ARE WONDERING IF MAYBE
YOU'D LIKE TO COME AND JUST STAY
AT THE LODGE FOR A WHILE.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, JUST IF YOU
WANT TO.
>> I CAN'T.
>> OH.
>> I'M HAVIN' A PARTY TONIGHT,
SO, YOU KNOW, THE BANDS COMIN'
DOWN AND EVERYTHING, AND IT'S
KIND OF A
BRING-YOUR-OWN-CANNED-GOODS SORT
OF THING, AND WELL, RED, YOU'RE
NOT INVITED.
I'M SORRY, BUT I JUST FIGURED,
YOU KNOW, YOU--WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU MIGHT NOT FIT IN.
I THINK YOU SHOULD LEAVE NOW.
>> WELL, JACK, MAYBE I SHOULD GO
NOW, EH.
BUT REAL GOOD TO SEE YOU, YOU
KNOW?
>> YEAH, YOU TOO.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> YOU WANT A POTATO OR
SOMETHING TO TAKE WITH YOU?
>> WELL, YEAH.
GEE, A POTATO WOULD BE GREAT.
YEAH.
>> WELL, YOU'LL HAVE TO WAIT A
WHILE.
I HAVEN'T PLANTED THEM YET.
>> WHAT A KIBITZER.
ANYWAY, TO MAKE A LONG STORY
FINISHED, MOOSE MADE THE SALT
AND PEPPER SHAKERS OUT OF
SHOTGUN SHELLS, BUT THEN HE GOT
'EM MIXED UP.
AND HE ENDED UP PUTTIN' REAL
LIVE AMMO ON THE DINING ROOM
TABLE.
MEANWHILE, BUSTER HATFIELD GOES
OUT DUCK HUNTIN' WITH THE SALT
AND PEPPER SHAKERS.
SO BUSTER FIRES OFF THE SALT AND
PEPPER, BRINGS DOWN A COUPLE OF
DUCKS.
NOW, WE HAD TO CLEAN 'EM AND
PLUCK 'EM, BUT THEY DIDN'T NEED
ANY SPICES.
AND I COOKED THE DUCKS UP FOR
DINNER, IN FACT, AND, GOD, WE
HAD OUR FIRST FORMAL SIT-DOWN
DINNER IN ABOUT, UH, EVER.
SO THEN, OF COURSE, MOOSE HAS TO
BRING OUT THE SALT AND PEPPER
SHAKERS, NOT REALIZING THEY ARE
ACTUAL SHELLS, AND WE'RE ALL
SPRINKLING GUNPOWDER AND
BUCKSHOT ALL OVER THE DUCK.
DIDN'T HURT THE TASTE ANY, YOU
KNOW, BUT THEN STINKY PETERSON
BURPED AND BLEW A HOLE IN THE
LAMPSHADE.
WELL, THEN OF COURSE, WE ALL HAD
TO GET INTO IT, YOU KNOW, AND
OUR NORMAL AFTER-DINNER BELCHING
CONTEST TURNED INTO TARGET
PRACTICE, WHICH MOOSE THOMPSON
WON WITH A 12-SECOND HONKER THAT
RIPPED THE ANTLERS OFF THE
DINING ROOM MOOSE HEAD.
BUT THEN MOOSE HAS ALWAYS BEEN
GOOD AT SHOOTIN' HIS MOUTH OFF.
SO THAT ABOUT WRAPS IT UP FOR
THIS WEEK, AND IF MY WIFE IS
WATCHIN', I'LL BE COMIN'
STRAIGHT HOME, AND I WILL TAKE
THE GARBAGE OUT TONIGHT IF YOU
JUST WANT TO SHOVEL IT INTO THE
BAGS FOR ME.
SO THANKS AGAIN FOR WATCHIN',
AND UNTIL NEXT TIME, ON BEHALF
OF MYSELF AND HAROLD AND THE
WHOLE GANG HERE AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.