YOU KNOW, ON A
BEAUTIFUL WEEKEND DAY
IN THE MIDDLE
OF TROUT SEASON,
THE LAST THING
YOU WANNA BE DOING
IS PAINTING THE
INSIDE OF YOUR HOUSE.
WELL, LET'S SAY YOUR
SIGNIFICANT OTHER ASKS
YOU TO PAINT THE FRONT ROOM.
INSTEAD OF WHINING
OR HIDING OR FAKING A HERNIA,
WHY DON'T YOU USE IT AS
A LEARNING EXPERIENCE?
YOU'LL LEARN THAT
THERE ARE OVER 75 SHADES
OF GREEN PAINT.
YOU'LL ALSO DISCOVER THAT
TWO SHEETS OF NEWSPAPER
COVERS THE AVERAGE
SIZE WINDOW.
AND YOU'LL SEE THE BENEFIT OF
THROWING YOUR DIRTY LAUNDRY
ON THE FLOOR ALL THESE YEARS.
YOU'LL ALSO FIND OUT
THAT IF YOU'RE OVER 55,
THERE'S A PRETTY GOOD CHANCE
THAT YOUR PYJAMA BOTTOMS
ARE LARGE ENOUGH TO FIT
OVER A STANDARD FLOOR LAMP.
NOW, I KNOW THAT YOU KNOW WHAT
A PAINT SPRAYER LOOKS LIKE.
BUT YOU PROBABLY DON'T REALISE
THAT THE HOSE FITTINGS
ARE THE SAME SIZE AS THE
ONES ON YOUR LAWN SPRINKLER.
OKAY, YOU'RE ALSO
GONNA FIND OUT
THAT YOU WANNA GET OUTTA
HERE BEFORE THE LATEX
HITS THE WALL.
AND NOW, IF YOU'LL BE KIND
ENOUGH TO EXCUSE ME,
I'VE GOT SOME
PAINTING TO DO.
[paint sprayer whirring]
[sprayer stops]
NOW THE SECOND COAT.
[paint sprayer whirring]
THEN WHILE YOU'RE WAITING
FOR THE PAINT TO DRY,
YOU CAN GO CALL A FEW
BUDDIES AND BRAG TO THEM
ABOUT HOW SMART YOU ARE.
[cheering and applause]
[chuckling]
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
CONTINUES ]
[chuckling]
OKAY, THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
NO, I APPRECIATE THAT.
I GUESS YOU KNOW THAT
THIS IS THE BIG WEEKEND,
THE SECOND ANNUAL CHAIN SAW
RACES UP HERE.
WE MOUNT THE CHAIN SAWS ONTO
SKATEBOARDS LIKE THIS,
AND BOY, DO THESE
BABIES EVER MOVE.
YOU TAPE THAT
THROTTLE WIDE OPEN,
THIS THING TAKES OFF ON YOU.
ZERO TO 60 IN UNDER
FIVE SECONDS.
EVEN FASTER IF YOU
REMEMBER TO LET GO.
AND TALK ABOUT
A CROWD PLEASER.
WE COULD HAVE CHAIN SAW
RACES EVERY MONTH,
IF PEOPLE WOULD HEAL FASTER.
UNCLE RED!
[cheering and applause]
THEY'RE EXCITED.
THEY'RE EXCITED, HAROLD.
ARE YOU COMING OUT
TO MEET THE BUS?
BUS?
WHAT BUS?
THE BUS FOR THE INTELLECTUALLY
GIFTED CHILDREN'S CLUB.
YEAH,
WHAT?
THEY BOOKED THE LODGE
FOR THE ENTIRE WEEKEND.
LOOK, SEE, IT'S RIGHT
HERE IN MY PALM PILOT.
WELL, UH,
LET ME CHECK
MY PALM PILOT.
OH, YEAH, HERE IT IS.
SO WHAT?
I CAN'T MEET THE
BUS, HAROLD.
I GOTTA WORK ON MY
CHAIN SAW FOR THE RACES.
OH! WE GOT A WHOLE PROGRAMME
PLANNED FOR THESE
SPECIAL KIDS.
OH, YEAH?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
NO!
YOUR POCKET PROTECTORS?
CLEAN AND RELOAD
BUT WE HAVE
VEGETABLE CLONING.
YES, AND WARHAMMER ACTION
FIGURE PAINTING CLASSES.
AND A CHANCE TO DRESS UP AS
YOUR VERY FAVOURITE ALIEN
"STAR TREK" CHARACTER,
WHICH IS SO COOL!
WHAT?
SHOULD DO, HAROLD?
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU
YOU SHOULD BRING THE KIDS
TO THE CHAIN SAW RACES.
OH, YEAH. YEAH.
NO, NO, NO.
HUH?
NO, NO.
NO, IT'S JUST THAT PEOPLE
WHO ARE VERY INTELLIGENT
HAVE LOW
PAIN THRESHOLDS.
WELL, THE SPECTATORS WILL
BE PERFECTLY SAFE, HAROLD.
I MEAN, WE'RE HOLDING IT UP
IN THE DRY RIVER BED UP AT
ROCK REEF POINT THERE.
THERE'S ABSOLUTELY NO
CHANCE THAT ANYBODY'S
GONNA GET HURT.
[chain saw rewing]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheering and applause]
TONIGHT'S WINNER GETS A
COPY OF MY BRAND NEW BOOK.
NOW, THIS IF FOR PEOPLE WHO
FIND THE "FOR DUMMIES" BOOK
A LITTLE TOO COMPLICATED.
"DRESSING YOURSELF
FOR UTTER MORONS."
AH! NUMBER FOUR...
OKAY, DALTON,
COVER YOUR EARS.
RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS TO
GET DALTON TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, DALTON, YOU SET
YOUR ALARM CLOCK
BECAUSE YOU
WANNA WAKE UP...
IRRITABLE.
OKAY, IF YOU'RE
NOT LATE, YOU ARE...
STILL ALIVE!
NO. NO.
OKAY, WHICH BIRD
GETS THE WORM?
THE BIG, MEAN ONE?
ALMOST OUTTA TIME, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, UM,
OKAY.
DALTON, WHAT MAKES A MAN
HEALTHY, WEALTHY AND WISE?
DO I LOOK LIKE I KNOW?
NO, BUT YOU DO KNOW.
SOMETHING TO BED;
SOMETHING TO RISE.
NO! NO! NO!
ALL RIGHT, NO.
NO. NO. NO.
YOU KNOW WHEN YOU
GO TO A PARTY,
AND YOU GET THERE BEFORE
YOU SHOULD, YOU ARE...
ALONE.
HOW DO YOU FIGURE ALONE?
BECAUSE IF I TAKE ANN MARIE,
I NEVER GET ANYWHERE EARLY.
THERE IT IS!
[applause]
[music blaring]
THAT'S THE FUTURE OF
OUR COUNTRY RIGHT THERE.
FIFTEEN HORSEPOWER CAR
WITH A 300 HORSEPOWER RADIO.
AND THE MUSIC'S TERRIBLE.
'COURSE, THAT'S WHY
THEY PLAY IT SO LOUD,
BECAUSE THEY KNOW YOU'D
NEVER LISTEN TO IT IF
YOU HAD A CHOICE.
NOW, I KNOW AS YOU GET OLDER
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO MATURE,
ACCEPT THINGS AROUND YOU
AND JUST KEEP QUIET.
TO ME, THAT MEANS
EVERYBODY IN THE CEMETERY
IS ABOUT AS MATURE
AS YOU CAN GET.
I PREFER TO STAY CHILDISH.
SO THIS TIME
ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA STRIKE BACK
BY TURNING THIS VAN
INTO THE WORLD'S
LARGEST BOOM BOX.
NOW, THEY DON'T BUILD THE
SIZE OF SPEAKER I HAD IN MIND,
SO I HAVE TO MAKE MY OWN.
HOW HARD CAN IT BE?
FOR STARTERS, I'LL NEED
A REAL BIG MAGNET
TO PUT ON THE BACK
OF MY SPEAKER.
SO I TOOK EVERY FRIDGE MAGNET
ANYONE HAD EVER GIVEN ME,
AND I PUT 'EM INTO
THIS METAL BUCKET.
THEY'RE FROM INSURANCE GUYS,
PIZZA DELIVERY PLACES,
RELIGIOUS FANATICAL GROUPS.
BOY, THAT'S A
STRONG MAGNET.
OKAY, PERFECT.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT
WHERE I WANTED IT.
THAT SAVED ME A LITTLE TIME.
HMM.
OKAY.
NOW, TO MAKE THE
CONE FOR MY SPEAKER,
I'M GONNA USE ONE OF THESE
KIDDIE SWIMMING POOLS.
JUST GIVE ME A MINUTE
TO INFLATE THIS, WILL YOU?
THERE WE GO.
COME, EH.
WE MADE A FAIR TRADE.
A DEAL'S A DEAL.
THERE YOU GO.
OKAY, THIS IS WHERE IT
GETS A LITTLE BIT TRICKY.
YOU GOTTA MAKE
AN ELECTROMAGNET ON
THE BACK OF YOUR POOL
THAT'LL FIT OVER THE
BUCKET OF FRIDGE MAGNETS,
AND YOU GOTTA DO ALL THIS
WITHOUT GOING OVER BUDGET.
SO I'M JUST USING
THIS OLD GARBAGE PAIL
BECAUSE I DON'T NEED
THIS UNTIL GARBAGE DAY.
AND I FIGURE BY THEN
THIS WHOLE PROJECT
WILL BE A DISTANT,
PAINFUL MEMORY.
THEN WITH THE ELECTROMAGNET
PART, ALL I'M DOING
IS WINDING THIS STRING OF
CHRISTMAS LIGHTS AROUND
THE OUTSIDE.
THESE ALL FELL OFF THE ROOF
DURING THAT BIG STORM
LAST JULY.
OKAY, I'M GONNA NEED SOME REAL
WATTAGE TO DRIVE THIS BABY,
SO HERE'S WHAT I DID.
I TOOK ALL THE AMPLIFIERS
OUT OF A BUNCH OF OLD
RADIOS I HAVE --
YOU KNOW, IN THE GARAGE,
DOWN IN THE BASEMENT,
IN THE ATTIC --
WIRED THEM ALL
TOGETHER IN SERIES.
I'VE PROBABLY GOT A TRILLION
GIGAWATTS OF POWER HERE.
IF IT DOESN'T
WORK OUT AS A RADIO,
IT'LL MAKE A DANDY
WELDER, HUH?
OF COURSE, I'M NOT
GONNA HAVE ANY MUSIC
UNTIL I TURN ON THE VAN RADIO.
BUT I STILL GOTTA
HOOK UP THE SPEAKER,
MAKE SURE THE POWER'S
GETTING THROUGH, YOU KNOW.
YEAH! I'M GOOD.
NO, THAT'S --
THAT'S ALL GOOD.
OKAY, NOW I JUST GOTTA
CRANK THE VOLUME ON HER.
OKAY, WE'RE READY TO ROCK.
SO REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME --
OH, BABY.
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[laughing]
[music blaring]
[music blasting]
[cheering and applause]
YOU KNOW,
AFTER YOU GET MARRIED,
THERE ARE THINGS YOU NEED TO
LEARN THAT NOBODY EVER
TALKS ABOUT.
THEY'RE NOT IN ANY MANUAL,
AND NEITHER YOUR PARENTS NOR
YOUR TEACHERS ARE EVER
GOING TO MENTION THEM.
SO I GUESS IT'S MY JOB.
OKAY, HERE'S THE MAIN ONE...
TO SURVIVE AS A
HAPPILY MARRIED MAN,
YOU HAVE TO LEARN
HOW TO SNEAK FOOD.
YOU GOTTA PRETEND THAT
WHEN YOU'RE GETTING OUT OF BED
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
IT'S BECAUSE YOU HEARD A
CLUNKING SOUND COMING
FROM THE BASEMENT,
NOT BECAUSE YOU HEARD A
GRUMBLING SOUND
COMING FROM YOUR
OWN STOMACH.
YOU GOTTA BE ABLE TO FIND
THE KITCHEN IN THE DARK.
YOU GOTTA BE ABLE
TO UNPLUG THE FRIDGE
SO THAT WHEN YOU OPEN
THE DOOR, THE LIGHT
DOESN'T COME ON.
YOU GOTTA EAT
THE FOOD REAL FAST.
AND WHEN YOUR WIFE CALLS DOWN
TO FIND OUT WHAT YOU'RE DOING,
YOU GOTTA BE ABLE TO STUFF
IT ALL INTO ONE CHEEK
SO THAT YOU CAN ANSWER HER
WITHOUT THE TELLTALE SOUND
OF A MOUTHFUL OF
COLD LASAGNA.
THEN WHEN YOU'RE FINISHED,
YOU'VE GOTTA BE ABLE TO
HIDE ALL THE EVIDENCE
AND CLIMB BACK INTO BED.
AND IF SHE STARTS MAKING
ADVANCES TOWARD YOU,
DON'T GIVE IN TO HER.
SHE'S NOT FEELING ROMANTIC;
SHE'S TRYING TO FRISK
YOU FOR TWINKIES.
REMEMBER I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
[siren blaring]
MAN, WHAT'S
THIS ABOUT?
WERE YOU SPEEDING?
SPEEDING?
IN THE POSSUM VAN, DALTON?
I LEFT MY WALLET
AT HOME.
I'VE GOT NO
DRIVER'S LICENSE.
OKAY.
SWITCH PLACES WITH ME.
QUICK, DALTON.
[grumbling]
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GOOD.
IS THAT A
GOOD IDEA?
I THINK DALTON'S
BEEN DRINKING.
I HAVE NOT, MIKE.
REALLY?
YOU MEAN HE ACTS
THIS WAY ALL THE TIME?
JUST GET YOUR
LICENSE OUT, DALTON.
UP HERE ANY SECOND.
THE COP'LL BE
NO PROBLEM.
WHAT'S TAKING HIM
SO LONG ANYWAY?
HE'S PROBABLY
RUNNING A CHECK ON
THE LICENSE PLATES.
NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
HEY, WHAT'S TODAY'S DATE?
THE 14th.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
MY LICENSE IS EXPIRED,
UNLESS IT'S STILL 1997.
NO, THAT WAS
YEARS AGO, DALTON.
ALTHOUGH, YOUR
WARDROBE IMPLIES 1962.
WELL, WHAT DO WE
DO NOW, GUYS?
HEY, I GOT A LICENSE.
LET ME DRIVE.
ALL RIGHT.
[grumbling]
GET OVER THERE.
GET OVER THERE!
OH!
OKAY, WE'RE FINE.
WE'RE FINE.
IT'LL BE SMOOTH SAILING
FROM HERE ON.
JUST LET ME
DO THE TALKING, OKAY?
LET ME SEE YOUR
LICENSE, MIKE.
YEAH, SURE.
JéSUS RODRIGUEZ?
IT WAS MY MAIDEN NAME.
HELLO, POLICE?
I'D LIKE TO REPORT
A ROBBERY IN PROGRESS
AT THE MAIN INTERSECTION
OF PORT ASBESTOS.
UH-UH, MY NAME?
UM --
UH, JéSUS RODRIGUEZ!
[ tires squealing,
siren blaring]
[applause]
[chain saw]
BOY, THIS THING'S
RUNNING GREAT.
UNCLE RED --
UNCLE RED,
I HAVE A PROBLEM.
WELL, WE'RE ALL
AWARE OF THAT, HAROLD.
I CANNOT DO MY JOB AS
PROMOTIONS MANAGER OF
THE POSSUM LAKE AREA
IF YOU CONTINUE TO STAGE
THESE DANGEROUS EVENTS,
LIKE THE
CHAIN SAW RACING.
YOU'RE FORCING ME
TO PULL RANK.
NOW, HAROLD, WAIT A SECOND.
YOU'RE NOT TELLING ME
YOU'RE PUTTING YOUR JOB
ABOVE THE WISHES
OF THE LODGE, ARE YOU?
I'M NOT, BUT I'VE HAD A BUS
LOAD OF GIFTED CHILDREN
PUT INTO MY CARE,
SO I'M PUTTING THEIR SAFETY
ABOVE THE WISHES OF THE LODGE!
OKAY, I KNOW YOU
FEEL THAT WAY,
BUT I BETCHA
THE KIDS DON'T.
OH-H!
I KNEW YOU WERE
GONNA SAY THAT.
YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
I KNEW YOU WERE
THORNTON! THORNTON!
COME ON IN HERE.
WELL, LOOKS LIKE THE
VEGETABLE CLONING WORKED.
ARE YOU THE MAN RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS IRRESPONSIBLE
AND SOPHOMORIC EXHIBITION?
WHAT?
HE'S TALKING ABOUT
THE CHAIN SAW RACES.
IT SETS A VERY POOR
EXAMPLE FOR TODAY'S YOUTH,
WATCHING GROWN MEN TEARING
DOWN TREES AND POLLUTING
THE ENVIRONMENT.
I HOPE YOU'RE SOAKING
HIS PARENTS FOR THIS
WEEKEND, HAROLD.
DO NOT BE MEAN,
UNCLE RED.
IT'S VERY DIFFICULT FOR
PEOPLE OF DIFFERENT
INTELLECTUAL LEVELS
TO COMMUNICATE.
WELL, WE'VE PROVEN THAT FOR
YEARS, HAVEN'T WE, EH?
THORNTON.
SOMETHING, THORN.
SO TELL ME
THORNTON.
EXCUSE ME.
OKAY, YOU'RE A KID, YOU
MUST SEE THE FUN SIDE OF
CHAIN SAW RACES, EH?
MAYBE A FEW YEARS AGO
I MIGHT HAVE.
OH, YEAH?
BUT YOU CAN'T JUSTIFY
ENDANGERING YOUR PEERS
AND DESTROYING THE OZONE
ALL FOR THE SAKE OF YOUR
OWN CHILDISH AMUSEMENT.
[ LAUGHTER AND
SCATTERED APPLAUSE ]
WE'RE GOOD.
THAT'S OKAY.
Red Green: A BUNCH OF
US DECIDED TO BUILD A
LITTLE CHILDREN'S AREA
OUT BEHIND THE LODGE THERE.
HAD A LITTLE WADING POOL.
PUTTING A SCREEN
AROUND THAT.
JUST KINDA MAKE IT
FRIENDLY FOR THE KIDS.
WINSTON WAS CUTTING
LUMBER FOR US.
AND I WAS ACTUALLY, UH --
OH, THERE'S WALTER PUTTING UP
THE SIGN FOR THE KIDDIE AREA.
AND HE HAD ONE OF THOSE NAIL
GUNS, AND BOY, THEY'RE
QUITE A UNIT, EH?
I WAS CAULKING, AS I SAY,
BETWEEN THE SCREENS
TO KEEP THE BUGS IN AND --
DALTON HAD THE STAPLE
GUN KINDA JAMMED
AND -- OH! OH!
WELL, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH, DALTON.
WELL, IT'S AN EYE FOR AN EYE
AND SOME CAULKING FOR
A STAPLE.
OH, RIGHT INTO
WINSTON'S COFFEE,
BUT LUCKILY HE DIDN'T
SEE IT UNTIL HE HAD A SENSE
SOMETHING WASN'T QUITE RIGHT.
THEN THINGS STARTED
TO GO BAD AFTER THAT.
THEN THE NAIL GOES RIGHT
INTO THE POOL AND THE
WATER COMES OUT,
HITS THE PLUG,
AND THEN -- OH! OH!
AND THE SAW KEEPS RUNNING.
THE BLADE'S DIGGING IN,
AND AWAY SHE GOES.
THE SAW'S HEADING
OVER TOWARD WALTER.
SO DALTON SAYS,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT --
THAT'S STUPID.
YOU FIRED THAT,
YOU HIT THE POOL.
JUST GIVE ME THAT THING.
NOW SHE GOES
INTO AUTOMATIC.
NOW WE GOT A REAL PROBLEM.
AND THOSE ARE
GOOD SIZED NAILS TOO.
DON'T FORGET ABOUT WINSTON.
HE'S LYING RIGHT IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE BATTLEFIELD.
WALTER GOES IN THERE,
AND THIS IS THE KIND OF THING
YOU HAVE TO
DO AT THE LODGE.
JUST IGNORE THE FIRE AND --
I'VE SEEN THIS IN A MOVIE
OR SOMETHING, HAVEN'T I?
WELL, ANYWAY, EVERYTHING
FINALLY SETTLED DOWN.
THE NAIL GUN STOPPED.
AND THE AREA WAS RUINED,
BUT WE SURVIVED.
WHAT ABOUT THE SAW?
I'M THINKING THE CIRCULAR SAW
IS STILL ON THE
LOOSE SOMEWHERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
HERE IT COMES!
LOOK OUT!
AND SHE GOES
RIGHT UP THE SIGN AND --
OKAY, NOW WE HAVE
A NEW NAME.
THERE'S TWO WAYS
TO PRONOUNCE THAT.
I DON'T LIKE
EITHER ONE OF THEM.
[applause]
IT'S TIME FOR THE EXPERTS'
PORTION OF THE SHOW,
WHERE WE ADDRESS THOSE
THREE LITTLE WORDS MEN
FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
THOSE ARE THE WORDS.
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
AND JOINING US TODAY,
MARINA OWNER
AND IDLE CURIOSITY,
DWIGHT CARTER.
ALL RIGHT, FELLAS,
HERE'S THE LETTER...
"DEAR EXPERTS, I HAVE RECENTLY
THOUGHT ABOUT TAKING UP
SKY-DIVING
"AND WANTED TO KNOW
IF YOU HAVE ANY TIPS."
OKAY, YEAH, SURE.
NOW, EVERY GUY HAS
A VOICE IN HIS HEAD
THAT STOPS HIM
FROM DOING DUMB THINGS.
ACTUALLY, IF YOU'RE MARRIED,
YOU HAVE TWO OF 'EM.
AND THE LOUD ONE
ISN'T EVEN YOURS.
BUT THIS VOICE STOPS YOU
FROM DOING IDIOTIC STUFF
LIKE JUMPING OUT OF AIRPLANES,
OR QUITTING YOUR JOB
TO BECOME A MIME,
OR SHARING YOUR THOUGHTS.
YEAH, I AGREE
WITH YOU.
I THINK
SKY-DIVING'S NUTS.
I MEAN, I HAVE
MY OWN BUSINESS,
SO IF I JUMP OUT OF A
PLANE AND DO A FACE PLANT
INTO THE GROUND
AT 120 MILES AN HOUR,
I'M OFF WORK
WITHOUT PAY.
YOU'RE OFF EVERYTHING
WITHOUT ANYTHING.
WELL, I LIKE
SKY-DIVING.
I THINK IT'S
A GREAT SPORT.
YOU GET SOME GUY
TO SUIT YOU UP,
STRAP ON YOUR CHUTE,
AND ALL YOU HAVE
TO DO IS FALL.
GRAVITY DOES ALL THE WORK.
AND OF COURSE
YOU HAVE TO STAY LOOSE.
AND I'M REAL GOOD
AT STAYING LOOSE.
BOY, I TELL YOU WHAT,
IF I FELL OFF AN AIRPLANE,
I'D BE SO LOOSE
I'D COME UNDONE.
AH, YOU'D BE SURPRISED.
FALLING THOUSANDS OF
FEET IN A FEW SECONDS
CAN BE VERY RELAXING.
SOMETIMES I FALL ASLEEP
ON THE WAY DOWN.
YEAH, BUT, DWIGHT,
YOU HAVE A VERY LOW
DROWSE THRESHOLD.
I'VE SEEN YOU FALL
ASLEEP WATER-SKIING.
WELL, IT'S A LOT OF FUN.
WE HAVE A GREAT TIME.
WE? YOU MEAN YOU'RE
NOT THE ONLY WHACKO THAT
JUMPS OUT OF THAT PLANE?
OH, NO, JUNIOR, BUSTER,
STINKY AND I GO
EVERY OTHER SATURDAY.
OKAY, WELL,
YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
THAT'S A LITTLE
BIT DIFFERENT.
YEAH, THAT'S NOT SO CRAZY
BECAUSE IF YOU GET A BUNCH
OF GUYS TO GO WITH YOU,
IT'S MORE LIKE BONDING.
OKAY, WELL -- OKAY, WELL,
THERE'S OUR ANSWER.
OKAY, THIS VIEWER, IT'S GREAT
FOR YOU TO GO SKY-DIVING,
AS LONG AS YOU GET A BUNCH
OF GUYS TO GO WITH YOU.
YEAH, THAT SOUNDS
LIKE A GOOD IDEA.
YEAH, BUT YOU GOTTA GET
EVERYBODY TO CHECK WITH
THEIR WIVES FIRST
AND MAKE SURE
THAT IT'S OKAY.
IF THE WIVES SAY NO,
THE GUYS DON'T GO, RIGHT?
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
AND IF THE WIVES SAY YES,
I'D SAY ALL YOUR MARRIAGES
ARE IN TROUBLE.
OKAY, UH, LOOKS LIKE THIS IS
GONNA BE THE LAST YEAR
FOR THE CHAIN SAW RACES.
YOU KNOW, ORDINARILY WE
RUN JUST TWO AT A TIME,
LIKE IN HEATS.
BUT WE THOUGHT IT
WOULD BE A LOT SAFER
IF WE GOT IT OVER QUICKER,
SO WE JUST LET ALL THE
CHAIN SAWS GO AT ONCE.
AND, UH, WE WERE HALF RIGHT.
IT WAS QUICKER.
UNCLE RED!
[laughter]
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO TELL
THE PARENTS WHEN THEY ASK
WHY WERE THEIR CHILDREN BEING
CHASED BY CHAIN SAWS?
JUST TELL 'EM IT WAS PART
OF THE CAMP EXPERIENCE.
IT TAUGHT THEM ROCK CLIMBING
AND TREE SHINNYING.
OH! OH! OH!
UNCLE RED!
LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF HIS HEAD.
HE'S A GIFTED PERSON;
THESE ARE GIFTED CHILDREN.
WELL, THEN THEY SHOULD
BE SMART ENOUGH TO GET
OUT OF THE WAY.
[applause]
YOU KNOW --
HAROLD, LOOK, OKAY,
THE CHAIN SAW RACE,
IT WAS A DUMB THING, BUT WE'RE
NEVER GONNA DO IT AGAIN.
BUT YOU GOTTA ADMIT
IT WAS KINDA FUN, EH?
ISN'T THAT PART OF THE WHOLE
CAMP FEELING, HUH?
NO, NO, IT'S NOT.
TELL HIM, THORNTON.
THERE WE GO!
MR. GREEN.
THAT WAS SO COOL,
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME, HAROLD
AWAY YOU GO.
WOW! CAN I COME?
NO, NO,
NOW, THORNTON --
THORNTON, THERE ARE NO
INTELLIGENT PEOPLE
DOWN THERE.
IT'S BEST THAT I GO DOWN AND
YOU GO TO TO CHESS CLUB, OKAY?
GO TO CHESS CLUB.
audience: A-A-AH.
HEY, THORNTON,
THORNTON.
SO IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND YOU WERE DEAD RIGHT
ABOUT THE CHAIN SAW RACES.
WE'RE NEVER
DOING THAT AGAIN.
WE'RE GOING WITH
BELT SANDERS NEXT YEAR.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND THORNTON
AND WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
WHAT HE SAID.
[applause]
SIT DOWN.
COME TO ORDER.
HEY, GUYS, SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, IS THERE ANYBODY
WHO DIDN'T GET THEIR
CHAIN SAW BACK?
[chain saw running]
OKAY, THERE IT IS.