It's the New Red Green Show
Here is the man who wears
his heart on his sleeve
Right next to his ketchup and gravy stains.
Your hero, my uncle Red Green.
Thank you, appreciate it.
Well, today I'm going to do something, I
really enjoy
You going fishing knucklehead.
No, I'm going to Ross Perot's house for a
fondue party.
Of course I'm going fishing.
Going fishing for lake trout, tried to go
last Sunday,
so many fishermen out there had
to jump up and down the boat
just to get her to touch the water.
Well, that's because the church is closed.
Reverend Frank just closed up the church and
left town.
Why? Because if you ran out of sinners, you
can just come to the lodge.
No, no, no, no, no.
He just went looking for a bigger church,
you know, I guess he's paid on commission
Anyway, church is closed up and there's no
more Sunday services.
Not at all. No church on Sunday.
We've got to do something about that here.
Can't let that go.
Well, what do you care? You never went to
church anyway.
Well, no, no, it's not for me.
It's for the other people.
They've got to be in church on Sunday with
the fishes of men
so I can be out in the lake with
the fishes, a trout.
What you're looking at now is
a bunch of
segments from this particular show.
The main message being, for gosh sakes,
don't even think about changing the channel.
I'll tell you something you want to make
sense out of this program.
You've got to give it your undivided
attention.
Well, I thought we should place an ad for a
new reverend, but the want ads don't seem to
have a classification for religious leaders.
Maybe under business personals,
Maybe under sales or delivery services.
Are you dressed like that? Here are the
village people hiring roadies.
No, my Boy Scout troop is meeting
here tonight
Boy Scouts coming to Possum Lodge,
was there a badge for that like indoor
survival or something?
No, no, no. Normally we meet at the church,
right?
But ever since Reverend Frank took off after
a bigger flock of followers, church is
closed. So, you know, Possum Lodge is here,
the boy scouts there, I figured.
You know...
You can't be ringing Boy Scouts to the lodge
just because the reverend
got the flock out of here, Harold.
I don't think you want to get the Boy Scouts
upset, Uncle Red.
They have sharp little knives
and they know a lot of knots.
We got to get a new reverend.
I'm going to get that church back up.
You know what? Maybe a school bus will come
into town.
One of those ones all painted up with the
flower power and the peace signs and
catch on fire and melt.
How would that help?
That's how we got Reverend Frank.
A little bit later in the show,
Bill and Harold are going to pitch a tent.
Go camping, that kind of thing.
Two heads are better than one.
Not those heads, I would say.
What they're going to do now
is a little bit of a preview here of
what's going to happen later on.
Harold’s got the tent pegs in there.
I was smart enough to stay away from
this adventure and watch Bill.
Ok? Wow.
Getting out the big hammer there...
What do you think Harold.
Is this is a good idea?
You're going to hold it. Good idea?
What do you think? You're going to hold the
pegs?
Good idea?
You're fine. Gosh, come on.
Come on, come on.
Part of the ritual, part of the
addition of being a man up at the lodge, you
got to hold the tent pegs for Bill.
Watch out!
Oh, you’re fine.
You're good. You're good.
Uh oh.
You’re fine, you’re good.
More of that later.
All the grass is wet this morning.
It glitters in the sun.
It soaks my shoes.
It makes me news, as the wetness, the
moisture comes.
I check all the plumbing and for leaks in
the watering can.
But this H2O seems to flow through
the hole in the roof of my van.
Ok, this is for the big one.
For some of Buster Hadfield's famous chili
and a new set of seat covers,
Uncle Red, you have 30 seconds to get
Mr. Dalton Humphreys
of the Humphreys’s Everything Store to say
this word.
Teenager.
And go.
All right, Dalton. Less than 20 years old.
Good as new.
I'm talking about a person
who's less than 20 years old.
Punk.
Younger than 20 older than 12.
Shoplifter.
This is a general term like like your
daughter.
She's a...
Burden.
A terrible, terrible burden.
All right, all right, all right. She was an
infant, then she became a toddler,
then an adolescence, and now she's a...
Demon Satan's spawn devil worshiping...
Yes, yes, I know she acts that way,
but that's because she became this...
Fat.
We're almost out of time, almost out of time.
All right, Dolton...
To you,
this person gets away with murder.
O.J Simpson, O.J. Simpson!
This week on Hany man Corner, we're going to do something,
make a lot of you guys feel young and alive
that will make a lot of you guys feel
young and alive again,
because it's dangerous.
Now I don't mean dangerous to build.
All my projects are that way.
I'm talking about dangerous to use.
That's what gets the juices going.
You know, the adrenaline, the testosterone,
the hydrogen peroxide.
Now I'm sure that most of you know what
these units are here, but I'll tell you.
With the invention of the space age,
plastic and the know wax floors and
everything. These units have become kind of
a thing of the past, so you can get them real
cheap, like at a yard sale or even a dump.
You're going to need two of
them.
One for the left foot, one for the right
foot.
What are we going to make? How about
electric roller blades?
You know those young people today and the
dumb things they're doing?
Well, I think we're one step ahead on this
time.
All right. First thing you got to do is you
got to separate the head of the unit from the
handle and you might use one of these
lubricating sprays and just very careful
where you put it. There's sometimes a
little hidden nut or bolt in there, and this
will kind of dissolve the rest of them, just
loosen them up to where they'll just come
apart, just that much easier.
There we go.
Remember a few winters ago when
you said, boy, you know, I need a winter
activity. Actually, it's probably your wife
that said it or your doctor.
So you went out and you got yourself some
cross-country skiing.
They tried it once and it was fine.
Everything. Then you came to your senses and
bought a snowmobile.
Well, here's a good news.
You're actually going to be able to use
those cross-country skis now because what we
want to do is we want to take the bindings
off there and the boots off there and then
attach them to our four postures.
All right now, it's probably a probably a
Scandinavian bolt of some kind, but it could
be any kind of threat. All right, that's
fine.
It's fine. It's fine.
You don't have to feel bad about how about
doing that to the skis?
Because if you cut up the skiing, you
probably would have done this yourself and
probably done the same thing for your leg.
All right now, what you want to do is take
that on to the top of the floor polisher
using maybe a bolt in the washer or hey,
whatever you like.
There we go. Now, take a look at how this
works.
See there...
So you know what was on that, that the brush
goes in opposite directions? So that
means that once you got them on, you know,
the steering and the direction, it's a little
bit sensitive you got to maybe if you want
to go backwards, I I'd say, lean forward,
want to go forward. You lean backwards, you
want to go left, you lean right, you want to
go right, you lean left, hand up, sit down,
fight, fight, fight.
If you want to stop altogether, you would
lean all the way forward into what I believe
they call a face plant.
All right, we're all set.
Let's go rollerblading.
Now, obviously, you need a
portable source of electricity, so gotten a
hold of a bunch of the nine volt batteries.
There is no Walkman working within 50 miles
of the lodge right now.
And when you wire these up, this is very
important.
Make sure you have the same amount of
electricity going to each foot.
All right now, I'm ready to go rollerblading
electrically.
So remember, the women don't find you
handsome.
They should at least find a happy.
All right, there's been a technique involved.
Yes, I need a little more Polish.
Stay down and relax, whatever this is, we got
lots more of it.
I want to talk to you, older
guys about diet and exercise because you're
running like me. You plan to start
exercising first thing tomorrow morning or.
Next week or possibly the week after that,
but certainly by the end of the summer, of
course, it's all talk and no action.
And why is that? Because you got no
motivation.
I was looking at a thing in the paper here.
Some doctor has done a study on guys who've
had heart attacks and get this usually when a
guy has his first heart attack, you know
what he does.
He jumps up and he starts exercise.
Well, that's what they do do they get up
there and they get going.
There's no talk at all. It's all action and
why?
Of course, he's motivated at that point.
So don't you guys be beating yourself up
because you eat too much of the wrong stuff
or you smoke or you drink or whatever?
Once the old ticker gives you the, you know,
or they find a lump or there isn't supposed
to be one or the doctor holds up your X-ray
and goes, “uh-oh”.
Then by golly, you'll have all the
motivation you need.
Remember, I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
Well, I've already received a couple of
applications for a new reverend here for the
Possum Lake area. This one's even got a
picture in it.
Hi, I'm a sun worshipper.
I believe that God wants us all to be naked.
Not you. He doesn't sir.
Oh, sorry, ma'am. I was just going to say?
Pope Larry...
The high priest of the Incas
It’s me, Harold. We're having a Morris
dance group meeting here Tonight.
Oh, no, you're not Harold.
Yes we are.
Not dressed like that, you’re not.
There laws, OK?
Yes, there are. Yes, there are laws and
there's a municipal bylaw, the one that
granted you the lease of this land.
It stipulates you have to create space for
the community.
Since when?
It’s in the charter.
Well, nobody's ever come here before.
No kidding. Yeah, a choice between the church
and here.
Where would you go? Even the Satanists
prefer the church.
Who else has dibs on this place, Harold?
Well, anyone else who ever used a church like
the Floor Hockey League, the bingo?
Yeah, I've got to find a Reverend
Yay Yay Group is going to be here.
The Hymn and Howl Group, it's going to be
here.
All sorts thing. So we're going to have the...
The heck is this?
Man, that’s loud.
The Irish dancers are going to be here.
Yeah.
There’s going to be the
the Wine and Cheese Club...
Did I mention the Model Airplane Club?
No you didn’t, Harold.
And today we're going to hear
from Mr. Buzz Sherwood.
Hey, my name's Buzz.
Well, I went two weeks without acting like a
guy.
All right.
But it gets hard because, you know, it's,
you know, seat up before.
Put the seat down when you're done.
But last Sunday, I had a setback.
Ok? I was in the backyard.
I was putting this new gas barbecue together
and everything was just going great.
But then I couldn't figure out how to attach
the burner to the main unit, right?
And I just started acting like a guy.
I said, Well, there must be parts missing.
And then I went in and I got more tools, and
then and then I got the duct tape and I said,
Oh, just Jerry, rig this and make it work,
and then I'll just throw it in the garbage
and I'll just make one with my own bare
hands.
And then the woman that loves me, she said
she saved me with three little words...
Read the instructions.
The instructions, man, you know, like these
were like, these are like the extra cards you
get in the new deck, right? You throw them
out, or it's like the little piece of paper
you get a new pair of jeans, right, that
says inspected by number forty seven.
What was I talking about?
The instructions.
So I read them right and and I was doing it
wrong, and then I realized this piece of
paper made me realize I was a failure.
And then I thought, No, man, you're not a
failure.
No way you, you would have figured it out
eventually, right?
You didn't need to read the stupid
instructions.
You know, you would have you would have got
it.
And then I thought, Well, then reading the
instructions, you're not asking for help.
You're cheating.
I'm not a loser man.
I'm a cheater. I felt a lot better.
Meanwhile, back at the tent pegs, we're going
to finish up the adventures with Bill now,
and they're still working on that, working
on the windows around the lodge and this is
one of these new kind of tents.
They're going to put out Bill and they're
out here.
It's got kind of the progress isn't always a
good thing there anyway.
It's one of the I don't know what they call
them, umbrella tent or something like that.
Where the frames all on the outside, and
it's got a lot of spring to it.
A lot of spring there. Oh boy, oh my night
fell anyway.
And they go, and you know, this is one of
the great things I think about camping.
You don't want to get too big a tent because
part of the experience is the is the bonding
feeling that you get just by being in a
confined, you know, something you don't need.
What you find is there are certain things
that you take, you really don't need.
But you know, the point being that when you
get into one of them smaller tents there,
just maybe a one man tent and you get two
men in there and you don't need they don't
need as many things as you. Maybe you might
think that you do.
You find a good while you find that you get
into kind of a thing where you know, you get
to talk about
Things and just, oh my gosh.
What the heck?
What do you got in there, Boys?
Oh, oh, it's a boy.
All right. And then they can just lay back
there and see that that's kind of when they
can talk about things and just just have
that camaraderie that goes hand in hand with
camping, camping and now this.
Ok. All right. All right.
Ok, we have. Ok.
All right, Harold. There's a problem there.
You have what you have is what we like to
call a snorer. Also known as a
fist magnet. And in this case, Harold is going to
try and take a little more peaceful.
Shine alight his eyes.
One thing about Bill, when he's asleep, he
is asleep, and when he's awake, he's really
too much awake to what he's going to do
now, is realizing one of the things they
thrown out because the snorkel masks that.
So he just grabs the mask, putting that
someplace.
Apparently, if the end to interrupt the
breathing... What’s that there?
Some sort of a massive Rattler or something
there. Any way, if you interrupt the
breathing pattern, apparently you can.
There we go. Yeah, I just like that.
There you go. See you there. There's a
problem.
Well, what? All right.
Not perfect, not perfect.
Herald realizes that he's got
the snorkel, but the snorkel in the mouth
there, but he doesn't grab the snorkel, you
know, grabs the assistance in this case, a
snake, Harold, that's a snake.
Harold Harold is his name.
Yeah, yeah. Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, see. And the lamb lie down with the
lion and the bill.
Shall I download the ruler?
Here's a love letter to Harold from a lady
viewer.
Nice stationery.
And now for that part of the show where we
explore the three little words that men find
so difficult to say...
I don’t know.
So true.
Joining me Uncle Red in the expert portion
of the show is a brand new
person in the Possum Lake area, building a
cottage up here.
Ladies and gentlemen, successful businessman,
Mr. Kevin Black.
I chose this letter, especially for you,
Mr. Black
Dear experts.
I am a corporate executive in a large
metropolitan area, and I'm thinking about
buying a cottage up around Possum Lake.
How can I go about making a purchase?
Hang on one second, guys. Yeah, I think we
should probably just take that right to bed.
See how it creases the sheets.
All right.
Guys, right up front, what I'd like to say
is that I think a summer property is just a
fantastic idea.
I love this area.
I figure I'll get used to the people.
As a matter of fact, I recently purchased a
thousand acres of waterfront.
Yeah, Kevin, here about blood point.
Actually, it's called Bluff Point on the real
estate survey map.
Yeah. Well, the guy who did the map never
lived there.
How are the mosquitoes, Kevin?
Oh, they're fine. Fine, fine.
And I'm I'm told, of course, they're not
always this bad.
No, no. They're a lot worse than the spring.
Don't you listen to him, Mr. Black.
It’s a beautiful spot, you got out
there, nice cottage, you're building and
everything. Is that a swimming pool you're
putting in?
Oh no, Harold. No, no, it's not.
No, it's a tennis court and I'm building it
right in a stand of cedar trees.
Oh, that's a great idea.
You know, you might want to do with that,
Kevin, just a suggestion, of course, is but a
real fine mesh on the fence on that unit or
maybe a sign saying no mosquitoes.
That wouldn't work, would it?
What I think Mr. Black is saying to this
viewer is by all means, come on up the lake
and buy up the property, there's some
bargain prices here for you.
But let me give you a suggestion don't buy
vacant property, OK?
The community's been here one hundred and
fifty years.
If there's land up here that hasn't been
built on by now, usually a pretty good reason
for that. Here's what you want to do find
the oldest building in the area, something
that's been around here since day one
because they had every location to choose
from in those days. That's going to be the
place on the best spot.
But an offer in on that one?
Hey, surprisingly, that's pretty darn good
information.
Uncle Red.
Yes. And you know what? I'd be interested in
pursuing this.
I have a number of investors.
We could put together some kind of limited
partnership now.
What did you say was the oldest building
around here?
Well, the lodge.
Well, good news, just got off the phone with
Reverend Frank.
I figured he had a problem because he called
Collect, you know, it turns out he couldn't
get another job, you know, because the
churches are all cutting back with the
financial things and everything.
I guess they figure it’s cheaper
to let everyone go to hell.
So Reverend Frank is coming back and the
church is open for business.
What happened Harold? Bad reviews?
No bad reviews. We were dow
in the basement,
and we're rehearsing our Andrew Lloyd
Webber's version of Cats, you know...
Bunch of the lodge members thought it would be
funny to let their dogs down in their.
They went wild. The way dogs do. Wild.
I know what you’re saying.
Yeah, we can't do cats anymore.
We're going to do Les Misérable.
Wow. Everything you actors do is pretty misérable,
if you ask me. Oh there’s the meeting.
If you change your clothes and get down
there all the down a minute.
Do you want to clean up your
kitty litter here, Harold?
My wife is watching, I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting and in keeping with
this religious theme.
If you're in the mood to guide a lost soul
to a heavenly body, I'm your man.
Thanks for watching on behalf of
Harold and myself,
and the whole gang of here, inlcuding
Rum Dum Tigger
Keep your stick on the ice.
Harold, do you start off here?
Yes. I like to ask ther person
who stole all the duct tape from my
bedroom to
please raise their hand.
All right, then maybe the person who taped me
to the bed would raise their hand.