YOU KNOW NOTHING SAYS STATUS
THAN HAVING TWO CARS
ESPECIALLY IF THEY BOTH RUN.
AND WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
TO HAVE A PLACE TO STORE THEM,
EVEN IF ALL YOU HAD
WAS A SINGLE-CAR GARAGE?
WELL, ALL YOU NEED IS A
COUPLE OF PLAYGROUND
SLIDES LIKE THESE
AND TWO SECTIONS OF THOSE
ROLLER CONVEYER THINGS
THEY HAVE AT THE BEER STORE.
YOU JUST DRIVE UP SO THAT
YOUR OUTSIDE WHEELS GO
UP THE SLIDES,
AND LET GRAVITY
TAKE CARE OF THE REST.
OH, DON'T FORGET
TO FASTEN YOUR SEAT BELT.
AND YOU MIGHT WANT TO STOP AND
LET YOUR WIFE GET OUT FIRST.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
[  CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
GOT A BIT OF A PROBLEM
THIS WEEK AT THE LODGE.
THIS IS TODAY'S PAPER, THE
"POSSUM LAKE DAILY MOVEMENT."
[ LAUGHTER ]
LOT OF INTERESTING
STUFF IN HERE.
APPARENTLY THE BERLIN WALL
IS DOWN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
BUT LISTEN TO THIS.
POSSUM LAKE CITY COUNCIL
HAS PASSED A NEW BY-LAW
THAT SAYS THAT IT IS UNLAWFUL
FOR ANY LOCAL CLUB OR
ORGANIZATION OR LODGE
TO OPERATE WITHOUT A PERMIT.
THEY WON'T -- THEY'LL NEVER
GIVE US A PERMIT.
I MEAN, THIS IS THE BEGINNING
OF THE END RIGHT HERE.
WE NEED TO FIND SOMEBODY WHO
KNOWS HOW TO GET A LEGAL
LOOPHOLE GOING FOR US.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
SO PERFECT
TIMING, MIKE.
DID YOU HAPPEN TO SEE PAGE
FOUR OF TODAY'S PAPER?
YEAH, THE POSSUM LAKE
SUNSHINE GIRL.
WHOA!
OH, NO, THAT'S
AN ORNAMENTAL SHRUB.
OH.
I'M TALKING ABOUT CITY
COUNCIL PASSING
THAT BY-LAW.
THEY'RE TRYING TO
SHUT DOWN POSSUM LODGE.
WELL, HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
WELL, IT SAYS
RIGHT THERE
"THEY'RE TRYING TO SHUT
DOWN POSSUM LODGE."
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELL, LIKE, DOESN'T THE
LODGE HAVE HISTORICAL
VALUE OR ANYTHING?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, IT'S OLD.
IT SMELLS OLD.
YOU KNOW, THAT MAY
BE GOOD ENOUGH.
IT WORKS FOR SENATORS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHY?
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
WELL, IN THE HISTORIC
ERECTION PROVISION,
SUBSECTION "C," PART 14,
IT SAYS -- AND I QUOTE,
"CONSIDERATION MUST BE GIVEN
TO ERECTED STRUCTURES,
EDIFICES AND BUILDINGS
"WHICH HAVE STOOD
FOR 150 YEARS.
"EACH ERECTION MUST
BE ASSESSED BY A COMMITTEE
"TO ASSESS ITS
HISTORICAL VALUE.
"SUFFICIENT SIGNIFICANCE
SHALL RESULT
"IN PRESERVATION
OF SAID ERECTION."
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, UH, SO ALL WE HAVE
TO DO IS PROVE THE LODGE
IS AT LEAST
150 YEARS OLD.
HOW DO WE DO THAT?
WELL, WE COULD SHOW THEM
THE KITCHEN AND BATHROOM.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
THE PRIZE FOR TODAY'S
CONTEST IS...
A FREE NECK WADDLE REDUCTION
AT POSSUM LAKE'S FIRST AND ONLY
PLASTIC SURGERY CLINIC,
TUCK AND ROLL.
[ LAUGHTER ]
RED, YOU HAVE
30 SECONDS TO --
RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON HUMPHRIES TO
SAY THIS WORD HERE...
AND GO.
ALL RIGHT, DALTON, FOR A STORE
TO BE SUCCESSFUL IT HAS
TO HAVE GOOD...
SECURITY.
NO, THIS IS SOMETHING
ALL YOUR CUSTOMERS WANT.
REFUNDS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
NO, NO, SOMEBODY COMES
INTO YOUR STORE,
AND THEY CAN'T FIND
WHAT THEY'RE LOOKING FOR.
THEY NEED...
THEIR BRAIN EXAMINED.
WE HAVE EVERYTHING.
IT'S THE EVERYTHING STORE.
THAT'S WHY IT'S CALLED
HUMPHRIES' EVERYTHING STORE
BECAUSE WE
HAVE EVERYTHING.
ALL RIGHT, BUT YOU KNOW,
I'M THINKING MAYBE THIS IS
ONE THING YOU DON'T HAVE.
REPEAT CUSTOMERS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
COME ON, GUYS.
TIME, TIME, TIME.
OKAY, YOU KNOW, SOMEBODY
COMES INTO YOUR STORE,
EVEN THOUGH THEY'RE NOT
BUYING ANYTHING,
AND YOU GIVE THEM...
A COLD STARE.
ALL RIGHT, DALTON, WHAT BUGS
YOU THE MOST ABOUT OWNING
THE STORE?
ALL OF IT.
I HATE ALL OF IT.
WELL, WHY THE HECK DID YOU
OPEN THE STORE IN THE
FIRST PLACE?
BECAUSE MY DAD LEFT IT
TO ME IN HIS WILL.
OF COURSE, I DIDN'T FIND OUT
ABOUT IT UNTIL THE FUNERAL
SERVICE, FOR CRYING OUT --
[ BELL RINGING ]
HI, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE OF
ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND SEPTIC
SUCKING SERVICES.
IF IT'S BURNING YOUR NOSE
AND CURLING YOUR TOES
AND CHANGING THE FLAME
ON YOUR CANDLE,
YOU'RE NOT LESS OF A MAN,
ASK FOR A HAND
'CAUSE YOU'VE GOT MORE ON
YOUR PLATE THAN YOU CAN HANDLE.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU MAY HAVE NOTICED THAT THE
REEL ON THIS FISHING ROD
HAS HAD SOME
FUNCTIONALITY PROBLEMS
IN THE AREA OF MANAGING THE
WINDING IN AND OUT OF THE
FISHING LINE,
WHICH REALLY IS THE SOLE
PURPOSE OF ITS EXISTENCE.
NOW, A YOUNGER MAN MIGHT TAKE
ALL THAT TANGLED LINE OFF THERE
AND REWIND IT ON PROPERLY,
BUT AT MY AGE,
I DON'T HAVE THE TIME
OR THE VOCABULARY
TO GET THROUGH THAT
MUCH FRUSTRATION.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN THIS
FISHING ROD IS USELESS.
IF WE THREW THINGS OUT JUST
BECAUSE THEY NO LONGER
DID THE JOB
THEY WERE ORIGINALLY
INTENDED TO DO,
BERNICE WOULD STICK ME OUT
AT THE END OF THE LANE
ON GARBAGE DAY.
NO, SIR.
WE'RE GONNA GIVE THIS
FISHING ROD A WHOLE NEW LIFE.
TAKING OUR INSPIRATION FROM THE
TECHNOLOGY OF THE WEED WHACKER,
WE'RE GONNA MAKE
A HEDGE WHACKER.
ALL'S YOU NEED IS A
FISHING ROD, A CORDLESS DRILL
AND A PAIR OF ROLLER BLADES
MAYBE YOUR KIDS GAVE YOU TO
SPEED UP THE INHERITANCE.
TO START OFF YOU WANT TO
ATTACH THE DRILL TO ONE
OF YOUR ROLLER BLADES,
USING THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
OKAY, THAT'S OUR BASIC HEDGE
WHACKER CONFIGURATION.
NOW, THE DRILL WILL SPIN
THE FISHING ROD,
AND THE ROLLER BLADES
WILL ALLOW THE WHOLE UNIT
TO RUN SMOOTHLY
ALONG THE GROUND.
NOW WHAT YOU WANNA DO IS ADD
A CHUNK OF FISHING LINE
AS YOUR CUTTER.
YOU CAN USE WHATEVER
STRENGTH OF LINE YOU WANT,
DEPENDING ON THE HEDGE
YOU'RE CUTTING.
I'D SAY WITH A CHINESE ELM,
GO WITH A 40-POUND TEST.
AND I'M USING
A FOUR-FOOT LENGTH
SO I'LL BE ABLE TO
CUT THE WHOLE HEDGE
IN ONE PASS.
NOW, TO GET THE
CENTRIFUGAL FORCE GOING,
YOU MIGHT WANNA ADD A COUPLE
OF LEAD SINKERS TO ONE END
OF THE LINE.
I'D SAY REALLY CRIMP
THOSE BABIES ON THERE,
'CAUSE IF THEY COME OFF AT
100 MILES PER HOUR,
YOU'LL NEVER FIND 'EM.
NOW YOU ATTACH THE OTHER END OF
THE LINE TO ONE OF THE GUIDES
ON THE FISHING ROD.
YOU GOT SEVERAL HEIGHTS
TO CHOOSE FROM,
DEPENDING ON HOW HIGH
YOU WANNA CUT YOUR HEDGE.
YOU GOT LOW, YOU GOT MEDIUM.
I'M GONNA GO
WITH EYEBALL HEIGHT.
I RECOMMEND
SAFETY GLASSES FIRST.
OKAY, WE'RE ALL SET TO GO,
AND HERE'S A
LITTLE EXTRA BONUS.
I RAN A LONG LENGTH
OF FISHING LINE
DOWN TO THE FAR END
OF THE HEDGE.
TIED HER OFF THERE.
AND ON THIS END
I'VE GOT A FISH HOOK,
WHICH I JUST PUT INTO
THE LOWEST ROD GUIDE.
NOW WHEN THE ROD TURNS
INSIDE THE DRILL, SEE,
THE LINE WINDS UP, AND
IT PULLS THE WHOLE UNIT
THE WHOLE LENGTH
OF THE HEDGE.
IS THAT GREAT OR WHAT?
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
LET'S GIVE HER A TRY.
JUST LOCK THE DRILL
IN THE 'ON' POSITION,
AND STAND BACK,
STAND WELL BACK.
I GOT A LETTER FROM A VIEWER.
SEEMED LIKE A NICE FELLA.
SAID HE'S NEVER
MISSED AN EPISODE.
HE WANTED ME TO DO ONE OF THESE
TALKS ABOUT MEMORY LOSS.
I DIDN'T HAVE
THE HEART TO TELL HIM
I'VE DONE THREE OR FOUR
OF 'EM ALREADY.
SO HERE GOES ANOTHER ONE.
APPARENTLY,
DOING CROSSWORD PUZZLES
WILL PREVENT MEMORY LOSS.
I HEARD THAT SOMEWHERE.
CAN'T REMEMBER WHERE.
ANYWAY, I THOUGHT I'D
GIVE IT A TRY.
SO LAST NIGHT, BERNICE WAS
GONNA BE HOME A BIT LATE.
SHE ASKED ME TO PUT
THE POTATOES ON TO BOIL
BEFORE SHE GOT THERE.
SO I DID THAT, THEN I
WENT INTO THE LIVING ROOM
AND STARTED ON
A CROSSWORD PUZZLE.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW, I'M KINDA
GAZING OFF THINKING,
BOY, I USED TO KNOW THAT WORD.
THEN I HEARD THE SMOKE ALARM
GO OFF IN THE KITCHEN.
THEN I REALISED THAT CROSSWORDS
DON'T PREVENT MEMORY LOSS,
THEY CONFIRM IT.
SO I SAY DON'T WORRY
ABOUT YOUR MEMORY.
AS LONG AS YOU HAVE A
WALLET AND A TACKLE BOX,
ANYTHING YOU WANT YOU
CAN EITHER BUY OR FISH FOR.
AND THE ONLY WORD
YOU NEED TO REMEMBER
ARE THE ONES YOU USE
TO EXPLAIN TO YOUR WIFE
HOW YOU BURNED HER
BEST POT BOILING POTATOES.
AND THOSE WORDS ARE,
"THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR ASKING ME TO COOK."
AND THERE'S ONE OTHER THING
YOU NEED TO REMEMBER...
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
HI, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
CALL ME WHEN YOUR BUSINESS
ISN'T GOING DOWN THE DRAIN.
WELL, WE'RE STILL TRYING
TO PROVE THE LODGE
IS OLD ENOUGH
TO AVOID THE
WRECKING BALL.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK OFFERED
TO HELP US OUT.
HE SAYS HE REMEMBERS
COMING TO THE LODGE
WHEN HE WAS JUST
A LITTLE KID.
HE'S NOT VERY
CONVINCING, THOUGH,
BECAUSE HE SAYS AT
THE TIME HE WAS
A LITTLE GIRL.
SO INSTEAD, WE'RE GONNA
TAKE SOME ARTIFACTS
DOWN THERE.
I'VE GOT THE ORIGINAL
POSSUM LODGE MAIL BOX.
I FIGURE THE DATES
ON SOME OF THESE BILLS
MIGHT PROVE
SHE'S KINDA OLD.
I DON'T THINK THEY
GO BACK FAR ENOUGH.
BUT THIS LOG
MIGHT DO THE TRICK.
I PULLED IT OUT
OF THE LODGE FOUNDATION.
IT GOES
BACK A WHILE.
WOW.
THAT'S PRETTY SPONGY.
YEAH, IT TAKES A LONG TIME
TO GET THAT ROTTEN.
THEY USED TO SAY THAT
ABOUT MY GRANDFATHER.
WAIT A MINUTE,
ISN'T THERE A KIND OF
ULTRA-VIOLET SCANNER
THEY PUT ON THINGS TO
TELL HOW OLD THEY ARE?
HEY, THAT'S RIGHT!
THE LOCAL COPS HAVE GOT ONE.
I ALWAYS WANTED TO TRY IT
OUT ON TINA TURNER.
WHY DON'T WE JUST GET
THE OLDEST THING
AT THE LODGE
AND TAKE IT DOWN THERE
AND GET IT TESTED?
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
WHAT'S THE OLDEST
PART OF THE LODGE?
WELL, I WOULD SAY
THE FRONT DOOR.
WHERE'S THE FRONT DOOR?
IT'S AT THE BACK.
OH.
RED! RED GREEN!
WELCOME.
YOU ARE WELCOME HERE, SIR.
YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
I BROUGHT YOU
A NEWSPAPER.
OH, FOR THE
HAMSTER CAGE, HUH?
WELL, THANKS ANYWAY,
BUT HOWARD DIDN'T
HAVE A VERY GOOD WEEK.
OH, NO, YOU DIDN'T
EAT HIM, DID YOU, GORD?
NO, I LET HIM OUT
OF HIS CAGE
SO THAT HE COULD
PLAY AROUND A BIT.
THEN I PUT HIM ON
TOP OF THE RAILING
SO HE COULD SEE
THE FOREST BETTER,
AND --
I GUESS HE MUST
HAVE SLIPPED.
HAMSTERS CAN'T FLY,
CAN THEY?
HE DID FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, GORD.
OKAY, WELL, CHEER UP.
ACTUALLY, THAT'S NOT
WHAT THE NEWSPAPER'S FOR.
NO?
NO. NO.
UH, DO YOU KNOW WHAT
PERSONAL ADs ARE, GORD?
OH, BOY, YEAH.
WHOA!
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
OKAY --
PERSONAL ADs ARE A
WAY TO USE THE NEWSPAPER
TO MEET WOMEN.
I'M LOVING THIS ALREADY.
SEE WHAT IT SAYS THERE?
"SINGLE WOMEN
SEEKING SINGLE MEN."
HOW DO I MEET
THESE WOMEN?
WELL, NO, YOU DON'T WANT
TO MEET JUST ANY WOMAN.
OH, YES, I DO.
YOU WANNA FIND THAT ONE
SPECIAL WOMAN TO BOND WITH.
BOND!
IS THAT WHAT THEY'RE
CALLING IT NOWADAYS?
GUESS I'VE BEEN
OUT OF TOUCH, HUH?
WELL, YEAH, YOU HAVE.
BUT YOU'VE GOTTA THINK
ABOUT WHAT KIND OF
WOMAN DO YOU LIKE?
OH, WELL, LET ME SEE.
UH, AGE IS IMPORTANT.
SHE HAS TO BE OVER 21
AND UNDER 100.
UH, OH, SHE CAN'T
BE AFRAID OF HEIGHTS.
AND, UH, NO,
I GUESS THAT'S ABOUT IT.
SO HOW DO I
MEET THESE WOMEN?
WELL, I GUESS YOU JUST PHONE
UP THE ONES WHO PUT THEIR
NUMBERS ON THEIR ADs.
REALLY?
YEAH.
I'D TALK TO A REAL,
LIVE WOMAN,
NOT A RECORDING?
I'D SAY, HELLO,
THIS IS RANGER GORD.
I WAS JUST WONDERING IF WE
COULD GET MARRIED SOME TIME.
UM, YOU MIGHT WANT TO
LET THEM DO THE TALKING.
YEAH, YOU'RE PROBABLY RIGHT.
PLAY HARD TO GET, HUH?
I'M NOT SURE I WANT TO GET
MARRIED AND SETTLE DOWN ANYWAYS.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW, THEY'D BE
ASKING ME TO GET RID OF MY
IMAGINARY GIRLFRIENDS.
OH, LIKE, AS IF.
UH, YOU KNOW, GORD, THIS MIGHT
BE A BETTER AD FOR YOU.
"HAMSTER, FREE TO GOOD HOME."
WHAT'S THE NUMBER?
GIVE ME THE NUMBER.
Red: WINSTON AND WALTER
CALLED ME OUT TO THE
BASEBALL DIAMOND.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT THEY WANTED
THEY WERE GONNA SET UP
A HOME RUN CONTEST
BETWEEN THE TWO OF 'EM.
PRETTY AMBITIOUS SCHEDULE,
I WOULD SAY,
IF YOU'RE GONNA GET
THAT MANY HOME RUNS.
I GOTTA BE HOME BY CHRISTMAS.
THEY WANTED ME TO BE THE JUDGE
STAND OUT BY THE FENCE.
CATCH ANY
ERRANT BALLS, I GUESS.
OH, THEY'RE GONNA FLIP A COIN
WINSTON WANTED TO FLIP A COIN
AND SEE WHO WOULD GO FIRST.
SO I SAID, "FINE."
WALTER GOES FIRST.
TAKE THE SIGN OUT WITH ME.
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON,
YOU'RE PITCHING.
OUT YOU GO.
AND I GET MYSELF
SET UP BY THE FENCE THERE.
IT'S JUST A NORMAL REASONABLE
SIZED BALL DIAMOND.
AND I'M ALL SET.
AND LET'S GET HER GOING.
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON,
FIRE HIM THE FIRST PITCH.
LET'S GET THIS GOING.
HE'S OUT THERE ON THE MOUND,
LOOKING FOR THE SIGN,
OF WHICH THERE IS NONE.
CAN WE PICK THIS
UP A BIT, BOYS?
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
HE LOOKS READY.
NOT YET.
ALL RIGHT, HE'S READY.
NO!
ALL RIGHT, OKAY, OKAY.
NO, JUST A MINUTE.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, TIME OUT.
TIME OUT.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT IN THERE?
SENSING YOUR LIFE IS GOING BY
JUST A BIT TOO SLOWLY?
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
FIRE IT IN THERE, WINSTON.
FIRE IT IN.
THROW THE BALL.
ALL RIGHT, HE'S READY.
FIRE IT IN.
OH, THE OL' SPITBALL.
MAN, THIS COULD GET UGLY.
ALL RIGHT, FIRE IT IN.
FIRE IT IN.
HERE SHE COMES.
AND --
OH, TOO MUCH SPIT.
YOU DO WHAT YOU
GOTTA DO, YOU KNOW?
THIS IS GONNA BE A WHILE.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
HERE WE GO.
AN-N-ND...
THERE IT IS.
OH, HIYA!
AND A LITTLE BIT
LATE ON THAT ONE.
THAT'S ONE OUT.
YEAH, OKAY.
HE GETS THE THREE OUTS
ON THIS, I BELIEVE.
AND HE --
WHAT'S THAT?
OH, HE DOESN'T LIKE --
OH, IT'S THE BAT.
THE BAT'S TOO HEAVY.
GET A LIGHTER BAT.
SPEED HIM UP A BIT.
IS THAT ONE GOOD?
THAT'S GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
HE'S READY.
LET'S GO.
HERE WE GO.
HE'S READY.
LET'S GO.
OKAY, THROW IT IN.
OKAY, HE'S READY.
HE'S READY.
LET HER RIP.
CHECK FIRST.
THERE'S NOBODY THERE!
WOULD YOU JUST THROW THE --
THERE WE GO, AND, OH!
THAT'S GOTTA HURT.
[ RED CHUCKLING ]
THAT'S RIGHT.
TWO OUT.
TWO OUT,
ONE MORE TO GO.
NO HOME RUNS FOR WALTER.
OH, YEAH.
OH, WHO COULD BLAME ME?
OH, A LITTLE
DIFFERENT APPROACH.
THAT SHOULD COVER THE ENTIRE
STRIKE ZONE, I WOULD THINK.
YES, HE GOT IT.
HE GOT IT!
IT'S GOIN' --
THAT COULD BE --
NO.
OKAY, I BELIEVE
THAT IS THE THIRD,
AND YOU'RE OUTTA THERE.
NOW, WINSTON, LET'S SEE
WHAT YOU CAN DO WITH IT.
OKAY, WALTER, GRAB THE BALL.
FIRE IT IN AT HIM.
[ SNORING ]
I HAD LOST ALL MY INTEREST IN
WHAT THEY WERE DOING HERE.
WINSTON'S ALL SET, AND HE'S
A STRONG LITTLE FELLA.
SO LET'S SEE --
OH, BOY.
AND, AND --
OH!
MAN, HE GOT --
OH, THAT --
IT COULD BE.
OH! OH!
THAT'S A HOME RUN!
WELL, WINSTON, YOU WIN.
YOU KNOW ANYBODY WHO COMMUTES
TO WORK ON A REGULAR BASIS
KNOWS JUST HOW GREAT IT
WOULD BE IF YOU COULD GET
JUST A LITTLE MORE SLEEP.
EVEN AN EXTRA 10 OR 15
MINUTES OF SHUT-EYE
WOULD MEAN THAT YOU
WOULDN'T HAVE TO DO
SO MUCH OF YOUR SLEEPING
WHILE YOU WERE
IN TRAFFIC OR AT WORK.
THINK ABOUT THIS.
INSTEAD OF HAVING TO GET
UP EARLY TO MAKE YOUR
COFFEE AT HOME,
OR ALLOWING TIME TO STOP
AT THE BUSY DRIVE-THRU,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW YOU
CAN MAKE YOUR OWN COFFEE
WHILE YOU'RE ON
YOUR WAY TO WORK.
YOU TAKE AN OLD KETTLE,
AND YOU MOUNT A SPARK
PLUG IN THE SIDE
AND A THERMOSTAT AND A SPOUT
IN THE BOTTOM OF HER THERE,
AND YOU HANG THE WHOLE
UNIT FROM YOUR SUN VISOR.
THEN YOU PULL ONE OF THE
IGNITION WIRES OFF YOUR ENGINE.
YOU RUN THAT UP
TO THE SPARK PLUG.
OH, SURE, SHE'LL RUN
A BIT ROUGH,
BUT YOU GET USED TO IT.
AND NOW WHAT HAPPENS IS THE
SPARK PLUG HEATS UP THE WATER,
AND ONCE THE
WATER GETS HOT ENOUGH,
THAT'LL OPEN THE THERMOSTAT.
LET'S THE HOT WATER FLOW DOWN
INTO THIS OIL FUNNEL,
WHICH IS LINED WITH
A NUMBER 10 COFFEE FILTER.
NOW YOU JUST FILL HER UP WITH
YOUR FAVOURITE BLEND,
BY GOLLY, YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY.
AND YOU'LL SEE I'VE GOT THE
OTHER END OF THE FUNNEL
POSITIONED OVER MY COFFEE MUG,
WHICH IS MOUNTED
IN THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON CUP HOLDER.
OF COURSE, YOU HAVE ALL THIS
PRE-SET THE NIGHT BEFORE
SO YOU CAN SLEEP IN THAT EXTRA
LITTLE BIT IN THE MORNING.
YOU COME IN AND YOU PULL
OUT OF THE DRIVEWAY,
AND AS SOON AS
THE ENGINE WARMS UP --
YOU CAN WAKE UP
TO THE SMELL OF COFFEE.
AND A COUPLE
OF MINUTES LATER,
YOU'LL BE ENJOYING
A FRESH CUP OF JOE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
HI, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
WE WANT YOUR BUSINESS,
AND WE'LL COME RIGHT TO YOUR
BACKYARD TO GET IT.
YOU'VE DONE SOMETHING
REALLY STUPID.
COULD BE THE WORST
STUNT YOU'VE EVER PULLED.
AND YOU KNOW THAT BECAUSE
IT'S SO QUIET AT HOME
YOU CAN HEAR YOUR STUFF
BEING TOSSED OUT ONTO
THE CEDAR HEDGE.
YOU'RE IN TROUBLE,
ALL RIGHT.
TROUBLE IS,
YOU DON'T KNOW WHY.
THE INFORMATION YOU SO
DESPERATELY SEEK
IS BEING DOLED OUT ON A
NEED-TO-KNOW BASIS.
AND IT GOES
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
"WRONG? WHAT MAKES YOU
THINK ANYTHING IS WRONG?"
OR "IF YOU NEED TO ASK,
I'M NOT GONNA TELL YOU!"
SEE, YOU
JUST CAN'T ASK.
WELL,
THAT'D BE SUICIDE
BECAUSE YOU'RE
ALREADY SUPPOSED TO KNOW.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
YOU ARE A GUERRILLA
IN A BORDER SKIRMISH
THAT'S BEEN GOING ON
SINCE YOU GOT MARRIED,
SO YOU DO WHAT
A SOLDIER DOES BEST.
YOU WAIT.
YOU STAND LOOSELY
AT ATTENTION
AND PRAY THAT THE BIG ARTILLERY
DOESN'T REACH THE FRONT.
SHOW NO FEAR!
MAINTAIN A
NON-AGGRESSIVE STANCE.
DO NOT, UNDER ANY
CIRCUMSTANCES,
QUESTION
THE COMMANDER.
YOU'LL BE ISSUED
NEW ORDERS SOON.
UNTIL THEN,
BE PREPARED
TO SURRENDER
AND STAND AT EASE
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE.
AND DO NOT THINK
ABOUT AN ATTACK.
YOUR REAR FLANK
IS FAR TOO EXPOSED.
DON'T THANK US.
THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS
ARE FOR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD
NEVER LOSE FAITH.
WHENEVER THE LORD
CLOSES A WINDOW,
HE'LL OFTEN BLOW OFF
A FRONT DOOR.
WELL, WE HAD THE
DOOR ANALYSED,
HOPING WE COULD SAVE
THE LODGE FROM BEING
TORN DOWN.
YEAH, HAD A COMPLETE
CHEMICAL EVALUATION.
TURNS OUT THE DOOR
ONLY DATES BACK TO 1952.
THEY DIDN'T EVEN GET
THAT FROM THE TEST.
THE PRICE TAG
WAS STILL ON THE DOOR.
SAID POSSUM LAKE LUMBER, 1952.
I PHONED OVER TO
MAKE SURE THAT WAS THE DATE
NOT JUST THE PRICE.
IT WAS THE DATE.
YEAH, WE STILL
OWE THEM THE PRICE.
BUT HERE'S
THE GOOD NEWS.
THE CHEMICAL ANALYSIS SHOWED
THAT THE LODGE IS FULL OF
ASBESTOS
AND P.C.B.s AND CARCINOGENS THEY
HADN'T EVEN THOUGHT OF YET.
IF THEY TEAR THE LODGE DOWN,
ALL THAT STUFF
GOES INTO THE GROUND.
IT'LL BE AN
ENVIRONMENTAL DISASTER.
SO CITY COUNCIL RULED TO
PRESERVE THE LODGE
BECAUSE IT'D BE TOO
DANGEROUS TO WRECK IT.
IS THIS OUR
LUCKY DAY, OR WHAT?
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, MEETING TIME,
Mr GREEN.
YOU GO AHEAD, MIKE.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
SHOULD I TAKE
THIS AS A DOOR PRIZE?
NO. NO.
WELL, THAT'S IT FOR
OUR SHOW --
DON'T SLAM THE DOOR.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I KIND OF LEARNED THAT
WE HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF
THE OLD THINGS.
WE'VE GOT TO
TREASURE OUR ANTIQUES,
ESPECIALLY IF
THEY'RE EACH OTHER,
SO I'LL BE COMING HOME TONIGHT
WITH THE FURNITURE OIL.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND THE
WHOLE GANG UP HERE AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
SIT. SIT. SIT.
SIT. SIT.
EVERYONE SIT.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
Red: ALL RIGHT, MEN, YOU KNOW
HOW WE'VE ALWAYS WONDERED
WHAT YEAR OLD MAN
SEDGWICK WAS BORN?
WELL, WE TOOK HIM DOWN,
AND WE HAD HIM TESTED
ON THIS SPECIAL
PIECE OF EQUIPMENT.
AND THEY'VE
NARROWED IT DOWN TO
SOME TIME DURING
THE MESOZOIC ERA.