[sounds of construction]
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
IF YOU GO OUT
IN THE WOODS TODAY
YOU'RE IN
FOR A BIG SURPRISE
HERE'S THE MAN WHO TURNED
THAT SONG INTO A WARNING,
MY UNCLE, YOUR HOST, RED GREEN!
[applause]
[cheering and whistling]
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE YOUR COMING HERE.
HAD A LITTLE ACCIDENT
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
JUNIOR SINGLETON BLEW THE ROOF
RIGHT OFF HIS GARAGE.
YEAH, BUT HE LEARNED SOMETHING.
YOU NEVER JUMP-START
A BARBECUE.
AND LUCKILY, YOU KNOW,
THE ROOF LANDED
COMPLETELY INTACT --
UPSIDE DOWN, OF COURSE --
IN POSSUM LAKE.
HERE'S THE KICKER --
SHE FLOATS.
SO GET THIS, RIGHT?
BECAUSE THE ROOF IS THE ONLY
THING THE LODGE MEMBERS HAVE
THAT DOESN'T LEAK,
INCLUDING THEMSELVES,
THEY'RE TURNING IT
INTO A BOAT.
NOT JUST ANY BOAT --
A FAN-BOAT.
WE'VE MOUNTED A DODGE
SLANT-SIX ON THE BACK.
GOT A HELICOPTER ROTOR ON
VERTICALLY.
PUT THE UNIT IN WHERE THE
EAVESTROUGH JOINS THE SOFFIT --
WHERE THE BIRD'S NEST WAS.
WE'RE GONNA TRY IT NOW,
SO STAY TUNED.
YOU CAN WATCH IT ON TELEVISION
OR GO TO OUR HOSPITAL
AND MEET THE GUYS IN AN HOUR.
[Horns honking]
[Geese honking]
[Quacking]
[Red]: TODAY'S SHOW'S
ABOUT INSECTS.
I'LL MAKE A BUG REPELLER.
RANGER GORD
IS GONNA BE TAGGING HOUSEFLIES.
HAROLD'S GONNA BE BUGGING
EVERYBODY, INCLUDING DOUGIE,
AND I'LL SHOW YOU HOW
TO DEAL WITH INSECTICIDE.
YOU HEARD OF MURPHY'S LAW?
THIS PLACE SHOULD BE CALLED
MURPHY'S LODGE.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO PAY
FOR THAT STATUE, YOU KNOW.
OH, HAROLD.
THEY GO TO START THAT MOTOR
ON THE HELICOPTER THING,
BUT THE FAN-BOAT
DIDN'T GO ANYWHERE,
'CAUSE IT NEVER WAS FLOATING.
IT WAS WEDGED ON A SANDBAR!
HAROLD, HAROLD.
I'LL TELL THE STORY.
MOOSE THOMPSON FIGURES
IT NEEDS MORE GAS,
SO HE GIVES IT MORE THROTTLE
AND MORE THROTTLE...
AND... MORE THROTTLE.
THAT'S CLEVER, ISN'T IT?
IF SOMETHING'S GONNA GO WRONG,
LET'S HAVE IT HAPPEN
AT MAXIMUM VELOCITY.
EXACTLY -- THE FAN-BOAT
STILL DOESN'T MOVE.
THE BACKWASH FROM THE PROP
WHIPS ACROSS TOWN,
LIFTS THE BILLBOARD
RIGHT OFF THE MAIN HIGHWAY.
THIS PICTURE OF A SMILING COW
ON A UNICYCLE
IS FLYING THROUGH THE SKY.
THAT'S NOT GONNA SELL
MUCH MILK.
NO.
SUDDENLY, BOOM! LANDS
IN THE CENTRE OF TOWN.
FLATTENED THE STATUE
OF SOME GUY.
THAT'S NOT "SOME GUY".
THAT'S EZRA BANGER.
HE'S THE FIRST CITIZEN
IN POSSUM LAKE
TO WANGLE A GOVERNMENT GRANT.
HE GOT $35 TO KILL MOSQUITOES
WITH A HAMMER.
YEAH, BUT YOU SAID
THE FAN-BOAT WOULD WORK
AND IT DIDN'T, SO
YOU MADE A MISTAKE
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU DID SOMETHING STUPID.
NOW YOU GOTTA PAY.
YOU MADE A MISTAKE
ALL RIGHT, FINE, I ADMIT IT.
I MADE A MISTAKE,
BUT SO DID YOUR PARENTS.
YOU MADE
A MISTAKE
HAROLD, I'M ARMED.
[Red]: BILL ASKED ME
TO GIVE HIM A HAND
GETTING THIS CAR GOING.
FIRST PROBLEM IS
HE'S LOCKED HIMSELF OUT.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
OH, HE'S GOT A COAT HANGER.
JUST HAVING COME OUT
OF A CLOSET RECENTLY,
HE'S STILL GOT THE HANGER
IN HIS SWEATER.
I NOTICE THAT
THE PASSENGER DOOR
IS, UH... THAT, TO ME,
SEEMED EASIER.
WHY DON'T WE GET IN THERE
AND SLIDE OVER?
YOU DON'T NEED THE COAT HANGER.
BILL? BILL? BILL?
HEY, BILL!
BILL, YOU'RE NOT-- BILL!
OW!
STOP! I'M-- BILL!
I'M IN THE-- BILL, I'M IN--
COME HERE -- I WANT
TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
HEY, LOOK AT THIS, BILL.
THE DOOR'S
ACTUALLY OPEN -- LOOK.
OHHHHH!
SEE? GOT HER
COMPLETELY UNLOCKED.
COME HERE A MINUTE.
YOU'LL SEE -- TAKE A LOOK.
SEE? OH!
WE'LL GET IT STARTED LATER ON.
THEY TELL ME
THIS IS THE BIG ONE.
FOR THE GRAND PRIZE
OF AN '82 LADA
AND FOUR SETS OF JUMPER CABLES,
HAROLD, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET DOUGIE FRANKLIN
TO SAY THIS WORD.
AND GO.
UH... UH... D-D-DECEIVE.
... THE BOSS.
UH, MISLEAD?
ADVERTISE?
ALL RIGHT, UH...
OK, ALL RIGHT,
IF YOU LOOKED AT THIS CARD NOW,
THAT
WOULD BE...
... FASTER.
[audience laughing]
YES, BUT YOU'D BE DISQUALIFIED
BECAUSE YOU...
... GOT CAUGHT.
MMMMM!
UH, OK, ALL RIGHT.
Y-Y-YOU DEBUNK SOMEBODY,
YOU STACK THE DECK,
Y-Y-YOU, UH...
Y-Y-YOU... FRAUD,
UH, THAT'S...
THAT'S...
BUSINESS.
OHHHH!
BUT IF SOMEBODY DOES THAT
TO YOU...
THEY'RE A
DIRTY CHEAT.
THERE YOU GO, HAROLD.
[ringing bell]
[applause]
BUTTONS WERE FLYING
EVERYWHERE
A BELT BUCKLE BOUNCED
OFF THE MAT
A ZIPPER RICOCHETED
OFF THE FISHBOWL
SUSPENDERS SPRANG
AT THE CAT
THERE'S A LESSON
TO BE LEARNED HERE
YOU MIGHT WANT
TO TAKE DOWN A NOTE
YOU CAN HAVE EXTRA HELPINGS
OR BEND OVER
BUT YOU OBVIOUSLY
CAN'T DO BOTH
YOU KNOW, HEARING HOW
EZRA BANGER GOT HIMSELF
HIS OWN STATUE
JUST FOR KILLING MOSQUITOES
HAS ME THINKING
THAT IF A PERSON FOUND
A BETTER WAY TO KILL BUGS,
THEY COULD NOT ONLY GET RICH,
THEY'D GET MORE DATES.
I THOUGHT I'D TAKE THIS WEEK'S
"HANDYMAN CORNER"...
SHOW YOU HOW YOU CAN TELL
THE INSECTS TO BUG OFF.
ALL RIGHT, THIS THING IS CALLED
A FOGGING MACHINE.
HOPE THAT CAME OUT RIGHT.
THE WAY THAT WORKS IS
YOU FILL HER FULL OF PESTICIDE
AND THEN YOU BLAST OUT
THIS TOXIC CRAP,
KILLING ALL THE MOSQUITOES.
IF YOU KILL ALL THE MOSQUITOES
IN YOUR AREA,
YOU'RE GONNA TAKE OUT
EVERY OTHER FORM OF LIFE.
INSTEAD OF THAT, I SAY
WE JUST... [coughing]...
WE CONCENTRATE ON MOSQUITOES
FLYING IN YOUR FACE
AND BITING YOU WHERE
YOU THOUGHT NOTHING EVER WOULD.
GET YOURSELF ONE OF THESE
ALUMINUM LAWN CHAIRS
AND AN ELECTRIC DRILL
AND GET BUSY.
THERE WE GO.
I CAN GO OUT
IN THE WORST MOSQUITO WEATHER.
I JUST SIT DOWN,
GET COMFORTABLE, TURN ON
MY MOSQUITO FOGGER, WHICH IS
HOOKED UP TO THE CHAIR
AND RUNS THROUGH THE HOLES.
GIVE HER A COUPLE OF SECONDS
TO KIND OF WARM UP.
SOON, THAT INSECTICIDE FOG
IS GONNA...
[coughing]
THE BEAUTY OF THIS SYSTEM IS
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PUT
ANY INSECT REPELLANT ON.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT TAKING TOXIC CHEMICALS...
[coughing]
... IN THROUGH YOUR SKIN.
OH... UH, YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
UH, THOSE WHO ARE ALLERGIC
TO THE RAGWEED OR THE POLLEN
OR THE [coughing] D.D.--
[coughing] OR THE D.D.--
[coughing] OR THE D.D.T.,
YOU MIGHT WANT
A MECHANICAL SOLUTION.
YOU KNOW HOW THE HORSE HAS
A TAIL AND THEY FLIP THAT
AND IT PUSHES BUGS AWAY?
IN AUSTRALIA, THEY GOT HATS
WITH CORKS ON 'EM.
THEY FLIP THEM AROUND
TO KEEP DIDJERIDUS
AND WALLABIES
OFF THEIR BILLABONGS.
YOU CAN DO THE SAME THING
BY TAKING ONE
OF THESE PATIO UMBRELLAS
AND A WASHING MACHINE.
ALL YOU DO IS HANG
YOUR VARIOUS LITTLE TRINKETS
ON THE EDGE OF THE UMBRELLA
AND THEN HOOK HER UP.
[Music mimicking
a ticking clock]
[grunting]
ALL RIGHT, THERE WE GO.
I GOT MY DOODADS DUCT-TAPED
TO THE UMBRELLA.
I GOT THE UMBRELLA DUCT-TAPED
TO THE WASHING MACHINE.
SHE'S ALL SET --
LET'S GIVE HER A TRY.
WELL, THERE IT IS.
PEOPLE WILL BE TALKING
ABOUT YOU ALL OVER TOWN.
THEY'LL SAY, "IT'S JUST LIKE
A FLICKING HORSE'S BEHIND!"
OR WORDS TO THAT EFFECT.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
UH-OH, SPIN CYCLE!
BILL IS ALL CRANKED UP
AND NOWHERE TO GO.
THE TOWN COUNCIL WILL REPLACE
THE STATUE WE DESTROYED
WITH OUR FAN-BOAT.
WE'RE IN THE WRONG BUSINESS.
SCULPTORS ARE GETTING THOUSANDS
FOR DOING NOTHING.
NOTHING?!
IT TAKES A LOT OF TALENT
TO TURN A HUNK OF ROCK
INTO A HUMAN FACE.
MOTHER NATURE DID IT WITH YOU.
[audience laughing]
... OR CLOSE
ENOUGH.
WE DON'T NEED
ANY STARVING ARTIST
TRYING TO RIP EVERYBODY OFF
WHILE THEY WAIT
FOR ANOTHER RENAISSANCE.
WE'RE GONNA BUILD
A STATUE OURSELVES.
I COULD BUILD A SCULPTURE
PRETTY CHEAP.
IN CUBS, I'D MAKE ASHTRAYS OUT
OF ASBESTOS FOR FATHER'S DAY.
THE LEADERS FIGURED
IF THEY SMOKE,
ASBESTOS WON'T BE HURTING THEM.
THANKS ANYWAY, HAROLD,
BUT WE'VE ALREADY DECIDED.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
HUH? SEE THAT, EH?
WE'RE GONNA HAVE A GIANT POSSUM
IN FRONT OF THE MAYOR'S OFFICE,
LOOKING DEAD.
TALK ABOUT LIFE IMITATES ART.
OH, YEAH, I'M SURE.
YOU GUYS THINK YOU CAN DO
EVERYTHING UNTIL YOU TRY IT.
YOU THINK YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING
AND YOU PROVE IT.
THAT'S RIGHT--
[applause]
OK, WHAT HAVE YOU GOT TODAY,
RANGER GORD?
WELL, TODAY, RED, LADIES
AND GENTLEMEN, I'M PERFORMING
ONE OF MY MOST FAVOURITE TASKS
AS A RANGER --
TAGGING WILDLIFE.
SOMETIMES I'LL BE TAGGING MOOSE
OR BEAR, BUT TODAY,
I'M DOING THE TRICKIEST
OF ALL -- I'M TAGGING FLIES.
THE FIRST THING WE DO
IS LURE THEM CLOSE.
IT'S A SHAME
STINKY PETERSON ISN'T HERE.
I HAVE THIS GREEN PORK CHOP.
[fly buzzing]
OH, THERE WE GO!
[buzzing]
GOT HIM!
NICE WORK!
NO, IT'S A HER.
OH, BOY!
I'M GOING TO BE TAKING
ONE OF THESE TAGS.
IF YOU'D TAKE DOWN THE DETAILS,
PLEASE, RED?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
FIRE AWAY.
NOW, IT IS A FEMALE BLACKFLY,
TAG NUMBER 22395...
22395...
NO DISCERNIBLE MARKINGS.
I GOT IT.
TO MAKE SURE THE TAG STAYS ON,
WE'LL USE THIS STAPLER.
OH, OH, OH!
OH, NO.
IT'S ON THERE.
I KILLED IT, RED.
I KILLED
ONE OF NATURE'S WONDERS.
NO, NO, COME ON...
NO, NO, NO.
NO, SHE'S FINE, GORD --
FLEW AWAY.
FLYING RIGHT AS RAIN.
SHE FLEW AWAY?
YEAH, JUST HAD TO GET USED
TO THE TAG'S WEIGHT.
OH! OK, GREAT.
WELL, LET'S DO
NUMBER 22396, HUH?
FOR DINNER, I'LL FRY US
SOME PORK CHOPS.
[Fly buzzing]
OK.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS A WOOD FILE
CALLED A COARSE BASTARD FILE.
THAT'S RIGHT, A COARSE BASTARD.
IT SAYS RIGHT THERE --
"COARSE BASTARD",
SO STINKY, IF YOU'RE WATCHING,
IT'S YOU WHO OWES ME
AN APOLOGY.
I DON'T MIND PEOPLE OFFERING
OPINIONS ON OUR SCULPTURE,
BUT I DON'T NEED PUNKS PLAYING
STREET-BALL NEAR THE STATUE.
THAT WAS THE POSSUM LAKE
HIGH SCHOOL TEAM.
THEY HAD A BAD ATTITUDE.
NO, THEY
DIDN'T.
I KNOW THOSE GIRLS.
[audience laughing]
THEY'RE IN MY
HOME EC. CLASS.
I DON'T KNOW WHY PEOPLE FEEL
THEY GOTTA OFFER SUGGESTIONS,
YELLING WHILE
WE'RE TRYING TO CARVE.
THEY'RE SAYING,
"TAKE A BIT OFF THERE!"
OR "PUT A BIT BACK ON THERE!"
OR... "WHOOPS!
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S
STANDING BACK, SAYING,
"THAT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE A DUCK."
YOU GET 30 MEN WALING AWAY
ON A BIG PIECE OF ROCK
WITH SLEDGE-HAMMERS
AND TIRE IRONS,
YOU'RE ASKING FOR TROUBLE,
BUT YOU KNOW, I'M BEING HONEST.
LOTS OF THOSE PEOPLE,
THEY'RE GIVING
CREATIVE SUGGESTIONS.
BY THE TIME WE GOT DONE WITH
THEIR CREATIVE SUGGESTIONS,
OUR HUGE ROCK HAD TURNED
INTO A GRAVEL DRIVEWAY.
NOW WE GOTTA CHANGE OUR MEDIUM.
WE'RE SWITCHING TO STEEL.
GOOD IDEA --
STEAL A STATUE.
NO, HAROLD, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO, HAROLD.
WE'RE GONNA GET
OUR WELDING GEAR
AND WE'RE GONNA MAKE
THE FOUR HORSEMEN
OF THE APOCALYPSE
OUT OF "K" CARS.
WOW!
NOW, THAT'S INNOVATIVE!
A STATUE THAT GETS
DECENT MILEAGE
AND A SEVEN-YEAR WARRANTY.
[audience laughing]
[Red]: BACK AT BILL'S CAR,
WE'RE READY TO START HER.
EVERY GUY HAS HIS OWN SECRETS
FOR STARTING A CAR.
WITH ME, IT'S A LOT
IN THE WAY YOU TWIST THE WRIST.
WITH BILL,
IT'S THE WAY HE NODS.
WITH ME, IT'S THE TWISTING.
WITH BILL, IT'S THE NODDING.
WHEN WE GET GOING,
THERE'S HARDLY A VEHICLE--
WE CAN USUALLY GET HER--
WE CAN USUALLY...
BUT NOT IN THIS CASE, IT SEEMS,
SO BILL'S GETTING OUT.
GONNA CHECK UNDER THE HOOD.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
WHAT DO YOU WANT? HUH?
OH, YEAH, OK.
OPEN THE HOOD, ALL RIGHT.
OHHHH!
OH, GOLLY, IT'S GOT ONE OF THEM
SPRING-LOADED HOODS.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
OK, UP SHE COMES.
THERE SHOULD BE A BAR THERE.
SHOULD BE SOMETHING THERE--
SHOULD BE A BAR TO HOLD THAT,
SOME TYPE OF BAR.
BILL, NO, I BELIEVE
THAT'S A DIPSTICK.
ACTUALLY, THERE'S A COUPLE
OF THEM I'M LOOKING AT.
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S GONNA WORK,
NO MATTER HOW LONG YOU DO IT.
WHAT HAVE WE GOT THERE?
THAT'S THE COAT HANGER
FROM EARLIER IN THE SHOW.
I'M NOT SURE A COAT HANGER
WOULD HOLD UP A HOOD.
WOULD THAT MAKE
A LOT OF SENSE TO YOU?
WELL, BY GOLLY!
IT DOES HOLD UP
THE WEIGHT OF THE HOOD...
JUST NOT FOR LONG.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
OH, OPEN THE HOOD!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
GOTCHA, GOTCHA.
IS THAT BETTER?
YOU ALL RIGHT? OK.
THIS IS GOING WAY BACK.
THEY USED TO BE ABLE TO HOOK
A CRANK INTO THE CRANKSHAFT.
THAT'S WHY THEY CALL IT
A SHAFT.
BILL'S GONNA TRY AND
TURN THE MOTOR OVER MANUALLY.
OH, BOY, THIS IS-- OH, OH, OH!
THE THING CAN START
GOING BACKWARDS ON YOU.
CAREFUL, THERE, BILL.
WATCH IT DOESN'T REVERSE.
LOOK OUT, SHE'S COMING
YOUR WAY!
ALMOST THERE -- OH, BOY!
LITTLE MORE -- ALMOST GOT HER.
OH, BOY! OH, GOSH!
OH, GOSH! OH, GOSH!
YOU ALL RIGHT, BILL?
LO OUT -- OH, OH, OH!
OH! OH! OH! OH!
[laughing]
ALL RIGHT, LET'S TRY THESE--
OH! GOSH!
I SHOULD KNOW BETTER
THAN TO STAND THAT CLOSE.
HE'S GOT JUMPER CABLES.
HE'S GOT THE DOUBLE SET.
HE'S GONNA PUT ONE END ON AND
WE'LL JUST HOOK 'EM TOGETHER.
IT'S AMAZING HOW MUCH POWER--
[sputtering]
... YOU CAN GET OUT
OF A COUPLE OF BATTERIES.
YEAH, THE QUICK START--
I BELIEVE THIS IS,
UH, ETHER.
ETHER WOULD BE A GOOD THING
TO HAVE AROUND BILL.
TAKE IT EASY, BILL.
YOU JUST NEED A LITTLE SQUIRT.
YOU DON'T NEED-- BILL.
NO, BILL, YOU'RE--
NO, BILL, THAT'S--
THAT'S ALMOST AN EXPLOSIVE,
BILL, I THINK.
I COULD BE WRONG,
BUT THAT'S AN EXPLOSIVE.
I COULD BE WRONG.
TWO CANS YOU'VE EMPTIED?
I COULD BE WRONG ABOUT THAT.
[explosion]
OHHHHH!
NO, I THINK I GOT IT
PRETTY MUCH RIGHT ON, THERE.
OH, BOY.
WHERE'S THE HOOD?
OH, THERE IT IS.
ALL RIGHT, UH...
IS THE ENGINE RUNNING?
IT'S NOT JUST RUNNING.
IT LEFT!
SO WE GOTTA FIND
AN ALTERNATE MEANS OF POWER.
GOOD GAS MILEAGE --
JUST TOO MUCH GAS.
STAY TUNED FOR MY BUDDY
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD,
THE KING OF PUMPS.
BY GOLLY, YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN
OUR "K" CAR STATUE.
I MAY NOT KNOW ART,
BUT I KNOW WHAT I LIKE,
AND IT'S WELDING VEHICLES
TOGETHER.
I KNOW I SAID THE FOUR HORSEMEN
OF THE APOCALYPSE.
WE HAD SO MANY CARS,
WE MADE SEVEN.
WAR, DEATH, FAMINE, SLEEPY,
DOPEY, GRUMPY, AND SHEMP.
IT WAS SOMETHING, WASN'T IT?
ALL THE WINDSHIELD WIPERS
WERE GOING.
THE LIGHTS WERE TURNED ON.
EVERY RADIO WAS TUNED
TO THE PORT ASBESTOS STATION.
IT WAS ONLY TIME AND WEATHER,
BUT STILL...
IT WAS A MULTI-MEDIA DISPLAY
OF KINETIC ART
AND SOCIAL COMMENTARY.
WHOO-HOO!
WHERE DID YOU LEARN
TO TALK LIKE THAT?
THE LIBRARIAN SAID THAT,
AND SHE WAS REALLY EXCITED
UNTIL SHE REALIZED
ONE OF THE "K" CARS WAS HERS.
JUDGING FROM HER LANGUAGE,
I BET SHE READS
A LOT OF D.H. LAWRENCE.
SHE WASN'T THE ONLY ONE
NOT IMPRESSED WITH YOUR WORK.
THE POLICE STUCK A TICKET
UNDER EVERYBODY'S WINDSHIELD.
THERE WERE SIX FOR PARKING
AND ONE LITTERING.
WE GAVE THE CARS BACK,
BUT WE GOT AN IDEA.
INSTEAD OF MAKING A STATUE,
WE'LL TAKE SOMETHING
WE ALREADY HAVE
AND CALL IT A STATUE.
WE SHOULD HAVE
THOUGHT OF THIS BEFORE.
SOMETHING YOU ALREADY HAVE?
LIKE WHAT? LIKE A LAWN MOWER?
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
THAT COULD BE CONSIDERED ART?
YOUR BEER CAN COLLECTION?
YOUR POLYESTER PANT
WALL HANGING?
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION.
ON THIS WEEK'S EXPERT PORTION,
WE HAVE EXPERTS:
MY UNCLE RED AND HIS FRIEND,
MR. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD.
[applause and cheering]
[whistling]
FIRST LETTER GOES AS FOLLOWS:
"DEAR EXPERTS...
WAHHHH!
"WHAT'S THE SECRET
TO GETTING A GREAT JOB?"
[laughing]
IF MY UNCLE KNEW THAT, HE
WOULDN'T BE HOSTING
THIS
SHOW.
THE KEY TO A GREAT JOB
IS TO HAVE AN UNCLE
THAT OWES YOUR FATHER MONEY.
UH, WELL,
ACTUALLY,
I HAVE TO DIVERGE WITH YOU
FOR A SECOND, RED.
MY DAD OWED ALL KINDS OF PEOPLE
ALL KINDS OF THINGS.
THE ONLY JOB
THAT EVER GOT ME WAS
A GUY CAME UP TO ME AND SAID,
"IF YOU BEAT UP ANOTHER GUY,"
HE WOULDN'T BEAT UP MY FATHER.
[audience laughing]
WE WOULDN'T ASK YOU
WHAT A GREAT JOB WAS ABOUT,
ANYWAY, WINSTON.
[laughing]
WELL, UH...
I DON'T AGREE,
ESPECIALLY
IF THE GUY EXPIRES TO OWN
HIS OWN SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICE.
MR. ROTHSCHILD,
I THINK
YOU MEAN
"ASPIRES".
NO, "EXPIRES" IS
RIGHT ON THE MONEY.
YEAH, WELL,
ANYWAY,
THE KEY TO A GOOD CAREER IS
FINDING THE KEY TO THAT CAREER.
THAT'S KEY, AND, YOU KNOW,
I HAPPEN TO HAVE FOUND THE KEY
TO THE SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING BUSINESS.
BLOCKED
SINUSES?
NO, NO, NO.
[audience laughing]
THE KEY TO SUCCESSFUL
SEWAGE SUCKING
IS THE PERSONAL TOUCH, EH?
YOU'VE GOT TO CHAT UP
THE CUSTOMERS.
YOU GOTTA MAKE THEM
FEEL AT HOME,
MAKE 'EM FEEL SPECIAL.
CATER TO THEIR EVERY NEED.
'CAUSE IN MY BUSINESS,
THE CUSTOMER IS KING.
ONLY WHILE
THEY'RE ON THE THRONE.
OOOH!
[laughing and applause]
WELL, IT TOOK US A WHILE,
BUT WE FINALLY GOT
A NEW STATUE IN TOWN
BY JUST USING SOMETHING
WE ALREADY HAD.
NOT BUSTER HADFIELD'S STOVE.
NO, NOTHING STUPID, HAROLD.
DIDN'T USE
THOSE UNUSED EXER-CYCLES
THE GUYS BROUGHT IN.
SOMEBODY SUGGESTED
WE HAVE OLD MAN SEDGWICK
STAND THERE
AND PRETEND HE'S A STATUE,
BUT WE WANTED SOMETHING
MORE LIFELIKE.
HAVEN'T YOU FIGURED IT OUT?
ART TAKES TALENT --
THAT'S WHAT'S MISSING HERE.
NOT THE MATERIALS OR SUPPLIES.
ART IS IN THE ARTIST,
NOT IN THE PALETTE.
NO, THAT'S
RIGHT, HAROLD.
WE DECIDED TO USE THE FAN-BOAT.
WE'VE GIVEN UP ON ART.
WE'RE GONNA GO
WITH PRACTICALITY.
T-T-THE FAN-BOAT'S
THE NEW STATUE?
TOWN COUNCIL WON'T ALLOW THAT.
YES, THEY WILL, HAROLD.
THE FAN BLOWS OVER THE LAKE,
BREEZE ALL THE TIME,
KEEPS THE BUGS AWAY
AND GUARANTEES YOU'RE UPWIND
FROM STINKY PETERSON'S PLACE.
THEY WON'T LET IT SIT THERE,
BLOWING OVER THE LAKE.
THEY WILL, BECAUSE
THE MAYOR HAS A SAILBOAT.
YEAH?
GET IT?
WAHHH?
I'M
TELLING YOU,
WE'VE CREATED A STATUE.
WE GOT THE MAYOR ON THE LAKE
WHERE HE CAN'T MAKE MISTAKES,
AND WE KILLED A COUPLE
OF HOURS.
IF THAT ISN'T ART,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IS.
[laughing and applause]
NO, I'M SURE
YOU DON'T.
[possum squeal]
SEE, THAT'S
MEETING TIME.
I'LL BE DOWN
IN A FEW MINUTES.
THIS WAS QUITE A DAY.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
MAYBE WHEN WE'RE SITTING
OUT BY THE LAKE
AND YOU HEAR A LOUD NOISE
AND LOT OF WIND,
YOU CAN BE SURE
THAT I'M RESPONSIBLE.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause and cheering]
[possum squeal]
[Harold]: ALL RISE!
[All]: QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
I WAS TELLING YOU EARLIER
THAT PEOPLE MAKE THINGS.
THE POSSUM LODGE SIGN
IS MADE BY THE SAME--
THIS GUY MADE THIS
AND BROUGHT THIS IN.
YOU FLIP IT AROUND...
IT'S JUST FANTASTIC.
HE'S JIM JACKSON.
HE LIVES IN SIMCOE.
POSSUM LODGE MEMBER 4118.
AND, UH, BOY, IS THAT
EVER GONNA BURN GOOD.