♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN,
ON TODAY'S SHOW BILL
FINDS QUICKSAND
AND HAROLD TALKS ABOUT
SHOW BUSINESS
AND I TURN A DRYER
INTO A PERSONAL SAUNA.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(SHATTERING OF GLASS)
>>HAROLD: IF YOU WORSHIP NATURE
THEN HERE'S THE HIGH PRIEST
OF THE FOREST,
THE GRAND POOBAH
WITH AN AMAZING RESEMBLANCE
TO POOH BEAR.
HERE HE IS MR. RED GREEN!
WOO! GO RED, OUR POOH BEAR,
EL BEARO, WOO! WOO!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
AND THANKS FOR TUNING IN,
AND I WOULD LIKE TO APOLOGIZE
FOR ANY OF THE RELIGIOUS
OVERTONES IN HAROLD'S
INTRODUCTION THERE.
HAROLD, POSSUM LODGE IS NOT
EXACTLY A PLACE OF WORSHIP,
YOU KNOW IF I COULD WORK
MIRACLES WOULD YOU
STILL BE HERE?
>>HAROLD: I CAN WORK
MIRACLES UNCLE RED.
SEE I JUST RAISED
THIS SHOW FROM THE DEAD.
>>RED: WELL IT CAN GO BACK.
AN INTERESTING WEEK UP HERE
AT THE LODGE, BOB STUYVESANT
WHO WORKS FOR THE DEPARTMENT
OF NATURAL RESOURCES
HAS TO DISPOSE OF A WHOLE
BUNCH OF RUSTY, OLD,
40,000 GALLON GAS TANKS
THESE ARE THE BIG, HUGE TANKS
THAT THEY PUT UNDER GAS STATIONS
YOU KNOW AND APPARENTLY WHEN
THE GAS STATION CLOSES
THE GOVERNMENT MAKES
THEM DIG THEM ALL UP.
I GUESS IT'S KIND OF A MAKE
WORK PROJECT OR SOMETHING.
SO ANYWAY BOB'S GOT TO GET
RID OF 50 OF THESE GREAT,
BIG, HUGE GAS TANKS EH?
FLINTY WATSON THE LOCAL SCRAP
METAL DEALER, HE TOOK ONE OF
THEM BUT IT WAS ABOUT
3/4'S FULL OF PREMIUM UNLEADED,
SO FLINTY'S SCRAP METAL TRUCK
AND FLINTY'S SCRAP METAL FURNACE
AND HIS SCRAP METAL CRANE
ARE NOW PRETTY WELL JUST
SCRAP METAL...
AND HAROLD REMEMBER
THAT BIG, HAIRY DOG
OF FLINTY'S?
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH,
IT'S A BOUVIER.
>>RED: WELL NOT ANY MORE
HAROLD, MORE OF A HAIRLESS
CHIHUAHUA AND A REAL JUMPY ONE.
BUT A BIG ONE, IT LOOKS A
LOT LIKE OLD MAN SEDGEWICK.
SO NOW BOB IS DOWN TO 49
OF THE TANKS AND THE NEXT
THING YOU KNOW IS HE'S OFFERING
$100 BUCKS A TANK TO ANYBODY
WHO'LL TAKE ONE OF
THEM AWAY.
>>HAROLD: YEAH, OKAY, RIGHT,
GOOD LUCK.
>>RED: I TOOK 49 OF THEM,
YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH
THAT HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: WELL YEAH,
I MEAN THEY'RE UGLY AND
THEY'RE DANGEROUS AND
THEY'RE TOXIC.
>>RED: WELL SO ARE THE
LODGE MEMBERS
SO WE'RE GOING TO GET ALONG FINE
AS A MATTER OF FACT WE SAT
AROUND THE OTHER NIGHT
AND IT WAS JUST AMAZING THE
NUMBER OF IDEAS WE CAME UP WITH
AS TO WHAT WE CAN DO WITH
ALL THESE HUGE GAS TANKS.
>>HAROLD: I BLAME THE BEER.
>>RED: WHATEVER, YOU KNOW.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED, I'M JUST
SAYING I GET A BAD FEELING
ABOUT YOU GUYS MONKEYING AROUND
WITH 50 HUGE, HUMONGOUS
GAS TANKS.
>>RED: 49 HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OKAY 49.
(LOUD EXPLOSION)
>>RED: (SNIFFING) 48.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
♪ WHEN I WAS JUST ♪
♪ A SCHOOLBOY ♪
♪ I HAD PENS AND PAPERS ♪
♪  AND A NICE LOOKING ♪
♪ TURTLE NAMED MORT ♪
♪ IT REALLY BOTHERED ME ♪
♪ THAT HE WAS SLOW ♪
♪ I WAS WILLING TO ♪
♪ OVERLOOK THAT HE WAS SHORT ♪
♪ WE STUDIED ♪
♪ EAST INDIAN CULTURE ♪
♪ AND I GOT AN IDEA IN CLASS ♪
♪ I STOPPED FEEDING MORT ♪
♪ FOR A MONTH OR SO ♪
♪ BECAUSE THE TEACHER SAID ♪
♪ THAT'S HOW YOU MAKE ♪
♪ THINGS FAST ♪
>>RED: SHE WAS WRONG.
>>HAROLD: YEAH.
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE GOING
TO SHOW YOU A FEW THINGS YOU
CAN DO WITH YOUR CLOTHES DRYER
DURING THOSE REGULAR 3 OR 4
MONTHS HIATUSES BETWEEN
LAUNDRY DAY.
I'M SURE A LOT OF OUR VIEWERS
MAKE THE MODEL PLANES AND YOU
GET PAINTING THEM UP WITH THAT
SPECIAL LACQUER ON THERE THAT
LOOKS SO GOOD BUT IT'S VERY,
VERY HARD ON THE EYES
AND SO ON.
NOW WOULDN'T IT BE NICE
TO HAVE A NICE PLACE TO
DRY THOSE IN?
WELL I SUGGEST THAT WHAT YOU
DO IS TAKE THE SPINNING
DRUM OUT OF YOUR DRYER,
PUT SOME SHELVES IN THERE
AND YOU CAN JUST LAY THE PLANES
OR WHATEVER IN THERE REAL NICE,
YOU GOT THE HEAT,
IT'S DUST FREE AND IT'LL TAKE
THE FUMES AND PUSH THEM
RIGHT OUTSIDE INTO YOUR
NEIGHBOUR'S YARD.
SO I SUGGEST YOU JUST SET
THE CONTROL ON THE DELICATE
AND RUN HER FOR ABOUT AN HOUR.
I DON'T KNOW, THAT IS
INTERESTING BECAUSE I HAD
SPECIFICALLY ASKED HAROLD
TO REMOVE THE SPINNING DRUM
BUT WELL HE'S EITHER FORGOTTEN
OR MAYBE HE GOT TOO BUSY
SIMONIZING HIS HEAD.
SO WHAT WE'RE LOOKING AT
HERE IS 3 YEARS OF MODEL
BUILDING DOWN THE TUBES,
OH I'M GLAD THEY WEREN'T MINE.
ALL RIGHT I'LL SHOW YOU
SOMETHING ELSE THAT
YOU CAN DO WITH YOUR DRYER,
BUT FOR THIS ONE WE DEFINITELY
HAVE TO REMOVE THE SPINNING
DRUM WHICH IS NO BIG DEAL,
USUALLY IT'S GOT SOME SCREWS
ON THE BACK HERE OR THERE
MIGHT BE SOME WING NUTS,
NOT A BIG JOB, MAYBE IT'S THE
LOCKING CLIPS ON THIS MODEL,
NO, NO, MAYBE IT GOT THE
SLIDERS... NO.
WELL I GUESS SHE'S PROBABLY
JUST A PRESS FIT.
(REPEATED THUDS OF HAMMERING)
WHERE WE ARE NOW IS WHAT WE
CALL THE POINT OF NO RETURN
FOR HANDYMAN WHERE IN ORDER
FOR ME TO CONTINUE TRYING
TO GET THE SPINNING DRUM
OUT OF THE DRYER WHICH IS
MORE TROUBLE THAN IT'S WORTH,
I HAVE TO MAKE THE CONSCIOUS
DECISION TO TAKE THIS PERSONALLY
BASICALLY WHAT I'M SAYING
IS THIS IS MY DRYER,
I OWN THIS DRYER,
I CAN DO WHATEVER I WANT
WITH THIS DRYER,
WHEREAS WHAT THE DRYER
IS SAYING TO ME IS OH NO, NO,
NO, YOU STUPID, BURNT OUT,
OLD MAN, THERE'S NO WAY
YOU'RE GETTING ANYWHERE NEAR
MY SPINNING DRUM AND TO ME THIS
IS AN ATTITUDE THAT
REQUIRES AN ADJUSTMENT OF
SIGNIFICANT PROPORTION.
ALL RIGHTY I DIDN'T
GET EVERYTHING OUT,
I LEFT THE MOTOR AND BELTS
AND STUFF, I DON'T
THINK THEY DO MUCH.
I GOT THE DRUM OUT THAT'S
THE MAIN THING, NOW WHAT
YOU WANT TO DO IS YOU WANT
TO TAKE A MARKER OF SOME KIND
AND YOU WANT TO DRAW A HOLE
ON THE TOP HERE JUST ABOUT
THE SAME SIZE AS YOUR HEAD
OR IF YOU GOT A SMALL HEAD
I GUESS YOU COULD DRAW IT
THE SIZE OF YOUR HAT,
NOW ONCE YOU'VE DONE THAT
NOW YOU CAN TAKE OFF ALL
YOUR CLOTHES AND GET A JIGSAW,
NO, NO, NO, NO,
GET A JIGSAW AND THEN
TAKE OFF ALL YOUR CLOTHES
I'M NOT MAKING THAT
MISTAKE AGAIN...
NOW WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS
CUT THAT THING OUT BECAUSE
YOUR HEAD'S GOT TO POP
THROUGH THERE,
WHEN YOU COME BACK BE NAKED,
WE'LL HAVE SOME FUN.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S THAT
TIME OF THE SHOW WE EXAMINE
THOSE 3 LITTLE WORDS THAT
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW.'
AND NOW HERE TO PROVE THAT
POINT ONCE AGAIN IS UNCLE RED
AND HIS GOOD FRIEND,
MR. DOUGIE FRANKLIN.
OKAY, 'DEAR EXPERTS,
I JUST BOUGHT A NEW CAR.'
>>DOUGIE: OH,
CARS ARE MY SPECIALTY.
>>RED: OH I'LL SAY, I'LL SAY,
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT, THERE'S
NOTHING THAT DOUGIE HERE
DOESN'T KNOW ABOUT CARS.
>>HAROLD: OH OKAY, EXCELLENT,
THAT'S GOING TO MAKE THIS
QUESTION SO PERFECT THEN,
OKAY IT'S SAYS, 'MY NEW CAR
HAS ELECTRONIC IGNITION AND
COMPUTER CONTROL FUEL INJECTION,
I WAS WONDERING WHAT IS THE
IMPORTANCE OF BULLION LOGIC
AND COMPUTER PROGRAMMING?'
EXCELLENT QUESTION.
>>RED: DOUGIE?
>>DOUGIE: WHAT?
>>RED: DO YOU WANT
TO FIELD THAT QUESTION?
>>DOUGIE: WAS THERE ACTUALLY
A QUESTION IN THERE RED?
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH, IT WAS THE
IMPORTANCE OF BULLION LOGIC
IN COMPUTERS, YOU KNOW LIKE
THEOREMS AND LOGICAL
PROPOSITIONS AND ENDOR GATES,
SET THEORY YOU KNOW,
WE TOOK ALL THIS IN ALGEBRA.
>>DOUGIE: WELL YOU KNOW THAT IS
A DANDY QUESTION, BUT YOU KNOW
I CAN'T ANSWER IT BECAUSE THEY
DIDN'T REALLY MENTION WHAT
MAKE OF CAR IT WAS THEY BOUGHT.
>>RED: WELL LET'S JUST
SAY IT WAS A FORD PRODUCT.
>>DOUGIE: OKAY A FORD PRODUCT,
WELL OF COURSE YOUR BULLION
LOGIC IS LESS IMPORTANT IN YOUR
FORD THAN SAY YOUR G.M. PRODUCT,
MAYBE A LITTLE BIT MORE
IMPORTANT THAN A CHRYSLER,
NOW YOUR DOMESTIC BULLION LOGIC
BY AND LARGE IS NOT QUITE AS
FANCY, INTRICATE OR CONVOLUTED
AS YOUR IMPORTED BULLION LOGIC,
BUT YOU KNOW IF YOU WERE TO HAVE
LIKE A SET THEORY BREAKDOWN.
OF COURSE IT'D BE A LOT EASIER
TO GET YOUR AND/OR GATES
OR YOUR OR/AND GATES OR
YOUR AND/OR/MAYBE GATES,
OH JEEZ AND YOU KNOW,
LORD KNOWS IF YOU'RE INTENDING
ON REBUILDING A DOMESTIC THEOREM
IT'S GOING TO BE A LOT EASIER
THAN ONE OF THOSE FLIMSY,
IMPORTED JOBS
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
>>RED: IT IS WINTER,
WE HITCH THE HORSE UP
TO THE SLEIGH LIKE
GRANDFATHER USE TO DO,
OVER HILLS AND THROUGH THE DALES
WE GLIDE FOR AN HOUR OR 2,
AND SOON MY EARS ARE BRITTLE
AND MY MOUTH IS FROZEN SHUT,
MY EYES ARE LOCKED WIDE OPEN
AND ALL I SEE IS A HORSE'S BUTT.
>>RED: OKAY SO WHAT YOU
HAVE IS YOUR VERY OWN
HIGH FASHION, SWEDISH SAUNA.
YOU JUST TURN ON THE HEAT
AND IT'LL SWEAT THE WORRIES
AND THE POUNDS AWAY.
AND BY GOLLY IT FEELS AWFUL GOOD
AND IF YOU'VE GOT A LINT FILTER
THERE, IT'LL EVEN CLEAN OUT
YOUR BELLY BUTTON FOR YOU.
SO YOU SET THE SETTING
ON THE DRYER TO WHATEVER
SUITS YOUR STYLE,
MAYBE YOU'RE NORMAL OR DELICATE
OR MAYBE A HOT, FAST TUMBLE
IS THE WAY YOU GO.
PERSONALLY I'M A PERMANENT
PRESS KIND OF A GUY,
SO I'M GOING TO HAVE A SAUNA
RIGHT NOW BUT YOU KEEP THIS
IN MIND, IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
(DRYER RUMBLING)
>>RED: WELL I STILL HAD A FEW
OF THOSE BIG TANKS TO GET RID OF
SO I THOUGHT MAYBE I COULD PAWN
THEM OFF ON THE LONELIEST MAN
IN THE WORLD, RANGER GORD.
>>GORD: OH MR. GREEN,
OH EXCUSE THE MESS,
I WAS HOPING TO HAVE MORE
OF THIS PUZZLE FINISHED
BEFORE YOU ARRIVED.
>>RED: WELL I CAN COME
BACK LATER GORD.
>>GORD: (SCREAMING) NO!
NO, ALL RIGHT,
IT'S FINE, COME IN.
>>RED: BOY THAT'S A HECK OF A
BIG JIGSAW PUZZLE YOU GOT THERE.
>>GORD: YEAH, 25,000 PIECES.
>>RED: GOLLY I DIDN'T KNOW
THEY MADE THEM THAT BIG.
>>GORD: WELL THEY DON'T,
SO WHAT I DID WAS I DREW
A PICTURE ON MY LINOLEUM FLOOR
AND I CUT IT OUT INTO
LITTLE PIECES,
IT TOOK ME 6 MONTHS TO PUT
IT TOGETHER THE FIRST TIME,
ONLY 5 MONTHS THE SECOND TIME.
>>RED: GOOD FOR YOU GORD.
YOU KNOW GORD THIS IS A BIT OF
A LONG SHOT BUT WOULD YOU HAVE
ANY USE FOR A COUPLE OF
40,000 GALLON GAS TANKS?
>>GORD: BOY WHAT'S BEEN GOING
ON UP AT THE LODGE THESE DAYS?
I'VE BEEN HEARING SOME PRETTY
BIG EXPLOSIONS COMING
FROM OVER THERE.
YOU KNOW I BET I CAN GUESS,
I BET I CAN GUESS WHAT IT IS.
>>RED: YEAH IT'S THE GAS TANKS.
>>GORD: NO, NO, NO, LET ME GUESS
LET ME GUESS LIKE I DO ON DOTTO,
ARE YOU GUYS BLOWING UP WHALES?
>>RED: IT'S THE GAS TANKS,
WE'VE HAD A COUPLE
OF ACCIDENTS.
>>GORD: NO I BET I KNOW WHAT
IT IS, YOU GUYS ARE TAKING
SOMETHING THAT IGNITES
AND SETTING FIRE TO IT?
>>RED: YEAH YOU GOT IT,
THAT'S IT.
>>GORD: YEAH I KNEW IT,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, THANK YOU,
DO I WIN A PRIZE OR SOMETHING?
>>RED: YES YOU DO GORD,
YOU WIN TWO 40,000
GALLON GAS TANKS.
>>GORD: OH WOW, THANK YOU,
OH THIS IS GREAT,
I REALLY APPRECIATE THIS,
WHAT WILL I DO WITH THEM?
I'LL MAKE THEM INTO MARBLE
TOWERS OR GUEST CABINS,
YOU GUYS CAN DROP BY,
I REALLY APPRECIATE THIS.
>>RED: YEAH I GUESS
THAT COULD HAPPEN.
WELL THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR YOUR TIME GORD,
I REALLY APPRECIATE TALKING
TO YOU AND WE'LL SEE YOU LATER
I GUESS EH?
>>GORD: NO YOU'RE
NOT GOING HUH?
>>RED: WELL I...
>>GORD: THE PUZZLE,
WHAT ABOUT THE PUZZLE?
PUZZLE HUH?
WHAT ABOUT YOUR GAME?
WE HAVEN'T FINISHED YOUR
LITTLE GAME SHOW HUH?
THE BONUS ROUND,
IT'S NOT FAIR!
YOU GOT TO STAY.
(GORD SOBBING)
>>RED: ALL RIGHT GORD
WHAT I'M THINKING IS,
NOW WAIT NOW, WHAT I'M
THINKING IS THAT I COULD
COME BACK WHEN YOU NEED
MORE TANKS HUH?
>>GORD: OKAY.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>GORD: YOU CAN NEVER HAVE
TOO MANY MARBLE TOWERS
OR GUEST CABINS.
>>RED: NO BUT FIRST YOU'LL
NEED GUESTS AND YOUR MARBLES.
>>RED: WELL IT'S NOT EVEN
LUNCH TIME AND MOST OF THE
TANKS HAVE BEEN SPOKEN FOR.
JUNIOR SINGLETON DUCT TAPED
3 OF THEM TOGETHER AND MADE
A PRETTY HEFTY PONTOON BOAT,
YOU SEE HE'S NOT GOING TO MOVE
TOO FAST BUT HE'LL NEVER
RUN OUT OF GAS.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED GET THIS,
THERE'S A WHOLE BUNCH OF THEM
DOWN AT THE BEACH AND THEY'RE
WELDING THEM ALL TOGETHER
AND HERE'S THE BEST PART,
THEY FIGURE THEY'RE GOING
TO MAKE A TUNNEL THAT GOES
RIGHT ACROSS THE BOTTOM
OF POSSUM LAKE.
>>RED: YEAH THAT'S RIGHT HAROLD
AND WE'RE GOING TO BE ABLE TO
DRIVE RIGHT INTO TOWN JUST LIKE
THE HOLLAND TUNNEL IN NEW YORK
CITY, THE BIG APPLE HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH I KNOW IT
SHOULD BE EXACTLY THE SAME
YOU KNOW EXCEPT OF COURSE
FOR YOU KNOW THE GAS FUMES
AND A ROUNDED BOTTOM YOU KNOW
AND THE LEAKS, YOU KNOW
THERE'S NO LIGHT,
THERE'S NO VENTILATION,
OTHERWISE BOOM, BOOM,
EXACTLY THE SAME.
>>RED: ANYWAY I JUST FINISHED
PUTTING THE LAST COAT OF PAINT
ON MY OWN PARTICULAR PROJECT.
>>HAROLD: OH EXCELLENT,
HAVE YOU GOT LIKE A PLAN
FOR THE TANKS TOO?
>>RED: YEAH I GOT ONE THAT HAD
QUITE A BIT OF GAS IN IT AND
I ROLLED HER UP ONTO THE
ROCK REEF POINT THERE,
FLIPPED HER UP ON THE REAR END,
WENT UP ON TOP AND DRILLED
A HOLE DOWN THROUGH HER,
PUT A WORK SOCK IN THERE
AS A WICK, LIT HERE UP
AND WE GOT OURSELVES
A LIGHTHOUSE HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: WOW!
>>RED: DO YOU WANT TO
GET IN ON THIS HAROLD,
I GOT ABOUT 15 OF THESE
TANKS LEFT?
(5 LOUD EXPLOSIONS)
>>RED: ROUGHLY.
>>HAROLD: TANKS BUT NO TANKS.
>>RED: WELL I DON'T KNOW
HAROLD, THEY MAKE GREAT
SPEAKER CABINETS.
>>HAROLD: OKAY I'LL TAKE 2.
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ ROSEN UP THE STICK ♪
♪ AND ROSEN UP THE BOW ♪
♪ ROSEN UP MY LEG ♪
♪ AS FAR AS YOU CAN GO ♪
♪ ROSEN UP THE TREETOPS ♪
♪ AND ROSEN OUT ON THE LAKE ♪
♪ WHO COULD EVER GUESS ♪
♪ THE CONSEQUENCES WHEN ♪
♪ AN OVERWEIGHT PERSON ♪
♪ SITS ON A VIOLIN ♪
>>RED: KIND OF A SCARY
'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'.
THIS WEEK, BILL BROUGHT
ALL THE PARAPHERNALIA,
YEAH WE SEE YOU BILL.
LIFE JACKETS AND EVERYTHING
BECAUSE HE SAID WE HAD A
PROBLEM OUTSIDE THE LODGE
WHICH REALLY GOT MY ATTENTION,
QUICKSAND...
BOY YOU DON'T WANT TO FOOL
AROUND AND I WAS NERVOUS RIGHT,
YOU KNOW THAT'S SOMETHING THAT,
I'LL JUST STAND, YEAH I'LL JUST
GET IN BEHIND YOU THERE BILL.
AND I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY
HOW QUICKSAND...
NOW HE'S JUST GOING TO FEEL
AROUND FOR IT, I DON'T KNOW
HOW QUICKSAND HAPPENS
OR ANYTHING BUT YOU KNOW HE'S
GOING AND ALL AND HE STARTS TO
SINK IN AND BUT THEN I LOOK AT
THE OTHER END OF THE PIPE AND
HE'S JUST FAKING IT, MAN, WOW!
YEAH, YEAH THAT'S REAL FUNNY
BILL, SO HE GOES AND TRIES,
NOW WHAT IF THE QUICKSAND
COMES FROM JUST A REAL NARROW
RAINSTORM, YOU KNOW JUST BECAUSE
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS BUT
ANYWAY NOTHING SO FAR,
SO IT SEEMS ALL RIGHT AND THIS
IS YOU KNOW RIGHT ON THE
DRIVEWAY TOO SO YOU REALLY WANT
TO KNOW IF YOU'VE GOT SOMETHING
THERE BECAUSE YOU CAN DRIVE,
OH, OH, OH, BOY, BOY.
THERE'S A PATCH OF IT RIGHT
THERE, GET BACK, GET BACK BILL,
GET BACK, GET BACK,
BOY THAT WENT DOWN FAST
TOO AND IT'S, LOOK AT THAT,
LOOK AT THAT, OH MY GOSH THAT'S
DEEP, SO BILL STICKS A SIGN
IN THERE TO WARN PEOPLE,
WHAT'S THIS WARNING?
OH YEAH SAW THAT, YEAH, YEAH,
SO NOW WE GO BACK TO THE FRONT,
MAYBE PUT SOME LIFEJACKETS
AROUND THAT, REALLY MARK IT
PROPERLY BECAUSE THE SIGN.
>>BILL EH?
>>RED: BUT WHERE'S THE?
OH WELL WE HAD A WHOLE BUNCH OF,
WHERE'S THE STUFF?
WE HAD A WHOLE BUNCH OF,
WHAT IS THIS?
OH, OH, OH, OH,
OH MY GOSH, THERE'S ANOTHER,
NOW THAT WASN'T THERE
BEFORE EARLIER.
IT'S JUST YOU KNOW,
WHAT THE HECK, OH AND THERE,
OH I SEE, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
THIS STUFF IS ALL FALLING
INTO THE QUICKSAND.
HOLY MACKEREL!
SO BILL'S GOING TO GO GET
THE SIGN BECAUSE IT'S BETTER TO
HAVE THE SIGN UP HERE BECAUSE
THIS IS PROBABLY A BIGGER,
BUT OH WELL, YEAH, YEAH,
OH SEE, ALL RIGHT, YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH, SHE FELL IN.
ALL RIGHT SO ANYWAY WE'RE
GOING TO LEAVE THAT,
THAT'S THE SMALLER,
WE NEED 2 SIGNS REALLY IS
WHAT WE NEED AND BILL'S GOING
TO COME BACK AND STICK THAT
IN THE FRONT AND THEN HE WANTS
TO FIND, WHAT IS THAT,
WATCH OUT NOW, WATCH OUT,
NO IT'S A LITTLE FARTHER
THAN THAT, NO IT'S UNDER THAT,
UNDER THAT OTHER LIFE THING,
UNDER THAT OLD SEAT CUSHION
THAT'S WHERE, UNDER THERE,
UNDER THE CUSHION,
MOVE THE, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
OH NO, NO, NO, OH MY GOSH!
HUH? WELL THAT'S VERY STRANGE,
I GUESS IT HEALED OVER.
HMM, SO BACK WE GO AND THIS TIME
I'M LOOKING FOR THE THING AND
BILL IS, OH, OH BILL, BILL,
UNFORTUNATELY I DIDN'T NOTICE
AND I GET BACK THERE AND I,
THAT ONE'S GONE TOO,
WELL THIS IS VERY STRANGE HERE.
(BILL SHOUTING)
>>RED: AND BILL'S GONE,
THAT'S NOT QUITE SO STRANGE,
WHERE THE HECK IS HE?
BILL, BILL, OH, OH.
(BILL CHOKING & GAGGING)
>>RED: OH MY GOSH, OH I GOT
TO GO GET THE SAFETY EQUIPMENT.
YUP, YUP, YUP, THOSE ARE
FLOTATION CUSHIONS THERE AND
THE LITTLE PIECE OF CHAIN JUST
IN CASE HE COMES UP TOO FAST,
AND WHERE IS HE?
I CAN'T FIND HIM,
OH BILL, WHERE ARE YOU?
OH OKAY, OH FOR GOD SAKES!
YEAH THAT'S BILL,
THAT'S FUNNY BILL!
THAT SUMS IT UP FOR ME,
WELL I'M OUT OF THERE,
I DON'T KNOW WHERE IT IS
WITH THE QUICKSAND BUT HOPEFULLY
IT'S ALL HEALED UP BY NOW.
OH, ONE MORE SPOT AND
ANOTHER ONE WHERE THE
CAMERA IS STANDING.
>>RED: AND NOW FOR ALL YOU
YOUNG KIDS WHO AREN'T OLD
ENOUGH TO KNOW BETTER,
HERE'S HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OH HI.
WELL GOOD EVENING AND WELCOME TO
MY NEW SHOW WHICH IS ALL ABOUT
HAVING A CAREER IN MOVIES
AND TELEVISION.
OKAY, IT'S A LITTLE FEATURE THAT
I LIKE TO CALL,
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, SO I KNOW IT
WAS SPELLED WRONG SO DON'T SEND
ME LIKE A MILLION LETTERS
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT OR HAVE
PROTESTS IN FRONT OF THE UNICEF
BUILDING BECAUSE I KNOW IT WAS
SPELLED WRONG BUT THAT'S THE
WAY THE PEOPLE IN THE BIZ
DO IT JUST TO SHOW EFFECT.
YOU KNOW THEY SAY THAT FOR
EFFECT YOU KNOW THINGS LIKE,
'LET'S DO LUNCH'
'I'D RATHER BE DIRECTING'
'NO HAROLD, MR SPIELBERG
WON'T TAKE YOUR CALL,
PLEASE STOP PHONING US.'
JUST SAY IT FOR EFFECT,
THAT DOESN'T MEAN MUCH,
IT JUST SHOWS THAT THEY
ARE INDEED, 'PLAYERS'.
OKAY SO WHAT DO YOU NEED
TO BE IN THE BIZ,
LIKE THEY LOOK LIKE RABBITS,
YOU KNOW THEY LOOK LIKE
A RABBIT GOING TO WORK,
I'M GOING TO WORK,
I'M A RABBIT.
OKAY STEP ONE,
WHAT YOU NEED IS LIKE A FRIEND
OR A RELATIVE WHO ALREADY HAS
A SHOW, THERE'S NO WAY THEY'RE
GOING TO KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
DOING RIGHT?
SO THEN THEY JUST HIRE YOU.
HEY UNCLE RED,
HI, DO YOU KNOW WHAT
I WAS DOING?
>>RED: NO.
>>HAROLD: THIS IS SO FUNNY,
SO FUNNY BECAUSE WHAT
I WAS DOING DO YOU
KNOW WHAT I WAS DOING
I WAS EXPLAINING WHAT PEOPLE
NEED TO BE IN 'THE BIZ'.
>>RED: OH, WELL HAROLD RIGHT
NOW I NEED YOU TO CLEAN
THE SEPTICS.
>>HAROLD: OH, OKAY, ALL RIGHT,
AND STEP 2 IS YOU MUST BE
PREPARED TO DO ANYTHING WHILE
WAITING FOR YOUR BIG BREAK.
>>RED: YEAH ESPECIALLY
DURING SWEEPS WEEK.
>>HAROLD: OH!
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: IT IS SUMMER,
IN THE INTENSE HEAT
EVERYTHING EXPANDS
WITH THE EXCEPTION
OF LAST YEAR'S SHORTS.
RIP, HEAT WAVE.
>>RED: REG IS A VEGETARIAN
HUNTER AND I THOUGHT HE MIGHT
BE ABLE TO USE A COUPLE
OF THE TANKS TO STORE
THE MEAT THAT HE'S NOT EATING.
REG YOU KNOW WHAT YOU COULD
USE I THINK IS A COUPLE OF
BIG TANKS TO MAKE INTO
SMOKEHOUSES FOR YOUR
VENISON AND SO ON.
>>REG: NO SORRY RED,
WHEN I CAME UP HERE
I STOPPED EATING MEAT.
>>RED: AND YOU STARTED
KILLING MEAT.
>>REG: IT'S NOT THE KILL
IT'S THE HUNT, SO FAR
I HAVEN'T BAGGED A THING.
>>RED: OH YEAH, WELL YOU
ALMOST BAGGED ME A MINUTE AGO.
(RATTLING NOISES)
>>REG: SHH!
GOOD, GOT YOU!
(RIFLE SHOT FIRES)
>>RED: YIKES!
>>REG: (SHOUTING) YOU GOT TO BE
A LOT MORE CAREFUL THAN THAT
WHEN YOU COME SAUNTERING
THROUGH THE WOODS YOU BIG...
YOU SHOULD HAVE FAXED ME
A MEMO OR SOMETHING.
>>RED: WELL I CAN SEE WHY
YOU BECAME A VEGETARIAN.
>>REG: I ALMOST GOT
SOMETHING THERE.
>>RED: WELL TODAY IS ONE
OF THOSE DAYS WHERE EVERYBODY
COMES AWAY YOU KNOW
A LITTLE WISER, A LITTLE
MORE HUMBLE YOU KNOW.
I GOT THE EYEBROWS SINGED OFF
THERE BUT LUCKILY NO ONE
WAS HURT SERIOUSLY.
>>HAROLD: THAT'S ONLY BECAUSE
NOBODY WAS ON ROCK REEF POINT
WHEN YOUR LITTLE LIGHTHOUSE
DECIDED TO TURN INTO
A HUGE FIRECRACKER.
>>RED: YEAH HAROLD BUT ON
THE BRIGHT SIDE THE EXPLOSION
COMPLETELY ELIMINATED ROCK REEF
POINT SO NOW WE DON'T NEED
A LIGHTHOUSE.
AND I'LL TELL YOU,
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S GAS POWERED
LAWN ROLLER TURNED OUT A LOT
BETTER THAN WE EXPECTED
NOW WE GOT A FLAT LAWN,
A FLAT DRIVEWAY AND
A NEW ROAD INTO TOWN.
>>HAROLD: AND THAT THING
MOVED TOO, YOU SHOULD HAVE
HEARD THE NOISE HUH?
BRRROOOMMM, BRRROOOMMM.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: THAT'S THE POSSUM,
IT'S MEETING TIME.
>>RED: YEAH ALL RIGHT,
YOU GO AHEAD HAROLD
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
YOU KNOW I THINK IT WAS
JAMES JOYCE WHO SAID THAT A
GENIUS MAKES NO MISTAKES,
THAT HIS ERRORS ARE ON PURPOSE
AND THEY BECOME THE PORTHOLES
OF DISCOVERY AND THAT'S THE KIND
OF THING YOU SAY WHEN YOU DO
SOMETHING REAL STUPID.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
YOUR GENIUS WILL BE COMING
STRAIGHT HOME AFTER THE MEETING
AND MY CLOTHES KIND OF SMELL
LIKE GAS SO I'M JUST GOING
TO LEAVE THEM ALL ON THE PORCH.
YOU CAN DO THE SAME THING
IF YOU LIKE...
I WOULDN'T MIND
A FEW MORE FIREWORKS.
AND SO ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING
AND KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
♪ ♪ ♪
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca