[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN
IN TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD
TALKS ABOUT COOL HAIR,
BILL IS GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW TO STORE FOOD
IN THE WOODS,
AND I'M GOING TO MAKE
A REAL NEAT CLOCK OUT
OF BEER BOTTLES.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(SHATTERING GLASS)
>>HAROLD: AND NOW HERE'S
THE ONE AND ONLY AND THEREFORE
THE GREATEST TV SENSATION
TO STEP OUT OF THE FOREST
SINCE BIGFOOT
OUR VERY OWN 'SAGQUATCH',
OUR VERY OWN
ABOMINABLE SHOWMAN,
RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
THANK YOU AND THANK YOU
HAROLD FOR GETTING THE SHOW
OFF ON THE WRONG BIGFOOT.
>>HAROLD: ABSOLUTELY
NO PROBLEMO, UNCLE RED.
I WILL NOW CROSS OVER
TO JOIN THE HOST.
>>RED: MAYBE YOU SHOULD
CROSS OVER AND JOIN
THE WOMEN'S NAVY.
WELL NOW THAT HAROLD HAS
PUT HIS BIG FOOT IN HIS BIG
MOUTH WE CAN GET ON WITH
THE SHOW AND ACTUALLY HAROLD
HAS A BEEN A BIT RELEVANT
JUST AS A FLUKE HERE BECAUSE
THIS WEEK WE'VE ACTUALLY
DISCOVERED WE HAVE A MONSTER
RIGHT HERE IN POSSUM LAKE
WHICH WE'VE NICKNAMED PESSIE.
>>HAROLD: PESSIE?
WHAT KIND OF A NAME IS PESSIE?
>>RED: WHAT KIND OF
NAME IS HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: WELL IT'S A MONSTER
IT SHOULD HAVE A MONSTER'S NAME
YOU KNOW LIKE GARGO (ROARING)
LIKE THAT YOU KNOW OR
RAZOR MOUTH, FIRE BEATER.
SOMETHING THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A VIDEO GAME.
>>RED: I DON'T KNOW HAROLD
I MEAN THE LOCHNESS MONSTER
IS NAMED NESSIE SO WE FIGURED
THE LOCH POSSUM MONSTER SHOULD
BE NAMED PESSIE.
WE THOUGHT ABOUT CALLING IT
POSSIE BUT THAT KIND OF IMPLIED
THERE WAS A WHOLE BUNCH OF THEM
AND THEN WE WENT THROUGH
THE OTHER VOWELS,
DECIDED WE WERE SAFEST WITH 'E'.
ANYWAY JUNIOR SINGLETON HAS
ALREADY SPOTTED PESSIE.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED NEED
I REMIND YOU THAT JUNIOR
SINGLETON BOUGHT A HUGE PONTOON
BOAT LAST WEEKEND AND HE'S BEEN
SINCE TOURING THE LAKE OFFERING
TOURS TO PEOPLE COINCIDENCE
OR AND OR WHAT?
>>RED: YES HAROLD BUT YOU KNOW
YOU CAN'T DENY IT JUNIOR SAYS
HE HAS SPOTTED THE MONSTER
EVERY DAY FOR THE LAST 3 DAYS.
>>HAROLD: YES BUT I WISH
HE JUST HAD A PAYING
CUSTOMER CONFIRM THAT THOUGHT.
>>RED: WELL HAROLD YOU KNOW
I DON'T THINK ANYONE WITH YOUR
LOOKS SHOULD BE SKEPTICAL
ABOUT UNUSUAL LIFE FORMS.
TAKE TIME TO READ
THAT'S A GOOD DEED
TO READ
GO TO THE LIBRARY
AND GET OUT A BOOK
THEY HAVE 2 OR 3
THAT ARE WORTH A LOOK
IF I HADN'T GONE
MY MIND WOULD BE PORRIDGE
AND HOW ELSE COULD I HAVE
FOUND OUT SO MUCH
ABOUT CURIOUS GEORGE?
>>RED: THIS WEEK IN
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE GOING
TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING YOU CAN
DO WITH SOME OF THOSE BEER
BOTTLES YOU GOT LYING AROUND
THE GARAGE OR DOWN IN THE
BASEMENT OR WHATEVER
I FOUND THESE BOTTLES IN
THE CUSHIONS OF THE COUCH.
NOW ORDINARILY I WOULD JUST
THROW THESE OUT OR TAKE THEM
BACK FOR A REFUND BUT I'M GOING
TO SHOW YOU HOW YOU CAN
MAKE YOURSELF A DARNED
INTERESTING CLOCK.
NOW THE FIRST THING YOU'RE
GOING TO NEED IS SOMETHING
BIG AND FLAT TO HOLD ALL
THE MECHANISM FOR THE CLOCK
EXCUSE ME A MINUTE.
(GRUNTING AND CRASHING)
I SUGGEST A FRIDGE DOOR
FOR THE TIMELESS LOOK
OF WHITE ENAMEL.
AND YOU'RE ALSO GOING
TO NEED AN ELECTRIC MOTOR
LIKE THIS ONE TO FEED THE
BOTTLES INTO THE CLOCK
AND YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
A WORK GLOVE JUST ONE THAT'S
GOING TO HELP FEED THE BOTTLES
AS WELL SO YOU JUST NEED ONE
YOU CAN SELL THE OTHER ONE
TO THE NEIGHBOUR'S KID AND HE
CAN GO OUT AND BE A ROCK STAR.
NOW YOU GOT TO SOAK THIS THING
IN A SOLUTION MADE UP OF MERCURY
LACQUER, RUBBING ALCOHOL,
GASOLINE AND PAINT STRIPPER
OR AS WE CALL IT,
POSSUM LAKE.
THERE WE GO, ONCE SHE'S DRY
SHE'S HARD AS A BRICK
AND YOU STICK THE GLOVE ONTO
A 1 BY 3 OR 2 BY 2 OR WHATEVER
SIZE PIECE OF WOOD YOU FIND
WHEN YOU'RE OVER AT YOUR
NEIGHBOUR'S GARAGE SELLING
HIS KID THE OTHER GLOVE.
YOU KNOW THAT WOULD MAKE
A DANDY LITTLE
BACKSCRATCHER OR LOWER.
YOU KNOW A PANHANDLER
COULD USE THIS COULD WORK
BOTH SIDES OF THE MALL
AT THE SAME TIME.
BUT WE'RE GOING TO USE IT
TO PICK UP THE BEER BOTTLES
AND THEN ROLL THEM INTO
THE FRIDGE DOOR.
SO WHAT WE GOT TO DO NOW
IS TO CONNECT THIS TO OUR
ELECTRIC MOTOR JUST STICK IT
ON THERE AND YOU'LL HAVE
A LITTLE HOLE IN THERE
AND YOU CAN JUST DROP A NAIL
THROUGH AND THEN BEND HER OVER
OR I GUESS YOU COULD
USE A CAUDER PIN
IF YOU'RE MADE OF MONEY.
AND THEN WHAT YOU DO IS
LINE HER UP SO IT'S GOING TO
GO RIGHT INTO THE FRIDGE DOOR
AND I THINK WE'RE LOOKING
PRETTY GOOD.
WHY DON'T WE PUT A BEER BOTTLE
IN THE GLOVE AND GIVE HER A TRY
THERE WE GO.
NOW SOON AS I PLUG THE MOTOR
IN THAT SHOULD JUST LAY THAT
BOTTLE IN THERE AS NICE
AS YOU PLEASE.
(BOTTLE SMASHING)
>>RED: YEAH OKAY THAT WORKS,
THAT WORKS EXCELLENT.
IT'S JUST MAYBE JUST A TAD
FAST SO WE'LL SLOW THE
ELECTRIC MOTOR DOWN
IT'S EASY TO DO YOU JUST
OPEN THEM UP AND YOU CAN JUST
START CUTTING WINDINGS UNTIL
YOUR WRIST GETS TIRED OR YEAH
WHY DON'T WE JUST HOOK HER UP
TO ONE OF THESE HOUSEHOLD
DIMMERS, PERFECT.
ALL RIGHT NOW YOU MAY HAVE
TO JIMMY AROUND WITH THE DIMMER
TO GET THE MOTOR DOWN TO EXACTLY
ONE REVOLUTION PER MINUTE
GREENWICH TIME A.M. BUT ONCE
YOU DO BY GOLLY YOU'RE ALL
SET UP AND HERE'S HOW SHE WORKS.
THE GLOVE NOW IS GOING TO PICK
UP THE BEER BOTTLE FROM THE
BASIN THAT'S OUR SUPPLY AND AT
EXACTLY EVERY MINUTE RIGHT ON
THE BUTTON SHE BRINGS IT OVER
DROPS THE BEER BOTTLE RIGHT
HERE ON OUR TOP SHELF THAT'S
OUR MINUTE SHELF AND THAT
CARRIES ON UNTIL YOU GET 9
BOTTLES ON THERE ON THE TENTH
BOTTLE THE WEIGHT ALL CHANGES
AND SHE SWINGS DOWN AND 9
OF THE BOTTLES DROP INTO THE
EAVESTROUGH AND CARRY RIGHT ON
BACK INTO THE BASIN FOR A SUPPLY
AGAIN BUT THE TENTH BOTTLE GOES
INTO THE 10 MINUTES AREA SO
THAT'S NOW 10 MINUTES AND THEN
THAT KIND OF REPEATS ITSELF
AND NOW WHAT HAPPENS IS YOU
BUILD UP UNTIL YOU HAVE I GUESS
8 ON THE, NO 9, NOT 10,
10 ON THE 10 MINUTES AND
THEN INTO THE HOURS AND
DOWN AND AROUND AND JUST IT'S
LIKE CLOCKWORK AND THE BEAUTY
OF THIS MACHINE IS THAT
WHENEVER YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT
TIME IT IS YOU JUST TAKE A LOOK
OVER AT YOUR FRIDGE BEER BOTTLE
CLOCK AND YOU ADD UP THE MINUTES
AND YOU'VE GOT 4 THERE.
SO THAT'S 4 MINUTES PLUS YOU
ADD UP THE TENS WE'VE GOT 3
TENS AND THEN WE GOT 1, 2, 3,
4 HOURS SO YOU PUT THEM ALL
TOGETHER AND THAT MEANS
THAT IT'S EXACTLY
(BOTTLES CRASHING)
TIME FOR A BEER.
THIS WOULD MAKE A DANDY ALARM
CLOCK WOULDN'T IT?
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S THAT
TIME IN THE SHOW WHERE
WE EXPOSE THE 3 LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE ON EXPERT SECTION
TODAY OF COURSE IS MY UNCLE RED
AND MR. HAP SHAUGNESSY.
'DEAR EXPERTS I DO NOT CONSIDER
MYSELF A STUPID PERSON SUCH
AS SAY MY BROTHER BUT TRY AS
I MIGHT TRY  I DO NOT
UNDERSTAND EINSTEIN'S
THEORIES OF RELATIVITY.
WELL YOU KNOW EINSTEIN SAID
THERE ARE ONLY 3 PEOPLE WHO
COULD UNDERSTAND RELATIVITY.'
>>HAP: REALLY?
WONDER WHO THE OTHER ONE IS?
>>RED: DO YOU UNDERSTAND
RELATIVITY HAP?
>>HAP: JUST THE STUFF
I WORKED ON.
>>RED: OH YOU WORKED
WITH EINSTEIN DID YOU?
>>HAP: YEAH WELL WHEN HE
STARTED OUT I GAVE HIM A HAND
WITH HIS RELATE-IVE-ITY.
>>HAROLD: BUT EINSTEIN WORKED
ON RELATIVITY WHEN
HE WAS REALLY YOUNG.
>>HAP: YEAH AND I DIDN'T
MIND GIVING THE KID A HAND
HE HAD SOME GOOD IDEAS
THEY WERE ROUGH BUT GOOD.
>>HAROLD: EXCUSE ME MR SHAUNESSY
BUT I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW IT IS THAT YOU KNOW
EINSTEIN IS YOUNGER THAN YOU.
>>HAP: 'WAS' HAROLD 'WAS'
I WORKED A LOT FASTER THAN
ALBERT THAT'S ALL MUCH MUCH
FASTER SO WE AGED
AT DIFFERENT RATES.
>>RED: OH THAT'S POSSIBLE
I JUST ALL OF A SUDDEN FELT A
LITTLE OLDER MYSELF RIGHT THERE.
>>HAP: WELL THERE YOU GO RED
YOU'D HAVE TO BE THAT THIRD
PERSON THAT ALBERT WAS
TALKING ABOUT.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT TIME
AND SPACE IS RELATE-TIVE
AND SUBJECTIVE.
>>RED: I'M LEARNING
SO IS THE TRUTH.
>>RED: IT IS SUMMER
IN THE HOT SUN YOUR HAIR
WENT FROM DARK TO LIGHT
IT WENT FROM STRAIGHT TO CURLY
AND EVENTUALLY IT JUST WENT.
>>RED: THOUGHT I'D DROP
IN ON RANGER GORD, SEE IF
HE KNEW ANYTHING ABOUT THIS
POSSUM LAKE MONSTER.
>>GORD: WELCOME, WELCOME.
>>RED: THANK YOU GORD.
>>GORD: I'VE GOT WATER
FOR 6 MONTHS, LOTS OF COTS
EXTRA COTS, CREAMED
CORN WHAT DO YOU NEED?
>>RED: I WAS THINKING MAYBE
A 10 MINUTE VISIT GORD
THAT'S ALL I'VE GOT IN MIND.
>>GORD: OKAY THAT'S GOOD TOO
WELL GOSH WE ALL GET SO
BUSY THESE DAYS, TOOTHPICK?
>>RED: YEAH SURE.
>>GORD: GOSH YOU KNOW
YOU'VE GOT A LODGE TO RUN
I'VE GOT A FOREST TO MANAGE.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>GORD: YUP GOSH I CAN'T TELL
YOU HOW BUSY I GET SOMETIMES
INSPECTING A TWIG OR LOOKING
AT A BUG OR SOMETHING AND YOU
KNOW YOU HAVEN'T FELT EXCITEMENT
UNTIL YOU'VE EATEN A FOIL
WRAPPED POTATO AND LIGHTNING
HITS THE TOWER, BOOM!
BURNED ALL MY NOSE HAIRS
ON THE LAST ONE.
>>RED: WOW FOR GOSH SAKES!
LOOKS GOOD, YEAH.
TELL ME SOMETHING GORD
YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
DINOSAURS IN THIS AREA?
>>GORD: DINOSAURS?
NO, NO, NOT ANY MORE.
ALTHOUGH LAST WEEK I THOUGHT
I HEARD A NOISE.
NO BUT NOT REALLY
MILLIONS AND MILLIONS
AND MILLIONS OF YEARS AGO
BEFORE I CAME HERE YEAH,
YEAH I FEEL SORRY FOR
THE DINOSAUR DON'T YOU?
>>RED: NOT REALLY, NO.
>>GORD: BIG ANIMAL LOOKING
OUT OVER THE FOREST TRYING
TO PROTECT PEOPLE, LOOKING OUT
FOR FOREST FIRES YOU'D THINK
HE'D GET SOME THANKS SOMETIMES
OR AT LEAST AN AWARD OR
PAY CHEQUE OR SOMETHING
(CRYING) POOR DINOSAUR!
>>RED: WELL WELL NOW GORD
YOU KNOW I DON'T KNOW ABOUT HIM
BUT BY GOLLY YOU'VE DONE A HECK
OF A JOB ON TOP HERE
FOR ALL THIS.
>>GORD: REALLY?
>>RED: OH GOSH, YEAH WELL I
MEAN HOW MANY FOREST FIRES HAVE
THERE BEEN SINCE YOU'VE
COME UP HERE?
>>GORD: 6.
>>RED: 6 AND YOU'VE SPOTTED
ALL OF THEM DID YOU NOT?
>>GORD: NO.
>>RED: OH, ALL RIGHT
BUT YOU SPOTTED I KNOW YOU
SPOTTED ONE OF THEM
FOR SURE DIDN'T YOU?
>>GORD: YEAH BUT HOW
COULD I MISS IT?
IT BURNED THE TOWER DOWN.
>>RED: WELL JUNIOR SINGLETON
HAS CONVINCED A LOT OF SKEPTICS
BY OFFERING A $10,000 REWARD
TO ANYBODY WHO SPOTS PESSIE
THE POSSUM LAKE MONSTER.
PERSONALLY I'D BE A
LOT MORE CONVINCED IF
JUNIOR OFFERED A $40 REWARD
BECAUSE I KNOW HE HAS $40.
>>HAROLD: YOU KNOW UNCLE RED
IT'S TRUE THOUGH YOU KNOW MAYBE
THERE IS A DINOSAUR FISH IN
THE WATER, IT COULD'VE SURVIVED
UP HERE YOU KNOW IF IT WAS
CUT OFF FROM EVOLUTION LIKE
EVERYONE ELSE WAS UP HERE.
>>RED: YEAH WELL THEY'VE GOT
MOOSE THOMPSON CONVINCED
MOOSE TOOK ALL THE NETS OFF
THE TENNIS COURTS AND WENT
SKIN DIVING TO CAPTURE PESSIE
MANO ET MONSTERO.
I THINK THE WHOLE CONCEPT
OF THE LARGE SMALL BRAIN
DINOSAUR KIND OF STRIKES
A NERVE WITH MOOSE.
WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED
IF THERE WAS A BRONTOSAURUS
IN HIS FAMILY TREE.
>>HAROLD: EXCUSE ME RIGHT
THERE UNCLE RED.
NOW IF THERE IS A DINOSAUR
IN POSSUM LAKE IT WILL NOT
BE A BRONTOSAURUS NO, NO, NO,
PERHAPS IT WILL BE THE LONG
NECK PLESIOSAUR OR PERHAPS
IT'LL BE LIKE THE FAMED
DUCK-BILLED ICHTHYOSAURS.
>>RED: WELL I DON'T KNOW HAROLD
SO FAR THE ONLY PEOPLE WHO'VE
SPOTTED THIS THING ARE ALL
IN THE LOCAL TOURIST BUSINESS.
>>HAROLD: OH NO, NO, THAT'S NOT
EVEN TRUE, THAT'S NOT EVEN TRUE
BECAUSE OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
HE SAID HE SAW A THING IN THE
LAKE AND IT WAS ALL GREY SKINNED
WITH A HUMPED BACK AND BIG
WATERY FISH EYES YOU KNOW AND
IT HAD LIKE NO NOSE AND THIS
GAPING TOOTHLESS MOUTH
WHAT DO YOU THINK
THAT COULD BE?
>>RED: HIS REFLECTION.
COME ON BUS DRIVER
SPEED UP A LITTLE BIT
THE COPS ARE REALLY
GAINING ON US
>>RED: GOT SOMETHING SPECIAL
FOR ALL YOU CAMPERS
ON THIS ADVENTURE OF
'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'
THE ADVENTURE WITH BILL
PART OF THE BILL ADVENTURE.
NOW WHAT WE'VE POINTED OUT
HERE WAS BILL HAD LEFT HIS
FOOD JUST LYING AROUND
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
YOU'RE CAMPING AND SO FORTH
YOU GET A LOT OF THE ANIMALS
GET IN THERE AND OH BOY OH BOY
AND THEY'VE GOTTEN INTO
THE BACON AND TIED HER
INTO A REEF KNOT.
I GUESS SO BILL'S THINKING
THAT GET THAT OUT OF THERE
THANKS FOR TIDYING THAT UP BILL
AND HEY HEY HEY THAT'S
MY SHIRT, SO HE'S GOT SOME
BURLAP THERE AND HE'S GOING
TO PUT THE FOOD IN HERE WE'RE
GOING TO TRY TO SHOW YOU
A SAFE WAY TO STORE THINGS.
PUT EVERYTHING ABOUT THE MIDDLE
OF THE BURLAP AND THEN YOU
NEED SOME SORT OF A WATERPROOF
FABRIC TO GO OVER THE BURLAP
YOU BRING THAT UP AND WE WERE
LOOKING FOR SOME WATERPROOF
STUFF AND I KIND OF SPOTTED
BILL'S YOU KNOW...
(MUFFLED GRUMBLING FROM BILL)
SO WE PUT THAT OVER THE BAG
AND THEN WE TIED HER ON THERE
AND THEN WHAT YOU DO YOU'VE
GOT SOMETHING THERE
YOU REALLY OH, OH! OH!
YOU'RE READY TO GO HANG THAT
NOW OVER THE BRANCH OF A TREE
YOU SEE THE IDEA BEING THIS
IS GOING TO MAKE IT HARD
FOR THE ANIMALS TO GET AT.
BILL DOESN'T HAVE A LOT OF
MOTOR SKILLS WHEN IT COMES
TO SWINGING THINGS AROUND
AND THROWING THEM AT PARTIES
YOU KNOW NO, NO, NO, NO, BILL
NOW I DON'T LIKE TO BUD IN
BECAUSE BILL IS THE EXPERT
ON THE OUTDOOR STUFF BUT
IT SEEMED TO ME THAT THINGS
WOULD PROBABLY GO A LITTLE
BETTER IF YOU THREW THE END
OF THE ROPE OVER RATHER THAN
THROW THE BAG OVER.
YEAH THEN IT'S JUST A
SIMPLE TASK OF PULLING
THAT UP SHOULD GO...
>>BILL: OH!
>>RED: WELL BILL HAS A WAY
OF MAKING THINGS A LITTLE MORE
COMPLICATED THEN YOU GOT TO.
BILL, STOP BILL, STOP!
OH ALL RIGHT YOU CAN PULL
THAT UP TOO FAR ANYWAY.
HE'S GOT HER UP THERE NOW HE'S
GOT THE BAG HANGING THERE AND
IT'S SAFE AND I DON'T KNOW WHY
BUT BILL FELT HE NEEDED TO
CHECK THAT ALL RIGHT MADE A BAD
CHOICE ON THAT BRANCH AND THEN
NOW HE'S GOT ANOTHER BRANCH
NO BILL, BILL NO, NO,
JUST LEAVE IT, IT'S FINE.
IT'S FINE NOW WE CAN GO
AND DO WHATEVER WE WANT.
ALL RIGHT WE'LL DO A LITTLE
FISHING SO WE DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT THE ANIMALS
CAN'T GET AT THAT
AND HOW FAR SOUTH ARE WE?
ALL RIGHT SO WE FISHED FOR
A WHILE AND I GOT MYSELF
A COUPLE OF NICE LITTLE TROUT
AND SO ON AND BILL GOT
AN 8 1/2 AND A 7,
I THINK AN 11 TRIPLE 'E'
THERE SO HE'S GOING TO GO OVER
NOW WE CAN TAKE THE FOOD DOWN
IT SHOULD BE IN PRETTY GOOD
SHAPE OH, OH, EGGS ARE HARD.
NOW WE TAKE HER BACK AND
I'D BE A LITTLE, I THINK
IF YOU WERE TO DO THIS YOU
MIGHT WANT TO BE A LITTLE
GENTLER WITH THE WAY YOU HANDLE
THE FOOD BECAUSE THIS REALLY
IS NOT ANY BETTER THAN IT WAS
BEFORE BUT AT LEAST YOU KNOW
IT'S YOUR OWN MESS AND YOU CAN
ALWAYS LIVE WITH YOUR OWN MESS
BILL'S WIFE DOES.
>>RED: AND NOW HERE'S SOMETHING
FOR ALL YOU YOUNGSTERS, ENJOY.
>>HAROLD: YO! CHECK IT OUT
WASSUP?
WELCOME TO THE VERY
FIRST EPISODE OF MY BRAND
NEW SHOW, COOL HAIR.
OKAY COOL HAIR WHAT IS IT?
WHO HAS IT WHO WANTS IT?
WHO REALLY NEEDS IT?
HOW DO YOU BUILD IT?
HOW DO YOU MAINTAIN IT?
HOW DO YOU TRAIN IT?
HOW DO YOU GET IT TO SIT UP
ON ALL FOURS AND BEG
FOR A BISCUIT?
LIKE THAT AND WHEN YOU
THROW IT ONE IT ROLLS
ALL OVER THE RUG AND LOOKS SO,
I FORGOT WHAT I WAS TALKING
ABOUT, OH OKAY, OKAY,
OKAY YEAH, OKAY COOL HAIR.
THE FIRST FACTOR TO
FAB FOLLICLES IS YOUR DIET
IT'S TRUE BECAUSE WHATEVER YOU
EAT GOES DIRECTLY TO YOUR HAIR
LIKE WHEN YOU'RE EATING THOSE
LONG SPAGHETTIS YOU KNOW AND
YOU SUCK THOSE UP LIKE THAT
RIGHT AND THEN IT COMES AND LIKE
SNAPS YOU IN THE HEAD RIGHT
AND THEN IT WRAPS AROUND
YOUR NOSE AND STUFF.
AND ALSO YOU KNOW WHAT A BAD
DIET CAN LEAD TO LIKE A
RECEDING HAIRLINE THEN
YOU GET LIKE MY UNCLE RED
YOU GET ONE OF THOSE GREAT
BIG BALD SPOTS IT LOOKS
LIKE A BIRD DROPPED...
A HI UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED!
>>RED: HAROLD HAVE YOU
SEEN MY COMBS?
IS BILL WASHING HIS DOG AGAIN?
>>HAROLD: NO.
>>RED: HAROLD WHAT HAVE
YOU DONE HERE?
YOU GLUED ALL MY COMBS ON HERE.
>>HAROLD: NO, NO, I DIDN'T
THEY STUCK
THAT'S THE GRAPHIC FOR
MY NEW SHOW THAT'S THE OPENING
FOR MY NEW SHOW AND WITHOUT
THOSE COMBS I CANNOT DO
MY NEW SHOW.
>>RED: OH THAT'S GREAT THEN.
>>RED: WE HEAR A LOT OF TALK
THESE DAYS ABOUT JUNK FOOD
SOMEBODY WILL SAY TOO MUCH
CHOLESTEROL OR THAT'S HIGH IN
UNSATURATED FAT OR GET THAT
BAG OF CHIPS OUT OF THIS BED.
WELL I SAY THE WHOLE THING
IS A CROCK, YOU PUT A BAG
OF CHEESIES DOWN BESIDE A
PLATE OF SAUSAGES AND EGGS
AND THE MEAL YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO EAT IS MADE OF PIGS
INTESTINES AND PREMATURE
CHICKEN BABIES.
THEY SAY YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO WATCH OUT, DON'T EAT TOO
MUCH SALT WELL I'LL TELL
YOU WHAT THE GIANT SEA TURTLE
HE GETS TO BE 4000 YEARS OLD
AND HE LIVES IN SALT.
SO IT'S NOT THE SALT OR
THE CHOLESTEROL OR THE
JUNK FOOD THAT'LL KILL YOU
IT'S WORRYING ABOUT IT,
THAT IS WHAT DOES YOU IN.
SO AS LONG AS YOU DON'T LISTEN
TO YOUR CRAZY DOCTOR OR THE
NUTRITIONIST THAT HE SENDS
YOU TO OR THE HEART SPECIALIST
THAT THE NUTRITIONIST SENDS YOU
TO OR THAT CLINICAL SPECIALIST
ON CIRCULATORY SYSTEMS THAT THEY
BRING IN BECAUSE THEY'VE NEVER
SEEN A CASE THIS BAD IN THEIR
ENTIRE HISTORY, AS LONG AS YOU
DON'T LISTEN TO THEM YOU'RE
GOING TO LIVE A LONG LONG TIME,
I PLAN TO...
>>RED: HELLO GLEN
DROP ANOTHER PING PONG TABLE
OFF THE ROOF RACK?
>>GLEN: NO RED JUST DOING
A LITTLE CUSTOMIZING
ON THE R.V.
>>RED: OH YEAH.
>>GLEN: YEAH YOU EVER SEEN
THOSE INDY CARS WITH
THE FRONT SPOILERS?
I THINK THEY CALL THEM APRONS.
>>RED: OH YEAH, YEAH.
>>GLEN: KEEPS THE FRONT WHEELS
ON THE GROUND EVEN IF THEY'RE
GOING 150 MILES AN HOUR.
>>RED: WOW DID YOU PUT A NEW
ENGINE OR FIVE INTO THE R.V.
DID YOU?
>>GLEN: NO I WISH RED
NO GRAB THAT OTHER END
THERE I'LL SHOW YOU.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH.
>>GLEN: SEE THERE YOU GO
INDY CAR WITH A FRONT SPOILER.
>>RED: UH HUH, OR A FREIGHT
TRAIN WITH A COW CATCHER.
>>GLEN: MAKES IT SAFER,
SPORTIER AND SHARPER RED.
>>RED: WHAT'S THE OTHER ONE
FOR HERE IN CASE YOU CAN TAKE
A STUPID IDEA AND DO IT TWICE?
>>GLEN: NO RED, THIS GOES UP
ON THE BACK AT THE TOP HERE
THIS IS AN AIRFOIL.
>>RED: OH WELL THAT'S GREAT.
>>GLEN: THERE YOU GO RED.
>>RED: THIS IS A GREAT THING
YOU GOT THIS AT THE BACK
TO SCRAPE THE ICICLES OFF
THE BRIDGE AND YOU GOT
THE FRONT FOR PLOWING SNOW.
>>GLEN: NO RED, ACTUALLY
IT'S FOR MILEAGE OKAY
IT HELPS OUT THE MILEAGE
QUITE A BIT.
>>RED: REALLY?
>>GLEN: YUP.
>>RED: HOW MUCH?
>>GLEN: WELL I DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY I KNOW IT'S QUITE A BIT.
>>RED: YOU KNOW WHAT I BET?
I BET IF YOU GO A 100,000
MILES YOU'LL SAVE ENOUGH GAS
MONEY TO MAYBE PAY FOR
THE PLYWOOD.
>>GLEN: WELL RED THERE'S
NO NEED TO BE NASTY OKAY
I MEAN I'M NOT
HURTING YOU ANY.
>>RED: NO YOU'RE RIGHT.
>>GLEN: GEE WHIZ!
>>RED: I'M SORRY.
>>GLEN: YOU KNOW?
>>RED: I'M SORRY
NONE OF MY BUSINESS HOW PEOPLE
WANT TO WASTE THEIR MONEY
I GUESS.
>>GLEN: RIGHT HERE'S FINE RED.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
>>GLEN: YOU KNOW WHAT I FIGURE?
I'LL FINISH THIS I'LL GET
HER ALL PAINTED UP AND
YOU'LL BE FIRST IN LINE TO GO
FOR A RIDE RIGHT THROUGH
THE MIDDLE OF TOWN.
>>RED: YEAH YOU'RE PROBABLY
RIGHT, I DO ENJOY WATCHING
PEOPLE LAUGH.
>>GLEN: YOU MUST.
>>RED: I WAS KIDDING GLEN.
>>GLEN: ME TOO.
>>RED: HEY WHAT'S THIS
WEIRD TRAILER HERE FOR?
IS THAT FOR CARRYING
EXTRA SPOILERS?
>>GLEN: NO THAT'S THE RESEARCH
GUYS FROM THE UNIVERSITY THERE
THEY HAD A SUBMARINE ON
THIS RED.
>>RED: OH.
>>GLEN: YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN
THIS THING, IT WAS PAINTED UP
LIKE A PREHISTORIC ANIMAL
MAN IT WAS UGLY.
>>RED: YEAH WELL YOU SEEM TO
GET A LOT OF UGLY THINGS UP
THIS END OF THE LAKE.
>>RED: (DEEP SIGH)
WELL THE MYSTERY OF PESSIE
THE POSSUM LAKE MONSTER
HAS KIND OF BEEN CLEARED UP.
I SHOULD HAVE GUESSED IT
WAS A SUBMARINE WHEN ONE
DESCRIPTION SAID THE TAIL
WAS A CHROME PROPELLER.
>>HAROLD: PESSIE IS A SUBMARINE?
>>RED: WELL IT WAS UNTIL MOOSE
THOMPSON CHASED IT UP ON SHORE
AND IT WEDGED BETWEEN
THE DOCK AND THE BOATHOUSE.
>>HAROLD: SO NOW IT'S
A SUBMARINE SANDWICH.
(GIGGLING & SNORTING)
BECAUSE IT WAS LIKE IT WAS
THERE AND SQUISHED RIGHT?
BECAUSE SANDWICH YOU SAID
SUBMARINE BUT I SAID SANDWICH
WHICH WAS YOU JUST GO RIGHT
AHEAD I'M NOT HERE.
>>RED: THAT'S THE FUTURE
OF OUR COUNTRY YOU'RE
LOOKING AT RIGHT THERE.
SO I WOULD RECOMMEND PLAY HARD
DIE YOUNG IS THE BEST POLICY.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED WHAT
WAS A SUBMARINE DOING
IN POSSUM LAKE ANYWAY?
>>RED: WELL APPARENTLY IT WAS
SOME KIND OF A MARINE SURVEY
TO FIND OUT WHY THERE ARE
NO FISH IN POSSUM LAKE
WHICH IS CRAZY THAT'S JUST
OUR TAX DOLLARS AT WORK
ISN'T IT HAROLD?
THERE'S PLENTY OF FISH
IN POSSUM LAKE,
THEY'RE JUST DOWN AT THE BOTTOM
YOU KNOW UNDER ALL THEM
APPLIANCES AND SCHOOL BUSES
AND THOSE THERE MUST BE HALF
A DOZEN POWER TRANSFORMERS
DOWN THERE, THERE'S A FEW
IN THERE FOR SURE.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: THAT'S THE
SQUEAL OF THE POSSUM
WE GOT TO GO TO THE MEETING NOW.
>>RED: YEAH YOU GO AHEAD
HAROLD I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
WELL THAT'S ABOUT IT FOR
THIS SHOW BUT ONE THING
I THINK WE'VE PROVEN IS
THAT SOMETHING CAN BE
65 MILLION YEARS OLD
AND STILL BE AN ATTRACTION.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
YOUR DINOSAUR WILL BE COMING
HOME RIGHT AFTER THE MEETING
AND I SURE HOPE I DON'T
WALK INTO THE ICE AGE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE
WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE, ALL RISE.
>>ALL: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: COUPLE OF QUICK
ANNOUNCEMENTS, IF ANYBODY FINDS
A HORSE AND IT LOOKS LIKE IT
MIGHT BELONG TO THE MOUNTIES
WOULD THEY PLEASE RETURN IT
TO JUNIOR SINGLETON
IN THE NEXT 24 HOURS.
THIS IS SERIOUS, OTHERWISE
THE MUSICAL RIDE WILL BE
MISSING A 'B' FLAT.