IF YOU LIKE TO FISH,
BUT DON’T HAVE A BOAT,
YOU END UP SPENDING YOUR
WHOLE LIFE CASTING FROM SHORE,
AND YOU NEVER GET YOUR
BAIT OUT IN THE MIDDLE
WHERE THE BIG ONES LIVE.
SO HERE'S WHAT YOU @O.
GET YOURSELF AN
OLD FLINTLOCK MUSKET.
YOU GET IT FROM
A MUSEUM OR AN OLD GUY
OR YOU COULD PROBABLY MAKE
ONE OUT OF A BICYCLE
OR SOMETHING.
THEN YOU JUST RAM THE POWDER
AND THE WADDING IN THERE
JUST LIKE THEY USED TO BACK
IN THE OLD DAYS, YOU KNOW,
WHEN KILLING SOMETHING
WAS A REAL PAIN IN THE NECK.
IN THIS CASE THE BALL OF LEAD
YOU DROP IN IS ACTUALLY
A SINKER,
AND IT'S HOOKED ONTO YOUR
FISHING LURE
AND THE WHOLE THING IS
ATTACHED TO YOUR FISHING LINE.
THEN ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS JUST AIM IT WHERE
THE FISH ARE AT,
AND YOU'RE IN BUSINESS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
APPRECIATE IT VERY MUCH.
JUST GOT BACK FROM THE
PLUMBING STORE IN TOWN.
THE PLACE WAS JAMMED
TO THE EYEBALLS.
THAT'S BECAUSE THE
PLUMBING STORE IS ALSO THE
COMMUNITY THEATRE
AND THEY'RE HAVING
AUDITIONS THIS WEEK
FOR ANOTHER ONE OF
THEIR YAWN FESTS.
I WENT IN THERE FOR
PIECE OF DRAIN PIPE,
BUT I RAN OUT OF TIME,
SO JUST GONNA RE-INSTALL
THIS OLD ONE HERE.
IT'S STILL GOOD.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
HEY, RED, DO YOU
HAVE A SWEAT -- SWEAT --
A SWEATBAND,
LIKE AN EXTRA --
AN EXTRA SWEATBAND?
IF I HAD AN SWEATBAND
AT ALL, DALTON,
IT WOULD BE AN EXTRA
ONE, BELIEVE ME.
WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO DO?
KILL YOURSELF SO YOU
CAN COLLECT THE INSURANCE?
NO, NO, TRYING TO GET IN
SHAPE FOR THE COMMUNITY
THEATRE AUDITIONS.
I'M JUST ABOUT EXHAUSTED
FROM ALL THIS JOGGING.
OH, YEAH?
HOW FAR HAVE YOU GONE?
OH, JUST FROM
THE DOOR TO HERE.
UPHILL, YEAH.
IT'S ALL UPHILL!
I GOTTA GET
IN SHAPE, RED.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE DOING A
STAGE VERSION OF THE
MOVIE "GLADIATOR."
OH, YEAH, NO,
I SAW THAT ONE.
THAT'S WHERE THE GUY FIGHTS
EVERYBODY TO THE DEATH.
THAT'S THE PART I WANT,
THE LEAD.
THAT'S GONNA TAKE
A FAIR BIT OF ACTING.
NO, NO,
I'LL BE READY, RED.
AND GET THIS.
THEY'VE ALREADY CAST
THE LOVE INTEREST.
OH, MY GOSH. WOW.
FLINTY McLINTOCK'S WIFE.
THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD
LOOKING WOMAN
TO BE HANGING OUT WITH
A GUY LIKE YOU, HUH?
WELL, THAT'S
SHOW BUSINESS.
OH, DALTON, DALTON,
I GOTTA GO.
HOW DOES
ANNE MARIE FEEL
ABOUT YOU DOING THE HOOCHIE
KOOTCHIE WITH FLINTY'S WIFE?
I'LL CROSS THAT BRIDGE
WHEN I COME TO IT.
DALTON, YOU'D BETTER BE
UNDER THAT BRIDGE WHEN
YOU COME TO IT.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER WALKS
AWAY WITH A COUPON
FOR TWO FREE BUNNIES
FROM POSSUM LAKE'S ONLY
ADOPTION AGENCY FOR RABBITS,
HARE TRANSPLANTS.
OKAY, RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET DWIGHT --
YEAH, COVER YOUR EARS --
TO SAY THIS WORD.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, DWIGHT, WHEN YOU SEE
SOMEONE WORKING REALLY HARD
YOU SAY, BOY,
THAT GUY SURE IS...
AN IDIOT.
OKAY, THIS IS A PERSON WHO
DOES A WHOLE LOT OF THINGS,
JUST GO, GO, GO
ALL THE TIME.
YOU CAN SEE
THAT GUY IS...
NOT FROM MY FAMILY.
ALL RIGHT, WHEN A GUY
RETIRES EVERYBODY SAYS
THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING IS TO STAY...
SOBER.
OKAY, THINK OF
AN EXPRESSION,
"AS SOMETHING AS A BEE."
I DON'T KNOW
ANY BEES, RED.
OH, COME ON, DWIGHT.
THIS IS DARNED EASY.
WHAT COMES TO YOUR MIND
WHEN YOU THINK OF BEES?
HAVING TO MOVE.
NOW, THINK, DWIGHT.
THEY'RE CALLED WORKER BEES.
THERE'S GOTTA BE
A REASON FOR THAT.
NOT NECESSARILY.
IT COULD JUST BE
A JOB TITLE
THAT DOESN'T REPRESENT
WHAT THEY REALLY DO,
LIKE SERVICE MANAGER.
YOU'RE JUST ABOUT
OUT OF TIME HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, DWIGHT,
YOU'RE AT THE MARINA,
YOU SUDDENLY REALIZE YOU
HAVEN'T DONE A DARNED
THING ALL DAY,
YOU THINK TO YOURSELF,
BOY, I BETTER GET...
AN ASSISTANT.
WHAT?
OH, YEAH, I NEED ONE.
THIS IS OUR BUSY SEASON.
THERE WE GO!
[ APPLAUSE ]
WHEN IT SMELLS SO BAD
IT CURLS YOUR TOES
AND SOON IT GETS INTO YOUR
HAIR AND YOUR CLOTHES,
DON'T STAND OUT FRONT
HOLDING YOUR NOSE.
GET ME OUT BACK
HOLDING MY HOSE.
THERE WE GO.
MAN, I SURE GET MY
SHARE OF FLAT TIRES.
MUST'VE PICKED UP
A NAIL OR SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, THE TROUBLE
WITH HAVING A FLAT TIRE
IS THE TIME YOU LOSE HAVING TO
PULL OVER TO THE SIDE OF THE
ROAD AND CHANGE THEM.
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT IF YOU
COULD CHANGE YOUR TIRE
WITHOUT STOPPING OR
EVEN SLOWING DOWN?
'CAUSE SOMETIMES ON THE ROAD
YOU GET A SOFT SHOULDER THERE,
AND JACKING UP A VEHICLE
CAN BE VERY DANGEROUS.
SO TODAY I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW YOU CAN MAKE
YOUR VERY OWN
MOBILE WHEEL CHANGER.
OKAY, THE FIRST THING YOU
NEED ARE A COUPLE OF LADDERS.
THEY SELL 'EM NOW WHERE
THEY HAVE THE WHEELS
ON THE ONE END
FOR CLIMBING
WALLS OR WHATEVER.
WELL, YOU WANNA PUT WHEELS
ON THE OTHER END AS WELL.
I WOULD SUGGEST TAKING WHEELS
OFF AN OLD BABY CARRIAGE
BECAUSE, AT MY AGE, A FULLY
FUNCTIONAL BABY CARRIAGE
IS JUST A CRUEL REMINDER OF
WHAT ONCE WAS, BUT IS NO MORE.
OKAY, YOU GOT YOUR LADDER,
YOU GOT YOUR WHEELS.
NOW YOU NEED TO TAKE A
COUPLE OF THESE MINI
HYDRAULIC JACKS
TO ATTACH THE LADDER SAFELY
AND SECURELY TO THE VEHICLE.
OKAY, AS YOU CAN SEE I GOT THE
LADDER RUNNIN' ALL THE WAY
DOWN THE SIDE THERE,
I'VE GOT THE
JACK AT THIS END,
AND I'VE EXTENDED THE LADDER
A FAIR WAYS OUT THE BACK
WHERE MY EMERGENCY
WHEELS ARE THERE.
THAT'LL KEEP ME A
FAIR DISTANCE FROM THE
DISASTER SHOULD THAT OCCUR,
WHICH IS CERTAINLY WELL WITHIN
THE REALM OF POSSIBILITY.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GIVE 'ER A GO.
[ TIRE BLOWS ]
OKAY, HERE'S A CHANCE TO
DEMONSTRATE OUR MOBILE
WHEEL CHANGER.
THAT WAS LUCKY.
STEP ONE...
SET THE CRUISE CONTROL.
OKAY, THIS IS WHERE YOU HAVE
TO BE A LITTLE BIT CREATIVE.
I GOT MY JACK HANDLE HERE.
WORK MY WAY
DOWN TO THE BACK.
THEN INSTEAD OF
JACKING THE CAR UP,
I'M GOING TO JACK
THE LADDER DOWN.
WHOA.
[ HORN HONKING ]
TAILGATER!
OKAY, THIS IS WHERE IT
GETS A LITTLE BIT TRICKY.
I GOTTA GET
THE SPARE OUTTA HERE
WITHOUT LOSING MY BALANCE,
AND I GOTTA GET IT
BACK ONTO THE WHEEL
BEFORE WE COME TO THAT
CURVE IN THE ROAD.
YOU KNOW,
I FIND TODAY'S CARS
TEND TO BE OVERBUILT
ANYWAY, YOU KNOW.
I'M SURE
ONE NUT IS ENOUGH.
IT IS IN MY FAMILY.
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[ TIRE BLOWS ]
I GOT AN IDEA I WANNA RUN
BY ALL YOU MIDDLE-AGED
GUYS OUT THERE.
YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS 19 THE
LEGAL DRINKING AGE WAS 21,
SO ME AND MY FRIENDS HAD TO
GET FAKE I.D. FROM WHEREVER,
JUST SO WE COULD GET
INTO THE BARS.
NOW, THAT DIDN'T
WORK REAL WELL FOR ME.
THAT'S BECAUSE MY FAKE I.D.
SAID I WAS A 27-YEAR-OLD
ORIENTAL WOMAN.
NOW, PRETTY SOON I GOT MY
56th BIRTHDAY COMIN' UP,
AND NOTHIN' SPECIAL ABOUT IT.
I'M LOOKIN' BACK OVER MY LIFE.
I'D SAY I'M A
PRETTY AVERAGE 56-YEAR-OLD.
I MEAN, I LOOK MY AGE,
AND I GOT ABOUT
THE SAME FACULTIES
AS AN AVERAGE PERSON.
AND I KNOW A LOT OF
56-YEAR-OLD GUYS,
SO I'M PAINFULLY AWARE
OF JUST HOW DEPRESSING
THOSE STATEMENTS ARE.
SO NOW MY IDEA IS I'M THINKING
ABOUT USING FAKE I.D. AGAIN.
NOW, YOU MAY LOOK AT ME AND
NOT BE THAT IMPRESSED
THAT I'M 56,
BUT WHAT IF I COULD PROVE
TO YOU THAT I WAS 73?
YOU'D THINK THAT WAS
PRETTY SPECIAL,
ALL THE ENERGY, THE NOT
COMPLETELY ADDLED BRAIN,
THE SIGNIFICANT
HAIR RETENTION.
I MEAN, I'D BE THE MOST
AMAZING 73-YEAR-OLD
YOU EVER SAW,
OTHER THAN TINA TURNER.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE ALL WIN WITH THIS IDEA.
I FEEL GOOD FROM
THE COMPLIMENTS,
AND YOU START LOOKIN' FORWARD
TO BEING A SENIOR CITIZEN.
REMEMBER I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW MY PERSONAL SELF-HELP
GURU ANTHONY ANTHONY?
HE SAYS THAT MEN DON'T
COMMUNICATE VERY WELL
WITH EACH OTHER, EH?
IT'S TRUE.
NO.
WE SHOULD DO
SOMETHIN' ABOUT THAT.
Red:
WELL, HE DIDN'T MEAN US.
WELL, SURE HE DID, RED.
COME ON.
WE SIT IN THIS
BOAT ALL DAY LONG,
AND WE BARELY SAY TWO
WORDS TO EACH OTHER.
Red:
WELL, I'M THINKIN' OF THOSE
TWO WORDS RIGHT NOW, WINSTON.
Mike:
YOU KNOW, MAYBE
HE'S RIGHT, MR. GREEN.
I MEAN, THIS WOULD BE A
PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
TO HAVE INTERPERSONAL
COMMUNICATION.
Winston:
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
WHY DON'T EACH OF US THINK
OF SOMETHING, YOU KNOW,
ABOUT OURSELVES?
SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
SOMETHING THAT WE
ORDINARILY WOULDN'T
SHARE WITH EACH OTHER.
WHO WANTS
TO GO FIRST?
Winston:
I'LL GO FIRST.
OH, BOY.
WITH A WOMAN.
I'VE NEVER BEEN
I HOPE YOU NEVER
GO TO PRISON.
IT'S TRUE.
IN MY WHOLE LIFE I'VE
NEVER BEEN WITH A WOMAN.
AND YOU KNOW
SOMETHIN'?
NOBODY
ELSE KNOWS THAT.
WELL, THE WOMEN
KNOW IT, WINSTON.
Mike:
OH, I GOT ONE.
Red:
NOW, DON'T FEEL YOU HAVE
TO TOP HIM, ALL RIGHT?
AH -- AH, ONCE,
WHEN I WAS IN CHURCH,
I EMPTIED THE COLLECTION
PLATE INTO MY POCKET.
OH, YEAH?
[ CHUCKLING ]
THAT WAS A
POOR CHOICE.
YEAH.
[ CHUCKLING ]
WELL, WHAT ABOUT
YOU, MR. GREEN?
WHAT'S YOUR SECRET?
WELL, THIS IS A LITTLE
EMBARRASSING,
BUT ACTUALLY,
I HAVE NEVER CHANGED THE
OIL IN THE POSSUM VAN.
GONNA BE SICK.
I THINK I'M
COME ON, NOW.
WELL, NO, I MEAN I'VE CHANGED
THE FILTER ONCE, YOU KNOW.
WELL, YOU STARTED THIS.
AH, I'M APPALLED.
WELL, MAYBE SO, BUT YOU
WENT WAY OVER THE LINE.
I FEEL VIOLATED.
WELL, I GOT MY NEW
PIECE OF DRAIN PIPE.
I GOT IT FROM --
WELL, IT DOESN'T
MATTER WHERE I GOT IT.
I JUST GOTTA HIDE
IT FOR A FEW DAYS.
THAT SHOULD BE FINE.
THERE WE GO.
[ LAUGHTER, CHEERING
AND APPLAUSE ]
HAIL CAESAR!
WHAT THE 'HAIL'
ARE YOU DOIN'?
I'M TRYING TO GET INTO
CHARACTER FOR THE AUDITION.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, HUH?
DO PANTYHOSE
COME IN KRYPTONITE?
RED, THIS IS THE WAY THAT
GLADIATORS LOOKED, ALL RIGHT?
WE'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE PRETTY BOYS.
WE'RE FIERCE WARRIORS!
AHHHHHHHH!
HEY! HEY! TAKE IT EASY!
TAKE IT EASY!
THAT WAS PRETTY GOOD.
I WAS ACTING.
YOU WERE ACTING STUPID
IS WHAT YOU WERE DOING.
WHAT?
LISTEN, RED.
I AM GOING
TO GET THE PART.
I'M GONNA LIVE THE LIFE
OF A POWERFUL MAN.
'CAUSE I'VE
NEVER DONE THAT.
AND I'M GONNA HAVE FLINTY
McLINTOCK'S WIFE RIGHT
BY MY SIDE.
THERE'S JUST ONE
THING MISSING.
A SUICIDE NOTE?
NO, I NEED AN AGENT.
I WANT YOU TO BE
MY AGENT, RED.
YEAH, ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS STAND THERE WITH
YOUR ARMS CROSSED
AND SAY NO
TO EVERYTHING.
YOU KNOW, BERNICE MIGHT
BE A BETTER CHOICE.
RED, I WILL GIVE YOU
TEN PERCENT OF MY PAYCHEQUE.
CAN WE MAKE IT 15?
SEE, YOU'RE GOOD!
YOU ARE GOOD.
AND YOU ARE GONNA
MAKE ME A STAR.
EASY. EASY.
AHHHHHHH!
CAREFUL. CAREFUL.
DIE!
DIE, CAESAR!
[ METAL CLANGING ]
OH! OH!
[ CHUCKLING ]
I HAD NO IDEA.
I DON'T KNOW.
Red:
SO MIKE HAD ASKED US TO MEET
HIM BEHIND THE LODGE
WITH AN
EXTENSION LADDER.
HE WAS BRINGING A BICYCLE
WITH A BAD BRAKE, APPARENTLY.
AND THAT WENT --
THAT WENT --
WELL, WE COULDN'T QUITE
FIGURE OUT WHAT HE
HAD IN MIND.
HE SAID HE WANTED US TO HELP
HIM BUILD SOMETHIN'.
IT WAS A SAILBOAT.
HE WANTED US TO HELP HIM
BUILD A SAILBOAT.
WELL, OKAY, THAT'S FINE.
WE COULDN'T FIGURE OUT THE
CONNECTION BETWEEN THE
BIKE AND THE LADDERS,
BUT WITH MIKE IT'S BETTER
NOT TO ASK QUESTIONS.
YOU END UP IN COURT AS
A CHARACTER WITNESS.
SO HE SAID HE HAD EVERYTHING
TO BUILD A SAILBOAT AROUND
THE CORNER,
SO WE BROUGHT
THE STUFF 'ROUND.
AND, YOU KNOW, THE MYSTERY
REALLY WASN'T SOLVED JUST
BY SEEING WHA --
I JUST -- IT WAS A --
SOMETHING UNDER A TARP
THAT DID NOT LOOK
SAILBOAT-LIKE TO ME.
BUT, YEAH, WE DON'T GET IT.
WHAT IS IT?
SO HE'S, OKAY --
OFF COMES THE TARP.
AND, NO THAT'S A --
THAT WOULD BE A VAN.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
THAT COULD POSSIBLY BE --
OH, IS THE STUFF INSIDE?
OH, THE STUFF'S --
WELL, THE DOOR HAD
RUSTED KINDA SHUT.
GIVE 'ER A GOOD --
YOU BUILD UP YOUR STRENGTH
IN PRISON, APPARENTLY,
AND YOU CAN REALLY --
IF YOU SET YOUR MIND TO IT.
HE'S A POWERFUL GUY,
THAT MIKE.
OKAY, I STILL WASN'T SURE
HOW THIS COULD BECOME
A SAILBOAT,
BUT MIKE SEEMED
PLEASED ABOUT IT.
NOW, PUTTING THE HAT ON IS
MAYBE NOT ENOUGH, MIKE,
BUT THEN HE SHOWED US THE
WHEELS COULD ATTACH TO
THE STEERING WHEEL,
AND WALTER HAD THE BICYCLE
THERE TO PULL THE SAIL IN.
AND MY JOB WAS TO ATTACH THE
EXTENSION LADDER TO THE
REAR OF THE VAN,
WHICH IS NOW THE FRONT
OF THE BOAT, APPARENTLY.
AND THEN MIKE SAYS,
JUST HOIST THE MIZZENMAST,
OR WHATEVER IT IS,
AND UP SHE GOES.
AND WE GOT THE
TARP AS A SAIL,
AND, BY GOLLY, BY THE TIME
WALTER WHEELED HER IN,
HEY, WE WERE UNDERWAY.
AND, UH, KINDA DIFFERENT.
WHAT MIKE HADN'T --
THAT WAS UNFORTUNATE.
WHAT HE HADN'T REALIZED
WAS THAT THERE'S
A KIND OF A LOW BRIDGE
BETWEEN THE LODGE
AND THE TOWN,
LOWER THAN,
SAY, THE MAST.
AND SO WALTER
AND I BAILED OUT,
BUT MIKE, HE TOOK THE
HIT FOR THE TEAM,
AND OF COURSE THE
PROBLEM NOW IS
THAT MIKE REALLY CAN'T
SEE WHERE HE'S GOI,
AND, OF COURSE, THERE
IS THE QUARRY THERE.
HIS VERSION OF THE
"PERFECT STORM,"
BUT I THINK MIKE IS
FINISHED WITH SAILING.
ANOTHER POWER BOATER
IN THE MAKING.
THIS IS THE
PORTION OF THE SHOW
WE FEATURE THOSE THREE
LITTLE WORDS MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
audience!
I DON'T KNOW!
OKAY, TODAY'S LETTER
READS AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS, I HAVE A
RATHER UNUSUAL PROBLEM.
"I'M A HAPPILY MARRIED MAN,
"YET I HAVE FALLEN IN
LOVE WITH ANOTHER WOMAN."
OH, GEEZ, READ ANOTHER
LETTER, WINSTON.
GET SOMETHIN' ON
TIME TRAVEL OR PUTTIN'
A BARBEQUE TOGETHER.
NO, NO, NO, NO, THIS IS
EXACTLY THE TYPE OF LETTER
THAT WE SHOULD
BE ANSWERING.
IT GIVES ALL OF US A CHANCE
TO SHOW OUR SENSITIVITY
AND COMPASSION.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
GO AHEAD, WINSTON.
HAROLD WILL ANSWER IT.
OKAY.
"WHENEVER I SEE HER,
MY HEART BEATS FASTER,
"I GET A LUMP IN MY THROAT,
AND I BREAK OUT IN
A COLD SWEAT."
OKAY,
COULD BE LOVE.
COULD BE MALARIA.
MY GUESS IS IF IT LASTS,
IT'S PROBABLY MALARIA.
YOU SAID I COULD
ANSWER THIS ONE.
ALL RIGHT,
I'M SORRY.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, LEMME ANSWER IT.
LEMME ANSWER IT.
ALL RIGHT.
GO AHEAD, WINSTON.
OH, YES HE IS.
"I'M NOT A NUT OR ANYTHING."
OH, YEAH,  WHENEVER THEY
SAY THEY'RE NOT A NUT,
HE'S NOT A NUT!
THEY'RE A NUT, BELIEVE ME.
HE'S A PERSON WITH A PROBLEM,
AND WE ARE GOING TO
HELP HIM SOLVE IT.
READ ON, WINSTON.
"I'M IN LOVE WITH
QUEEN ELIZABETH"
[ LAUGHTER ]
"SHOULD I TELL MY WIFE NOW
OR WAIT UNTIL I'M KING?"
SIGNED,
"ON THE THRONE."
OKAY, I'M GOING
TO NEED A MINUTE.
WELL, I'M NOT.
DON'T TELL YOUR WIFE A THING
UNTIL YOU BECOME KING.
THAT WAY, IF SHE GIVES
YOU ANY GRIEF AT ALL,
YOU CAN HAVE HER
LOCKED UP IN SCOTLAND.
THAT'S NOT HOW
YOU BECOME KING.
FOR INSTANCE, WHAT'S THE NAME
OF THE HUSBAND OF QUEEN
ELIZABETH RIGHT NOW?
PRINCE PHILIP.
EXACTLY.
NOT "KING" PHILIP.
SEE, MARRYING THE QUEEN
DOESN'T AUTOMATICALLY
MAKE YOU KING.
GEEZ, I NEVER NOTICED
THAT BEFORE.
SEE, I THINK THIS FELLA'S
GONNA HAVE TO RE-THINK
HIS WHOLE PLAN.
I DON'T THINK THE ANSWER IS
MARRYING QUEEN ELIZABETH.
OH, I AGREE.
THAT'D BE WEIRD BEIN'
MARRIED TO THE QUEEN,
HAVIN' HER FACE ON
ALL YOUR MONEY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
INSTEAD OF JUST HAVIN'
HER HANDS ON YOUR MONEY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OH, I'M JUST KIDDIN',
BERNICE.
NOW, MY ADVICE
TO THIS PERSON IS
IF YOU WANT TO BE
MARRIED TO A QUEEN,
THEN YOU COULD PRACTICE BY
TREATING THE WIFE YOU
HAVE LIKE ONE NOW.
audience:
A-A-A-A-AH.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT IS SOUND ADVICE
FOR ANY MARRIED MAN.
YOU GUYS HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
IF YOU COME TO SIT
DOWN TO DINNER
AND THERE'S A NINE-INCH
FLAME ON YOUR CANDLE,
YOU BETTER GET YOUR
SEPTICS PUMPED OUT,
OR YOU'LL HAVE MORE ON YOUR
PLATE THAN YOU CAN HANDLE.
WELL, I JUST CAME BACK
FROM THE AUDITIONS.
I'LL TELL YOU,
IT'S NO FUN BEIN' AN AGENT.
I JUST MADE A COUPLE OF
VERY SIMPLE DEMANDS
REGARDING RATE OF PAY AND
DRESSING ROOM BEVERAGES,
AND THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW
THEY KICKED ME OUT OF
THE THEATRE
AND TOLD ME NEVER
TO COME BACK.
AND THAT'S THE ONLY PLUMBING
STORE IN THE TRI-COUNTY AREA!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
DALTON, THAT WAS
NOT MY FAULT.
OKAY, THOSE MORONS
DON'T KNOW TALENT.
I TELL YOU WHAT,
I'M GOING TO GET YOU
OUT OF COMMUNITY THEATRE
INTO THE BIG MONEY.
ADVERTISING.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
WEARING A CHICKEN SUIT
AND HANDING OUT FLYERS?
LISTEN, RED.
LISTEN TO ME.
OH, I KNEW YOU WOULD.
I GOT THE PART.
THERE'S JUST
A SMALL PROBLEM.
WELL, I'M A
PROBLEM-SOLVER, DALTON.
THAT'S WHY YOU PAY
ME THE 25 PERCENT.
I THOUGHT IT
WAS 20 PERCENT!
HE'S RIGHT.
I AM GOOD.
WELL, FLINTY
McLINTOCK'S WIFE CANCELLED.
SHE'S NOT GONNA
PLAY THE EMPRESS.
SHE'S OFF TO DO
A ONE-WOMAN SHOW
FOR THE PORT ASBESTOS
SEEDLESS FRUIT FESTIVAL.
AND THE PRODUCERS PULLED
THE OLD SWITCHEROO ON ME.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
THEY CAN'T DO THAT.
YOU WON THAT PART.
YOU ARE MAXIMUS.
YOU WON IT
FAIRUS AND SQUARUS.
AND I WON'T
LET THEM "SHAFTUS."
THEY DIDN'T SWITCH ME.
THEY SWITCHED THE
LEADING LADY!
YES!
WHAT?
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU ARE ROME,
AND I BELONG TO ROME.
TAKE ME.
RED, WE HAVE TO PLAY
A LOVE SCENE!
IT'S VERY TASTEFUL.
WELL, WE'LL SURE FIND
OUT IF YOU CAN ACT.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
YEAH, YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
MEETING TIME.
I'LL BE DOWN IN
A MINUTE.
OH!
CARRY ME?
AWAY YOU GO.
[ APPLAUSE ]
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMIN' STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I HAD ANOTHER
LIFE LESSON TODAY.
I LEARNED THAT IT'S BETTER
TO DIE BY THE SWORD
THAN TO HAVE A SAME SEX LOVE
SCENE WITH AN EX-CON.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
Winston:
EVERYBODY SIT.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red:
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE.
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, DALTON'S
JUST INFORMED ME
THAT HE'S BOWING OUT
OF THE PLAY,
SO THE ROLE OF MAXIMUS
IS UP FOR GRABS.
WHO WANTS IT?
I GET TO PICK!