[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN,
IN TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD HAS
A SURPRISE FOR ME,
BILL'S GOING TO MAKE
AN OUTDOOR SHOWER,
AND I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW TO EXERCISE
USING A STEPLADDER.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(SHATTERING OF GLASS)
>>HAROLD: SHAKESPEARE WROTE
THAT BREVITY IS THE SOUL OF WIT
AND THAT'S TRUE AND TO PROVE
THAT BREVITY AND SOUL AND
WIT WOULD ALL GO TOGETHER,
HERE'S A SHORT, FUNNY GUY,
MY UNCLE, YOUR HOST, RED GREEN!
WOO! UNCLE RED YEAH!
IT'S UNCLE RED, IT'S UNCLE RED,
IT'S UNCLE RED!
>>RED: THANK YOU, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH AND THANK YOU HAROLD
FOR THAT CLASSY INTRO,
I TAKE IT YOUR ENGLISH
CLASS IS STILL STUDYING
THE BARD OF AVON.
>>HAROLD: WELL SHE SOLD
SOME EYE MAKEUP AND SOME
FACE CREAM TO MY MOM.
>>RED: THE BARD OF AVON HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OH I THOUGHT YOU SAID
BARB FROM AVON, I'M SORRY.
>>RED: SHAKESPEARE HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH, YEAH WE'RE
STUDYING HAMLET IN SCHOOL,
YEAH I GET TO BE HAMLET.
I THINK HE'S THE STAR
YOU KNOW UNLESS IT'S ONE
OF THOSE WEIRD TITLES
THAT'S LIKE WAY OUT THERE,
YOU KNOW SORT OF LIKE
'FRIED GREEN TOMATOES'
THAT ONE YOU KNOW,
BUT I'M GOING TO JAZZ IT UP,
I'M GOING TO ADD SOME PIZZAZZ
TO IT YOU KNOW LIKE THIS.
>>RED: WELL THAT OUGHT
TO DO IT HAROLD.
YOU QUOTING SHAKESPEARE,
I CARRY A LITTLE SHAKESPEAREAN
QUOTE AROUND WITH ME.
IT'S FROM 'MID SUMMER'S
NIGHT DREAM' A LOCAL HABITATION
AND A NAME, SUCH TRICKS
HAVE STRONG IMAGINATION.
>>HAROLD: SO TRUE ISN'T IT?
>>RED: YEAH.
>>HAROLD: I WONDER
WHAT IT MEANS?
>>RED: I HAVE NO IDEA.
>>HAROLD: I'M SORRY,
YOU GO AHEAD UNCLE RED.
>>RED: OH WELL THANK YOU.
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO TELL
EVERYBODY ABOUT THAT PLAN
WE GOT TO DO, BIOSPHERE THREE.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH, ALL RIGHTY,
THAT'S GOOD BECAUSE THAT'S
LIKE BIOSPHERE TWO.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>HAROLD: THAT'S THAT EXPERIMENT
THOSE ENVIRONMENTALISTS
DID IN THE AMERICAN DESERT
WHERE THEY BUILT THIS SEALED
UP COMPLETELY ENCLOSED WORLD,
IT WAS LIKE A GIANT GREENHOUSE
OR SOMETHING.
>>RED: YEAH THAT'S RIGHT,
SO WE'VE GOT SOMETHING.
>>HAROLD: SO YOU KNOW THE
WAY HE IS, THEY GOT LOTS
OF IMPORTANT SCIENTIFIC
INFORMATION FROM THAT BUT MORE
IMPORTANTLY THEY GOT LOTS
OF MONEY TOO.
>>RED: YUP, SO OUR PLAN.
>>HAROLD: SO UNCLE RED
AND ALL THE GUYS,
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
GOING TO DO?
THEY'RE GOING TO LIKE
COMPLETELY ENCLOSE
POSSUM LODGE,
THEY'RE GOING TO PUT PLASTIC
OVER THIS WHOLE MESS,
TRY AND TAP INTO THOSE
GOVERNMENT FUNDS YOU KNOW.
>>RED: SO YOU'RE GOING TO
BE HAMLET ARE YOU HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: YEAH.
>>RED: HAMLET DIES DOESN'T HE?
>>HAROLD: YES BUT NOT UNTIL
AFTER HE KILLS HIS UNCLE.
WHEREVER YOU GO
I'M GOING WITH YOU
WHATEVER YOU DO
I'LL DO IT TOO
WHENEVER YOU MOVE
I'M MOVING WITH YOU
BECAUSE WE'VE
HAD AN UNFORTUNATE
ACCIDENT INVOLVING A VERY
POWERFUL INDUSTRIAL GLUE
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' I'M GOING
TO SHOW YOU A BUNCH OF THINGS
YOU CAN DO WITH A LITTLE
TWINGE OF IMAGINATION
AND SOME STEPLADDERS.
NOW IF YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY STEPLADDERS
I GUESS YOU COULD PORK
A FEW FROM A CONSTRUCTION SITE,
OR YOU COULD JUST TAKE NORMAL
LADDERS AND DUCT TAPE THE
TOPS TOGETHER, THAT'LL WORK TOO.
OKAY THE FIRST PROJECT I WANT
TO SHOW YOU IS YOU GET SOME
OF THESE SPLIT RAILS,
YOU CAN GET THESE JUST BY
PULLING THEM OFF THE BACK
OF A LUMBER TRUCK WHEN HE'S
IDLING AT A LONG TRAFFIC LIGHT.
YOU GET A FEW OF THESE AND
YOU RUN IT RIGHT BETWEEN
YOUR LADDERS, NOTHING TO IT.
AND WHAT YOU'VE GOT THERE IS
A LITTLE SPLIT RAIL FENCE WITH
2 GATES, IF YOU LIVE IN ONE OF
THEM TOWNHOUSE DEVELOPMENTS
NOW AND YOU GET EVERYBODY
TO CHIP IN A STEPLADDER,
YOU COULD HAVE ONE LONG
CONTINUOUS FENCE WITH EVERYBODY
HAVING THEIR OWN GATE WHERE
THE KIDS CAN RUN RIGHT
OUT ONTO THE ROAD.
AND SPEAKING OF KIDS
IF YOU'VE GOT A PIECE OF PIPE
DOWN IN THE BASEMENT OR WHATEVER
OR OUT IN THE GARAGE,
OR MAYBE YOU DON'T SMOKE A PIPE
BUT YOU'LL FIND SOMETHING.
STICK THAT BETWEEN YOUR
LADDERS, HANG YOUR JUMPER
CABLES ON THERE AND YOU GOT
YOURSELF THE DANDY BACKYARD
SWING FOR THE KIDDIES
AND IN THE WINTERTIME NOW
YOU COULD RUN 12 VOLTS THROUGH
THE JUMPERS AND IT WON'T KILL
YOU OR NOTHING, JUST GIVE YOU
ENOUGH OF A HUM TO TAKE THE
CHILL OFF, OR YOU COULD EVEN
HOOK HER UP TO THE 120 HOUSE
CURRENT AND USE IT AS A
DANDY ELECTRICAL FENCE.
ALL RIGHT YOU CAN HAVE A
HECK OF A TIME WITH THIS
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN,
YOU KNOW THIS BRINGS BACK
I THINK THIS BRINGS BACK.
NOW APPEARANCES CAN
BE DECEIVING, THIS IS NOT
JUST AN OLD CRAPPY STEPLADDER,
A WAD OF DUCT TAPE
AND AN OLD DRILL,
THIS HAPPENS TO BE A HIGH
PRECISION VERTICAL DRILL PRESS.
(DRILL BUZZING)
>>RED: BEAUTIFUL, OR YOU COULD
USE THIS SECTION UP IN HERE
TO SAY CRACK WALNUTS,
LOBSTER CLAWS OR EVEN BREAK
THE FOOTBALL HELMET OFF
THE FAT KID.
OR IF YOU GOT A STEPLADDER
AND SAY YOU GOT A SON WHO'S GOT
A COUPLE OF BUNGEE CORDS ON
HIS BIKE RACK, YOU HOOK THE
BUNGEE CORDS UP AND YOU GOT
YOURSELF ONE OF THEM EXERCISER
THIGHMASTER BIKES.
NOT ADVISED FOR ANYBODY
WITH A BIG NOSE OR OTHER
OF THE LARGER OPTIONS.
NOW HERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
YOU CAN USE, A PORTABLE PEN,
YOU JUST TAKE THE STEPLADDER
LIKE THIS AND PUT HER UP AGAINST
A WALL OR A FENCE AND YOU CAN
PUT YOUR KID IN THERE OR A DOG
OR A STRAY CATTLE OR WHAT
HAVE YOU, THEY'RE NOT GOING
TO GO ANY WHERE.
ANOTHER INTERESTING USE
OF A STEPLADDER IS FLIP HER
UPSIDE DOWN, IT WILL HELP
YOU PUT THE DRYWALL ON
YOUR CEILING.
YOU MOUNT THE WHOLE THING
LIKE THAT, PUT YOUR DRYWALL UP
ON TOP OF THE 4 LEGS
INVERTED LIKE SO.
NOW YOU PUT THE WHOLE RIG
ONTO A HYDRAULIC JACK OR
MOOSE THOMPSON, WHATEVER
IS HANDIER AND THEN YOU JUST
JACK THE WHOLE THING UP,
UP AGAINST THE CEILING,
AND THEN GO GET YOURSELF
ANOTHER LADDER AND CARRY
YOUR VERTICAL DRILL PRESS UP
WITH YOU AND YOU CAN SCREW THE
DRYWALL RIGHT INTO THE CEILING,
IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
OF COURSE NOW THE BEST USE OF
THE STEPLADDER IS A LADDER
THAT SAVES YOU STEPS,
SO LET'S SAY YOU GOT TO
GO SOMEWHERE REAL HIGH
AND YOU WANT TO HAVE A REAL
BIG LADDER, WELL YOU DON'T
NEED A REAL BIG LADDER,
ALL YOU NEED IS
MORE STEPLADDERS.
SO YOU TAKE YOUR 2 STEPLADDERS,
YOU PUT THEM TOGETHER,
PUT AN EXTRA BOARD ON THE TOP
TO GIVE IT A LITTLE BIT
OF EXTRA WIDTH.
TAKE YOUR THIRD LADDER,
PUT THAT UP ALONGSIDE
THE OTHER TOO.
(GROANING & GROWLING)
AND THAT'S A LOT EASIER
THAN GETTING A BIG LADDER.
AND I THINK THIS IS WHAT
MICHELANGELO USED WHEN HE
DID THE SISTINE CHAPEL.
NOW YOU'RE UP TWICE AS HIGH,
IF YOU WANT TO GO UP 3 TIMES
AS HIGH YOU'D NEED 3 LADDERS
AND I GUESS ABOUT 30 LADDERS.
OH 6, OKAY 6, 6 LADDERS,
IF YOU WANT TO GO UP 4 TIMES
AS HIGH YOU'D NEED 5...
YOU'D NEED SCAFFOLDING.
WELL OKAY, WELL I GUESS
THAT'S ABOUT IT FOR
A STEPLADDER.
SO UNTIL THE NEXT TIME REMEMBER
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
TIME TO HIT THE WILD,
BLUE YONDER, OH BOY!
IT'S A LITTLE SHAKY
BUT IT'S ALL RIGHT,
OH MY, I DON'T,
OH, OH, OH, UH OH, GRAVITY.
(LOUD CRASHING)
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S FOR
THAT PART OF THE SHOW WHERE WE
EXPOSE THE 3 LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN JUST FIND IT SO
DIFFICULT TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE ARE MY GUESTS
ON 'THE EXPERTS' SEGMENT TODAY,
OF COURSE MY UNCLE RED
AND HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
LETTER NUMBER ONE,
'DEAR EXPERTS, ALTHOUGH
I HAVE A DEGREE IN BOTH
ECONOMICS AND POLITICAL SCIENCE
AND HAVE WON MANY FRIENDLY
GAMES OF 'I'M WAY SMARTER
THAN YOU ARE',
I HAVE NEVER REALLY UNDERSTOOD
HOW COMPUTERS WORK,
CAN YOU EXPLAIN?'
>>RED: HAP?
>>HAP: NO GO AHEAD.
>>RED: WELL, WELL COMPUTERS
ARE A VERY SIMPLE THING.
>>HAP: YEAH THERE'S
NOTHING TO IT.
>>RED: YEAH MAINLY YOU HAVE
YOUR COMPUTER PROGRAMS WHICH
ARE ON THE DISCS AND THE DISCS
GO INTO THE COMPUTER AND
THEY'RE SPUN AROUND THERE
BY A TYPE OF ELECTRIC DRILL,
AND THAT'S FLYING AROUND IN
THERE SO THAT YOUR SOFTWARE
HIGH DENSITY DATABASE UNITS
COME SPINNING RIGHT OFF THE DISC
AND RAM RIGHT UP AGAINST YOUR
TV SCREEN AND THAT ALLOWS YOU
TO PRINT STUFF OFF AND YOU CAN
GET GRAPHS WHICH WILL SHOW YOU
EXACTLY HOW MUCH MONEY YOU'RE
GOING TO LOSE NEXT YEAR.
>>HAP: NOW I BETTER CLARIFY
THAT A BIT I THINK.
BUT TO DO THAT I'D HAVE TO
GO BACK AS FAR AS THE OLD
MORSE CODE THAT I USED DURING
W.W.II WHEN I HAD TO LET MY
SQUAD KNOW THAT I CAPTURED
THIS ENEMY BATTALION SINGLE
HANDEDLY AND THAT I HAD
TO DECLINE THE MEDAL BECAUSE
THERE WASN'T ENOUGH ROOM LEFT
ON THE TUNIC ANY MORE,
IT WAS DISAPPEARING
OVER THE SHOULDER.
BUT WHERE MORSE CODE WAS DOTS
AND DASHES, COMPUTERS ARE
ONES AND ZEROS OR BITS AND
BYTES OR I'S AND BM'S.
AND THEY GOT THIS LITTLE
JAPANESE ROBOT INSIDE THE
CPU AND HE'S GOING LIKE
THAT TO BEAT THE BAND.
>>RED: IT IS WINTER,
I COME HOME LATE FROM
THE OFFICE CHRISTMAS PARTY,
SHE IS ANGRY AT THE SMELL
OF GARLIC ON MY BREATH,
SHE KNOWS I DON'T EAT GARLIC
BUT MY SECRETARY DOES.
>>RED:WHEN YOU'RE IN A BIOSPHERE
YOU GET LONELY SO I THOUGHT
I'D TALK TO THE EXPERT ON THAT
SUBJECT, GORD, ARE YOU ASLEEP?
>>GORD: (SCREAMING) OH FIRE!
FIRE! FIRE! FIRE!
>>RED: GORD, GORD, GORD, GORD,
GORD, GORD, GORD, GORD,
IT'S JUST US.
>>GORD: OH GREAT, VISITORS,
THIS IS GREAT.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>>GORD: OH WONDERFUL, YOU KNOW
IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOUR VISITS
I'D PROBABLY GO TOTALLY WACKO.
>>RED: WELL THAT'S.
>>RED: YEAH WELL THAT'S GOOD,
I'M GLAD TO HEAR THAT.
>>GORD: YEAH THANKS TO YOU
I'M STILL CLINGING ONTO
MY SANITY YOU KNOW.
>>RED: YEAH, GORD WE'RE DOING
A KIND OF A BIOSPHERE THING UP
AT THE LODGE AND I THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU COULD GIVE US A FEW TIPS
ON YOU KNOW HOW TO
LIVE IN ISOLATION.
>>GORD: OH YEAH.
OH YEAH, YEAH WELL YOU KNOW
THE THING TO REMEMBER IS THAT
MIND AND BODY AREN'T SEPARATE,
SO YOU KNOW IF YOU WERE TO
HIT YOUR HEAD REALLY, REALLY
HARD AGAINST A TREE OR A
RANGER STATION OR SOMETHING
YOU KNOW THEY'RE ONE.
SO YOU KNOW TO KEEP THE MIND
ACTIVE YOU'VE GOT TO
KEEP THE BODY FIT.
SO YOU KNOW YOU MUST,
YOU MUST,
YOU MUST INCREASE THE BUST.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>GORD: YOU KNOW WHEN YOU GET
A NEW MIRROR PUT ON THAT VAN
SEND ME THE BILL ALL RIGHT?
>>RED: WITHOUT A DOUBT.
>>GORD: YOU MIGHT WANT TO HAND
DELIVER IT THOUGH BECAUSE
YOU KNOW THE MAIL RARELY
GETS THROUGH HERE, I'M SORRY.
>>RED: WELL THAT'S ALL RIGHT,
I'LL TAKE MY CHANCES ON
THE MAIL DELIVERY,
THANKS ANY WAY GORD.
>>RED: WELL THIS BIOSPHERE THREE
THING IS COMING TOGETHER PRETTY
GOOD ALTHOUGH NOBODY WAS
WILLING TO MAKE A COMMITMENT
UNTIL MOOSE THOMPSON PROMISED
TO WEAR PAJAMAS.
>>HAROLD: YOU KNOW I DON'T
THINK THAT YOU GUYS,
WELL OKAY LET ME REPHRASE
THAT, DO YOU GUYS REALLY
THINK THAT YOU'RE GOING
TO PACK EVERYTHING THAT
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED,
BECAUSE I DON'T.
>>RED: WELL HAROLD I DON'T
REALLY CARE, NO, NO, LET ME
REPHRASE THAT, NOBODY IN THEIR
RIGHT MIND WOULD CARE WHAT
YOU THINK HAROLD.
SO THE GUYS ARE GATHERING UP
ALL THE ESSENTIALS AND THEY
ALL REALIZE THEY'RE GOING
TO NEED THEIR OWN SPACE.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED DO YOU
REALLY REALIZE WHAT'S
REQUIRED OF ALL THIS?
YOU KNOW IT'S GOING TO
BE AN ENCLOSED SPACE,
I MEAN YOU GOT TO BE
COMPLETELY SELF SUFFICIENT,
NOTHING GOES IN,
NOTHING COMES OUT.
>>RED: YEAH HAROLD WE KNOW
HOW THE DEAL WORKS,
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE ALL OUR
OWN FOOD AND BEVERAGES,
THE ONLY PROBLEM WE'RE HAVING
WE CAN'T FIGURE OUT
HOW TO MAKE CHIP DIP.
>>HAROLD: I DON'T KNOW,
I HOPE YOU REALIZE YOU GOT TO
DISPOSE OF YOUR OWN WASTE TOO.
>>RED: WELL THANKS ANYWAY
BUT WE'RE GOING TO KEEP
TRYING FOR THE CHIP DIP.
>>HAROLD: I DON'T KNOW,
I REALLY DON'T THINK
THIS IS GOING TO WORK.
>>RED: IT'S GOING TO WORK FINE,
THESE ARE VERY SIMPLE GUYS,
A LOT OF THESE GUYS COULD
LIVE FOR 2 WEEKS ON A COUPLE
OF COMIC BOOKS AND A
BOTTLE OPENER.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED I KNOW
THESE GUYS COME ON,
THERE'S GOING TO BE ARGUMENTS,
THERE'S GOING TO BE FISTFIGHTS,
THERE'S GOING TO BE LIKE TAG
TEAM TEXAS DEATH MATCHES.
>>RED: I DON'T THINK THERE'LL
BE ANY ARGUING OR FIGHTING
BECAUSE OF COURSE HAROLD
WON'T BE THERE.
>>HAROLD: NO, NO, NO, NO, NO,
I WILL NOT BE THERE, YOU'RE
GOING TO FORGET SOMETHING.
>>RED: IF WE FORGET SOMETHING
WE'LL JUST BORROW IT BEFORE
WE GO IN THERE.
>>HAROLD: NEITHER A BORROWER
NOR A LENDER BE,
SHAKESPEARE SAID THAT.
>>RED: SHUT UP HAROLD,
THE WHOLE WORLD IS SAYING THAT.
UP AT THE LODGE
THE MEN ARE FULL OF BEER
AND THEMSELVES
AND BRAVADO AND BULL
THEY DON'T TAKE NO GUFF
THEY DON'T SETTLE FOR LESS
SO THANK GOD FOR WOMEN
OR WE'D BE IN ONE
HELL OF A MESS
>>HAROLD: I SAID HELL.
>>RED: LOOK OUT! LOOK OUT!
LOOK OUT! LOOK OUT!
OH BILL'S HERE.
NOW BILL SAID HE HAD KIND
OF A SURPRISE FOR ME,
EVERYBODY'S GOT SURPRISES
FOR ME THIS WEEK.
ANYWAY HE WANTED TO MAKE
SOMETHING YEAH, OH YEAH,
AND HE'D GONE DOWN TO THE,
HEY THEY GOT SWISS FAMILY
ROBINSON PLAYING AT THE
POSSUM THEATER IN TOWN,
LIKE I DON'T GO TO THE SHOW
ANY MORE, I JUST CRY AT THE
MOVIES AND THEN THAT'S
JUST WHEN I BUY MY TICKET.
KIND OF A SPRINKLER THERE
AND SOME HOSES AND SOME
HOCKEY STICKS AND CANVAS,
GOT A BICYCLE RIM,
GOT AN OLD PUMP OFF THE
FARM THERE AND I'D PUT THAT,
THAT'LL BE FINE I GUESS.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT HE HAD
IN MIND, SO HE'S TRYING TO,
NO BILL YOU'RE BREAKING IT,
OH I SEE, OKAY, HE'S BREAKING IT
ILLEGAL CURVE I GUESS
ON THAT ONE.
AND THEN HE WANTED ME TO
HOLD THAT AND I SAID, NO,
I DON'T, NO, NO, NO, DON'T,
LIKE LET'S, YEAH THIS IS A
BETTER IDEA, I'LL HOLD THE,
I'D RATHER BE A HAMMER THAN
A GARFUNKEL AND THEN HE WRAPPED
THE CANVAS AROUND THE HOCKEY
STICKS AND DUCT TAPED AND THEN
ONE HOCKEY STICK WENT UP HIGH
AND THEN WE PUT THE SPRINKLER
ON THERE, I'M STARTING TO GET
AN IDEA NOW, THE HOSE IS HOOKED
UP TO THAT PUMP YOU SEE,
AND SO WHAT HAPPENS GOING
TO IS THAT WHATEVER'S IN THE
PUMP IS GOING TO GO AROUND
THE HOSE AND UP THE THING
AND OUT THE AND I THINK WHAT?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, I THOUGHT SO,
IT'S A SHOWER TYPE THING
BUT I'M SAYING WHERE'S THE
WATER GOING TO COME FROM?
YOU GOT TO HAVE WATER GOING
INTO THE PUMP BEFORE YOU CAN
HAVE WATER COMING OUT OF
THE PUMP, BUT HERE AGAIN THE
OLD SWISS FAMILY ROBINSON
INFLUENCE, HE'S GOING TO,
NO BILL NOBODY WANTS,
OH YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
IT'S A RAIN BARREL, YEAH,
YES THAT'LL BE FINE.
WELL THAT'S GOOD, NOW YOU
NEED SOMETHING TO MAKE
THE PUMP GO AROUND.
THE PUMP'S GOT TO SPIN BILL,
YOU JUST KIND OF TURN THAT WAY,
NO, NO, WELL HE HAD JACKED UP
NOT ONLY THE PRICE OF HIS CAR
BUT ACTUALLY THE WHOLE BACK END,
AND HE TOOK THE TIRE OFF
AND HE PUT JUST A RIM ON THERE,
NOW WHAT'S GOING ON THERE?
OH I SEE, WHAT HE'S THINKING
THERE IS HE CAN USE THAT AS
A DRIVE WHEEL, HE GOT AN OLD
FIRE HOSE THERE AND YEAH OKAY,
THIS IS LIKE A POWER TAKEOFF
ON THE OLD JOHN DEERE,
NOTHING TAKES OFF LIKE A DEER.
AND SO I WRAPPED THE FIRE HOSE
AROUND THERE AND WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN IS I GUESS IS THAT
WHEN YOU START HER UP AND PUT
HER IN GEAR AND WHAT HAVE YOU,
THE WHEEL'S GOING TO SPIN WHICH
IS GOING TO MOVE THE, WHICH IS
GOING TO, YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S GOING TO DRIVE THE PUMP,
IT'S GOING TO PUMP THE WATER
FROM THE RAIN BARREL,
DOWN TO THE HOSE AND UP
THE SPRINKLER.
SO HE SAID TO ME HE IS GOING
TO GET READY TO TAKE A SHOWER,
LET ME START HER UP HERE
AND SHE'S, OH THERE YOU
GO, SHE'S RUNNING GOOD,
OH BILL YOU'RE GOING TO SPOOK
THE HORSES THERE, WOW!
HE WANTS ME TO PUT HER INTO GEAR
AND YOU KNOW IT'S UNFORTUNATE
HE'D FORGOTTEN ONE LITTLE DETAIL
THAT BABY IS A FRONT WHEEL DRIVE
OH THAT'S UNFORTUNATE ISN'T IT?
YOU KNOW ANYBODY WHO PUTS THAT
MUCH WORK AND INGENUITY
INTO SOMETHING DESERVES
A SHOWER DON'T YOU THINK?
>>HAROLD: THIS WEEK ON
WE'RE GOING TO BUILD STUFF
TO IMPRESS THE GIRLS
IN YOUR SCHOOL.
NOW IN MY EXPERIENCE WOMEN
LIKE TO MAKE THE MOVE ON
GUYS WHO HAVE A LOT OF
ELECTRICAL EQUIPMENT,
BUT YOU KNOW VIDEO AND AUDIO
EQUIPMENT COSTS MAJOR DOLLARS
AND IF ALL YOU'VE GOT IS LIKE
YOUR ALLOWANCE OR EVEN WORSE
YOU KNOW A PAY CHEQUE FROM
YOUR UNCLE, THEN YOU KNOW
THE HANDY TEEN'S GOING
TO HAVE TO BE CREATIVE.
SO FIRSTLY LET'S BUILD A
FAKE WALKMAN OUT OF A PIECE
OF BLACK WOOD AND SOME
BLACK STRING.
WELL NO IT'S NOT GOING
TO WORK OR ANYTHING,
BUT LOOK, YOU JUST PLUG IT
IN RIGHT AND THEN YOU KNOW
YOU SING LIKE A POPULAR SONG
ALONG WITH IT AND WHO'S GOING
TO BE THE WISER YOU KNOW?
HAROLD SINGING
OH LOOK THAT GUY IS
WEARING A WALKMAN,
WHO KNOWS THAT IT DOESN'T WORK,
I CERTAINLY DON'T.
YOU KNOW IT'S LIKE THAT,
YOU CAN DO THAT RIGHT,
SO TO GET STARTED WHAT
WE'RE GOING TO NEED OF COURSE
IS THE HANDY TEEN SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
>>RED: HAROLD, HAROLD?
(DOOR LOCK RATTLING)
>>HAROLD: NEXT WEEK
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO BUILD
A LOCK FOR YOUR ROOM.
>>RED: (SHOUTING) HAROLD!
>>HAROLD: SO WE'LL
JUST TAPE THAT UP.
>>RED: HAROLD,
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: WELL IT'S MY PART
OF THE SHOW AND YOU SAID
IF I COME UP WITH
AN ORIGINAL IDEA.
>>RED: ORIGINAL HAROLD?
HANDY TEEN CORNER?
A HANDY TEEN SECRET WEAPON?
>>HAROLD: REMEMBER IF THE
CHEERLEADERS DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME, AT LEAST THEY
SHOULD ASK YOU TO DO
THEIR HOMEWORK FOR THEM.
>>RED: NOW I KNOW A LOT OF
YOU TEENAGERS FEEL YOU HAVE
TO REBEL AND BE OBNOXIOUS
AND EMBARRASS YOUR PARENTS
AT RESTAURANTS, BUT THAT'S JUST
A NORMAL PART OF GROWING UP
WHEREAS GETTING A
TATTOO IS STUPID.
A TATTOO IS BASICALLY
A LIQUID SLIVER AND A
LIQUID IS PERMANENT INK.
GETTING A TATTOO IS KIND
OF LIKE SUCKING ON A PEN
WITH YOUR WHOLE BODY,
AND IT'S PAINFUL.
THERE'S ONLY 2 THINGS MORE
PAINFUL THAN GETTING A TATTOO,
THE FIRST ONE BEING GETTING
2 TATTOOS AND THE SECOND ONE
IS GETTING EITHER ONE OF
THEM REMOVED.
NOW I KNOW THERE MIGHT BE
SOME APPEAL IN HAVING GUNS
AND ROSES TATTOOED ON YOUR BUTT,
BUT 60 YEARS FROM NOW IN
THE MIDDLE OF YOUR HEMORRHOID
OPERATION YOU'RE GOING TO
FIND OUT WHY IT'S NOT
A GOOD IDEA TO GET YOUR
SURGEON LAUGHING.
>>REG: HEY HELLO RED,
I FIGURED ONCE THE SMELL
OF THIS STARTED WAFTING
ACROSS THE LAKE YOU'D
SHOW UP.
>>RED: YUP, WE THOUGHT EVERY
JOGGER IN THE WORLD HAD TAKEN
THEIR SHOES OFF AT EXACTLY
THE SAME MOMENT.
>>REG: YOU CAN'T FOOL ME RED,
I KNOW YOU JUST LOVE TO WRAP
YOURSELF AROUND A BOWL OF
MY SPECIAL CHOWDER.
>>RED: WELL MAYBE SOME TIME REG
BUT UNFORTUNATELY YOU'VE CAUGHT
ME ON A DAY WHEN I'M NOT
STARVING TO DEATH.
WHAT IS IN THERE ANYWAY,
IS THAT SKUNK?
>>REG: NO, NO MEAT RED,
I DON'T EAT MEAT
I'M A HUNTER NOT A BARBARIAN.
NO RED WHAT YOU GOT HERE
IS CABBAGE, BEET ROOT,
BRUSSEL SPROUTS, BROCCOLI
AND A BIG, YELLOW TURNIP.
YOU SOAK THEM ALL IN VINEGAR
UNTIL YOUR EYES WATER SO BAD
YOU CAN'T TIE YOUR SHOES,
THEN YOU BRING THE WHOLE
DEAL TO A BOIL FOR A DAY
AND A HALF AND THEN POUR IT
INTO EXPLOSION PROOF CONTAINERS.
MMM, IF I HAD EATEN THIS
HEALTHY BACK IN THE LAW FIRM
I'D BEEN ABLE TO HANDLE
TWICE THE CASELOAD.
>>RED: WELL YOU WOULD OF GONE
THROUGH A LOT MORE SUITS
THAT'S FOR SURE.
NOW LISTEN REG, WE'RE DOING
THIS BIOSPHERE THING UP AT
THE LODGE AND I THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU MIGHT HAVE SOME LEGAL TIPS
YOU KNOW BEFORE WE ALL KIND
OF BUNK IN TOGETHER
LIKE THAT.
>>REG: WHOA, YOU HAVE TO BE
VERY CAREFUL THERE RED,
YOU SHOULD REALLY DRAW UP
A CONTRACT GOING IN THAT
EXPLAINS HOW PROBLEMS
WILL BE DEALT WITH.
MY NIECE WENT INTO ONE OF
THESE DEALS AND SHE CAME OUT
WITH A BUNCH OF NEW FRIENDS
AND A BRAND NEW BABY.
>>RED: GOLLY, HOW LONG
WAS SHE IN THERE?
>>REG: WELL THE BIOSPHERE
PROGRAMS ARE ALWAYS FOR
A MINIMUM OF 2 YEARS
LESS A DAY RED.
>>RED: 2 YEARS, MY WIFE DOESN'T
LET ME BE AWAY FOR 2 YEARS,
SHE SAYS I CAN EITHER BE AWAY
FOR THE ODD WEEKEND HERE
AND THERE OR I CAN BE AWAY
ALL THE TIME FOREVER,
BUT NOTHING IN BETWEEN.
>>REG: OH SURE, MY WIFE
WENT FOR PLAN 'B'.
BUT I DON'T BLAME HER,
YOU KNOW I THINK SHE'D LIKE
ME BETTER NOW BUT SHE'S OFF
IN EUROPE WITH THAT TENNIS
INSTRUCTOR SO SHE HAS NO
IDEA WHAT SHE'S MISSING.
>>RED: WELL AS SOON AS EVERYBODY
FOUND OUT THIS BIOSPHERE THREE
THING WAS A 2 YEAR COMMITMENT
THAT PRETTY WELL KIND OF
KIBOSHED THE WHOLE DEAL.
I MEAN WE ALL GET ALONG
PRETTY WELL BUT 2 YEARS
IS 730 DAYS OR MORE
IMPORTANTLY 730 NIGHTS.
THAT'S 98,000 MEALS
AND 6 LAUNDRY DAYS,
SOMEBODY WOULD GET
HURT GUARANTEED.
>>HAROLD: DO YOU KNOW UNCLE RED
IT'S TOO BAD WE CAN'T TREAT THE
EARTH LIKE A BIOSPHERE,
ALWAYS BEING CAREFUL NOT TO
TAKE OUT MORE THAN WE PUT IN.
>>RED: WELL WE CAN START
BY BURYING YOU.
>>HAROLD: I'M JUST SAYING
WE SHOULD RESPECT THE
BIOSPHERE THAT WE HAVE.
>>RED: AND WILL THE GOVERNMENT
PAY US TO DO THAT HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: NO.
>>RED: SEE THERE'S A PROBLEM
RIGHT THERE, SEE THEY GOT THEIR
PRIORITIES ALL COMPLETELY
SCREWED UP DOWN THERE YOU KNOW.
I WOULD BE HAPPY TO SAVE THE
PLANET FOR THE NEXT GENERATION
IF THERE WAS ANY MONEY IN IT.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH IT'S MEETING TIME,
IT'S MEETING TIME, HERE WE GO.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD
HAROLD, I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
>>RED: I'M SURE HE MEANS
WELL BUT WHO CARES.
ANYWAY IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
I MIGHT BE A BIT LATE
BUT I'LL STILL BE 2 YEARS
EARLIER THAN I THOUGHT I'D BE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT HAVE A SEAT.
ALL RIGHT I KNOW A LOT OF
YOU HAD YOUR HEART SET ON
THE BIOSPHERE THING AND I'M
JUST SORRY IT DIDN'T WORK OUT.
>>ALL: OHHHH!