ARE JUST IMPROVEMENTS ON
EXISTING TECHNOLOGY.
I'M TALKING ABOUT LASER
BEAMS, NUCLEAR POWER,
EVEN THE
JIFFY-POP POPCORN.
IN THE OLD DAYS PEOPLE USED
TO PAINT THEIR HOUSES
WITH A PAINT BRUSH,
BUT THEN SOME GUY INVENTED
THE PAINT ROLLER.
NOW, TODAY I'M GOING TO
PUT ON A COAT OF CLEAR
DRIVEWAY SEALER,
AND YES, I'M GOING TO USE THE
PAINT ROLLER TECHNOLOGY.
BUT I'M TAKING HER TO
A WHOLE NEW LEVEL.
[applause]
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
YEAH, WELL,
I APPRECIATE THAT.
WE'VE GOT A BIT OF A SITUATION
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
SOME GIANT BIRD HAS CHOSEN THE
CHIMNEY AT POSSUM LODGE HERE
AS ITS NESTING PLACE.
YOU SHOULD SEE THIS THING.
IT'S GOT THE SKINNY LEGS
AND THE WING SPAN IT'S LIKE,
KIND OF DOES A THING
WHERE IT JUST --
OH,
IT'S OKAY, RED,
I'LL COME BACK WHEN YOUR
DEODORANT DRIES.
NO, I WAS JUST
TELLING EVERYBODY ABOUT
THE BIG BIRD WE GOT HERE.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
QUITE THE STIR, ISN'T IT?
OH, GEEZ, THAT'S CAUSING
YOU KNOW WHAT, I SMELL
A BUSINESS OPPORTUNITY HERE.
WELL, SURE, YOU KNOW,
A GIANT BIRD FLYING
THROUGH THE SKY,
GREAT TIME TO
OPEN A CAR WASH.
RED, IT'S A WHOOPING CRANE.
THEY'RE PRACTICALLY EXTINCT.
WELL, I KNOW
HOW THEY FEEL.
YEAH.
THE EGG IN THE BIRD'S NEST?
HAVE YOU SEEN THE SIZE OF
OH, WHOOPING CRANES
HAVE HUGE EGGS.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT
MAKES THEM WHOOP.
HAS ANYBODY GOT
ANYTHING TO EAT?
MIKE, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO
BE KEEPING AN EYE
ON THAT BIRD?
I WAS BUT SHE FLEW AWAY ABOUT
THREE HOURS AGO AND
NEVER CAME BACK.
THREE HOURS, BOY,
THAT'S A LONG TIME
FOR A MOTHER TO BE
AWAY FROM THE NEST.
NOT REALLY.
MY MOTHER WAS AWAY FOR
TWO YEARS LESS A DAY ONCE.
WELL, WHAT IF SOMETHING
HAPPENS TO HER?
YOU KNOW WHAT,
SOMEBODY'S GOT TO GO UP ON
THAT ROOF AND CHECK THAT EGG.
OKAY, OKAY,
I GOT IT.
SHORT STRAW GOES, OKAY?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
SHORT GUY GOES.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheering and applause]
TODAY'S WINNER WILL RECEIVE
THIS BRAND NEW CELL PHONE.
I ALREADY GOT A
PHONE IN MY CELL.
OKAY, COVER
YOUR EARS, MIKE.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET MIKE TO SAY THIS WORD.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT, MIKE, WHEN YOU
WERE IN SCHOOL AND YOU
WROTE AN EXAM,
YOU WOULD EITHER
FAIL OR YOU --
CHEATED.
OKAY, THE SPACE BETWEEN TWO
MOUNTAINS, THAT'S CALLED --
CLEAVAGE?
OKAY, WHEN THE GUY IN FRONT
OF YOU IS DRIVING TOO SLOW,
WHAT DO YOU DO?
OH, SHOOT HIS TIRES.
OKAY, MIKE, WHEN YOU WANT TO
GO TO JAIL FOR THE WEEKEND,
YOU GOTTA GET A --
HOSTAGE.
OKAY, LET'S GO
ANOTHER WAY WITH THIS.
LET'S SAY YOU SEE A WOMAN IN
A BAR WHO INTERESTS YOU,
YOU GO OVER TO HER
AND YOU MAKE A --
FOOL OF MYSELF.
ALMOST OUT OF
TIME HERE, RED.
YEAH, UM,
ALL RIGHT, MIKE,
JUST TELL EVERYBODY WHERE
YOU WERE LAST NIGHT
BETWEEN THE HOURS OF
ONE AND THREE-THIRTY A.M.
UM, I'LL PASS.
THERE YOU GO!
[applause]
WHEN THE AIR IN YOUR YARD
HAS A SLIGHT TINGE OF BLUE,
WHEN YOU FIND LITTLE TREES
ON THE SOLE OF YOUR SHOE,
WE'LL COME WHEN YOU CALL
'CAUSE WE LOVE WHAT WE DO.
AT ROTHSCHILD'S WE'RE PUMPED,
AND YOU SHOULD BE TOO.
YOU KNOW, A LOT OF THE VIEWERS
ASK ME WHERE I GET ALL
MY IDEAS FROM,
I WANT TO GIVE THEM AN
ANSWER BECAUSE SOMETIMES
THEY MEAN IT IN A NICE WAY.
NOW, I'M NOT ONE
OF THOSE GUYS WHO JUST
WALKS AROUND IN A VACUUM
AND COMES UP WITH THINGS
OUT OF THIN AIR.
I KNOW THAT WORKED FOR
EINSTEIN AND GALILEO,
BUT I GUESS THAT'S JUST
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
ME AND THEM.
NOW, I ALWAYS START
WITH SOMETHING
AND THEN KINDA
TAKE IT FROM THERE.
FOR EXAMPLE, RIGHT HERE I
HAVE A 500-FOOT ROLL
OF BUTCHER PAPER.
YOU KNOW, THAT STUFF THEY WRAP
MEAT IN TO HIDE THE EVIDENCE
AFTER YOU'VE KILLED,
SKINNED AND GUTTED
A HARMLESS
DOMESTIC ANIMAL?
I'M JUST KIDDING YOU.
OKAY, FIRST THING I
DO IS TAKE A LOOK AT THE
PROPERTIES I'M WORKING WITH.
THIS STUFF HAS ONE SIDE THAT'S
SHINY AND KIND OF STICKY
AND THE OTHER SIDE IS
SMOOTH AND VERY SLIPPERY.
NOW I JUST TAKE A MINUTE
AND SEE WHAT MY MIND
CAN COME UP WITH.
[laughter]
OH, I'M SORRY.
WHAT WAS I SAYING?
OH, RIGHT, YEAH,
THE BUTCHER PAPER.
[harp music]
I COULD USE IT
AS A MEMO PAD,
WHERE YOU COULD JOT DOWN
PHONE NUMBERS OR MESSAGES
OR MAYBE A GROCERY LIST
WHERE YOU WRITE DOWN
WHATEVER YOU NOTICED YOU
WERE RUNNING OUT OF
AND THEN HAVE THE
CONVENIENCE OF BEING ABLE
TO RIP THE NOTE OFF
AND TAKE IT WITH YOU.
OR FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO
DON'T HAVE A GARAGE --
OH, SURE,
THOSE ARE GREAT IDEAS,
BUT THEY'RE
JUST NOT PRACTICAL.
NOW, THIS IS WHERE THE
CREATIVE HANDYMAN TAKES IT
TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
ALL RIGHT, WHAT'S THE
WORST PART ABOUT SUMMER?
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN'T GO TOBOGGANING.
THAT'S BECAUSE TOBOGGANS
WON'T SLIDE ON GRASS AND SAND.
THEY NEED
SOMETHING SLIPPERY,
LIKE ICE OR SNOW
OR THE SLIPPERY SMOOTH SIDE
OF MY BUTCHER PAPER.
OKAY, YOU WANT TO
POSITION YOUR TOBOGGAN
FACING DOWN THE HILL IN
THE WAY YOU WANT TO.
BUT BEFORE YOU
GET TOO EXCITED,
YOU WANT TO GET SOMETHING
HEAVY, SOME WEIGHT
OF SOME KIND.
I'VE GOT A COUPLE
OF ROCKS HERE,
AND YOU WANT TO PUT THEM ON
THE END OF THE PIECE OF PAPER.
I'LL EXPLAIN WHAT THAT'S
ALL ABOUT A LITTLE LATER.
BUT THE BEAUTY NOW IS
I CAN GO TOBOGGANING
ANY TIME I WANT.
AND IF I DO HAPPEN TO
SPLIT MY HEAD OPEN ON A ROCK
WELL, I'VE GOT PLENTY OF
PAPER TO WRAP IT UP IN.
SO REMEMBER, IF WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING,
THOUGH, IT DOESN'T END HERE
BECAUSE I'VE STILL GOT TO GET
THE TOBOGGAN BACK UP THE HILL.
SEE THIS?
THIS IS A CORDLESS DRILL.
THIS IS OUR FRIEND.
REMEMBER THOSE ROCKS
I PUT ON THE PAPER?
NOT LOOKING SO
DUMB NOW, AM I?
[applause]
A LOT OF STRANGE THINGS
HAPPEN IN LIFE, DON'T THEY?
LIKE YESTERDAY I SAW THIS
MIDDLE-AGED COUPLE.
THEY STOPPED AT AN
INFORMATION BOOTH AND
ASKED FOR DIRECTIONS.
THE WIFE ASKED ALL
THE QUESTIONS.
THE HUSBAND JUST STOOD THERE
AND STARED AT THE PERSON
BEHIND THE COUNTER.
AND THEN WHEN THEY WERE DONE
THE WIFE TURNED AROUND,
STARED AT THE HUSBAND.
HE TOLD HER EVERYTHING THE
INFORMATION PERSON HAD SAID,
AND THEN THEY LEFT.
SEE, THEY WERE
WORKING AS A TEAM.
THE WIFE WAS FOCUSED
ON THE QUESTIONS,
PAID NO ATTENTION
TO THE ANSWERS,
THE HUSBAND ONLY HEARD
THE ANSWERS,
DIDN'T HAVE A CLUE WHAT
THE QUESTIONS WERE.
THAT'S BECAUSE THIS COUPLE'S
BEEN TOGETHER LONG ENOUGH
TO REALIZE MARRIAGE IS
ABOUT JOB SHARING.
I MEAN, YOU CAN FEED, CLOTHE
AND SHELTER YOURSELF
ON YOUR OWN.
BUT ISN'T IT MORE INTERESTING
TO SHARE THAT WITH
ANOTHER PERSON?
NOT ONLY BRINGS US CLOSER
TO ZERO UNEMPLOYMENT,
IT GIVES YOU
SOMEONE ELSE TO BLAME.
LIKE, TO ME,
MARRIAGE AND JOB SHARING,
WELL, THAT'S A NATURAL,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU
DECIDE TO HAVE KIDS.
CONCEPTION IS THE BEST
JOB SHARING IN THE WORLD.
IT'S GREAT WORKING CONDITIONS
AND REALLY SHORT SHIFTS.
MOST DAYS YOU DON'T EVEN
HAVE TO GO IN TO WORK.
REMEMBER I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
THIS A BAD TIME,
GORD?
HAVE A SEAT.
I'LL BE WITH
YOU IN AOMENT.
OH, LOOK,
A FOREST FIRE.
YEAH, THEY GO OUT
ON THEIR OWN.
THERE WE GO.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
WRITING A LETTER, GORD?
THAT'S KIND OF A PERSONAL
QUESTION, DON'T YOU THINK?
I MEAN, WHAT IF I WAS
WRITING A LETTER?
WHAT IF I WAS
WRITING A LOVE LETTER?
WHAT IF I WAS WRITING A
LOVE LETTER TO SUSAN SARANDON?
I STILL DON'T SEE HOW THAT'S
ANY OF YOUR BUSINESS.
HERE, COULD YOU
MAIL THIS FOR ME?
DIDN'T YOU WRITE HER A
LOVE LETTER BEFORE?
YEAH.
EXACTLY, YEAH.
DID SHE WRITE BACK?
REALLY?
SHE DID.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
OH, YEAH.
WOW!
LETTER RIGHT THERE.
THERE'S HER
NO, THIS IS FROM
HER LAWYER, GORD.
OKAY, THAT'S
THE WRONG LETTER, OKAY.
YEAH.
THIS STRAIGHTENED OUT.
I MEAN, I'VE GOT ALL
I'VE MET ALL
THEIR CONDITIONS.
YEAH, THERE'S HER
LETTER RIGHT THERE.
DEAL RIGHT THERE.
THERE'S THE REAL
THIS IS IT?
THIS IS FROM
SUSAN SARANDON?
YES, SIR.
CAREFUL WITH THAT.
BOY, GORD,
YOU KNOW,
HER HANDWRITING IS
IDENTICAL TO YOURS.
I KNOW.
ISN'T IT GREAT?
SHE IS SO
PERFECT FOR ME.
WE WRITE THE SAME.
OH, YEAH.
THIS IS STARTING TO
FEEL LIKE "SESAME
STREET" HERE.
IN TODAY'S EPISODE,
BIG BIRD HAS BUILT A
NEST UP IN OUR CHIMNEY
AND NOW BERT
AND ERNIE HERE
ARE GOING TO GO UP
AND CHECK THE EGG.
OH, NO, NOT ME, RED.
JUST MIKE.
OH, THE ROOF'S IN SUCH
BAD SHAPE IT'LL ONLY
HOLD ONE OF US.
YOU THINK THAT RIG
IS SAFE, MIKE?
OH, SURE, I'LL JUST THROW
THIS ANCHOR OVER THE
PEAK OF THE ROOF
AND TIE THE OTHER END OF
THESE BED SHEETS TO
THE DOOR OVER HERE.
AND I'LL PULL MYSELF UP.
IT'S JUST LIKE
BREAKING OUT OF PRISON
I'VE DONE IT
100 TIMES.
RED, COME HERE.
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OKAY, UM, OKAY.
WE CAN TALK TO MIKE
THROUGH THIS STOVEPIPE,
WHICH IS CONNECTED TO THE
CHIMNEY UP ON THE ROOF.
OH, OKAY.
WHAT'S HE GONNA DO ONCE
HE GETS TO THE NEST?
WELL, WE DON'T KNOW
IF THAT MOTHER CRANE IS
GONNA COME BACK, RIGHT?
SO MIKE'S GONNA HAVE TO
BRING THE EGG DOWN HERE.
OH, BOY.
[footsteps on roof]
Mike:
CAN YOU GUYS HEAR ME?
YEAH, YEAH.
WE HEAR YOU.
YEAH, YEAH,
Mike:
OKAY, I'M GOING OVER
TO THE CHIMNEY NOW.
OKAY WATCH
YOUR STEP, MIKE
Mike:
IT DOESN'T LOOK TOO BAD.
[crunch!]
MIKE,
ARE YOU OKAY?
Mike:
WELL, YEAH I'M FINE, BUT
MY FOOT'S STUCK IN THE HOLE.
I CAN'T PULL IT OUT.
GIVE HER A GOOD YANK,
THERE, MIKE.
Mike: OKAY.
[Mike groaning]
Mike:
GOT IT!
[footsteps on roof]
Mike:
OKAY, I'M AT THE NEST.
I CAN SEE THE EGG.
IT'S HUGE!
IT'S LIKE
MOOSE THOMPSON'S HEAD!
YEAH, EXCEPT THE EGG HAS
GOT SOMETHING IN IT.
ANY SIGN OF
THE MOTHER CRANE?
Mike: No.
I GUESS YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO BRING IT DOWN, MIKE.
Mike:
OKAY, I'VE GOTTA DIG
IT OUT OF THE NEST HERE.
GIVE ME A SECOND.
BE CAREFUL, MIKE.
WE WANT THE EGG OVER
EASY NOT SCRAMBLED, EH?
Mike:
HEY, I GOT IT.
WHAT THE HECK IS THAT?
[brid cawing]
Mike:
OH, NO, THE MOTHER
CRANE IS BACK!
OW! OW! OW! OW!
SHE'S TRYING TO
PROTECT THE EGG, MIKE.
PUT IT BACK
IN THE NEST.
Mike:
OW! OW! SHE WON'T LET ME
GET NEAR THE NEST.
I'VE GOT TO
TOSS IT BACK IN.
NO! NO! NO!
Mike:
OW! OW!
YOU TAKE IT.
[Mike screaming]
RED, COME ON,
MIKE MIGHT BE HURT.
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS,
DALTON.
YOU'RE GOING
TO BE A MOTHER.
Red:
A BUNCH OF US WERE PLAYING A
LITTLE ROAD HOCKEY, THERE,
AND WALTER, COMES IN ON
A BREAKAWAY AND HE
JUST FIRES ONE
RIGHT UP, RIGHT OVER
THE WHOLE DEAL,
AND IT GOES RIGHT DOWN
THE DARN SEWER.
SO NOW HOW WE GONNA --
IT'S THE ONLY PUCK WE GOT,
AND WE GOTTA GET THE PUCK
BACK, AND AS I'M SAYING
WELL, WALTER, YOU DID IT.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
GET THAT OFF THERE?
PULL THE GRATE OFF THERE.
PULL THAT OUT,
LIFT THE --
I'LL PULL YOU AND
YOU LIFT THE GRATE.
SO THEN DALTON HAD AN IDEA
THAT MAYBE HE COULD GET
HIS ARM DOWN THERE.
MAYBE IT GOT CAUGHT ON
A LEDGE OR SOMETHING,
AND THEN SOMETHING GRABBED
HIM, AND I'M THINKING
HE'S IN TROUBLE,
BUT TURNS OUT HE'S
JUST JOKING AROUND.
THAT'S REAL FUNNY, YEAH.
SO DALTON BRINGS
HIS JOCK OVER,
WHAT DID YOU BRING
YOUR JOCK FOR?
WELL, HE SAYS,
THAT'S A PUCK MAGNET.
AND SO HE'S GONNA DROP
THAT IN THERE AND --
I'VE GOT ANOTHER IDEA.
I FIGURE LET'S GO IN
SOMEWHERE ELSE
AND THAT WAY WALTER CAN CRAWL
BACK TO THE GRATE WHERE
THE PUCK IS AND --
SO THEY DROP THE FISHING ROD
AND THEY COME ON OVER
I FIGURE WALTER SHOULD DO IT.
HE'S THE ONE WHO PUT IT DOWN
THERE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
SO WE PULL THAT
THING UP AND --
WALTER DOWN YOU GO,
AWAY YOU GO.
GET IN THERE.
DOWN YOU GO.
AWAY YOU GO.
SO WALTER GOES DOWN FOR
THE PUCK AND THEN
DALTON IS HUNGRY
HE WANTS TO GO GET --
SO I SAY TO WALTER, WELL,
ALL RIGHT, TELL YOU WHAT,
YOU GET THE PUCK.
WE'RE GONNA GO
GET SOME LUNCH.
OKAY, WE'RE JUST GONNA
GO GET SOME LUNCH.
NOW, HE'S CONCERNED THAT
A CAR MAY COME
AND THE WHEEL MAY GO DOWN
THE HOLE AND EVERYTHING --
WELL, DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
HERE'S WHAT WE'LL DO.
WE'LL PUT THE LID DOWN.
DON'T WORRY IT'LL BE FINE.
THERE.
AND WE GO OFF
TO GET SOME LUNCH.
AND WHAT WE DIDN'T REALIZE IS
THAT WINSTON IS ON HIS ROUNDS
AND HE COME UP AND PARKED
RIGHT ON THE ACTUAL
MANHOLE COVER HIMSELF.
AND I DIDN'T KNOW WHETHER
WINSTON WAS STOPPING
FOR LUNCH.
NO, APPARENTLY NOT.
HE'S JUST COMING FOR A --
HE COULDN'T FIGURE WHAT
THIS ALL WAS ABOUT,
SO HE JUST PULLED THAT
OUT OF THERE AND --
I THINK THE PUCK WAS
IN THERE WASN'T IT?
ANYWAY HE -- WELL, HE
DOES WHAT HE HAS TO DO
AS PART OF --
I'M FIGURING --
NOW BY THIS POINT
WALTER'S HAVING A TOUGH DAY.
SO WE COME BACK -- OH,
WE REALIZE WHAT'S GOING ON,
WE'VE GOTTA BACK
THE TRUCK OFF THERE,
SO WE FIRE IT UP
AND BACK IT UP.
AND WINSTON CAN'T FIGURE
OUT WHAT'S GOING ON
BUT WALTER WAS,
I'LL TELL YOU,
IN A BIG HURRY TO GET
OUT OF THERE.
BUT HE'S OKAY.
HE'S OKAY.
AND, OF COURSE,
ALL I'M CONCERNED ABOUT --
I WANNA MAKE SURE
HE GOT THE --
DID YOU GET THE PUCK?
DID YOU GET THE PUCK, WALTER?
THAT'S THE MAIN THING.
NO, HE DIDN'T GET IT,
BUT WINSTON'S GOT IT
HE TOOK IT OUT OF --
WE'LL THERE WE GO --
SO WE CAN GO --
C'MON, DALTON.
WE CAN GET BACK --
AND WINSTON,
GREAT GUY THAT HE IS,
OFFERED TO GIVE WALTER
A RIDE HOME,
WHICH I THOUGHT WAS
REAL NICE OF HIM.
BUT, OF COURSE, HE DIDN'T
MEAN IN THE CAB.
YOU GO BACK WITH
YOUR OWN KIND THERE, WALTER.
WE'LL SEE YOU LATER.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT'S
PORTION OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE FEATURE THOSE THREE
LITTLE WORDS MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY,
audience: I DON'T KNOW.
THOSE ARE THE WORDS.
AND A SPECIAL
WELCOME TO HAROLD.
WELL, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH, WINSTON,
I'M ALWAYS HAPPY TO
SHARE THE WISDOM OF
MY ACCUMULATED YEARS.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S ALWAYS
CERTAIN RIGHTS OF PASSAGE
OF EVERY YOUNG MAN --
OKAY.
SHUT UP, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW,
THAT WAS WRONG.
I SHOULDN'T
HAVE SAID THAT.
THAT WAS WRONG.
I APOLOGIZE.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE
TOLD YOU TO SHUT UP.
APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
SHALL I CONTINUE?
OKAY.
NO.
TODAY'S LETTER
READS AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS, I WORK IN AN
OFFICE NEXT TO SOMEBODY
"WITH A BODY ODOUR PROBLEM.
"IS THERE SOME WAY I
CAN LET HIM KNOW ABOUT IT
WITHOUT CAUSING OFFENSE?"
OH, NO, JUST GET
UPWIND OF THE GUY.
THAT'S WHAT
A BREEZE IS FOR.
THAT'S NOT REALLY THE ADULT
WAY TO HANDLE THE PROBLEM,
YOU KNOW.
THERE'S ALWAYS A SUBTLE,
SENSITIVE WAY TO POINT
OUT THE PROBLEM
AND SUGGEST SOLUTIONS.
OFTENTIMES A GIFT
WOULD DO THIS.
OH, SURE, LIKE ON
HIS BIRTHDAY
YOU COULD GIVE
THE GUY A BATH.
YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT'S BETTER TOO?
YOU KNOW WHAT'S BETTER TOO?
IS LIKE, AT CHRISTMAS -- AT
CHRISTMAS YOU COULD GET HIM
AN ANONYMOUS
SECRET SANTA GIFT.
LIKE A SECRET SANTA
SOAP ON A ROPE.
I OFTENTIMES USE
THE SECRET SANTA APPROACH
TO DISTRIBUTE
MY HOMEMADE FUDGE.
THAT WAS YOU?
YES, WHY?
YOU OWE ME A BOTTLE
OF KAOPECTATE.
YOU OWE ME A
SET OF SEAT COVERS.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT,
ACTUALLY IN RETROSPECT
I THINK YOU
TWO ARE RIGHT.
WHAT YOU SHOULD DO IS TAKE
THE GENTLEMAN ASIDE
IN PRIVATE
AND THEN POINT OUT
THE PROBLEM WHERE --
YOU KNOW, GIVE HIM TIME
TO FIND A SOLUTION.
I THINK THAT'S
SOMETHING WE'VE ALL
LEARNED HERE TODAY.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT,
I THINK SO TOO.
WINSTON, I WONDER IF I COULD
SPEAK TO YOU IN PRIVATE
AFTER THE SHOW.
SURE.
UNCLE RED, I'D LIKE TO
SPEAK TO YOU IN PRIVATE
AFTER THE SHOW TOO.
DALTON, THEY WERE OUT
OF JALAPEÑO CHIPS
SO I HAD TO GET YOU
SOUR CREAM AND ONION.
ISN'T THAT GREAT?!
YOU HAVE DONE NOTHING FOR
THIS ENTIRE PREGNANCY.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE ACTING
KINDA STRANGE, DALTON.
I'M SORRY, RED.
I AM SO SORRY.
THE SOUR CREAM AND ONION
CHIPS WILL BE FINE.
I'M SORRY.
GO GET THEM.
GO GET THEM!
WINSTON!
Winston:
YEP? YEP?
YEP?
WINSTON!
WHAT?
THIS ICE CREAM
IS TOO COLD.
I'VE GOT TO BE CAREFUL
ABOUT MY BODY TEMPERATURE.
LOOKIT, WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE A BIRTH HERE SOON.
I'VE GOT MUCH BETTER
THINGS TO BE DOING
THAN WARMING UP
YOUR ICE CREAM.
YEAH, AND I SUPPOSE I'VE GOT
NOTHING BETTER TO DO
THAN TO SIT ON
THIS STUPID EGG!
OH, OH, IT'S HAPPENING!
IT'S REALLY HAPPENING!
OH, OH.
SOMEBODY BOIL
SOME WATER!
WE'RE NOT GOING TO
COOK THE EGG, MIKE.
STOP SQUEEZING MY ARM
SO HARD, YOU BONEHEAD.
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
OH, I'M AFRAID.
NO, I'M AFRAID
I'M AFRAID.
OKAY, OKAY.
TO BREATHE.
JUST REMEMBER
[breathing heavily]
OH,
IT'S CRACKING!
OKAY.
GIVE THE THING A CHANCE.
WELL, GET UP, DALTON.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
[bird chirping]
Red:
CONGRATULATIONS, DALTON,
IT LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU.
I'M GONNA TAKE HER OUTSIDE
TO HER NEW HOME,
THE SKY.
ALL RIGHT.
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU TWO
GUYS GO AHEAD.
DALTON AND I WILL BE
DOWN IN A MINUTE.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT, DALTON.
COME ON NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
SHE WENT BACK TO
HER BIRTH MOTHER.
YEAH, WELL,
OF COURSE SHE DID.
BUT YOU DID
THE RIGHT THING.
AND DALTON, DID YOU REALLY
WANT ANOTHER DAUGHTER?
AWAY YOU GO.
IT'S AN EXCELLENT POINT.
YOU GO ON DOWN
TO THE MEETING.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
AND IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND WITH ALL THESE CRANES
FLYING AROUND HERE TODAY
I WAS WONDERING IF MAYBE
YOU AND I MIGHT
DO A LITTLE WHOOPING IT UP
OURSELVES TONIGHT.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND MOTHER DALTON
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE.
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
Mike: SIT DOWN EVERYBODY.
OKAY, EVERYBODY SITTING DOWN?
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, I WOULD
LIKE TO SHOW ALL OF
OUR APPRECIATION
FOR DALTON'S EFFORTS TO
PRESERVE A DYING SPECIES
AND ALSO FOR
HATCHING THAT EGG.