WHEN YOU READ CLASSIC MYTHOLOGY
BY AUTHORS LIKE HOMER
OR THE BROTHERS GRIMM
OR SUPERMAN COMICS,
YOU REALIZE THAT A LOT OF MEN
ARE OBSESSED WITH IMMORTALITY.
THAT'S WHY THEY HAVE KIDS
SO SOME PART OF THEMSELVES
WILL LIVE ON.
AND THEN WHEN THEY SEE
HOW THE KIDS TURN OUT,
THEY COME UP WITH
ANOTHER PLAN.
LIKE THEY'LL BUILD SOMETHING
THAT WILL LIVE FOREVER.
THEY MIGHT CARVE A STATUE
OF, SAY, PAUL BUNYEN'S OX.
THEY'D RATHER CARVE A
STATUE OF THEMSELVES,
BUT THEY KNOW NOBODY
WILL GO LOOK AT IT.
MEN WOULD RATHER LIVE IN
REFLECTED GLORY
THAN HAVE NONE AT ALL.
THAT'S WHY THEY
WEAR TEAM JACKETS.
IT'S NOT SMART OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT MAKES US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red: IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
HOTDOGS WITH ALL THE TRIMMINGS,
MAN, HAVE YOU COME
TO THE RIGHT PLACE,
OR HOW ABOUT
A LITTLE TURKEY?
THAT'S HAROLD
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
RANGER GORD WE'RE
GOING TO SEE HIM,
HE'S BEEN OUT THERE A
WHILE, HASN'T HE?
AND WINSTON IS GOING
TO TRY TO GET A WORD IN.
AND NOW HERE'S A GUY WHO
NEEDS NO INTRODUCTION.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Red: THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AND HERE'S A GUY WHO NEEDS
MORE INTRODUCTION
THAN I HAVE THE STOMACH
TO GIVE HIM,
MY NEPHEW HAROLD.
A BUNCH OF US SITTING AROUND
THE LODGE LAST NIGHT,
KIND OF CHOWING
INTO THE PORK AND BEANS,
AND WE STARTED THINKING ABOUT
WAYS WE CAN MAKE MONEY.
WE'VE BEEN DOING AN AWFUL
LOT OF THAT LATELY.
HE MEANS THE SITTING AROUND
AND THE PORK AND BEANS PART,
THAT'S WHAT THEY
DO A LOT OF,
AS OPPOSED TO THE MAKING MONEY
AND THINKING PART.
YOU KNOW, IT OCCURRED TO US
THAT A LOT OF PEOPLE WILL
PAY BIG MONEY
TO SEE THOSE ATTRACTIONS
LIKE GRAND CANYON OR
NIAGARA FALLS
OR EVEN THAT GIANT SLEEPING,
GIANT SLEEPING GIANT,
GIANT THING
THEY GOT UP THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THESE THINGS ARE?
THESE ARE NATURAL WONDERS.
SO NATURALLY WE'RE WONDERING,
WHAT ABOUT ROCK REEF POINT?
HAROLD, WHAT DO YOU SEE
WHEN YOU LOOK AT ROCK
REEF POINT?
A ROCK,
A REEF AND A POINT.
HAROLD, DON'T USE YOUR EYES,
USE YOUR IMAGINATION.
OH. ALRIGHTY.
WELL, ON A CLEAR SUMMER DAY,
YOU KNOW, REALLY LATE
IN THE DAY,
SOMETIMES I SEE A
MARUVIAN SPACE STATION.
YOU KNOW, IT'S GOT TWIN
LANDING PODS,
AND IT'S GOT THOSE PHASER
OUTPOSTS, YOU KNOW,
THAT PROTECT THE MICROWAVE
TRANSPORTER BASE
AND IT SITS DIRECTLY IN FRONT
OF THAT COMPUTER ENHANCED
DIGITAL BETA
SCREEN THING.
IT'S A SLEEPING POSSUM,
THAT'S WHAT IT LOOKS
LIKE, HAROLD.
HO HO HO, OKAY.
I DIDN'T SEE THAT.
IT LOOKS LIKE A GIANT
SLEEPING POSSUM
MADE OUT OF GRANITE,
LYING ON ITS BACK.
WELL, WHERE'S THE LEGS?
WHERE ARE THEY?
WELL, WE'LL ADD THEM ON,
WE'LL MAKE THEM OUT
OF PLYWOOD.
WHAT ABOUT THE HEAD
AND THE TAIL?
SAME THING, HAROLD,
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
WE'VE GOT THE BODY,
THAT'S THE TOUGH PART.
SO ONCE YOU GET ALL THAT
STUFF GLUED ON THERE,
WE'RE GOING ADVERTISE
IT AS THE GIANT
SLEEPING POSSUM
MADE OUT OF STONE.
WHY DON'T YOU LEAVE IT
AS IT IS AND ADVERTISE IT
AS THE GIANT SLEEPING
POSSUM THAT WAS RUN
OVER BY A TRAIN?
YOU KNOW ON THIS JOB
I'M ALWAYS SUPPOSED TO BE
WATCHING OUT FOR
FOREST FIRES.
BUT ONCE IN A WHILE I'VE GOT
THIS INCREDIBLE URGE TO BLINK,
BUT I DON'T.
OH YOU HEAR A LOT OF TALK
ABOUT SPINACH AND SOY
AND WHICH ONE MAKES
THE PERFECT SUPPER
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO
THAT I'LL TELL YOU BOY
YOU CAN'T BEAT
PEANUT BUTTER
EASY TO CUT,
EASY TO CHEW
AND IT NEVER GOES
HARD AS A ROCK
PEANUT BUTTER IS
THE ONE AND ONLY FOOD
SO GOOD IT MADE
MR. ED TALK
ALL RIGHT, THAT SPECIAL
LADY IN YOUR LIFE HAS GOT
A BIRTHDAY COMING UP,
AND YOU HAVE ABSOLUTELY
NO IDEA WHAT TO GET HER.
NOW, JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE
CLOSE THAT DON'T MEAN
SHE'S GOING TO WANT
THEM POWER TOOLS
YOU'VE BEEN EYEING, EH?
AND NEVER, NEVER,
NEVER, NEVER, NEVER
GO INTO A LADY'S CLOTHING
STORE, ALL RIGHT?
'CAUSE YOU'RE JUST GOING
TO END UP BUYING SOMETHING
THAT THE MANAGER
NEVER THOUGHT SHE'D
SELL TO ANYBODY WITH
WORKING EYESIGHT.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, GUYS
WHO HATE SHOPPING SHOULD
NEVER FIND THEMSELVES
IN A WOMEN'S
CLOTHING STORE, EH?
YOU'RE GONNA JUST WALK
OUT WITH SOME DRESS
MADE OUT OF
LIKE CARPETING
OR SOMETHING, EH,
OR THE UGLIEST SEE-THROUGH
NIGHTY IN THE WORLD
FULL OF THEM LIKE
HAPPY FACE PATCHES.
AND YOU GOT TO BE CAREFUL
YOU DON'T BUY A GIFT
SHE TAKES AS
AN INSULT, YOU KNOW,
LIKE, SAY, A MEMBERSHIP
TO A FITNESS CLUB
OR DANCE LESSONS
OR A FACELIFT COUPON.
I RECOMMEND CASH, EH,
IT'S THE GIFT THAT
KEEPS ON GOING.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU COULD DO,
EITHER BUY SOMETHING TO
EAT OR SOMETHING THAT DIES.
LIKE A PET?
NO, LIKE FLOWERS.
OH.
YEAH. YEAH.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW YOU'RE
GOING TO MAKE A MISTAKE,
BUT WITH FOOD OR FLOWERS,
YOU KNOW, THERE'S A LIFE
EXPECTANCY THERE.
YOU CAN THROW THEM OUT,
IT'S OKAY.
WHEREAS WHEN YOU GET ONE
OF THEM JELLY-FILLED
GLOW IN THE DARK
COMBINATION NECK MASSAGER
AND BEER COOLER
WITH THE BUILT-IN DIGITAL
CLOCK AND REPLICA SWISS
ARMY KNIFE,
THEY GO ON FOREVER.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK
THE BEST GIFT IS?
JUST SPEND SOME
QUALITY TIME WITH
THE LITTLE MISSUS,
YOU KNOW, TAKE HER TO
ONE OF THEM CLASSY
RESTAURANTS
WHERE THEY GOT
REAL METAL CUTLERY.
OH YEAH, OH YEAH,
THAT WILL SHOW HER
THAT YOU THINK SHE'S
SOMETHING SPECIAL
ALL RIGHT.
UNLESS SHE'D
PREFER THE CASH.
[ RED COUGHING ]
WELL, WITH ROCK REEF POINT
ABOUT TO BECOME
THE NUMBER ONE TOURIST
SPOT IN THE AREA,
I THINK IT'S UP TO THE
RESIDENTS OF POSSUM LAKE
TO MAKE THOSE
TOURISTS FEEL AT HOME
BY TAKING AS MUCH OF
THEIR MONEY AS POSSIBLE.
AND THE BEST WAY TO DO THAT
IS BY SELLING THEM
OVERPRICED FOOD.
SO TODAY ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW
YOU CAN MAKE A PORTABLE
SNACK COUNTER.
YOU KNOW, TODAY'S URBANITE,
EVERYTHING IS GO, GO, GO,
SO IF YOU WANT TO
SELL THEM ANYTHING,
YOU GOT TO BE
ON THE GO YOURSELF.
THAT'S THE BEAUTY OF
THIS UNIT RIGHT HERE.
ALL'S YOU NEED IS A PIECE OF
KITCHEN COUNTER TOP
AND A COUPLE OF
OLD SEAT BELTS
THAT WERE JUST WEARING
A HOLE IN THE BACK OF
YOUR PANTS ANYHOW
AND YOU'RE ALL SET.
JUST PICK HER UP AND YOU
CAN FOLLOW YOUR TOURIST
DOWN THE STREET
OR EVEN INTO THE WOODS
PREPARING FOOD
AS THEY CHECK OUT
THE VARIOUS SITES.
NEXT STEP, PICK YOURSELF UP
A BUNCH OF THESE SMALL
APPLIANCES,
WHICH YOU CAN GET AT
A YARD SALE OR WHATEVER.
YOU MIGHT
GET AN OLD TOASTER
OR ONE OF THESE HOT AIR
POPCORN POPPER UNITS
OR A CAMP STOVE OR --
YOU GET THE IDEA OF IT.
NOW, YOU NEED ELECTRICITY
FOR SOME OF THESE
BECAUSE THEY'RE ELECTRICAL
APPLIANCES AND THEY USE
THAT TYPE OF THING.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS GET
YOURSELF A SHOPPING CART.
NOW, A LOT OF
THE SENIORS USE THESE
SO THEY'RE EASY
TO BORROW... OR WHATEVER.
AND WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS OPEN THAT UP
AND FILL THAT UP WITH
SOME OF THE CAR BATTERIES,
AND THEN YOU WANT TO CUT THE
HANDLE HERE RIGHT IN HALF
SO SHE'LL THREAD
THROUGH YOUR BELT LOOPS,
MAKES IT EASIER
FOR TOWING.
NOW TO CONNECT ALL THE
APPLIANCES ON TO THE COUNTER,
WE COULD DRILL HOLES
AND BOLT THEM IN THERE
OR WE COULD GLUE THEM ON
WITH SOME SORT OF A
POLYMER ADHESIVE,
BUT THAT WOULD PROBABLY RUIN
THE MARBLE LAMINATE
BAKE STUFF,
SO INSTEAD WE'RE GOING TO USE
THE HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
SHE'S STARTING TO
TAKE SHAPE, ISN'T SHE?
GOT EVERYTHING LAID OUT HERE
JUST THE WAY I WANT IT.
GOT THE POPCORN MAKER
THERE AT THE END, GOT THE
TOASTER NEXT TO THAT,
AND THEY'RE BOTH SITTING
ON TOP OF MY MICROWAVE
OVEN THERE.
THAT'S ALL PLUGGED IN TO
THE BATTERIES OF COURSE
AND I GOT THE CAMP BARBECUE,
KIND OF A NEAT LITTLE THING,
THE BRIQUETTES
ARE A LITTLE SCARY.
AND OVER ON THIS SIDE
I GOT THE DEEP FRYER,
AND I GOT THE CREPE MAKER,
I GOT DONUTS THERE,
I GOT THE DRINKS AND I GOT A
LITTLE HOT PLATE OVER HERE
AND I GOT A LITTLE HOT
CHOCOLATE, CAPPUCCINO
OR SOMETHING.
AND THIS HERE IN THE TAP HOLES,
SOMETHING REAL NEAT HERE,
IDEAL FOR THE CONDIMENTS.
I JUST REACH DOWN UNDERNEATH
GIVE THIS A LITTLE SQUEEZE,
AND I GOT MYSELF
SOME KETCHUP.
WANT TO ADD A LITTLE MUSTARD
TO THAT, NO PROBLEM.
LET'S FIRE HER UP.
MAYBE FIRE
IS A BAD WORD.
I GOT HER WORKING NOW,
AND I CAN FOLLOW THOSE TOURISTS
ANYWHERE THEY WANT TO GO,
MAKING FOOD FOR THEM.
EVEN IF THEY'RE
NOT ON THE GO,
THEY CERTAINLY WILL BE
AFTER EATING THIS STUFF.
SO IF WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
HERE'S COOKING
AT YOU, KID.
Red: STAY TUNED AND
SEE WHAT NOT TO DO
WITH ONE OF THEM RADIO
CONTROLLED MODEL AIRPLANES;
AND I'M GOING TO MAKE AN EAR
BIGGER THAN PRINCE CHARLES'.
I WANT TO TALK
TO ALL YOU GUYS
WHO ARE JUST CELEBRATING
YOUR 50th BIRTHDAY
OR JUST GETTING
OVER THE HANGOVER.
YOU'LL KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT WHEN THEY BRING IN
THE BIRTHDAY CAKE
AND TELL YOU EVERY CANDLE
REPRESENTS A DECADE.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU GET
TO MID-LIFE A LOT OF TIMES
YOU STOP AND REFLECT
ON YOUR ACCOMPLISHMENTS,
YOUR POSITION
IN THE COMMUNITY
AND YOUR CAREER
AND YOUR FAMILY SITUATION.
AND A LOT OF TIMES YOU COME
TO THE CONCLUSION THAT
LIFE STINKS
AND YOU REALLY BLEW IT.
BUT YOU KNOW YOU GOT TO LOOK
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE, YOU KNOW,
ACTUALLY ALMOST
EVERYBODY'S LIFE STINKS.
HARDLY ANYBODY GETS
WHAT THEY WANT.
MILLIONAIRES WANT TO BE
BILLIONAIRES,
MARRIED GUYS WANT
TO BE PLAYBOYS,
PLAYBOYS WANT TO MEET
SOMEONE WORTH MARRYING.
MAYBE YOU REGRET NOT MARRYING
THAT FIRST GIRLFRIEND
WHEN YOU WERE
BOTH SWEET 16.
BUT, REMEMBER, YOU'RE
NOT SWEET 16 ANYMORE
AND NEITHER IS SHE.
IF YOU PASSED EACH OTHER
ON THE STREET TODAY,
YOU'D BOTH BE THINKING, BOY,
SOMEBODY'S REALLY LET
THEMSELVES GO.
SO IF YOU'RE SITTING
THERE THINKING
THAT YOUR LIFE IS OVER
AND YOU REALLY BLEW IT,
REMEMBER YOUR LIFE
IS ONLY HALF OVER
AND YOU ONLY HALF BLEW IT.
SO GET OUT THERE
AND FINISH THE JOB.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, THE PROJECT TO
TURN ROCK REEF POINT
INTO A GIANT SLEEPING POSSUM
HAS HIT A FEW SNAGS.
I MADE THE LEFT EAR,
STINKY MADE THE RIGHT EAR
AND MOOSE THOMPSON MADE A
HEAD OUT OF HOLLOW PLYWOOD.
WHY WOULD HE MAKE
THE HEAD HOLLOW?
WORKING FROM EXPERIENCE,
I GUESS, HAROLD.
THEN STINKY ATTACHED A SHEET
METAL TAIL TO THE END
OF HER THERE
AND THEN THE WIND COME UP
AND WE HAD A REAL PROBLEM.
YEAH, I KNOW, A BIG WOODEN
EYE WENT FLYING PASSED
MY BEDROOM WINDOW.
I THOUGHT I WAS IN
THE TWILIGHT ZONE.
YOU ARE, HAROLD.
THE WHOLE FACE WENT UP AND
SMASHED TO A MILLION BITS
ON TOP OF
ROCK REEF POINT,
BUT THE METAL TAIL SWUNG DOWN,
JAMMED RIGHT INTO
THE ROCK FACE,
AND THEN WE NOTICED
WHAT WE HAD THERE,
WE HAD A ROCK FACE
WITH A GIANT METAL TAIL
JAMMED IN THERE FOR A NOSE.
AND YOU KNOW WHO THAT
LOOKED LIKE, HAROLD?
OH, YEAH,
IT WAS AMAZING, YEAH.
IT LOOKED JUST LIKE A
GUY WITH NO FACE
AND NO HAIR
AND A BIG POSSUM TAIL
FOR A NOSE.
EXACTLY,
JOHN A. MacDONALD.
RONALD McDONALD'S
BROTHER?
SIR JOHN A. MacDONALD,
HAROLD,
THE FIRST
PRIME MINISTER OF CANADA.
AND NOW WE'RE GOING TO
PUT ANOTHER FACE ON EACH
SIDE OF HIM THERE,
AND WE CAN HAVE A
NATURAL FORMATION
LIKE THAT MOUNT RUSHMORE
THEY GOT IN THE STATES.
UNCLE RED, THOSE FACES ARE
CARVED INTO THAT STONE
OF MOUNT RUSHMORE.
IT'S NOT A
NATURAL FORMATION.
YOU SHOULD TALK.
WELL,
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
IF THEY CAN CARVE THEM,
WE CAN CARVE THEM.
WHAT WE'LL DO IS PUT
SOME FACES UP THERE
OF THE MEN WHO HAVE MADE
THIS COUNTRY AS GREAT
AS IT IS, HAROLD.
OH, GREAT, THE FATHERS
OF CONFEDERATION AND
WAYNE GRETZKY!
WE'RE HERE AT
FIRE TOWER 13
WITH THE MAN WHO STANDS
ON GUARD FOR TREES,
RANGER GORD.
THANKS A LOT
FOR COMING, RED.
ALL RIGHT,
NO PROBLEM.
THANKS A LOT.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
COME HERE, HAROLD.
COME HERE.
WHERE ARE THE
REST OF THE GUYS?
OH, THEY'RE UP AT
ROCK REEF POINT,
YOU KNOW, CARVING ROCKS,
THAT KIND OF THING.
I MADE STONE BAKED
PIZZA FOR EVERYONE.
OH MY GOSH.
YEAH.
IT'LL BE COOKED
BY HIGH NOON.
WELL, MAYBE HAROLD AND I
WILL HAVE A PIECE
OF THAT LATER,
BECAUSE WE DO WANT TO
TALK TO YOU ABOUT ROCKS,
YOU KNOW,
IF YOU WERE GOING TO,
SAY, DO SOME CARVING
OR MAYBE MAKE LIKE A
MOUNT RUSHMORE TYPE
OF THING,
WHATEVER IT WAS THAT
YOU HAD IN MIND.
YOU GUYS ARE MAKING
A MOUNT RUSHMORE?
WELL, YEAH, BUT WE'RE
DOING IT WITH FAMOUS
CANADIANS, YEAH.
THAT'S WHY YOU
CAME TO ME?
WELL, YEAH, BECAUSE
I THOUGHT WITH THE
ROCK THING.
OKAY!
WHAT? WHAT?
I'M GOING TO BE
IMMORTALIZED
IN STONE.
GOSH.
THE MAN WHO NEVER
ABANDONED HIS POST.
THE MAN WHO
NEVER LOST FAITH,
RANGER GORD, WHO'S HEAD,
100 FEET HIGH,
SOLID ROCK.
YEAH, THAT PART
SOUNDS RIGHT.
OKAY, WELL, A LOT OF
THE ROCK AROUND HERE
IS IGNEOUS ROCK.
IT'S PART OF THE
CANADIAN SHIELD.
IT'S GRANITE.
PERFECT FOR CARVING.
AND WHAT ABOUT THE ROCK
UP AT ROCK REEF POINT?
WELL, MOST OF THAT IS
MICA, SANDSTONE AND
LIMESTONE.
WOW.
YEAH, IT WAS FORMED FROM
THE WASTE OF THE QUARRIES
THAT USED
TO BE AROUND HERE.
OH, SO IF YOU TRIED
TO CARVE THAT STUFF.
LANDSLIDE.
OH BOY, HAROLD,
WE GOTTA GO.
NO. NO.
WHAT ABOUT THE PIZZA?
[ SLOSHING SOUND ]
Red: EW! OH!
JUST HAVE SOME
OFF YOUR SHOE.
IT'S MAIL CALL.
WHOO!
ALL RIGHT,
WE GOT A LETTER HERE.
HERE'S THE FIRST LETTER.
IT'S FROM NEIL BARON OF
MOUNT PEARL, NEWFOUNDLAND.
AND NEIL POSES A
NUMBER OF QUESTIONS,
BUT THE ONE THAT STRUCK
MY FANCY WAS,
"DEAR RED  GREEN, WHAT IS
YOUR FAVOURITE POWER TOOL?"
THAT'S A
TOUGH ONE, NEIL, 'CAUSE,
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY
THERE'S A RIGHT TOOL
FOR EVERY JOB,
EXCEPTION BEING
HAROLD HERE.
YOU REALLY HAVE TO CLARIFY
WHAT THE WORK IS
BEFORE YOU CAN PICK
YOUR FAVOURITE TOOL.
FOR EXAMPLE, YOU WOULDN'T
WANT TO BUILD A DOCK
WITH A LATHE.
MAYBE THE MOST VERSATILE TOOL
WOULD BE A GOOD CHOICE,
YOU KNOW, LIKE AN
ELECTRIC DRILL.
IT HAS A VARIETY OF
APPLICATIONS.
YEAH, OKAY, MOST DEFINITELY
AN ELECTRIC DRILL
WOULD BE MY CHOICE,
MOST DEFINITELY.
HE'S NOT ASKING
YOU, HAROLD.
OKAY, TRUE ENOUGH,
YOU KNOW,
BUT I WAS JUST, YOU KNOW,
I'M THINKING, I'M SUGGESTING,
YOU KNOW, ELECTRIC DRILL
AS A SUGGESTION.
THAT'S JUST WHAT I'M JUST
THINKING IS, YOU KNOW,
ELECTRIC DRILL.
WELL, SUDDENLY I'M
THINKING PILE DRIVER.
NOW, NEIL, THERE ARE
REALLY TWO COMPONENTS
TO YOUR MAJOR POWER TOOL.
YOU GOT THE ROTATIONAL SPIN
AND YOU GOT
THE FORWARD IMPACT.
NOW, THERE'S A THING CALLED A
ROTOHAMMER, OR A HAMMER DRILL,
THAT ACTUALLY COMBINES
THESE TWO FORCES.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH!
I SAW ONE OF THOSE.
YEAH.
IT'S GOES WA-BOO, WA-BOO,
WA-BOO, WA-BOO.
IT'S GOT LIKE A BIT AND A
CHISEL, WA-BOO, WA-BOO.
IT'S SO
COOL, RIGHT?
NO ONE CARES, HAROLD,
WHAT YOU SAW.
SO, NEIL, TO GET YOURSELF
THE BIG FRAME ROTOHAMMER,
TAKE THAT ELECTRIC MOTOR
OFF THERE, THROW THAT
ONE INTO THE LAKE
AND STICK ON, SAY, A SLANT SIX
OUT OF A '63 VALIENT,
CLAMP HER DOWN WITH THE BIG
BUFFER CLAMPS ON THERE
AND I'LL TELL YOU, YOU GOT
ONE HECK OF A POWER TOOL
IN YOUR HAND, FELLA.
IT WOULD BE A LITTLE HARD TO
HANDLE, WOULDN'T IT?
WELL, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO RUN HER FOR LONG.
AND REMEMBER, NEIL,
LET THE WEIGHT OF THE TOOL
DO THE WORK, ALL RIGHT?
AND SEND US A PICTURE
IF YOU TRY THIS
'CAUSE ACTUALLY I JUST
THOUGHT OF IT RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD
LEAD OUR VIEWERS ON
LIKE THAT.
JUST A LITTLE
HARMLESS FUN, HAROLD.
YEAH, WELL, WHAT IF
SOMEBODY GETS HURT?
IT'S HARMFUL FUN THEN.
WHAT IF SOMEBODY
SUES YOU?
ALL RIGHT,
AN ELECTRIC DRILL.
ONE OF MY FAVOURITE
HOBBIES TODAY,
MODEL AIRPLANE FLYING
ON ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
IT TOOK ME TWO YEARS TO BUILD
THIS PARTICULAR MODEL THAT
I HAVE RIGHT HERE.
BUT BILL'S HERE NOW.
THANK YOU, BILL.
NOW, YOU DON'T WANT TO GET
UPSET SOMETIMES WHEN
THINGS HAPPEN
BECAUSE LOOK WHAT HE'S DONE
HERE, LOOK WHAT HE'S DONE,
LOOK WHAT HE'S DONE.
HE'S BROUGHT
A REPLACEMENT.
AND SUDDENLY I'M THINKING,
HEY, I DIDN'T LIKE THAT
OLD PLANE ANYHOW.
WHO CARES, HUH?
WHAT? WHAT?
OH. OH.
I GUESS I MIS --
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
DOESN'T MATTER
WHOSE IT IS.
THE THING WITH A HOBBY IS
IT'S A GREAT IDEA,
RELAXING AND TAKES YOUR
MIND OFF YOUR WORRIES
AND JUST GO OUT
THERE AND JUST --
BILL TAKES A TURKEY
BASTER OUT OF JACKET,
WHICH MAKES SENSE.
AND I'M TRYING TO FOOL
AROUND -- THIS IS THE
RADIO CONTROL.
IT DOESN'T EVEN HAVE
THE STRINGS OR THE WIRES.
THIS IS ONE OF
THESE FANCY UNITS,
BUT SHE DOESN'T
SEEM TO BE --
A COUPLE OF FUNNELS
TO GET THE GAS IN,
GOT HER GASSED UP.
AND I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THE
CONTROLLER.
AND I THINK IT'S
THE BATTERIES ON THAT.
YOU KNOW, I THINK WHEN YOU
LEAVE THE BATTERIES IN THERE
FOR OVER 7, 8 YEARS --
BILL, I THINK YOU
MAY BE A LITTLE PREMATURE --
I THINK YOU WERE
EARLY ON THAT ONE.
I'M TRYING TO
SHOW HIM THE --
WITH BILL ANYTHING HE DOESN'T
UNDERSTAND, HE LICKS,
WHICH CAN BE A DANGEROUS,
DANGEROUS HABIT.
ANYWAY, UP SHE GOES,
THE PLANE.
AND THEN SHE TURNS AROUND
AND SHE STARTS HEADING BACK
TOWARDS US AND TAKES OFF.
YOU KNOW, WITH A HOBBY
YOU'RE GETTING OUT IN
THE OUTDOORS,
YOU'RE GETTING
SOME EXERCISE THERE,
AND YOU GET TO
EXPERIENCE, YOU KNOW,
SOME BONDING AND SPENDING
A LOT OF TIME TOGETHER
AND, YOU KNOW, IT GETS
THE HEART GOING, GETS
THE BLOOD BUMPING.
BILL SUDDENLY REALIZES WHAT
HE NEEDS IS ANOTHER
RADIO CONTROLLER.
SO WE GOT ONE IN THE
BACK OF THE VAN THERE,
AND I GUESS ONE'S
AS GOOD AS THE NEXT
AND HE STARTS
FLICKING THAT AROUND.
NO. NO.
THAT'S NOT THE RIGHT --
WHAT THE HECK?
NO. NO.
GET RID OF -- ALL RIGHT.
AS I SAY, YOU GET A CHANCE TO
THINK AND BE INNOVATIVE
AND COME UP
WITH OTHER SOLU --
HERE'S ANOTHER
RADIO CONTROLLER.
WE GOT TONS OF
THEM IN THERE.
AND THIS ONE I THINK
IS GOING TO -- WHAT?
I DON'T --
OH THAT'S --
HE'S TURNED IT
INTO A CAR.
AS I SAY, THE HOBBY
CAN BE RELAXING
AND CAN KIND OF GET
YOUR FRUSTRATIONS UP.
WAY YOU GO, BILL.
WAY YOU GO.
Red: STAY TUNED WHILE DALTON
GIVES US ALL THE FINGER,
AND I EXPERIENCE
THE LONELINESS OF THE
LONG DISTANCE POET.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, THE BIG SCULPTURE
PROJECT UP AT ROCK REEF POINT
IS MOVING AHEAD OKAY.
WE FIND THAT WHEN YOU'RE
DOING PAINTING A PICTURE
OR PERHAPS DOING
A SCULPTURE OF A
CANADIAN FAMOUS PERSON
YOU'RE BETTER TO STAY KIND OF
NONCOMMITTAL ON WHO IT IS
UNTIL YOU SEE HOW
SHE TURNS OUT.
BOY, BY THE TIME YOU
GUYS ARE FINISHED WITH
ROCK REEF POINT,
IT'S GOING TO LOOK LIKE
ROCK REEF SPEED BUMP.
THAT TYPE OF ROCK IS
VERY HARD TO WORK
WITH, HAROLD.
WE HAD SIR CHARLES TUPPER
JUST ABOUT COMPLETELY DONE,
AND THEN WE KNOCKED OFF
A REAL IMPORTANT BIT,
AND NOW HE'S
MARGARET TRUDEAU.
WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'T
TRY DOING SO MANY,
YOU KNOW, JUST STICK WITH
THE ONE YOU GOT ON THE
VERY END THERE,
THAT LOOKS JUST
LIKE JOHN DIEFENBAKER.
THAT'S ANNE MURRAY.
REALLY?
BOY, SHE'S LET
HERSELF GO.
I DON'T THINK WORKS OF ART
SHOULD BE THIS HARD.
ARE WE DOING SOMETHING
WRONG, HAROLD?
OH YES, ALWAYS.
I THINK YOU SHOULD GET THE
PROPER EQUIPMENT AND THE
PROPER MATERIALS.
YOU KNOW, OFTENTIMES WHEN
PEOPLE ARE DOING SCULPTURES,
IT'S BEST IF THOSE PEOPLE
KNOW HOW TO, SAY, SCULPT,
LIKE, SAY,
A SCULPTOR.
HAROLD, YOU TAKE THE
FUN OUT OF EVERYTHING.
NO, I TAKE THE DANGER.
THAT'S WHAT
I JUST SAID.
"MY SNOWMOBILE,"
BY ME.
"ROARING ALONG ON MY
SNOWMOBILE THROTTLE WIDE OPEN,
"ZOOMING OVER THE HILLS,
SAILING DOWN THE GULLIES,
"SMASHING INTO
A HIDDEN ROCK,
"CAREENING THROUGH
A RAIL FENCE,
"TEARING UP
A STAND OF SHRUBS,
"CARTWHEELING OFF
THE ROOF OF THE BARN
"AND FINALLY COMING TO REST
26 FEET UP A PINE TREE.
"GOLLY, THAT'S FOUR FEET
HIGHER THAN LAST YEAR."
WE'RE OUT HERE BY THE
MAIN HIGHWAY AT HUMPHRIES
EVERYTHING STORE
TO SHOW YOU PEOPLE
THE ART OF BARTERING.
WHERE I'M GOING TO TRADE
SOME OF THESE COLLECTIBLES
AND SO ON
TO GET MYSELF SOME
TOOLS THAT WE CAN USE
ON OUR SCULPTURE UP
AT ROCK REEF POINT.
ALRIGHTY, DALTON, READY
TO DO SOME BARTERING?
YEAH, YEAH,
I GUESS, YEAH.
OKAY.
THIS HERE BELONGED
TO MY GRANDFATHER.
IS THAT WORTH ANYTHING,
DO YOU THINK?
WELL, IF IT IS,
DON'T TELL YOUR KIDS.
THEY'LL JUST TAKE THE
MONEY AND WASTE IT
AND SPEND IT ON
SOMETHING STUPID.
YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
THIS ACTUALLY WAS PART
OF THE ORIGINAL HOMESTEAD,
YOU KNOW.
YEAH. YEAH.
I'VE SEEN TONS OF THEM.
SOLD BRAND NEW IN 1900
FOR 30 CENTS.
AND WHAT WOULD IT BE WORTH
NOW, WOULD YOU THINK?
30 CENTS.
IT'S SCRAP.
OH.
OF COURSE, I BET MY
DAUGHTER WOULD SPEND
50 BUCKS ON IT.
IS SHE AROUND?
YOU KNOW, IT USED TO BE
PEOPLE DIDN'T THROW
MONEY AWAY.
TODAY'S KIDS JUST
SPEND IT WILLY-NILLY.
AND WHO PAYS?
THE PARENTS.
NOT THE DAUGHTERS.
NO, SIR.
YOU KNOW THAT MY
DAUGHTER TOOK MY MONEY
AND BOUGHT TWO BURNT OUT
CARS AND AN OLD TOUR BUS.
PROBABLY BOUGHT THEM
FOR SCRAP IRON.
TO LIVE IN!
OH.
YES, OH YES.
SHE AND THE GUY SHE'S
SEEING ARE GOING WELD
THEM TOGETHER
AND LIVE IN IT WITHOUT
HEATING, WITHOUT LIGHTING,
WITHOUT A
MARRIAGE LICENSE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THAT, RED?
WELL, NOW, WHEN I ANSWER
THOSE KINDS OF QUESTIONS,
I EITHER END UP
GETTING PUNCHED OR
DRIVEN HOME IN A COP CAR.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
THOUGH, DALTON,
I COULD TAKE THOSE
VEHICLES OFF YOUR HANDS.
WE'LL STRIP
THEM FOR PARTS.
I'D LIKE TO STRIP HER
BOYFRIEND FOR PARTS.
I'M THINKING WE CAN USE
THE CAR PARTS FOR
OUR SCULPTURE.
GOT TO BE EASIER
THAN CARVING, RIGHT?
I COULD USE THE CAR PARTS
AS PARTS OF THE FACES,
LIKE THAT CHRISTO
GUY DOES WITH THE
BED SHEETS.
YEAH, WHAT WILL YOU
GIVE ME FOR THEM?
WELL, I'LL GIVE YOU
EVERYTHING I BROUGHT.
WELL, IT'S NOT
WORTH ANYTHING.
WELL, THAT'S HOW
BARTER WORKS,
WE'RE TRADING THINGS
OF EQUAL VALUE HERE.
IT'S A DEAL.
GREAT.
ACTUALLY,
I'M UP 30 CENTS.
WE CAME THAT CLOSE
TO A HUGE SUCCESS
TURNING ROCK REEF POINT
INTO THE CANADIAN
MOUNT RUSHMORE.
I HEARD OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
GOT NAILED BY A GREYHOUND
BUS GRILL.
NO, BUT WE CAME
THAT CLOSE.
BOY, YOU SHOULD
HAVE SEEN IT, HAROLD.
WE HAD CAR GRILLS FOR TEETH,
WE HAD TRUNK LIDS FOR EARS,
WE HAD HEADLIGHTS FOR EYES,
AND WHEN YOU WAVED AT
IT THEY'D FLICK UP ON
TO THE HIGH BEAMS.
THERE'S SOMETHING ODD ABOUT
SEEING DR. NORMAN BETHUNE
MADE OUT OF BRICKLIN PARTS,
AND SIR WILFRED LAURIER
LOOKED LIKE ONE OF THE
POWER RANGERS.
AH, IT WAS BEAUTIFUL,
ART, ENTERTAINMENT
AND THE HISTORY OF
TRANSPORTATION
ALL INTO ONE
ATTRACTION.
THEY ONLY THING WE
LEFT OUT WAS GRAVITY.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
GRAVITY WAS THERE.
YEAH, RIGHT AT THE
END ESPECIALLY, BOY,
I'M TELLING YOU.
YOU KNOW WE SHOULD HAVE
ATTACHED THINGS A LITTLE
MORE SECURELY.
DUCT TAPE IS GOOD,
BUT IT'S NOT
THAT GOOD.
LUCKILY
NOBODY WAS HURT.
EXCEPT THE BEACH.
ALL THAT SCRAP METAL
ALL OVER THE PLACE,
IT LOOKED LIKE THE
COVER TO A NEIL YOUNG C.D.
WELL, THAT STUFF WON'T
BE THERE LONG,
THE WAVES REALLY
POUND IN OVER THERE.
YOU'RE GOING TO LET THAT
SCRAP METAL DISSOLVE
INTO POSSUM LAKE?
IT'S GOOD FOR IT,
HAROLD, IT'S IRON.
POPEYE WOULD BE REAL
HAPPY WITH POSSUM LAKE.
YEAH, BECAUSE IT LOOKS
SO MUCH LIKE OLIVE OIL.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU
GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I WILL BE DOWN IN
A LITTLE WHILE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'VE COME TO REALIZE
THAT IF YOU'RE GOING
TO SCULPT THE HUMAN FORM,
YOU HAVE TO STUDY
THE HUMAN FORM,
SO I WILL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I MAY NOT KNOW ART,
BUT I KNOW WHAT I LIKE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
UNTIL NEXT TIME, ON BEHALF
OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
OKAY, WE HAVE
A PRESENTATION.
DON'T LOOK,
IT'S NOT FINISHED.