YOU KNOW, INSTEAD OF
COMPLAINING ABOUT WINTER,
PEOPLE NEED TO
GET OUT IN IT.
YOU KNOW, HAVE A
LITTLE BIT OF FUN.
THAT'S HOW YOU STAY WARM.
SOME PEOPLE SKATE.
SOME PEOPLE SKI.
SOME PEOPLE GET NAKED AND
ROLL AROUND IN THE SNOW.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT, INSTEAD OF
BEING ON A COLD SNOW BANK,
THEY'RE IN A WARM POLICE CAR.
PERSONALLY,
I LIKE TOBOGGANING.
IN FACT, I LIKE IT SO MUCH,
I'VE IMPROVED IT.
WHAT I'VE DONE HERE IS I'VE
DUCT TAPED A FROZEN TURKEY
TO A COUPLE OF TOBOGGANS
GOING DIFFERENT DIRECTIONS.
WE CALLED THIS A DOUBLE-ENDER
BACK WHEN I WAS DATING.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, THIS IS THE
ROPE THAT COMES UP FROM
THE TURKEY TOBOGGAN.
ALL'S YOU DO IS WIND THAT
AROUND SOMETHING SOLID AT
THE TOP OF THE HILL,
MAYBE A STEEL PIPE OR A BIRCH
TREE OR A FROZEN FAT GUY.
AND THEN WHAT I'VE DONE IS
I'VE TIED THE OTHER END
OF THE ROPE TO THE BACK
OF MY TOBOGGAN.
I'M BASICALLY
READY TO GO.
NOW, I'VE SET UP THIS TOBOGGAN
JUST LIKE THE OTHER ONE,
EXCEPT THAT THIS TIME,
I'M THE TURKEY.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE THAT.
WELL, WE'VE GOT A REAL BIG
DAY TOMORROW AT THE LODGE.
WE'RE HAVING A CANOE RACE
AGAINST THE GUYS FROM
CARIBOU LODGE.
SO, JUST GOT OUR EQUIPMENT
BACK INTO SHAPE THERE.
THESE CANOE PADDLES TOOK A
BIT OF A BEATING DURING
THE TALENT SHOW.
BUSTER HADFIELD WAS
TRYING TO JUGGLE THEM,
AND FORGOT ABOUT
THE CEILING FAN.
OH, GEEZ. OH!
( groaning and complaining )
RED, I'VE FOUND THE CANOE.
IT WASN'T WHERE
YOU SAID, THOUGH.
IT WASN'T BEHIND THE BACK STOP
ON THE TARGET RANGE.
IT WAS THE BACK STOP
ALL RIGHT, WELL JUST
LEAVE IT THERE, DALTON.
WE'LL FIX IT LATER.
WE'LL DO THE PADDLE'S FIRST.
JUST HOLD THIS, WILL YOU?
THINK THAT CANOE'S
GONNA FLOAT WITH
DUCT TAPE PATCHES?
WELL, NOT FOR TOO LONG,
BUT IT'LL JUST MAKE
YOU PADDLE FASTER.
HOW LONG'S THIS PADDLE
GOING TO HOLD TOGETHER?
THE SAME AS THE CANOE.
I FIGURE YOUR BEST BET
IS TO GO LIKE STINK
AND WEAR A BATHING SUIT.
OKAY.
THAT ROLL'S DONE.
SEE ANOTHER ROLL OF DUCT
TAPE ANYWHERE, DALTON?
NO, NO.
YOU MIGHT TRY
THE CUPBOARD.
THE GUYS ALL KNOW THEY'RE
SUPPOSED TO PUT IT BACK
WHEN THEY'RE DONE.
YEAH, RIGHT.
OKAY.
WE'RE OUT OF
DUCT TAPE, DALTON!
OKAY. OKAY. OKAY.
TRY TO STAY CALM, RED.
STAY CALM!
WE'RE OUT OF
DUCT TAPE, DALTON!
OKAY, I'M GOING TO PHONE
THE HARDWARE STORE.
THEY'LL DELIVER
IT TODAY.
NOW,
WHAT'S THE NUMBER?
NUMBER ONE
ON THE SPEED DIAL.
THIS HAS NEVER
HAPPENED BEFORE.
I MAY HAVE TO SHUT
DOWN THE WHOLE LODGE.
HELLO, THIS IS POSSUM LODGE.
WE NEED A DOZEN --
TWO DOZEN!
OKAY WE NEED THREE
DOZEN ROLLS OF DUCT
TAPE DELIVERED RIGHT AWAY!
PARDON.
RIGHT, YEAH.
WHAT?
WHAT IS IT?
(voice quivering)
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
THANKS.
THEY'RE ON BACK ORDER.
WHAT?
THEY WON'T HAVE
THEM FOR TWO WEEKS.
TWO WEEKS
WITHOUT DUCT TAPE.
RED, RED, TRY AND
HOLD IT TOGETHER.
HOLD IT TOGETHER
WITH WHAT?
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
TODAY, DALTON HUMPHREY
WILL BE PLAYING FOR
250 POUNDS WORTH OF
FREE WEIGHTS.
DELIVERY NOT INCLUDED.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
EARS, DALTON.
OKAY, RED,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON HUMPHREY
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, DALTON,
WHEN YOU GO TO BED
WHAT DO YOU DO
TO THE ALARM CLOCK?
UNPLUG IT.
OKAY, IF YOU STARTED BUYING
THOSE BEANIE BABIES,
YOU WOULDN'T STOP UNTIL
YOU HAD A COMPLETE...
FINANCIAL BREAKDOWN.
OKAY, WHEN YOU PUT SOMETHING
DOWN SOMEWHERE, YOU...
FORGET WHERE IT IS.
THIS IS AN EXPRESSION
THEY USE IN A MOVIE.
THEY'LL SAY,
"QUIET ON THE..."
WESTERN FRONT!
YOU'RE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME, RED.
OKAY, DALTON,
AT SUPPERTIME,
WHAT DO YOU DO TO
THE DINING ROOM TABLE?
PUT AWAY MY TRAIN SET.
THAT'S IT!
[ RINGING BELL ]
WELL, THERE YOU GO!
THIS IS THE UP CLOSE AND
PERSONAL PART OF THE SHOW,
AND WE'VE HAD ABSOLUTELY NO
FEEDBACK ON THE SEGMENT,
AND WE FIND THAT
VERY ENCOURAGING.
SO, TODAY, WE'RE GOING TO
TAKE A LITTLE CLOSER LOOK
AT THE MAN WE
KNOW AS ED FRID.
SO, ED, MAYBE YOU COULD TELL
US A LITTLE BIT ABOUT
THE FRID HOUSEHOLD
BACK IN THE EARLY DAYS BEFORE
YOU BECAME AN ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICER.
OH, WELL, WE HAD A
GREAT FAMILY.
EVERYTHING WAS PERFECT.
MOM, DAD, SIS, ME.
WE HAD A A LITTLE HOUSE
AND A TIRE SWING,
A LITTLE WHITE PICKET FENCE.
IT WAS THE KIND OF
CHILDHOOD ALL KIDS WANT.
AT LEAST IT WAS
UNTIL WE MOVED.
MOVING CAN BE VERY
DIFFICULT FOR A CHILD.
WHAT PART OF THAT
WAS TRAUMATIC FOR YOU?
WELL, IT'S HARD FOR ME TO
TALK ABOUT THIS, RED.
BUT MY DAD BOUGHT A
HOUSE RIGHT NEXT TO
AN ANIMAL SHELTER.
OH, SO THAT'S HOW YOU WERE
REALLY INTRODUCED TO ANIMALS.
OH, NO, RED, THERE WERE
NO INTRODUCTIONS.
NO, THEY CAME OVER
WHENEVER THEY WANTED TO.
THEY CLAWED THEIR WAY
UP OVER THE FENCE.
THEY'D TUNNEL THEIR WAY
INTO OUR BASEMENT.
THEY'D SLITHER INTO
OUR HOUSE THROUGH
THE MAIL SLOT
AND THEY ALWAYS CAME
RIGHT FOR ME.
YOU KNOW, MY FATHER COULD BE
ASLEEP ON THE COUCH,
IN HIS UNDERSHIRT,
BUT, OH, NO, THEY'D GO RIGHT
PAST HIM AND UP TO MY ROOM.
WELL, DID YOU TELL YOUR
PARENTS THAT THIS
WAS GOING ON?
WELL, YES.
YES, I DID.
THEY SAID I WAS MAKING
THE WHOLE THING UP
TO EXPLAIN WHY
MY BED WAS WET.
AND WERE YOU
MAKING IT UP, ED?
NOT TOTALLY.
WELL, DOESN'T IT
SEEM ODD TO YOU
THAT A GUY WHO WENT
THROUGH ALL THAT
WOULD END UP BEING AN
ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER?
NO, NO,
NOT REALLY.
YOU SEE, I DON'T
BLAME THE ANIMALS.
I NEVER BLAMED THE ANIMALS.
UH, IF THERE ARE ANY
ANIMALS WATCHING NOW,
I NEVER BLAMED YOU,
AND PLEASE DON'T HURT ME.
I'M JUST SAYING YOU
SHOULD HAVE MAYBE
BEEN A TEACHER
OR LIBRARIAN OR SELL
UNPAINTED FURNITURE
OR SOMETHING.
WELL, NOW, THAT WOULDN'T
SOLVE ANYTHING, WOULD IT?
BECAUSE ANIMALS CAN STILL GO
INTO SCHOOLS AND LIBRARIES
AND EVEN UNPAINTED
FURNITURE STORES.
THAT'S WHY WE NEED TO CONTROL
THEM, NOT HURT THEM.
I NEVER SAID HURT THEM.
WE HAVE TO
MANAGE THEM AND,
YOU KNOW, KEEP THEM
WITH FOOD
AND A PLACE TO LIVE
AND KEEP THEM SAFE.
OTHERWISE, THEY MIGHT END
UP ATTACKING INNOCENT
PEOPLE IN BED,
EVEN THOUGH THEIR FATHER'S
A WAY BETTER TARGET,
JUST LYING THERE IN HIS
UNDERSHIRT SNORING AND
REEKING OF PORK RINDS.
OKAY. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, ED.
WELL, WE'RE PRETTY MUCH
OUT OF TIME HERE.
SO MAYBE YOU CAN CAP THIS OFF
BY GIVING A BIT OF ADVICE
TO SOME OF THE YOUNGSTERS
WHO ARE WATCHING OUT THERE.
SURE.
KIDS, YOU MAY FIND THAT THERE
ARE MANY THINGS IN LIFE
THAT ARE VERY SCARY.
AND YOU MAY BE TEMPTED
TO RUN AWAY,
BUT DON'T DO IT.
THEY CAN RUN 10 TIMES
FASTER THAN YOU.
GOT A REAL HUMMER OF A
TIP FOR YOU THIS TIME.
YOU KNOW IN THE WINTER
EVERYBODY HAS A FIRE GOING,
AND I'M THINKING,
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
IF YOU COULD USE THAT SMOKE
TO SEND SIGNALS TO YOUR
NEIGHBOURS?
IT WOULD COME IN REAL HANDY
IF, SAY, YOUR PHONE
WAS CUT OFF
'CAUSE, MAYBE, YOUR PHONE BILL
HAD ACCIDENTALLY SLIPPED
THROUGH THE CRACKS
OF YOUR GARBAGE CAN LID.
SPEAKING OF WHICH, I'M LOOKING
AT THIS KITCHEN GARBAGE CAN,
AND I'M THINKING, HEY,
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT IF I
PUT THIS ON TOP OF THE CHIMNEY
AND USE IT AS A
VALVE FOR THE SMOKE?
NOW, I TOOK THE PEDAL OFF,
AND I MOUNTED THE REST OF
THE UNIT OVER THE CHIMNEY.
THEN I EXTENDED THIS ROD FROM
THE LID ALL THE WAY DOWN,
THROUGH THE ROOF,
DOWN HERE, INSIDE, COMES
ALL THE WAY DOWN THROUGH
MY HOOK-UP,
RIGHT UP TO THE FOOT PEDAL,
WHICH I'VE SITUATED BY
THE WOOD STOVE.
SO BASICALLY,
I CAN CONTROL THE WHOLE
COMMUNICATION PROCESS
FROM THE COMFORT
OF MY LIVING ROOM.
PLUS, I GOT THIS
BOOK ON MORSE CODE,
WHICH'LL ALLOW ME TO CONVERT
MY FILES TO DIGITAL.
SORT OF LIKE A COMPUTER.
SO YOU CAN EITHER STAND
OUTSIDE TO GET MY MESSAGES,
OR YOU CAN USE WINDOWS
IF YOU HAVE 'EM.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GIVE HER A TRY.
SEE IF YOU CAN
UNDERSTAND THIS.
THE PEDAL'S COME OFF.
( coughing )
DID YOU GET THE MESSAGE?
ONE OF THE THINGS THAT
CHANGES AS YOU GET OLDER
IS YOUR ATTITUDE
TOWARDS PARTIES.
THAT'S BECAUSE AFTER YOU'VE
BEEN MARRIED FOR A WHILE
YOU REALIZE MEN AND WOMEN
HAVE TOTALLY DIFFERENT
APPROACHES TO THEM.
THE WOMAN WANTS TO KNOW
WHO'S COMING TO THE PARTY;
THE MAN JUST WANTS TO KNOW
WHO'S BRINGING THE BEER.
THE WOMAN CLEANS UP WHATEVER'S
LYING AROUND THE HOME
SO THE GUESTS WILL THINK SHE
KEEPS A NEAT HOUSE.
THE MAN WILL LEAVE TOOLS
LYING AROUND THE HOME
SO THE GUESTS WILL
HELP BUILD A DECK.
THE WOMAN ALWAYS WANTS TO
FIND OUT WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH EVERYBODY;
THE MAN AVOIDS
THAT INFORMATION.
IT'S SAFER.
IT PREVENTS HIM FROM BLURTING
OUT SOMETHING HE'S NOT
SUPPOSED TO KNOW
IN FRONT OF SOMEONE WHO'S
NOT SUPPOSED TO HEAR IT,
ESPECIALLY IF THAT SOMEONE IS
CARRYING ONE OF THE TOOLS
THAT I MENTIONED EARLIER.
SO MY ADVICE IS WHEN
YOU GET TO OUR AGE,
STOP GOING TO PARTIES.
BRINGING FRIENDS TOGETHER
FOR THE SOLE PURPOSE
OF LETTING LOOSE
IS NOT A GOOD IDEA.
PEOPLE ARE LIKE
NUTS AND BOLTS.
THEY DON'T WORK
WELL LOOSE.
THERE'S TOO MUCH PLAY.
YOU WANT TO HAVE A WING-DING,
YOU'RE BETTER OFF IN A
BAR FULL OF STRANGERS
THAN A HOUSE FULL OF FRIENDS.
YOU WANT TO GO WHERE
THE LIGHTS ARE LOW,
PEOPLE ARE ALL THE SAME.
YOU WANT TO GO WHERE
NOBODY KNOWS YOUR NAME.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THE TOGETHER.
WELL, THERE DOESN'T SEEM TO
BE A SINGLE ROLL OF DUCT TAPE
IN THE WHOLE
POSSUM LAKE AREA.
I THINK THOSE GUYS
FROM CARIBOU LODGE
ARE HOARDING IT ALL.
SO WE'RE FORCED
TO FIX THE CANOE
BY RECYCLING DUCT TAPE WE'VE
USED ON OTHER STUFF.
I THINK IT'S GONNA
WORK OUT FINE.
RED, I FOUND SOME
DUCT TAPE WE CAN USE.
WOW, WHERE'D
YOU GET THIS?
DALTON, THIS STUFF
DOESN'T STICK.
OH SURE IT DOES.
LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
LOOK, IT'S FINE.
NO, DALTON IT'S NOT FINE.
OH, YEAH, I'M GOING.
NO, NO, RED, DON'T DO IT.
I'VE GOTTA GO.
I'M GOING.
PLEASE, RED, NO!
DALTON,
THIS IS AN EMERGENCY.
RED, NO ONE HAS BROKEN THAT
GLASS IN 50 YEARS.
Mr GREEN!
I BROUGHT YOU
SOMETHING I THINK
MIGHT CHEER YOU UP.
OH, MY GOSH.
DALTON, MIKE BROUGHT
US DUCT TAPE.
MIKE BROUGHT US DUCT TAPE.
WAY TO GO, MIKE!
WAIT A MINUTE.
HOLD IT.
THIS ISN'T DUCT TAPE.
IT'S MASKING
TAPE PAINTED GREY.
Audience: O-O-OH!
IT'S NOT THE
SAME THING, MIKE!
IT'S NOT THE SAME THING!
WAY TO GO, MIKE.
AW, MIKE, SORRY I
SNAPPED AT YOU THERE.
I HAVEN'T HAD DUCT TAPE
IN OVER THREE HOURS.
GIMME THAT
HAMMER, DALTON.
ARE YOU SURE YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
DALTON, WE CANNOT GO ON
LIVING LIKE THIS.
50 YEARS IT'S
BEEN THERE, MIKE.
I GOT IT!
WE'RE GOING
TO BE OKAY, GUYS.
EVERYTHING'S
GOING TO BE OKAY.
WHEN YOU SEND A SPECIAL
PACKAGE TO A LOVED ONE
OR WHATEVER,
IT CAN BE VERY DISAPPOINTING
WHEN IT ARRIVES ALL BEAT
UP LIKE THIS,
ESPECIALLY, IF THERE'S AN
EXPENSIVE CLOCK INSIDE
OR A SMALL ANIMAL
OR SOMETHING.
AND THAT'S EVEN AFTER YOU
COVER THE DARN THING WITH
WARNING STICKERS.
I TELL YOU, TO THEM,
"FRAGILE" IS FRENCH FOR
"THROW UNDERHAND."
AND "THIS END UP" MEANS
THEY'LL DECIDE HOW
THIS'LL END UP.
WELL, HERE'S A
DIFFERENT APPROACH.
MAYBE THIS WARNING SIGN
WILL WORK A LITTLE
BETTER FOR YOU.
ALL RIGHT, GORD?
JUST GIVE
ME A MINUTE.
BEEN SOME KIND OF AN
ACCIDENT OR SOMETHING?
YEAH, I'M GOOD.
NO. IT'S JUST THAT
DARN LIGHTNING AGAIN.
OH, BOY, THAT STINGS.
YOU GOT HIT BY LIGHTNING?
I THINK SO.
THERE WAS A BRIGHT
FLASH OF LIGHT
AND THEN THE SMELL
OF BURNT HAIR.
SO IT'S EITHER LIGHTNING,
OR SOMEBODY THREW A SQUIRREL
THROUGH MY BUG ZAPPER.
WHAT DOES IT FEEL LIKE WHEN
LIGHTNING NAILS YOU LIKE THAT?
WELL, IT'S
NOT TOO BAD.
YOU LOSE CONSCIOUSNESS
AND ABOUT 90 PERCENT
OF YOUR MEMORY.
BUT IT'S INVIGORATING,
YOU KNOW.
OH, BUT YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER
NOT TO TAKE YOUR CLOTHES
OFF FOR A FEW DAYS.
OTHERWISE HUGE SPARKS
LEAP OFF YOUR BODY PARTS,
AND THAT CAN BE DANGEROUS.
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE
SLOW DANCING.
I WONDER, GORD, IF YOU WOULD
CONSIDER GETTING OUT OF
THE FIRE TOWER,
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU
SEE A STORM COMING.
WELL, IT'S MY JOB, RED.
I MEAN, IF I LEFT THE TOWER,
LIGHTNING COULD VERY WELL
STRIKE A TREE AND START
A FOREST FIRE.
YOU SEE, RED, TREES ARE
MADE OUT OF WOOD,
AND THEY BURN
VERY EASILY.
I'VE LOOKED INTO IT.
IT'S NOT YOUR DUTY TO
BE KILLED, THOUGH, GORD.
WELL, I REALIZE
THAT, RED.
I'M VERY PLEASED
TO REPORT THAT I'VE
NEVER BEEN KILLED.
I DON'T THINK YOUR BRAIN
CELLS GOT OFF THAT LUCKY.
WELL, MAYBE NOT,
BUT IF THERE'S ONE TREE
OUT THERE I CAN SAVE,
WELL, DARN IT, THAT'S WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO.
YOU KNOW SOME PEOPLE
CALL ME CRAZY.
DO YOU THINK I'M CRAZY, RED?
OH, FOR SURE.
YEAH.
I LOVE THAT SENSE
OF HUMOUR.
I LOVE IT.
ALL RIGHT, GORD, WELL,
IF YOU'VE GOT TO STAY
IN THE TOWER,
WOULD YOU AT LEAST GET
ME A LIGHTNING ROD
AND PUT IT ON TOP
OF THE THING?
I HAVE A LIGHTNING ROD.
IT'S RIGHT ON THE ROOF
OF MY TOWER.
AND IS IT GROUNDED RIGHT
INTO THE GROUND?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, THERE'S SUPPOSED TO
BE A WIRE THAT RUNS
DOWN TO THE --
WELL, HERE'S A WIRE.
WHERE DOES THIS GO?
WELL, IT'S ATTACHED TO
YOUR CHAIR, GORD.
Red: ED FRID HAD CALLED
US OUT BEHIND THE LODGE.
HE'D LOST HIS PET GROUNDHOG,
AND HE WANTED SOME HELP
FINDING IT.
AND WALTER WAS THERE.
WALTER WENT ONE WAY,
WE WENT THE OTHER.
A LOT OF TIMES
THEY'LL DIG SEVERAL --
THERE IT IS.
THEY DIG SEVERAL HOLES,
SO WALTER WAS WORKING ON
ONE OF THE GROUNDHOG HOLES,
AND WE DIDN'T REALIZE THAT WE
WERE WORKING IN ANOTHER ONE
IN CLOSE PROXIMITY.
AND, OF COURSE, WE THOUGHT
WE'D GRABBED THE GROUNDHOG.
OH, OH, TURNS OUT --
HE GAVE US THE SLIP.
A LOT OF TIMES, THE GROUNDHOG
WILL STAY UP IN A TREE.
LOOK AT THAT.
THEY SUN THEMSELVES.
SO ALL YOU'VE GOT TO DO IS
GO UP AND GET THEM OUT
OF THE TREE.
THIS IS SOMETHING
I DIDN'T REALIZE,
THAT THEY LIKE
TO STAY UP THERE.
I FIGURE ALL WE GOTTA DO IS
TAKE A ROCK AND JUST
A LIGHT NIP...
BUT ED SAID NO.
YOU'RE NOT DOING THAT.
YOU'RE GOING TO HURT HIS
FAVOURITE GROUNDHOG.
SO I JUST CHUCKED THE ROCK
AWAY, WHICH HE TOLD HE TO DO.
THANK YOU, ED, FOR A
BRILLIANT SUGGESTION.
SO, ED, WITH THE ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICE HE
WORKS OUT OF,
HAS ALL KINDS OF EQUIPMENT.
A BLOW GUN IS
REALLY WHAT IT IS.
THEY HAVE THE
TRANQUILIZER DARTS,
WHICH GIVES THEM THE EXACT
DOSAGE FOR A GROUNDHOG,
APPARENTLY.
ALL HE WANTED WAS FOR US
TO CATCH THE GROUNDHOG
WHEN IT FELL.
CATCH THAT IN THE BLANKET.
IT'D BE ASLEEP FOR A FEW
MINUTES, AND THEN IT'D
BE ALL RIGHT.
ED GOT ALL SET THERE
AND UNFORTUNATELY
HE INHALED.
THERE WE GO.
SO THEN, WALTER HAD AN IDEA.
HE THOUGHT IF HE COULD
ACTUALLY GO UP THE TREE
WITH THE DART AND
THE DART GUN,
AND THEN HE COULD
GET A BETTER SHOT AT IT.
IT WOULD WORK OUT BETTER.
THEN ED AND I WOULD STAY DOWN
WITH THE BLANKET TO CATCH
THE GROUNDHOG.
SO WALTER GETS HIMSELF
INTO POSITION.
HE'S USUALLY A
PRETTY GOOD SHOT,
BUT GROUNDHOGS ARE CAGEY.
THEY'LL MOVE ON YOU
IF YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL.
SO HE GETS THE DART AND
GETS ALL SET AND SHOOTS.
THE GROUNDHOG DUCKS AND
THE DART HITS THE TREE AND...
OH!
WELL, HE'S YOUNG
HE'LL GET OVER IT.
SO I THOUGHT I'D
GRAB THE BRANCH,
AND I COULD PULL
THE BRANCH DOWN,
AND WE'LL JUST GRAB THE
GROUNDHOG THERE.
BUT IT SEEMS THE BRANCH IS A
LITTLE BRITTLE AND --
HE TAKES OFF AND HE'S WAY
OUTSIDE THE CENTRE LINE,
AND IT LOOKS GOOD.
LOOKS GOOD.
THAT'S THREE POINTS!
IF YOU'RE A HANDYMAN,
YOU PROBABLY HAVE ONE
OF THESE SOMEWHERE,
A BIG CAN FULL OF
NUTS AND BOLTS,
PARTS LEFT OVER FROM THINGS
YOU'VE PUT TOGETHER
OR THINGS YOU'VE
BLOWN APART.
IT'S A LOT BETTER
THAN THROWING THE STUFF AWAY,
BUT WHAT A PAIN TO HAVE
TO SORT THROUGH EVERYTHING
WHEN YOU NEED SOMETHING.
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW,
THERE IS A BETTER WAY.
GET YOURSELF A RACK OF
THESE GUMBALL MACHINES.
THEN PUT YOUR DIFFERENT SIZED
HARDWARE INTO EACH ONE.
FOR EXAMPLE, SAY I'M LOOKING
FOR A HALF-INCH BOLT.
I JUST TURN THE CRANK.
I NEED A HALF-INCH NUT
TO GO WITH IT.
NO PROBLEM.
BY GOLLY.
AND HERE'S THE BEST PART,
INSTEAD OF USING COINS,
I'M USING WASHERS, EH?
I'M USING WASHERS AS SLUGS.
( muttering )
I THINK WE'RE GOING TO BE
READY FOR THE CANOE RACE
EVEN WITHOUT DUCT TAPE.
THE REAL HANDYMAN IS
RESOURCEFUL.
WHEN THE WORLD HANDS
YOU A LEMON,
YOU JAM IT INTO
A CANOE HOLE.
WE GOT THE PADDLES
DONE, RED.
YEAH, THEY TURNED
OUT PRETTY GOOD.
YEAH,
WE'LL BE FINE.
WE'LL PROBABLY
COME IN SECOND,
UNLESS THERE'S MORE
THAN TWO BOATS.
HEY, GUYS,
HOW'S IT GOING?
ED, WHAT DO YOU GOT
THERE IN YOUR HAND?
OH, TURTLE BITE.
I FORGOT THE LITTLE GUY
WAS IN MY POCKET.
NO, I MEAN IN
YOUR OTHER HAND.
YOU'VE GOT SOMETHING THAT
LOOKS LIKE A ROLL OF
DUCT TAPE, THERE.
OH, IT'S A ROLL
OF DUCT TAPE.
THERE'S ALL KINDS OF
IT UP IN THE ATTIC.
WHAT'S IT DOING UP THERE?
WE WERE USING IT TO
FIX THE HEATING DUCTS.
I DIDN'T KNOW IT
WAS GOOD FOR THAT.
WELL, THERE OUGHT TO
BE A COUPLE MORE
ROLLS UP THERE.
STAND BACK, GUYS.
I'M GOING TO OPEN
THE TRAP DOOR.
HOLY SMOKES.
HOLY SMOKES!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, IT'S
MEETING TIME.
OKAY, YOU GUYS
GO AHEAD.
DON'T TELL THE OTHERS
ABOUT THE DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT, IF MY
WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING HOME
RIGHT AFTER THE MEETING,
AND IT LOOKS LIKE
WE CAN START ON THAT
HOUSE ADDITION RIGHT AWAY.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
GATHER ROUND. SIT DOWN.
HAVE A SEAT. SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
KEEP YOUR HEADS BOWED, MEN.
I WANT TO ADD A LITTLE
PERSONAL PRAYER.
LET'S NEVER FORGET THAT ALL
GOOD THINGS COME FROM ABOVE.