ONE OF THE MOST MADDENING THINGS
IN THE WORLD IS TO DISCOVER
THAT SOME BRAIN-DEAD MORON
HAS TAKEN HIS KEY
AND COME DOWN THE SIDE
OF YOUR VEHICLE,
SCRATCHING THE PAINT JOB.
BUT, HERE'S A CHEAP, EASY WAY
TO TURN BAD NEWS INTO GOOD NEWS.
TAKE A ROLL OF DUCT TAPE
AND ADD SOME PIZZAZZ
TO YOUR VEHICLE,
WHILE COVERING UP
THE UGLY SCRATCHES.
THIS SCRATCH IS GOING TO
MAKE A DANDY RACING STRIPE,
BUT WHATEVER SHAPE
THE SCRATCH IS...
COVER IT WITH DUCT TAPE AND
IT'LL BE YOUR LITTLE SECRET.
THE SECRET THAT EVERY
HANDYMAN KNOWS, WHICH IS:
"THINGS AREN'T ALWAYS
WHAT THEY SEEM."
[laughter]
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW!!!
HERE'S THE MAN WHO ONCE SAID:
"I BEG YOUR PARDON,
I NEVER PROMISED YOU A BUICK."
YOUR HOST AND HERO, MY UNCLE:
RED GREEEEEEN!!!
[applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
GOT A LITTLE ADVICE FOR YA:
IF YOU'RE IN THE MARKET
FOR A CHAINSAW,
I WOULD SUGGEST YOU STAY AWAY
FROM THE SWANSON PRUNE PAL.
I BOUGHT ONE OF THOSE
AND IT'S TOTALLY USELESS.
HE USED HIS PRUNE PAL
TO SAW OFF THE ROOF OF A CAR.
OF COURSE, THEN THEY TRIED
TO STIFF ME ON THE WARRANTY.
BUT, WE GOT OVER THAT HURDLE.
OH YEAH, YEAH,
YOU SURE DID.
YOU SHOWED THEM.
HA! HA! HA!
YEAH, HE LIED!
YEAH, HE SAID
IT WOULDN'T CUT.
HE DIDN'T MENTION
THAT IT WOULDN'T CUT
THROUGH SHEET METAL.
ANYWAY, THE COMPANY SENT
ME A REFUND CHEQUE,
A MONTH AGO.
AND WHERE IS IT?
WELL, IT'S TRAPPED INSIDE
OUR USELESS POSTAL SYSTEM,
THAT'S WHERE IT IS.
DID YOU EVEN BOTHER
TO CHECK THE MAIL?
HAROLD, I CHECK
THE MAIL EVERY DAY.
I LOOK AT IT ALL, HAROLD.
I GUESS THESE JUST
SLIPPED THROUGH
THE CRACKS?
LOOK AT THIS...
WE GOTTA VISA BILL.
ELECTRIC BILL...
GAS BILL...
TAX DEPARTMENT...
SHERIFF'S OFFICE...
ED MCMAHON...
ED MCMAHON.
HAROLD, THE LETTER'S NOT THERE.
THE POSTAL SYSTEM IN THIS
COUNTRY IS AN EMBARRASSMENT.
HERE IT IS!
WHAT?
OH, FOR GOSH SAKE.
BUT, I STILL SAY
THE SYSTEM STINKS.
I'VE GOT A GOOD MIND
TO START MY OWN
POSTAL SYSTEM.
[laughing]
[sarcastically]
YOU GOT A GOOD MIND.
[laughter]
IT'S TIME FOR
"THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME."
AND TODAY'S CONTESTANT
WILL BE PLAYING FOR
A FREE COUPON
FOR ONE OF THESE
DIRT SUCKER VACUUMS.
OH! OH! OH!
WHOA!!!
[laughter]
PRIZES ARE INSIDE.
TODAY'S CONTESTANT
IS MR. MIKE HAMAR.
[applause]
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. MIKE HAMAR
TO SAY THIS WORD:
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
GO!!!
MIKE, THE THING
AROUND A HOUSE?
AN ALARM SYSTEM?
NO, THIS IS FLAT,
ON THE GROUND,
SPREAD OUT.
ME, GETTING ARRESTED?
YOU KNOW THAT PLACE
YOU'RE IN NOW...
WHAT HAVE YOU
GOT OUT FRONT?
AH, TIRES...
A RUSTY BIKE?
SHOPPING CARTS?
NO.
A CAMARO ON
CEMENT BLOCKS.
A TRANS AM ON WOODEN BLOCKS?
A FORD PICKUP ON FIRE?
UNDER THE VEHICLES,
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
DOGS.
NO, THIS IS KIND OF
A FUZZY GREEN THING.
OH, THAT OLD SICK CAT?
I THINK HE'S
GOT A DISEASE
'CAUSE THE DOGS WON'T
BITE 'EM NO MORE.
NO, I'M SAYIN' UNDER THE DOGS
AND THE SICK CAT,
YOU'VE GOT WHAT?
UH, UH... OH!
ASTROTURF?
YOU'RE SO CLOSE.
SOD?
A BUNCH OF GRASS?
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT
OF TIME, UNCLE RED.
OKAY, YOU SAID,
"A BUNCH OF GRASS".
IF YOU HAVE A BUNCH
OF GRASS YOU GET...?
TWO YEARS LESS A DAY?
[laughter]
WELL, WE GOT OUR POSSUM LODGE
POSTAL SERVICE UP AND RUNNING.
BUSTER HADFIELD WAS
THE FIRST TO SIGN UP.
WELL, THAT'S ONLY BECAUSE
THE REAL POSTAL SERVICE WON'T
DELIVER TO HIS HOUSE.
RIGHT, THE MAILMAN SAID
HE WON'T GO BACK THERE
UNTIL BUSTER GETS
HIS DOG NEUTERED.
I'LL TELL YA, NOTHING
THAT COMES IN THE MAIL
IS WORTH THAT.
DUSTY FARNSWORTH
WAS A WIRY CODGER
BLIND IN ONE EYE
AND HALF LAME
PEOPLE SAY HE WAS
BORN IN A BARN
AND RAISED IN
A POKER GAME
ONE DAY, HE TRIED TO DRINK
ALL THE BEER IN THE LODGE
WE THOUGHT HE WAS
ONLY BLUFFIN'
BUT, WHEN HE WAS DONE
WE SAID, YOU
MUST'VE BEEN DRY
HE SAID, THEY DON'T CALL ME
DUSTY FOR NOTHIN
YOU KNOW, AFTER 50 YEARS OF
OVEREATING AND UNDERACHIEVING,
YOU START WORRYING THAT SOMEDAY
YOUR HEART'S GONNA GO OFF
LIKE A WARM CAN OF POP
IN AN EARTHQUAKE.
THERE IS A WAY TO
AVOID THIS SCENARIO.
YOU CAN CHANGE YOUR DIET.
OR MAYBE, GET INVOLVED IN
A PHYSICAL FITNESS PROGRAM,
BUT HEY, WHO ARE WE KIDDIN'.
SO, THIS WEEK ON
"HANDYMAN CORNER,"
I THOUGHT I'D SHOW YOU HOW TO
MAKE YOUR VERY OWN PACEMAKER.
THE FIRST THING YOU NEED IS
ONE OF THESE HERE BALLOONS.
THE LONG, WIENER-SHAPED KIND,
NOT THE ROUND KIND.
OKAY, THAT'S GOT 'ER.
I HOPE THAT WAS THE BALLOON.
NOW, WE'RE GONNA USE THIS
TO CHECK OUR PULSE.
I KNOW, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO USE YOUR WRIST,
BUT AFTER DECADES OF
LIFTING CHEESEBURGERS
AND LARGE DRAFTS,
YOUR WRIST GETS PRETTY THICK
AND THE PULSE GETS BURIED
WAY DOWN THERE.
SO, WE'RE GONNA CHECK
OUR PULSE IN OUR NECK.
SEE, AS YOU GET OLDER,
YOUR BLOOD STARTS TO PICK
WHERE IT WANTS TO GO,
BUT IT WILL ALWAYS
GO TO YOUR BRAIN.
IF YOURS DOESN'T,
YOU'RE PROBABLY NOT
WATCHING THIS ANYWAY.
YOU KNOW THE FUNNY SOUND
A BALLOON MAKES WHEN YOU
LET THE AIR OUT SLOWLY?
[squeak, squeak]
WE'RE GONNA USE THAT SOUND
TO COUNT OUR HEARTBEATS.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS
PUT THE BALLOON IN YOUR COLLAR.
IF IT'S TOO LOOSE,
JUST BLOW 'ER UP A BIT.
OR, IF YOU'RE SHORT ON CASH,
JUST LEAVE THE BALLOON THERE
AND SUE SOMEONE FOR WHIPLASH.
HA, HA, HA.
[balloon pops]
OWWW!!!
OR, SUE THE BALLOON MAKER.
BOY, THE HEART'S RACING NOW.
NOW, IN A SECOND, THIS BALLOON
IS GONNA START PULSING ALONG
WITH MY HEART, ALL RIGHT?
AND, YOU'LL WANT TO RECORD
THAT SOUND FOR YOUR PULSE.
GET YOURSELF ONE OF THESE
LITTLE CASSETTE RECORDER DEALS
OFF A TEENAGER WHILE
THEY'RE ASLEEP,
SAY, DURING CLASS.
OKAY, SET THAT ON RECORD.
AND START 'ER PULSING.
[squeak, squeak]
[squeak, squeak, squeak]
SOUNDS LIKE HAROLD
WHEN HE WAS A KID.
[squeak, squeak]
NOW, YOU DON'T NEED
A LOT OF THAT.
A HALF-HOUR IS PLENTY.
WHAT YOU NEED NOW IS TO GET
YOURSELF A DIGITAL CLOCK
THAT DISPLAYS SECONDS.
NOW, YOU PLAY BACK THE TAPE,
AND THEN, YOU ADJUST THE CLOCK,
SO THAT, YOU'RE GETTING
A PULSE EVERY SECOND.
I'VE GOT THE DIGITAL CLOCK
SET TO MY OWN HEARTBEAT.
THAT BRINGS ME TO
THE FINAL STEP:
WIRING THE DIGITAL CLOCK
UP TO MY HEART.
I'VE GOT A WIRE RUNNIN' OFF
THE BACK OF THE DIGITAL READOUT.
I'LL JUST TAKE THE OTHER END
AND HOOK IT UP TO THE HEART AREA
BY SOLDERING IT TO A COUPLE
OF ADJACENT CHEST HAIRS.
[sizzle]
OW... OW...
YOU MIGHT WANNA HAVE
A COUPLE OF ASPIRINS
BEFORE YOU TRY THAT.
BUT, SHE'S DONE,
[clock beeping]
AND NOW, TINY ELECTRICAL JOLTS
FROM THIS DIGITAL UNIT
[clock beeping]
ARE GOING TO KEEP MY HEART
RUNNING LIKE CLOCKWORK.
[clock beeping]
NOW, WHEN PEOPLE SAY:
"HOW'S THE OLD TICKER?"
[clock beeping]
I DON'T HAVE TO DO
A BAD, DIRTY JOKE, ANYMORE.
[clock beeping]
SO, REMEMBER:
" IF WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
[clock beeping]
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY."
[continuous tone]
OH MAN, AM I DEAD?
OH NO, JUST ON SNOOZE.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU OLDER GUYS
WHO'VE REACHED THAT AGE
WHERE YOU JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW ANYTHING WORKS, ANYMORE.
LIKE, UH, SAY YOU WANT
TO PHONE A FRIEND.
USED TO BE, IF HE WASN'T HOME,
HE JUST WOULDN'T ANSWER.
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS NOW?
YOU GET THE VOICE MAIL.
IT TELLS YA TO PRESS
THE POUND SIGN.
SO, YOU SAY TO YOURSELF:
" WHAT'S THE POUND SIGN?"
LB.
[laughter]
YOU LOOK AT YOUR PHONE,
I HAVEN'T GOT ANY LB HERE.
I GOT MEM, DEL, SHIFT, SAVE,
HOLD, MUTE, BUT NO LB.
AND NOW, YOU FEEL LIKE AN IDIOT.
BUT IT'S NOT YOU, IT'S THEM!
YOU KNOW,  THEM.
THE PEOPLE WHO CHANGE THINGS
JUST TO BUG YA.
REMEMBER THE OLD DAYS...
YOU HAD A RECORD PLAYER AND
ALL YOU HAD TO FIGURE OUT
WAS WHETHER TO PUT IT ON
33 AND A 1/3 OR 45 RPM?
AND THE SIZE OF THE RECORD
WAS A BIG HINT.
[laughter and applause]
AND NOW, THEY GOT
GRAPHIC EQUALIZERS
AND DOLBY 5.1, AND SO ON.
HEY, IF YOUR EARS CAN'T TELL
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
A.M. AND F.M.,
WHAT DO YOU NEED WITH
A DUAL MONO PREAMPLIFIER
AND ELECTROSTATIC
HYBRID SPEAKERS
AND NON-METALLIC
CARBON-FIBRE INTERCONNECTS?
[loud applause]
YOU GOTTA FEEL
BETTER ABOUT THIS...
YOU'RE NOT A COMPLETE MORON
LIVING IN THE STONE AGES.
I'LL TELL YA SOMETHING,
ALL THAT OLD TECHNOLOGY
IS GONNA COME RIGHT BACK.
YOU KNOW, THEY WENT TO
THE DIGITAL WATCHES,
BIG, BIG DEAL.
NOW, THEY'RE BACK TO
THE SWEEPING THING AGAIN.
I BET, IN SIX MONTHS,
THEY'LL COME OUT AND SAY
THAT BETA IS WAY BETTER
THAN VHS AND SWITCH BACK.
AND, I'LL BE RIDING
THE CREST OF THAT WAVE,
LEMME TELL YA!!!
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YA.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
I'M TELLIN' YA,
THIS HOMEMADE MAIL SYSTEM
IS WORKING OUT GREAT.
YOU GOTTA HELP ME
WITH THIS, HAROLD.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I'D LIKE TO,
BUT I JUST HAVE THIS THING
ABOUT BEING LAUGHED AT.
[laughter]
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BE LAUGHED AT.
DO YOU THINK I'M
BEING LAUGHED AT?
YES.
OH, C'MON HAROLD,
LOOK AT ALL THESE LETTERS.
I'M TELLIN YA,
THIS IDEA IS WORKING.
YOU GOT FIFTY CENTS
FOR EACH ONE OF
THESE LETTERS?
NO, THIS IS MY FREE
INTRODUCTORY OFFER,
BUT YOU CAN SEE THAT
THE DEMAND IS THERE.
NOW, COME ON HAROLD,
HELP ME DELIVER THESE.
I CAN'T, I'VE GOT AN ESSAY DUE
ON THE IMPORTANCE OF CULTURE
IN MODERN SOCIETY,
AND THERE'S A TWO-HOUR
XENA THE WARRIOR PRINCESS.
TWO HOURS!
OH, COME ON, HAROLD.
YOU NOW, HAROLD...
WITH THE TWO OF US
WORKING TOGETHER,
WE'LL GET THIS DONE
IN NO TIME AT ALL.
YOU KNOW, HOW YOU
ALWAYS SAY TO ME:
"UNCLE RED,
I'D REALLY LIKE TO DO
SOMETHING TOGETHER."
YOU ALWAYS SAY THAT.
HUH?
YEAH, I GUESS I DO.
OKAY, OKAY?
OKAY.
YOU'LL HELP ME?
YEAH, OKAY.
THAT ONE'S YOURS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
THIS IS NEW MEMBER NIGHT
AND RANGER GORD HAS A GUY
HE WANTS TO PROPOSE
AS A NEW MEMBER.
SCARY.
[laughter]
THANK YOU, RED.
THANK YOU,
MEN OF POSSUM LODGE.
IT'S NOT OFTEN I COME TO YOU
LOOKING FOR A SPECIAL FAVOUR
OR CONSIDERATION.
WELL, MAYBE THAT ONE TIME WHEN
I WAS ON FIRE FROM LIGHTNING.
AND THAT TIME WHEN THAT
HAND PUPPET GOT STUCK.
[laughter]
ANYWAY, TONIGHT,
I'M HERE TO ASK YOU
TO OPEN YOUR LODGE...
NO, TO OPEN YOUR HEARTS
TO BERTRAM J. MERDON.
BERT AND I HAVE
BECOME QUITE CLOSE
SINCE HIS MOM KICKED
HIM OUT OF THE HOUSE
LAST YEAR.
WE ACTUALLY HAVE GONE
HIKING EVERY WEEKEND.
AND LET ME TELL YOU
SOMETHING HERE,
BERT HAS A FIRST AND LAST NAME
FOR EVERY SHRUB BETWEEN HERE
AND PORT ASBESTOS.
THINK ABOUT THAT.
THAT'S DEDICATION!
WHAT DO YOU SAY,
CAN HE JOIN?
GUYS...?
UH, GORD, IF BERT
JOINS THE LODGE,
WOULD HE BE
TAKING YOU OUT
HIKING ALL THE TIME
AND AWAY FROM
THE LODGE?
ABSOLUTELY.
ALL THOSE
IN FAVOUR?
[in unison]:
AYE!!!
[this sequence is
narrated by Red]
BILL HAD ASKED ME TO MEET
HIM OUT BEHIND THE LODGE
FOR A LITTLE TARGET PRACTICE.
DID YOU BRING THE GUN?
THAT'S A FISHING ROD.
OH BOY! OH NO!
KIDS, DON'T DO THIS AT HOME.
OH BOY! OOH!!!
I'VE NEVER SEEN A MAN
OF HIS CALIBRE BEFORE.
OH, YOU'VE GOT A POP CAN.
WHERE ARE GONNA PUT IT?
THERE'S A BUNCH OF JUNK THERE.
ON WHAT... ON WHAT?
THERE YOU GO, WE GOT A STUMP,
...A STUMP, YEAH, YEAH.
GIVE ME THE POP CAN,
GIVE ME THE POP CAN.
LET'S GET GOING.
YOU'RE GONNA EMPTY THAT?
YOU'RE GONNA DRINK
THE WHOLE POP CAN?
JUST POUR IT ON THE GROUND.
BILL, THAT'S GONNA HURT.
THAT'S GOTTA SMART.
JUST POUR IT OUT.
BILL, BILL, GOSH!
OH, BILL!
OH, MAN!
SEE NOW, IF I DID THAT,
I'D HAVE INCREDIBLE HEARTBURN,
BUT HE SEEMS ALRIGHT.
[a huge burp erupts from Bill]
I GUESS HE'S FINE.
ALL RIGHT, SO...
I PUT THE CAN UP THERE.
GIMME THE GUN.
HERE WE GO, HERE WE GO!
[bang!]
THERE WE GO!!!
NOT BAD, EH?
FIRST SHOT.
[a huge burp erupts from Bill]
HEY, IF YOU'RE SICK,
GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL PUT THE CAN
BACK UP THERE.
OKAY, BILL, AWAY YOU GO.
[bang!]
TAKE ANOTHER SHOT.
FIRE A FEW OFF.
THAT'S NOT WORKING FOR YOU,
YOU NEED AN UZI.
WHAT'S HE UP TO?
OH, LITTLE STONES AND
PIECES OF GRAVEL.
[bang! Bang! Bang!]
HOLY MACKEREL!
HE'S PEPPERIN' 'ER.
YOU MUST'VE GOT IT.
THE POP CAN'S STILL THERE.
HOLY SMOKE!
LOOK WHAT YOU DID TO THE LOG!!!
WOW, LOOK AT THAT!
YEAH, BUT, BILL...
YOU STILL DIDN'T
GET THE POP CAN.
WHAT? WHAT?
[burp!!!]
[dogs barking]
HAROLD, GET YOUR
CAN IN HERE.
[dogs barking]
YOU WANNA TALK ABOUT STRESS
IN THE WORKPLACE?
WE'VE GOT A SERIOUS FLAW
IN OUR PLAN, UNCLE RED.
I'LL TELL YOU
THE PROBLEM.
I'M NOT THINKING
BIG ENOUGH.
NO, THE PROBLEM IS
YOU'RE NOT THINKING
OFTEN ENOUGH.
NO... NO, NO.
WE GOT PEOPLE PAYING
50 CENTS APIECE TO
DELIVER A LETTER.
WHAT IF WE CHARGE THEM
A DOLLAR NOT TO DELIVER
A BILL TO THEM, HUH?
AND THEN, MAYBE FIVE BUCKS,
NOT TO GET ANY JUNK MAIL
FOR THE WHOLE YEAR.
YEAH!!!
AND THEN, WE'LL PAY
$10,000 TO POST BAIL.
IT'S A FEDERAL OFFENSE
TO WITHHOLD MAIL,
UNCLE RED.
I'M NOT WITHHOLDING MAIL.
I'M DISTILLING IT.
[laughter]
WHAT IF A GUY PAYS
50 CENTS TO DELIVER
A BILL, RIGHT?
AND THE OTHER GUY
PAYS A DOLLAR NOT
TO RECEIVE THAT BILL.
WHAT HAVE WE GOT?
WE GOT A BIDDING
WAR, HAROLD.
I'M TELLIN' YA, MAN.
WE'RE GONNA BE
ROLLIN' IN IT.
OH YEAH, YEAH.
I JUST WISH
IT WAS MONEY.
[laughter]
WELCOME TO THE "EXPERTS"
PORTION OF THE SHOW.
WHERE WE EXAMINE THOSE
THREE LITTLE WORDS THAT
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY:
[studio audience]:
I DON'T KNOW!!!
HA, HA!
WAY TO GO!
JOINING MY UNCLE RED
ON THIS PART OF THE SHOW
IS HIS BEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE WIDE ROOM:
MR. MIKE HAMAR.
[applause]
MIKE'S UP HERE TRYING
TO LIVE DOWN HIS
CRIMINAL PAST,
BUT EVERYBODY JUST
KEEPS BRINGING IT UP.
SORRY.
[laughter]
WE HAVE A LETTER FROM
A VIEWER IN OREGON WHO WRITES:
"DEAR EXPERTS..."
"I JUST RECEIVED AN INVITATION
TO GO BACK TO MY HOMETOWN
FOR A HIGH SCHOOL REUNION."
"IF I DON'T GO,
PEOPLE WILL ASSUME
MY LIFE IS A MESS,"
"I'M FAT AND UGLY,
I'M A FAILURE,"
"AND I'M ASHAMED
OF MY LIFE."
"WHEREAS, IF I DO GO,
PEOPLE WILL KNOW FOR SURE."
[laughter]
"WHAT CAN I DO?"
YOU GO TO THE REUNION,
BUT YOU ARRIVE LATE
AND YOU SEND YOUR WIFE
INTO THE REUNION HALL.
WHAT IF YOU'RE NOT MARRIED?
THEN, YOU SEND IN
ONE OF YOUR KIDS.
[laughter]
SO, THEY GO
INTO THE HALL
AND THEY GO
TO THE TABLE WITH
ALL THE NAMETAGS ON IT
AND THEY SCAN
THE NAMETAGS
LEFT LYING THERE.
AND THEN,
THEY COME OUT
TO THE CAR
AND THEY TELL YA
WHO DIDN'T SHOW.
AND THEN, YOU
QUICKLY DECIDE
WHO IS THE PERSON
YOU HATED THE MOST
AND THEN, YOU
GO IN THERE,
YOU PICK UP
THEIR NAMETAG,
AND PRETEND
TO BE THEM.
[laughter]
THAT'S THE MOST OUTRAGEOUS
PLAN I HAVE EVER HEARD.
YOU KNOW, IT WOULD
PROBABLY WORK, TOO.
I DID THIS.
REMEMBER AT OUR
HIGH SCHOOL REUNION?
I PRETENDED THAT I WAS
THE CLASS PRESIDENT,
WALLY KIBBLER.
AND EVERYONE WAS GOING:
"BOY WALLY,
YOU'VE CHANGED."
AND I SAID THAT IT WAS
ALL THE HARD LIVIN'
AND DRINKIN'.
AND THEN, I MADE UP
A WHOLE BUNCH OF STUFF
ABOUT WHAT A
LOSER I WAS
AND HOW I ENDED UP
IN JAIL FOR A SERIES
OF PETTY CRIMES.
AND SO ON.
REAL PITIFUL, EH?
AND THEN, I SAID,
DID YOU HEAR ABOUT
MIKE HAMAR?
HE MARRIED A SUPERMODEL AND
NOW HE'S THE HEAD OF CHRYSLER.
I ALWAYS KNEW
THAT GUY WOULD GO FAR.
YOU KNOW, MIKE,
IT DIDN'T WORK
ALL THAT WELL.
EVERYBODY KNEW
IT WAS YOU
'CAUSE THEY EITHER
SAT ON THE JURY
OR TESTIFIED
AT YOUR TRIALS.
IT'S ALSO UNFORTUNATE
THAT YOU CHOSE THE FELLA
WHO'S NOW THE MAYOR.
THE MAYOR?
BOY, HE'S SURE LOOKIN' ROUGH.
[laughter and applause]
[police sirens blaring]
ALL RIGHT,
I GUESS STARTIN' UP
OUR OWN POSTAL SYSTEM
IS NOT AN ENTIRELY
RISK-FREE VENTURE,
BUT I THINK WE
PROVED OUR POINT.
WHAT POINT
IS THAT?
WHAT POINT WOULD
THAT BE?
THE POINT THAT
CRIME DOESN'T PAY?
ONE SIZE HANDCUFF
FITS ALL?
BEING FRISKED ISN'T AS
MUCH FUN AS IT LOOKS?
WHAT POINT IS THAT?
WE GOT CHARGED
WITH A FEDERAL
MISDEMEANOR
AND FINED $500.
AND NOW, I HAVE
A CRIMINAL RECORD.
THAT'LL MAKE YOU MORE
POPULAR AT SCHOOL.
OH, AS IF!!!
OH, ALL RIGHT, HAROLD,
WHAT DO YOU SAY...
I SHOULD JUST
GO ALONG TO
GET ALONG?
YOU CAN'T FIGHT
CITY HALL, IS THAT IT?
RIGHT, YOU CAN'T!
LAWYERS CAN,
MILLIONAIRES CAN,
YOU CAN'T!!!
YOU FIGHT CITY HALL,
WE END UP IN CITY JAIL.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
I'LL DO NOTHING.
WILL THAT MAKE YOU HAPPY?
IF I STOP TAKING PART
IN TRYING TO MAKE THIS
A BETTER WORLD TO LIVE IN?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
THAT'S ALL I EVER
WANTED, UNCLE RED.
[squeal of the Possum]
MEETING TIME.
COME ON, THINK ABOUT IT.
WASN'T THAT JUST
A LITTLE BIT FUN?
YOU ALWAYS WANTED TO
RIDE AROUND IN A POLICE CAR
WITH THE SIRENS GOING,
YEAH.
JUST NOT FROM THE BACKSEAT
WITH A COAT OVER MY HEAD.
[laughter]
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
IT LOOKS LIKE I'M NOT COMING
STRAIGHT HOME,
AFTER THE MEETING TONIGHT.
I'M HOPING TO COME STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE ARRAIGNMENT.
AND, UH...
YOU BETTER PUT SOME MONEY ASIDE,
IN CASE THE COURT LEVIES A FINE.
UNLESS, THEY MAIL IT TO ME.
AND TO THE REST OF YA,
THANKS FOR WATCHING
AND ON BEHALF OF MYSELF,
AND HAROLD,
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
"KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE."
ALL RISE.
[lodge members]:
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
OKAY, OUR FIRST ANNOUNCEMENT:
WE HAD A LITTLE MIX-UP
IN OUR MAIL SYSTEM.
APPARENTLY, A LETTER THAT
WAS SUPPOSED TO GO TO
SUSIE McCLINTOCK
WENT TO SOMEBODY ELSE.
IF ANYBODY HAS THAT LETTER,
PLEASE RETURN IT TO ME
IMMEDIATELY,
AS IT CONTAINS COMMENTS
OF A HIGHLY PERSONAL NATURE.