[quirky upbeat music]
If all the world's a stage, then we all must
work for Wells Fargo, Dennis Wells Fargo and
I don't work for them.
I will. I'm up here.
I'm producing and directing this television
show for my uncle,
And I love doing it for a lot of reasons.
But I guess lack of alternatives would be
pretty close to the top.
It's pretty close to the top and lack of it.
Here's Map Knuckle.
The star of the Red Green Show.
Here he is, Mr. Red Green.
Thank you. Welcome to Possum Lodge, where men
are men and Harold is understudying.
Tell them what you can do if you're a
tasteless gimmick machine there, Harold.
Oh, you mean my special effects axe?
Just a little taste of Hollywood.
Hopefully not a lethal dose.
Setting up the lodge last night.
Bunch of us were sitting around the wood
stove talking about the differences between
people and how irritating that can be.
And we got some members here who have a big
conniption over the least little thing.
And then on the other end of the spectrum,
you get somebody like old man Sedgwick.
You can stroll down to the dock with his
pants on fire and check the temperature of
the water before he jumps in the lake.
That's probably because he uses his pant
Cuffs as an ashtray.
Why does he do that? Well, I think an old
man, Sedgwick, the part from the ankles down
is the smoking section.
Anyway, we all have a squash button.
Our pants once in a while, don't we?
But you know, it's it's it's kind of funny
if you're going to play a trick on somebody,
you don't you don't pick somebody who isn't
going to get upset.
You know, you go to the guy who's going to
give you the the biggest reaction.
So it's kind of strange that the fellows who
are the ones who don't want to be bothered at
all are the ones that get bothered all the
time.
That's ironic, isn't it?
It's mean. Same thing, Harold, I guess.
You know, the two exceptions of that have to
be a helmet, winter garden and Moose
Thompson, because these guys are huge.
And when they get upset, they have a habit
of ripping your head off and throwing it down
the two hole or.
Well, with that visual fresh in our minds,
why don't we just move on to the next
segment, you know, unless of course, you
have a point to make.
Whereas when I get upset, I fire people,
You know, you can always take your time and
feel like you're right
In the next segment. Would you, Harold?
Yes, sir. Right away, sir.
Whatever you like, sir. You know, Harold, I
can remember the days when we'd catch so
many fish on Possum Lake at the water level
had dropped six feet or better.
No way, no possible way that could happen.
And then the fish would be in the boat with
you, causing
Them to displace his own weight in water,
resulting in a zero net change in the
perceived volume of the lake.
What do you say about that? What do you say
about that?
Well, all I know is that the water level went
down eight feet.
You said six. I was just being conservative
in case you questioned me.
Now I see the hell with it.
The water level was down at least 10 feet.
We came in on our boats and our prop cut all
the water lines and the fishing boat went
right underneath the dock.
Yep, all I got to show for it, of course,
was a bump on the head and a face full of
spiders, which I killed by slapping them
with a speckled trout.
Sounds like quite a date. Oh golly.
My Robert Goulet albums are missing all of
them.
Even the best stuff.
Well, that's good news. I'm just kidding,
Ed.
Bob Goulet is a friend of mine.
What did you do with them? Duck me.
I wouldn't touch Old Bob Wills albums.
Heck, the Bob Meister and I were like
brothers.
I know it was. You duck.
Last month you took my special clipper for
four unsightly nose and deer hairs.
And you always put down me and my showbiz
aspirations.
By Robert Goulet. Albums are missing there.
They're gone. They're just gone.
Oh, not a problem.
Why don't you just get old doc there to send
down to his friend Bobby Goulet?
Maybe he'll send them up and said, Huh?
You will bob bow Mr.
Hop before the level in here sinks another
eight feet.
So I hear there's been a theft by Robert
Goulet albums.
Still, technically it is theft.
Can you describe the stolen items?
Well, I can. I can.
They're around had a hole in the center and
they just slightly off center.
A lot like Eddie here.
Do you have any suspects? There's your man?
Eddie things-I took the albums.
We all know it was Elvis who did it.
Well, we're going to treat me like a fool.
I would think of offering a reward if the
recipient were willing to donate the money to
the Possum Lake Little Theater Group, which
I would start as soon as I received the
money. Are you going to need a bodyguard or
some sort of personal protection?
I don't think so.
He will, if he goes ahead, have that little
theater thing.
I love seeing lipstick in various
Shades
From Ruby Red through purple into that like
pink stuff that Joey Heathers more in earlier
days. The sight of lipstick makes my libido
take action.
Mind you, when Uncle Bob wears lipstick, I
almost always have a completely different
reaction. But still.
This week on Handymen Corner, we're going to
show you what you can do with all those old
hot water heaters you got sitting out on
your front porch.
I know it's kind of fun just to watch them
rust out as the seasons come and go, but
maybe there's something better that you
could do for yourself or your neighbor.
For all of mankind or just yourself, you
ever never looked at a hot water heater.
I mean, really looked at one.
Because when I look at it, I don't see a hot
water heater.
I see a twelve thousand cup coffee maker.
I see the world's most private phone booth.
I see a lawn roller.
I see a beer cooler.
I see a dandy place to keep magnets.
More importantly, I see a project.
Now you're going to need an egg beater, an
aquarium, an oxygen tank and a very
understanding insurance agent.
I guess they're not laughing now, are they?
We build ourselves a one man sub.
No, I, that's the top part off here.
What you do now is take that aquarium that I
mentioned and invert that, turn it over and
put her on here and make it sealed off with,
say, silicone caulking or even duct tape as
long as it's watertight. If you don't have
an aquarium, you could use one of those Pyrex
roasting pans. So your choice, really?
So there you are along the way, down to the
bottom of the ocean floor and you can propel
yourself forward with manual power.
They would do this once in a while.
You go
Up periscope.
I don't really understand a periscope.
And then when you want to rise to the
surface, you just drop your ballast and up
you go, it's that simple.
And I got her mounted here on the launching
ramp.
You just slide this down into the water.
But of course, it's not going to go anywhere
now because I got the wedges in place, but
it's just that simple. Then there's a lot of
fun, and I think you're going to really enjoy
your hot water heater. So remember, the
women don't find you handsome, they should at
least find you handy.
I did remember to put those wedges in
tonight.
It is summer, I shall never see a sky so
blue.
I shall never see a cloud so white, I shall
never see another day like because I looked
into the sun with binoculars.
Wow, now we got Eddie in a real flap over
his missing albums and with Doc as a suspect,
you never really know where you stand.
It's not that doc lie so much, it's just to
embellish, embellishes the truth to the point
where it's unrecognizable.
Kind of like buying a Hyundai pony fully
loaded manager.
You should never buy anything when you're
fully loaded.
Well, not to worry, I'll go read the novels
on the case.
He's got all the private detective equipment
he's going to need.
You got it from the back of a comic book at
A nose from the back of the comic book out
here.
Anyway, is another guy who gets real upset,
so adding him to the mix is kind of fun to,
you know, old man Sedgwick now.
He says he never touched the LP, but he's
offered a reward to anybody who steals the
rest of them. Sticky Peterson says he
doesn't think the records are going to turn
up, but just to be on the safe side, he
smashed the record player.
Of course, all these things are just bugging
the crap out, Eddie.
So I'm I'm more or less in favor of them.
You know, rat, I find this all incredibly
childish and irresponsible.
That's my opinion.
Well, Harold, if you can't stay young, you
can only stay immature.
You know, I wonder if I'm ever going to be
able to continue taking part in this life.
Don't tease me, Harold.
Why it's always so much colder up this end,
the league
There,
It's mean all do I order fries through this
thing to
Get identification?
Well, I have my body.
How many, Zach? How far?
We didn't have a perfect storm.
Oh, cats.
Oh, just a second.
Expecting relatives, perhaps
A theft, which means a thief walks amongst us
a little extra security would be a prudent
response for everyone except for said thief.
Would it not?
Well, I'll take my chances.
No.
Ok, that is a victim mentality.
No wonder your life's a disaster.
Me, I'm confronted by a thief that would
make my day, you know, red.
I have the strength and training to reach
right into a man's chest.
Rip his heart out and hand it back to him
before he dies.
Oh, imagine that.
Oh, sick.
Oh, Lucian, in your hand.
I wear a glove, I guess.
Starship entry number four, oh, six, a
reminder, wear a glove when you're doing that
heart ripping thing. Well, I'm ready for
him.
What's your plan?
Well, my plan is I don't have anything worth
stealing kind of an ounce of prevention thing
I do.
There's a double impact.
No? Well, good luck.
Great theater was crowded, wasn't all.
But I come by because I want you to see if
you could find what happened to Eddie's
record. You know, you're like searching
around in garbage and stuff.
Light years ahead. You read Item eight, a
letter to Doc Render from a certain lady
friend.
Where'd you find that? Oh, oh.
So you also have the training to reach into
a man's mailbox and take a letter?
I don't want. Where is it?
It's in my good pants, but I wrote one
myself.
I have authority. It's in the charter.
Well, I think you better get that back to
talk.
All in good time.
This is potential evidence.
There are several overt references to the
golden era of musical comedy.
We hear that Doc stole those records, and he
set them as a gift to his pen pal in the
Philippines. You want me to run that one
now?
No, not really. No.
You're a sack of fat, right?
Not mentally and physically, especially
physically.
Me, I'm a rock star freak like a rock.
Great album. Well, I'll do the tough thing
and I'll phone the woman.
I'll find out your answer and probably won't
even thank me
How you got that right now.
That's why they say there's a thousand Fred
MacMurray for every one.
Clint Eastwood.
Well, from the neck up anyway.
Oh, great.
That's. Thank you, Bill.
This week we're going to build a campfire,
and one thing you should know was we're doing
it where there have been a lot of pesticides
that didn't really occur to us at the moment.
Thank you again. But that's the of an
slinked into the ground.
Pretty heavy there. Over the last 60, 70, 80
years or so, it seemed like a good place for
us to build a campfire, not going to burn
any brush or anything.
We're just trying to get some kindling
together here.
Bill's using the psi, kind of.
I don't have time for things like sore eyes
I.
I kind of like a real good, a real good
accent like out there.
Oh, it breaks up the kindling and burns a
lot better, and it's just nice to around that
kind of a fun thing that I do.
Is it do?
Oh, it's hard to stick anything into the
ground because there's so much chemical in
there. There's very little soil.
So anyway, we got the the big lungs bill's
going to lighter up there and
To match Colin Quinn bill for gonorrhea.
Actionscript, but you know, we could we could
feel heat coming off off the fire, and it
wasn't even going yet, and that's that's
very peculiar.
But here again, I guess what was happening
was that, gosh, some of those some of those
pesticides and what have you apparently were
were flammable.
We were we were in a very confused at this
point because we couldn't we could feel the
heat and we could see we could smell smoke.
But there wasn't any. Oh, yes, there was.
Yes, there was a fire there.
Oh, I see. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Hmm. Mm hmm.
But, you know, Bill always looks on the
bright side, and then he figures that's going
to save him a lot of money and matches
All that,
And then he thought maybe he should just put
it out.
You know, he's he's a trained firefighter
bill is I don't think that's how you put out
a chemical fire in London.
And then he got a good idea.
If you can't get your wood to get on fire,
you move your wood over to where the fire is.
No hair that was going up and down the TV
channels.
They saw that music video one.
They got there.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Have you ever seen that
before?
Well, yeah, I've seen it before, but you
know, I always thought there was something
wrong with it. I mean, the pictures change
is about forty eight times a second.
I thought, maybe you needed a D Scrambler,
you know,
That's the way music videos are fast cutting
lots of
Images. What do you mean?
How do you mean? I mean, what do you mean?
I mean, I mean, what's the point of it, you
know?
Well, it's an art form, isn't it?
You know, I directed my best friend's music
video for his band, The Slugs of Attila.
That's the band's name, right?
They used to be called gaping wound, but
that guy left the group right.
So they don't explain that to me.
Oh, OK.
You see music videos have lots of images,
right?
See that way. They contrast the lyrics,
definitely adding hidden meanings and
poignancy and women in underwear.
That's a very important motif.
Really? Yeah.
Well, I watch for about 20 minutes, and I
can't remember one thing that I saw.
You know, I looked like the camera was
attached to one of them machines.
They used to shake up your paint at the
hardware store.
It's very easy to remember music videos only
have three elements.
One women with huge cleavages to a guy
standing in a pile of rubble singing or
three. It would be, and probably the most
popular of all, people fighting.
That's all I got to remember is those three,
unless, of course, it's a country and
western. Then there's going to be like a guy
in a horse and a woman sitting on a fence.
You know, it was heavy metal.
There's going to be like a guy in a
Burned-out factory singing.
That's where they do those. And of course,
if it's rap, it's going to be like in front
of a brick wall, a guy yelling, That's how
you tell the difference.
Well, the one I saw, I didn't have any
horses, didn't have any shaking camera,
didn't have any factories, OK?
Had the women with the big cleavages and it
had a lot of men shouting and fighting.
Well, yeah, see that.
That's an opera. Oh.
So that is turning the whole larger part, you
know, looking and looking for these missing
out, or at least I've been told I don't see
any difference.
I guess there's no harm done with this
missing album business, but it has.
It has drawn a lot of attention to Bob Gale
and that bothers me a little.
Hopefully, we'll get the whole mess
straightened out at tonight's lodge meeting.
We we'd all hate to think we had a thief
among us.
We know we have a womanizer, a liar, three
con artists, two bullies and a tightwad.
I don't think that's a very respectful way to
talk about your fellow lodge members.
Oh yeah, and a socially challenged idiot.
Thanks for reminding me, Harold.
You know, a thief is something else and
unsurprising, considering we have nothing of
any value up here at the Lodge.
I mean, other than the intangibles, you
know, friendships and and petty jealousies.
And I guess the arm wrestling, you wouldn't
want a thief to mess any of that up.
I don't get it. I'll go rat hawk.
I'm like, You know, you guys are always
borrowing stuff from each other than wrecking
it, then returning it. You know, what's the
big difference?
Really big difference, Harold.
I mean, number one, you get it back when
it's totaled.
And number two, you can then borrow
something from that guy and mangle it,
especially if you're a little upset, huh?
There's so much to being a man that I have
yet to really understand.
Oh, there it is. That's the call of the
meeting.
Come on, uncle. Rent the day of reckoning.
Let's get down there and find out what's
going on.
Yeah. Ok, Harold.
Well, we'll be able to probably straighten
this album thing out pretty, pretty quickly,
and then we can all get back to our normal
lives, with the exception of Harold for
obvious reasons.
Three, three, three or
five? All right.
Because now, Simon Theodore, I seem pretty
anxious here, ready to find your albums.
That's not funny.
We can prove that Thug stole them.
I didn't take them.
You took them, Mr. I didn't take them.
Give it a rest. What about this lady friend
in the Philippines?
Huh? I don't have any lady friend in the
Philippines, and I didn't take the stupid
albums, huh? I thought something like that.
Maybe, maybe Redd would like to make a
comment about that letter I showed you
earlier today.
I sure want that letter was none of Noel's
damn business.
Hey, hey, hey.
What's sauce for the goose red?
No. Took that letter because Duck took my
albums.
I did not. Several large members saw you
pick up stuff on Eddie's room last night,
huh? I was borrowing a pillow.
The gate, you understand.
Are you not listening?
Read my lips.
I did not take the album.
We found an album cover under your bed.
All right. Sure.
I took it, and I even know you took them.
You took them because you want to make a
gift.
I did not. So you did.
Well, I didn't. They did.
All right. I did. Sure. You got me there.
All right. Yeah, I put them because I wanted
to make a gift to Freddie.
No, I wanted to make something for you out
of the album.
Oh, sure. Well, where is it?
Oh, well, I'm not exactly sure where the dog
got picked out here.
Oh, wow.
I mean, it's a it's an order of trade.
It's it's beautiful.
I don't know what to say.
Thank you for all the stock.
You know, I thought we could have a barbecue
themed dinner one night, you know, would fill
the tray with chunks of ham and we could all
wear album covers.
That's great.
That's thoughtful of you.
I forgive you.
Oh, I wanted to go.
Well, just before I lose my entire meal and
you turned the manpower here.
Once you get up, entertain us with one of
your jokes.
Hey.
Twenty one, huh?
Well, now it seems it was this traveling
sale.
Well, now that's one of the reasons I never
lose faith in man's ability to solve his own
problems. It's going to be a long time
before Eddie realizes that was more of a gift
to us than it was to him anyway.
If his wife is watching, I'll be coming
straight home after the meeting and I think I
figured out what it was. I said at that
party last week that got you so upset and I'd
like to take my third guest tonight.
I'm wrong. I'm going to have to go with a
blanket apology covering the last 30 years,
which I know you're getting real tired of
hearing.
So until next time on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole gang up here at Possum
Lodge. Keep your stick on the ice.
You guys ready with an indoor outdoor, the
Couch kind of a gift.
I guess whatever I was trying to whack
carpet nails in the cell could.
It was a long, long trip, boy.
Forty five days after the curry beef, oh.
With this traveling salesman is out in the
country, and he's tired, sleepy and he sees
his farmhouse off in the distance.
One of those lovely on this job kind of a
hip roof.