[quirky upbeat music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> OKAY, EVERYBODY IT'S
SHOWTIME, SO SMOKE 'EM IF YOU
GOT 'EM.
CHEW 'EM IF YOU HAVE TO,
AND PUT YOUR FEET UP IN THE OLD
EASY CHAIR, BUT DON'T GET TOO
COMFORTABLE BECAUSE IT'S TIME
FOR THE RED GREEN SHOW,
STARRING MY UNCLE AND MY BOSS--
WHICH IS MORE THAN COINCIDENCE,
UNLESS OF COURSE I'VE MISSED MY
GUESS--BUT HERE HE IS, THE
STARCH OF OUR SHOW,
MR. RED GREEN.
STAR OF OUR SHOW.
SORRY, I SAID--I SAID STARCH.
[chuckles]
WRECKED THAT ONE.
HERE--OH, HERE HE IS.
>> THANK YOU, AND WELCOME TO THE
SHOW.
>> KEEP IT MOVIN'.
>> WHAT?
>> KEEP--KEEP IT MOVIN'.
>> WELL, I HAVEN'T EVEN STARTED
YET, HAROLD.
>> WELL, EXACTLY.
>> OKAY.
WE HAD A HECK OF A DAY UP AT THE
LODGE YESTERDAY.
A BEAR COME WANDERIN' IN HERE
RIGHT IN BROAD DAYLIGHT.
A BEAR COME RIGHT INTO THE
LODGE, AND NONE OF US EVEN
NOTICED.
OF COURSE, THERE WAS A SMELL AND
EVERYTHING, BUT WE THOUGHT
SOMEBODY HAD JUST STIRRED UP THE
POND.
>> UNCLE RED, DON'T TELL THAT
STORY.
>> WHY NOT?
IT HAPPENED.
>> YEAH, WELL, JUST 'CAUSE IT
HAPPENED DOESN'T MAKE IT
INTERESTING.
[chuckles]
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENS ISN'T
INTERESTING.
[laughs]
I'M HAROLD GREEN.
I'M UNCLE RED'S PRODUCER AND
DIRECTOR AND NEPHEW, AND I MAKE
THE PICTURE DO THIS.
[laughs]
NEAT, EH?
UNCLE RED, MY ADVICE IS THAT YOU
JUST DROP THIS WHOLE BEAR STORY
THING, GET RIGHT ONTO THE NEXT
SEGMENT TOUT DE SUITE.
WE'RE LOSING VIEWERS.
>> WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE YOU KEEP
WANDERIN' IN HERE AND
INTERRUPTIN' THE FLOW.
>> OH, YEAH.
CLICK, CLICK, CLICK, CLICK,
CLICK, CLICK.
I HEAR 'EM CHANGIN' CHANNELS
RIGHT NOW.
YOU SHOULD GET ONTO THE NEXT
SEGMENT, I THINK.
IT'S MORE INTERESTING THAN THIS.
THIS IS BORING.
THIS IS--THIS IS AS BAD AS A PBS
SUBSCRIPTION DRIVE.
THAT'S HOW BAD THIS IS.
NEXT SEGMENT'S INTERESTING
THOUGH.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE'LL GET BACK TO
THE BEAR STORY LATER, AND I
GUESS WE'LL JUST GO TO OUR--OUR
FILM CLIP NOW.
WHAT IS IT ANYWAY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
[chuckles]
>> [strumming guitar] I HAVE A LITTLE STORY
A SAD ONE TO TELL
A FELLA SELLING SANDWICHES
MORE OR LESS ACCIDENTALLY
DROPPED DOWN THE WELL
ON HIS WAY DOWN
HE MUST'VE KICKED THE BUCKET
WE ASKED THE NEIGHBORS
FOR HELP
BUT THEY JUST SAID
WHO CARES?
HE SPENT ABOUT AN HOUR
SWIMMING 'ROUND AND 'ROUND
THAT WAS GETTIN'
A BIT ANNOYING
AND THEN HE DROWNED
AND THAT'S HOW THE SALESMAN
HE FOUND HIS WATERY GRAVE
BUT ALL'S WELL
THAT ENDS WELL
THE SANDWICHES WERE SAVED
>> THIS WEEK ON THE HANDYMAN
CORNER, I THOUGHT I'D TAKE YOU
OUTDOORS AND SHOW YOU HOW TO
BUILD ONE OF THEM OUTDOOR
ENTERTAINMENT CENTERS,
VIS-A-VIS, A BASKETBALL HOOP.
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING THAT THE
YOUNGSTERS CAN ENJOY PLAYIN'
WITH, AND ALSO THE OLD MAN CAN
PARTAKE OF WHEN RELATIVES DROP
OVER UNEXPECTEDLY.
THE FIRST THING THAT WE'RE GONNA
NEED IS A POLE.
[chopping]
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, WHAT WE WANT TO DO IS, WE
WANT TO DIG A HOLE FOR THE POLE.
OKAY, NO.
THE FIRST THING WE WANT TO DO IS
WE WANT TO DIG A HOLE FOR THE
SHOVEL.
EH, ALL RIGHT.
IF AT FIRST YOU DON'T SUCCEED,
SWITCH TO POWER TOOLS.
OKAY, NOW, THIS IS CALLED A
GAS-POWERED POSTHOLE DIGGER.
AND THE WAY IT WORKS IS THE GAS
GOES IN HERE, AND THE HOLE COMES
OUT DOWN THERE.
SO I'M JUST GONNA START HER UP,
AND AWAY WE GO.
[motor choking]
[motor puttering]
OKAY, WE GOT OUR POLE UP THERE
NOW.
I GUESS I COULD'VE JUST USED
THIS TREE RIGHT WHERE IT WAS,
BUT, OH, WELL.
IT'S HERE NOW.
NOW WE NEED SOMETHING TO USE AS
A BACKBOARD.
[banging]
OKAY.
TOOK THIS OFF THE BACK OF
STINKY'S PICKUP TRUCK, BUT WHAT
WE'LL DO IS WE'LL JUST LET THE
AIR OUT OF THE FRONT TIRES AND
SHE'LL DIP.
THEN NOTHING'LL ROLL, SO IT
WON'T--IT'LL BE FINE.
ALL RIGHT.
WE NEED NOW SOMETHING TO USE
FOR--WE NEED SOMETHING FOR THE
NET, FOR THE BASKETBALL TO GO
INTO THE NET.
[clattering]
I THINK THIS'LL BE PERFECT.
IT'S GOT THE HOOP IN IT THERE,
AND--FOUND THIS IN THE VAN AFTER
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK BORROWED IT.
HE WAS DATIN' ONE OF THE
DAUGHTERS OF THE EMPIRE.
ANYWAY, WE'LL--NOW WE'LL ATTACH
THE--THE BACKBOARD TO THE POLE,
AND WE'LL ATTACH THE HOOP TO
THE--TO THE BACKBOARD USING THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON, DUCT
TAPE.
SO THERE YOU HAVE IT.
KIND OF LOOKS LIKE THE HARLOT
GLOBETROTTERS, DON'T IT?
ANYWAY, UNTIL NEXT TIME,
REMEMBER.
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[tearing]
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE OF
THE SHOW AND THE EXCITING
CONCLUSION TO THE BEAR STORY
RIGHT AFTER THIS.
>> EXCITING CONCLUSION?
MUST BE A NEW STORY ABOUT THE
BEAR.
>> IT IS WINTER.
A BLANKET OF SNOW OUTSIDE.
YOU SHUFFLE OUT IN THE MORNING
DARKNESS TO THE ROW OF CARS ON
THE STREET.
SHOVEL AWAY THE DRIFTS
AROUND THE TIRES,
SWEEP THE SNOW PILED ON THE CAR,
SCRAPE THE CRUST OF HARD ICE
FROM THE WINDOWS.
DAMN IT!
THAT'S NOT YOUR CAR.
>> SO I WAS SAYING, A BEAR JUST
CAME WONDERING RIGHT INTO THE
LODGE, BIG, UGLY, STINKY BEAR
THAT WE ALL JUST FIGURED WAS
MOOSE THOMPSON.
WE DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE THAT THE
BEAR'S EARS WERE TOO SMALL.
KINDA FUNNY THAT A GUY WHO
LOOKED LIKE A BEAR WOULD BE
NAMED "MOOSE."
INDIANS ARE A LOT BETTER AT
NAMING PEOPLE THAN WE ARE.
YOU KNOW, WHEN THEY CALL A GUY
"EAGLE BEAK," YOU HAD A PRETTY
GOOD CHANCE OF SPOTTIN' HIM IN A
CROWD.
>> GREAT STORY, UNCLE RED.
GO TO THE NEXT SEGMENT.
>> WELL, THE STORY'S NOT
FINISHED, HAROLD.
>> WELL, I--I THINK IT PRETTY
MUCH PEAKED.
IN THREE, TWO, ONE, CUE.
>> DON'T EVER LET AN INDIAN NAME
YOU, HAROLD.
>> OKAY.
>> HI THERE, GLEN.
>> HELLO, RED.
HOW'D YOU LIKE TO TAKE OFF AND
GO CAMPING?
I GOT THE R.V. ALL WASHED UP,
GASSED UP, OILED UP,
WINDOW-WASHERED UP, BATTERY
ACIDED UP.
I EVEN FLUSHED OUT THE HOLDING
TANK.
YOU COULD EAT A CASSEROLE OUT OF
THERE, RED.
>> WELL, NO THANKS, GLEN.
NOT TODAY.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I CAN SHUT DOWN THE ARENA.
I'VE DONE IT BEFORE.
WE CAN JUST BE TWO VAGABONDS ON
THE OPEN ROAD, RED.
>> WELL, ACTUALLY, GLEN, I
JUST NEED YOU TO FIX THIS
OUTBOARD MOTOR FOR ME.
>> OH, WELL, I'M KIND OF BUSY,
RED.
>> WELL, GLENN, YOU KNOW, WHEN
YOU--WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
YOU ARE THE ONLY MARINA WITHIN
100 MILES, AND YOU ARE A LODGE
MEMBER,
AND YOU SOLD ME THIS OUTBOARD
MOTOR.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN.
ALL RIGHT.
JUST LEAVE IT.
I'LL TAKE A LOOK AT IT LATER.
>> OH, THANKS, GLEN.
REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
WHERE DO YOU WANT ME TO PUT IT?
>> JUST PUT IT RIGHT THERE.
>> RIGHT HERE?
>> RIGHT THERE'S FINE.
WATCH THE R.V.
>> YEAH, FINE.
NO PROBLEM.
SO DO YOU WANT ME TO TELL YOU
WHAT THE PROBLEM IS?
>> NO, I CAN FIX ANYTHING, RED.
I'LL BE FINE, THANKS.
YOU MIGHT WANT--CAN YOU SNAP
THAT ON FOR ME?
>> YEAH.
>> CAN I OFFER YOU A BEVERAGE,
RED?
GOT A COOLER RIGHT THERE.
I'VE GOT GINGER ALE, CREAM SODA.
I THINK WE'VE EVEN GOT SOME ROOT
BEER IN THERE.
>> NO, NOTHING FOR ME, THANKS.
>> I'LL HAVE A ROOT BEER.
>> DO YOU WANT ME TO GET IT FOR
YOU?
>> WELL, RED, I'M GONNA BE
LOOKIN' AT YOUR MOTOR.
>> ALL RIGHT.
RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
>> JUST TOSS IT OVER, RED.
IT'LL SAVE YOURSELF A FEW STEPS.
IS THAT SOME CORN CHIPS?
CAN YOU HUM THEM OVER TOO, RED,
PLEASE?
RED, CAN YOU POP THE SPRINKLER
ON TOP OF THE R.V.?
THAT'S HOW I LIKE TO WASH IT.
>> YEAH.
[strumming guitar]
I'VE CROSSED THE MIGHTY DESERT
I'VE CLIMBED THE HIGHEST PEAKS
I'VE HUNTED IN THE JUNGLE
I'VE WORN
MY BROTHER'S BREECHES
I'VE SEEN A LOT OF LIFE
FROM THE HIGHEST
TO THE DREGS
BUT THE GREATEST DANGER
I EVER FACED WAS
SHARING A TENT WITH A GUY
WHO ATE PICKLED EGGS
>> [laughs]
HOLD ONTO YOUR SOCKS TODAY,
UNCLE RED, 'CAUSE THIS IS SO
EXCITING.
THE LETTERS, THEY HAVE CELEBRITY
STATUS AND INTERNATIONAL
OVERTONES.
IF I WAS ASKED TO GIVE A BRIEF
EVALUATION OF TODAY'S SEGMENT,
THAT'S HOW I WOULD DESCRIBE IT.
>> WELL, YOU WON'T BE, HAROLD.
>> OH, OKAY.
BUT THAT'S HOW I'D DESCRIBE IT
IF--IF I WAS ASKED AT A LATER
DATE.
I WOULD DESCRIBE IT AS SUCH, BUT
I WASN'T, SO I WON'T.
ANYWAY, HERE'S THE FIRST LETTER.
THIS IS THE INTERNATIONAL ONE,
"DEAR OH CUPANT."
THAT'S FRENCH.
>> THAT'S OCCUPANT.
>> OH, YEAH.
OKAY.
WELL--WELL, THE CONTENT'S STILL
INTERNATIONAL--IS SO.
ANYWAY, HE GOES, "HOW MUCH WOULD
YOU GIVE FOR A WORLD FREE OF
WAR, FEAR, HUNGER, AND WANT?"
>> 280 BUCKS.
>> THAT'S FAIR.
THAT'S--THAT'S MORE THAN FAIR.
VERY FAIR.
>> OKAY, NEXT LETTER.
THIS IS THE CELEBRITY ONE.
GET THIS.
IT'S FROM ED MCMAHON.
YOU KNOW EVERYBODY, UNCLE RED.
THAT'S SO GREAT.
ED MCMAHON, YOU KNOW HIM.
THIS IS GREAT.
A PERSONALIZED LETTER TO YOU.
[chuckles]
"DEAR MR. GREEN.
YOU MAY HAVE ALREADY WON
$1 MILLION CASH, TAX FREE."
OH, EXCELLENT.
YOU'RE A MILLIONAIRE.
OH, THAT'S EX--THAT IS SO
FANTASTIC.
THIS IS GREAT.
ED GOES ON TO SAY, "WOULD YOU BE
INTERESTED IN RECEIVING
MAGAZINES AT A TREMENDOUS
DISCOUNT?"
>> WHY, HAROLD, I THINK YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO TELL ED THAT NOW
THAT I'M A MILLIONAIRE, I WANT
TO PAY FULL PRICE.
SO I'M NOT REALLY INTERESTED IN
THE MAGAZINES.
IN FACT, I MIGHT BE WILLING TO
GO UP TO, SAY, 500 BUCKS TO PUT
AN END TO WORLD FEAR, HUNGER,
AND WANT.
>> THAT IS EXCELLENT.
THAT IS FANTASTIC.
YOU MILLIONAIRES SURE KNOW HOW
TO LIVE.
>> RIGHT.
>> [laughs]
UNCLE RED, NOW THAT YOU ARE A
MILLIONAIRE AND ALL, CAN I
BORROW $2?
>> WELL, OF COURSE YOU CAN,
HAROLD.
BUT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO WAIT
TILL ED'S CHECK CLEARS.
THOUGHT WE'D TRY SOMETHING
KIND OF EXCITING THIS WEEK.
THOUGHT BILL'D SHOW US HOW TO
GO SCUBA DIVING.
SO HE BROUGHT ALL THE GEAR, AND
WHAT HE WANTED TO SHOW ME WAS
THIS FANCY WATCH HE'S GOT
WITH--IT SHOWS YOU YOUR DEPTH
AND HOW MUCH TIME YOU GOT LEFT
IN YOUR TANK.
AND I DIDN'T REALLY WANT HIM TO
TAKE IT OFF, YOU KNOW.
HE JUST--HE GETS IN AND
THIS--AND THAT'S WHY.
AND THEN HE HAD THE OXYGEN TANK,
WANTED TO SHOW ME--
>> OOH!
>> OKAY, SO WE'RE NOT GOING WITH
PLAN A.
WE'RE GOIN' WITH PLAN B, WHICH
IS SNORKELING RATHER THAN SCUBA
DIVING.
BUT A LOT OF THE GEAR IS THE
SAME, THE MASK AND THIS LITTLE
AIR HOSE DEAL, YOU KNOW.
FIRST THING, YOU WANT TO GET A
REAL GOOD SEAL BETWEEN YOUR SKIN
AND--AND THE MASK.
AND THEN YOU BEND THIS UP AND
STICK IT--ONE END IN YOUR MOUTH.
AND THEN BILL'S SHOWING YOU
HERE.
THE AIR GOES IN HERE, AND THIS
IS UNFOR--HE WAS INHALING WHILE
HE WAS--AND THEN IT GOT JAMMED
IN THERE, AND...
I DIDN'T REALIZE THAT BILL
WAS HAVIN' A PROBLEM...
>> GET MY FINGER OUT OF THERE!
>> BREATHIN' THERE.
I WAS KIND OF--BUT I SAVED HIS
LIFE, REALLY.
THERE YOU GO.
>> YIKES!
>> AH, HE'S OKAY.
NOW HE PUTS THE--THE BIG
FLIPPERS ON.
NOW, I'VE NEVER DONE THIS BEFORE
SO I--I'M JUST AN AMATEUR.
I JUST SAT DOWN, PUT THEM ON,
BUT APPARENTLY, THERE IS A
TECHNIQUE WHERE YOU JUST--YOU
JUST STEP INTO THEM LIKE BILL'S
SHOWING YOU THERE.
BUT I GUESS, YOU KNOW, WITH ME
NOT KNOWING, I WAS KIND OF
MAKING A FOOL OUT OF MYSELF,
BUT--AND I WASN'T GONNA WORRY
ABOUT THAT.
YOU KNOW, BILL'S THE EXPERT.
I NEVER CLAIMED TO--TO KNOW WHAT
I'M DOING, YOU KNOW?
AND THIS SEEMED UNUSUAL TO ME,
BUT IT DIDN'T SEEM TO BOTHER
BILL THAT MUCH, SO I GUESS HE'S
JUST GONNA MAKE RIGHT-HAND
TURNS.
ANYWAY, THIS IS A DIVING CAGE,
AND THIS IS BILL IN A WETSUIT,
WHICH YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE ON A
FULL STOMACH.
AND IN HE GOES.
I THINK IT WAS BILL.
HE SHOULD'VE MAYBE HAVE
TIGHTENED THE MASK UP JUST A BIT
THERE.
BUT HE'S OKAY,
SO HE DECIDES HE'S GONNA--THIS
TIME, INSTEAD OF JUMPING IN,
MAYBE CLIMB DOWN THE LADDER,
WHICH IS TRICKY, BECAUSE YOU
GOT--WELL, HE ONLY HAS THE ONE
FLIPPER TO WORRY ABOUT, WHICH IS
AN ADVANTAGE I SUPPOSE.
BUT ALSO, YOU SHOULD REALLY
CHECK HOW TIGHT THE BOLTS ARE,
YOU KNOW?
AND, YOU KNOW, HE JUST BLEW THE
WATER RIGHT OUT OF HIS TUBE INTO
MY FACE, WHICH MADE MY DAY.
LOOK OUT, BILL.
AND THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
HE FELT THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
NOW THAT'S A DIVING CAGE.
DOWN HE GOES, AND WHATEVER HE
FINDS, HE PUTS IN THE CAGE.
THEN HE PULLS ON THE ROPE, AND I
HAUL IT UP.
THAT'S THE IDEA OF IT.
HE WAS DOWN THERE THE BETTER
PART OF--WELL, NOT MORE THAN
FIVE HOURS I WOULDN'T THINK.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE.
BUT THEN EVENTUALLY HE DID PULL
ON--HE PULLED ON THE ROPE, AND I
STARTED HAULING HIM UP.
AND HE COMES UP, AND OF COURSE
THE FIRST THING HE WANTS TO DO
IS TO--IS TO CLEAR OUT HIS TUBE
AGAIN, YOU KNOW.
THANK YOU, BILL.
IT'S REFRESHING BUT SCARY AT THE
SAME TIME.
ANYWAY, UP COMES--UP COMES--UP
COMES THE CAGE, AND LOOK WHAT
HE'S GOT HERE.
FIRST DEAL HE'S GOT, HIS WATCH.
SO I MEAN, I WAS IMPRESSED BY
IT.
AND HE HAD THE SCUBA TANK IN
THERE, AND THERE WAS THE LADDER,
AND HE EVEN HAD THE FLIPPER.
SO IT WAS A GREAT DAY, BUT HE
DIDN'T DO A LOT FOR HIS UPPER
BODY STRENGTH.
IT IS SUMMER,
THE ICE CREAM SEASON.
BY LATE AUGUST,
EVERYONE IN YOUR FAMILY
IS CONE SHAPED.
>> [laughs]
>> BOY.
>> UNCLE RED, DID YOU HAVE FUN
AT GRANDMA GREEN'S PICNIC?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW ME, HAROLD.
AS LONG AS THERE'S A LIZARD
AND A PUNCHBOWL,
I CAN MAKE MY OWN FUN.
[cat yowls]
>> I HAD A HORRIBLE TIME.
I REALLY COULDN'T STAND ALL
THOSE RELATIVES COMING UP TO ME
SAYING, "OH, MY, HOW YOU'VE
GROWN.
OH, MY, HASN'T YOUR COMPLEXION
CLEARED UP."
MAKES ME WANT TO BE EVEN MORE
OBNOXIOUS THAN THEY ARE.
>> WELL, I THINK THAT'S WITHIN
YOUR REACH, HAROLD.
>> OH, YEAH, I KNOW.
I MEAN I COULD SAY THINGS MEAN
TOO.
I COULD SAY THINGS LIKE "OH, I
HAVEN'T GROWN.
YOU SHRUNK," OR, "OH, LAST
TIME, I SAW YOU, YOUR BELLY WAS
ONLY HALF THAT SIZE."
[chuckles]
OR LIKE, "OH, LOOK.
HEY, GRANDMA'S STILL ALIVE."
[laughs]
I DON'T WANT TO, BUT I WILL IF I
HAVE TO.
>> HEY, WATCH IT!
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, HAROLD.
THERE'S AN OLD SAYING.
"YOU CAN PICK YOUR FRIENDS, AND
YOU CAN PICK YOUR NOSE."
>> WHAT'S THAT GOT TO DO WITH
ANYTHING?
>> TOOK YOUR MIND OFF THE
PROBLEM, DIDN'T IT?
>> YEAH.
[splashing]
>> SO, GLENN, FIGURE OUT WHAT
WAS WRONG WITH THE MOTOR?
>> WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW, RED.
>> YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT IT MIGHT
BE THE CARBURETOR.
>> COULD BE.
YOU SHOULD SEE THE CARBURETOR ON
THE R.V.
GOT A THROAT ON IT THE SIZE OF A
TOILET BOWL, RED.
THINK ABOUT THAT NEXT TIME
YOU'RE GONNA BUY SOME GAS.
>> YOU KNOW, I SAW THIS TUBE ON
THE SIDE HANGIN' DOWN HERE.
I THOUGHT MAYBE THAT SHOULD BE
ATTACHED TO THE CARBURETOR.
>> COULD BE.
>> YOU THINK I SHOULD TAKE IT
BACK TO THE LODGE AND TRY IT?
>> I WOULD, SURE.
>> OKAY, WELL, THANKS A LOT,
GLENN.
WHAT DO I OWE YOU?
>> HOW ABOUT A LITTLE SOMETHING
FOR THE R.V., RED?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH, THAT COULD HAPPEN.
WE'LL BE RIGHT--RIGHT BACK AFTER
THESE MESSAGES.
>> WELL, GIVE THEM MORE REASON,
YOU KNOW, LIKE YOUR GUESTS.
>> OH, OKAY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK, AND I'LL
TELL YOU ABOUT THE BEAR WHO
WANDERED INTO THE LODGE.
HE WAS A GUEST.
>> IT IS SPRING.
WE WALK AMONGST THE FLOWERS,
BENDING CLOSE TO SMELL THEIR
FRAGRANCE,
PRESSING OUR NOSTRILS
TO THEIR PISTOLS AND STAMENS.
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE IT IF SOMEONE
STUCK THEIR NOSE INTO YOUR
REPRODUCTIVE ORGANS?
SORRY I ASKED.
>> [roars]
>> HEY, BOB.
HI, BOB.
>> OH.
[chuckles]
HI, RED.
I DIDN'T EVEN HEAR YOU COMIN'
I'M SO CAUGHT UP WORKING, YOU
KNOW, WATER TESTING FOR THE
MINISTRY.
>> WHAT'S THE GOLF CART FOR?
>> MY CLUBS.
OH, IT'S ALSO A COVER.
FOOLS THE POLLUTERS.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> SOMETIMES THEY SEE YOU
COMIN', AND THEY--THEY TRY TO
CLEAN UP A LAKE REAL QUICKLY.
MM-HMM.
>> YOU KNOW, SPEAKING OF WHICH,
WE'VE GOT TO GET POSSUM LAKE
RESTOCKED, EH.
AND I THOUGHT WITH YOUR JOB WITH
THE MINISTRY OF RESOURCES THERE
AND BEING A LODGE MEMBER, YOU
COULD GET THE GOVERNMENT TO KIND
OF CHIP IN ON THAT.
>> OH, POSSUM LAKE'S ALL FISHED
OUT, IS IT?
>> IT'S AT THAT POINT NOW WHERE
FISHIN' IS JUST A WASTE OF
DYNAMITE.
>> OH, WHY DON'T THE GUYS PLAY
SOME GOLF INSTEAD?
>> WELL, I DON'T THINK THE GUYS
WOULD WANT TO, YOU KNOW, GET--
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, GOLF'S A REAL
SPORT.
IT'S THE ONLY SPORT THAT WAS
INVENTED IN SCOTLAND.
NOW THAT TELLS YOU SOMETHING.
YEAH.
WELL, HMM.
OH, WATER LOOKS FINE.
>> I DON'T THINK THE GUYS--YOU
KNOW, THEY'D HAVE TO--THEY'D
HAVE TO GET GOLF CLUBS, YOU
KNOW?
THEY DON'T HAVE ANY OF THOSE,
AND--
>> OH, WELL I'VE GOT ENOUGH TO
OUTFIT EVERYBODY.
>> WELL, BOB, BUT THERE'S--
THERE'S LIKE 40 GUYS IN
THE LODGE, YOU KNOW?
>> NO PROBLEM.
>> I KNOW, BUT I--THESE GUYS,
WELL, THEY'RE NOT GOLFERS AT
HEART, EH?
NOT LIKE YOU.
>> OH, WELL, COME ON.
RED, EVERYONE'S A GOLFER AT
HEART.
IT'LL ALSO DO THE GUYS SOME GOOD
TO GET OUT AND GET SOME FRESH
AIR, EVEN IF IT'S JUST FOR ONE
GAME.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> YEAH.
>> AM I IN YOUR WAY HERE AT ALL?
>> OH, I DON'T THINK SO.
>> NO?
>> [chuckles]
I WON'T HURT YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> I'VE BEEN DOIN' THIS FOR A
LONG TIME.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> FORE!
>> OH, LOOK AT THAT.
NICE SHOT, NICE SHOT, NICE SHOT.
>> YES!
>> OH, OH, OH--
>> NO.
>> OH.
>> WELL, THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
I'VE GOT TO CHECK ALL THE WATER
HAZARDS ANYWAY.
>> OKAY.
SO ABOUT STOCKING THE LAKE.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU'VE GOT TO KEEP
YOUR HEAD DOWN.
HEAD DOWN.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE
THOSE GUYS ARE NOT IN FOR A GAME
OF GOLF, YOU KNOW?
GET OUT THERE, GET SOME FRESH
AIR.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE THEY'RE--
WHAT ARE THEY?
THEY DON'T LIKE TO HAVE FUN?
IS THAT IT?
>> WELL, NO, I--YOU KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE LIKE.
THEY JUST DON'T LIKE JOINING
THINGS, THAT'S ALL.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THEY JOINED THE LODGE, DIDN'T
THEY?
BESIDES, WITH GOLF, THERE'S NO
FISH GUTS TO CLEAN OUT.
>> WELL, THEY REALLY ENJOY THAT.
>> WELL, THEY DON'T--THEY DON'T
REALLY KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
MISSING.
>> NO, NO.
>> FORE!
>> OH, BOY.
OH, BOY.
>> HO--
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
>> [groans]
>> BOB, TAKE IT EASY NOW.
>> [grunts]
>> OH.
>> I CAN'T BE--
SO WHAT SO YOU SAY?
WE GET A LITTLE TOURNEY GOIN',
HUH, BETWEEN THE GUYS?
A LITTLE TOURNAMENT?
>> YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK SO,
BOB.
I--YOU KNOW, THEY DON'T HAVE ANY
GOLF SHOES.
YOU KNOW, I GUESS THEY COULD USE
FLIP FLOPS.
BUT THEY'D HAVE TO PAY THEIR
GREEN FEES AND THEN BALLS AND
TEES.
THAT'S GONNA SET THEM BACK A,
YOU KNOW, FAIR BIT OF CHANGE
THERE, YOU KNOW.
>> WELL, IT'S CHEAPER THAN
PAYING A PRIVATE COMPANY TO
RESTOCK THE LAKE WITH FISH.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, IF I PUT IT
TO THEM THAT WAY, I THINK THEY
MAY--THEY MAY SIGN UP FOR IT,
YOU KNOW.
>> OH, HO, THERE YOU GO.
>> HAVE A LITTLE--HAVE OWN
TOURNAMENT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> THE POSSUM OPEN, HUH?
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND THE GUYS COULD CATCH DEW
WORMS WHILE THEY'RE GOLFIN'.
>> WELL, THERE YOU GO.
>> YEAH.
>> SO WHAT DO WE SAY?
SATURDAY AT 6:30?
>> 6:30 IN THE MORNING?
>> WELL, SURE.
THE EARLY BIRD GETS THE WORM.
THE WORM GETS THE FISH.
>> WELL, ALL RIGHT.
6:30 IT IS.
>> OKAY.
>> SEE YOU THEN, BOB.
>> LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'LL BE FUN, RED.
>> [laughs]
YEP.
FORE!
[groans]
>> SO ANYWAY, TO MAKE A LONG
STORY FAIRLY LONG, THE BEAR THAT
WANDERED INTO THE LODGE
SPENT A COUPLE OF DAYS HERE
BEFORE STINKY PETERSON REALIZED
THAT IT WASN'T MOOSE THOMPSON.
IT WAS DURING A POKER GAME
'CAUSE THE BEAR WAS WINNIN'.
AND BESIDES, HE WAS GETTIN'
HONEY ALL OVER THE CARDS.
BUT STINKY'S STILL THINKIN' IT
WAS MOOSE, YOU KNOW, AND HE
ACCUSED HIM OF CHEATIN' BY,
LIKE, HIDIN' CARDS UP HIS
SLEEVE.
SO HE GETS UP, AND WHEN HE TRIES
TO RIP THE FUR COAT OFF OF
MOOSE, IT TURNED OUT THAT HE WAS
TRYIN' TO RIP THE HIDE OFF THE
BEAR, AND THAT'S WHEN WE FIGURED
OUT IT WAS A GRIZZLY.
AND THAT SORT OF EXPLAINED WHY
MOOSE HAD LICKED DOWN NINE JARS
OF PEANUT BUTTER FOR SUPPER.
I LOOKED UP FROM MY CARDS.
I SAYS, "HEY, WHAT'S WILD?"
AND THEY SAID, "THE BEAR."
HE HAD US GOING FOR
A WHILE THERE.
WE THOUGHT HE WAS GONNA HURT US
REAL BAD, BUT LUCKILY, HE GOT A
WHIFF OF OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S
BREATH AND HIGHTAILED IT OFF
INTO THE WOODS.
SO ANYHOW, IF MY WIFE IS
WATCHIN', I'LL BE COMIN'
STRAIGHT HOME TONIGHT, AND TRY
TO LEAVE THE GARAGE DOOR OPEN.
AND THAT WAY I'LL BE ABLE TO SEE
IF YOUR CAR'S ALREADY IN THERE
AND HOPEFULLY, AVOID IT THIS
TIME.
YOU KNOW, I ONLY DRIVE WITH MY
HEADLIGHTS OFF SO I WON'T WAKE
YOU.
ANYWAY, THANKS, EVERYBODY, FOR
TUNIN' IN.
UNTIL NEXT TIME ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD AND THE WHOLE
GANG UP AT THE LODGE, KEEP YOUR
STICK ON THE ICE.