BUT, YOU KNOW, PROGRESS
ISN'T ALWAYS A BAD THING.
FOR EXAMPLE, THEY HAVE THAT
E-MAIL, ON THE INTERNET NOW,
WHERE YOU CAN KEEP IN
TOUCH WITH LOVED ONES
WITHOUT HAVING TO
BLOW 50 CENTS ON A STAMP.
AND THE BEST THING I
LIKE ABOUT E-MAIL IS THAT
YOU HAVE A FILTER ON THERE SO
YOU CAN KEEP JUNK MAIL OUT.
SO I'M THINKING
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
TO HAVE THAT KIND OF A
FILTER ON YOUR NORMAL MAIL,
SOMETHING THAT WOULD ALLOW
THE GOVERNMENT CHEQUES
TO COME IN,
BUT WOULD FILTER
OUT THE FLYERS
TRYING TO SELL ME
A TIMESHARE IN AFGHANISTAN?
SO HERE'S WHAT I'VE
COME UP WITH...
TO HELP SORT
THE REGULAR MAIL
I'VE GOT A BELT SANDER
LYING ON ITS SIDE.
IT TAKES UP A
FAIR BIT OF ROOM,
WHICH MEANS ALL MY INCOMING
MAIL HAS TO STAY VERTICAL,
WHICH IS IMPORTANT,
BECAUSE BACK HERE
I'VE MADE A SECOND DOOR,
BUT IT'S ONLY AS
HIGH AS YOUR STANDARD
LETTER-SIZE ENVELOPE.
SEE, JUNK MAIL
TENDS TO BE LARGER.
I GUESS SO THEY CAN PUT
PICTURES OF BIG THINGS ON IT,
LIKE AMPHIBIOUS CARS
OR MOBILE HOMES
OR ED McMAHON'S HEAD.
SO NOW ALL I GOT TO DO
IS TURN ON MY BELT SANDER
TO RECEIVE MY MAIL.
INCOMING.
OKAY, AND NOW TO GET
RID OF MY JUNK MAIL,
ALL I GOT TO DO IS HIT THE
REVERSE SWITCH ON THE
BELT SANDER.
BE SURE TO RECYCLE.
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE THAT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
EVEN THE GUYS AT THE LODGE
ARE REAL EXCITED THIS WEEK.
YOU CAN TELL BECAUSE
WHEN YOU TALK TO THEM,
THEY DON'T FALL
ASLEEP AS FAST.
HAROLD HAS REALLY
DONE IT THIS TIME.
HE'S LOCKED UP A CONTRACT
WITH THE U.S. ARMED FORCES
TO USE POSSUM LODGE AS PART
OF THEIR TRAINING CENTRE.
APPARENTLY THEY
LIKE COMING TO PLACES
THAT ARE ALREADY
ENVIRONMENTAL DISASTERS.
UNCLE RED!
[cheers and applause]
THEY'LL LIKE
ANYTHING, HAROLD.
I GOT YOUR GIFT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HAROLD, IT WAS THE
LEAST I COULD DO.
I KNOW.
WHAT IS IT?
WELL IT'S A
FISHING LURE.
IT'S FOR CATCHING BASS.
IT'S CALLED A BASS-ACKWARDS.
IT'S GOT A LEAD SINKER
RIGHT INSIDE THERE.
YOU CAN CATCH ANYTHING
NEAR THE BOTTOM WITH IT.
WOW!
THAT'S -- THAT'S... OKAY.
NO PROBLEM.
THANK YOU.
SO WHEN ARE YOU
EXPECTING THE TROOPS TO
COME ROLLING IN, HAROLD?
WHEN DO WE SEE THE TANKS
AND THE ANTI-AIRCRAFT GUNS
COME THUNDERING DOWN THE --
[laughing]
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE
ARMY CAMP FROM THE STATES.
THE THING YOU BOOKED.
I DIDN'T BOOK ANY ARMY
CAMP FROM THE STATES.
I BOOKED THE BOY SCOUTS
FROM ST. CATHARINES.
BOY SCOUTS?
YOU MEAN WE'RE NOT
GETTING COLIN POWELL'S MEN?
NO. WE'RE GETTING
BADEN-POWELL'S BOYS.
WHY WOULD BOY SCOUTS WANT
TO COME TO POSSUM LODGE?
WELL, THEY VOLUNTEERED TO
HELP CLEAN UP AROUND HERE.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
THEY'VE ALSO VOLUNTEERED
TO HELP TEACH YOU GUYS TO
SURVIVE IN THE OUTDOORS,
'CAUSE WHAT YOU DON'T
KNOW CAN HURT YOU.
WHAT I DO KNOW
CAN HURT YOU, HAROLD.
ALL RIGHT,
LOOK HERE. LOOK HERE.
THESE ARE SIGNAL
FLAGS, RIGHT?
SO...
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
THE HOCKEY GAME'S ON.
IT'S EIGHT O'CLOCK.
SEE, YOU GOT THINGS TO
LEARN, EVEN AT YOUR AGE.
BUT ANYWAY, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH FOR THE LURE.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
VERY KIND OF YOU.
AH! OW! OH!
I TOLD YOU IT'D CATCH
ANYTHING NEAR THE
BOTTOM, HAROLD.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
TONIGHT'S WINNER RECEIVES
THIS COUPON FOR A MILLION...
COUPONS.
BUT IF YOU HAVE A FIREPLACE,
ALL THE COUPONS ARE FLAMMABLE.
AND ALL THE COUPONS
ARE STAPLE FREE,
SO THEY MAKE AN EXCELLENT
BATHROOM ACCESSORY.
OKAY, COVER YOUR EARS, MIKE.
RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS TO
GET MIKE TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, OKAY, WINSTON.
AND... GO!
ALL RIGHT, MIKE, THIS IS KIND
OF AN OLD-FASHIONED WORD.
PEOPLE DON'T SAY
IT ANYMORE.
PLEASE.
OKAY. OKAY.
WHAT DO YOU CALL
A REALLY BIG PIANO?
HARD TO STEAL.
NO. OKAY.
SOMETHING THAT'S IMPRESSIVE,
IMPOSING AND SUBSTANTIAL
IS SAID TO BE...
PAMELA ANDERSON.
OKAY, THINK OF YOUR
OWN FAMILY, OKAY?
IN RELATION TO YOU,
YOUR FATHER'S FATHER IS...
ANYBODY'S GUESS.
OKAY, RED, YOU'RE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME HERE.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
OKAY, MIKE, THIS IS
ANOTHER WORD FOR $1,000.
A BRIBE.
BUT THIS IS
NOT A BRIBE.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT I SAID,
BUT THE GRAND JURY WOULDN'T
GO ALONG WITH IT.
THERE YOU GO!
[applause]
[quirky upbeat music]
announcer:
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
COMBINE THE RAW POWER
OF A 23-YEAR-OLD
RUSTED OUT DIESEL ENGINE
WITH A 3,500-GALLON
SEWAGE TANK?
[gagging]
VROOM, VROOM.
VROOM, VROOM, VROOM
VROOM, VROOM,
VROOM, VROOM VROOM
VROOM, VROOM
[quirky upbeat music]
MY WIFE BERNICE BOUGHT
SOME NEW FURNITURE,
BUT INSTEAD OF GETTING
A FULL-SIZE COUCH,
SHE GOT THIS LOVE SEAT.
I'M NOT HAPPY.
OH, SURE,
LOVE SEATS ARE FINE
FOR LADIES SITTING
THERE WATCHING OPRAH.
BUT A MAN ON A LOVE SEAT
IS KIND OF LIKE
RIDING SIDE SADDLE.
I NEED MY SPACE.
I NEED ROOM TO STRETCH OUT.
SO I NEED TO FIND A WAY TO
HAVE A LOVE SEAT FOR BERNICE
THAT WILL ALSO DOUBLE AS A
FULL-SIZE COUCH FOR ME.
AND THAT'S
TODAY'S PROJECT,
RIGHT HERE ON
HANDYMAN CORNER.
HERE'S A SMALL GLIMPSE INTO
THE WORLD OF INSPIRATION
AND HOW IT CAN ENTER YOUR
LIFE IF YOU'RE ONE
OF THE GIFTED.
SEE HOW THIS WORKS?
THIS IS AN
EXTENSION LADDER.
SO I'M THINKING, WITH THIS
SECOND UNIT RIGHT HERE,
WE CAN MAKE AN
EXTENSION LOVE SEAT.
OKAY, NOW, THE EXTENSION
LOVE SEAT WORKS
ON EXACTLY THE SAME PRINCIPLE
AS THE EXTENSION LADDER,
EXCEPT WITH
A LOT LESS ALUMINUM.
BOTTOM LINE: ONE PART'S
GOTTA FIT INSIDE THE OTHER.
SO WHAT I'M GOING
TO DO IS LOP OFF
THE RIGHT SIDE OF
BERNICE'S LOVE SEAT HERE.
WELL, ACTUALLY IT'S MY LEFT;
IT'S YOUR RIGHT.
IT'S STAGE LEFT --
CAMERA ---
OKAY, THIS END RIGHT HERE.
OKAY, NOW, TO MAKE
THIS WORK RIGHT,
YOU GOTTA HAUL
MOST OF THE STUFFING
OUT OF THE BACK AND THE
SEAT OF THE MAIN UNIT.
OKAY.
REALLY STARTING
TO TAKE SHAPE, ISN'T SHE?
NOW MY SMALLER LOVE SEAT CAN
SLIDE INTO AND OUT OF
THE EXISTING UNIT.
THE BIG QUESTION IS,
HOW DO WE GET IT TO SLIDE?
AND THE BIG ANSWER
RIGHT OVER HERE.
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN GET THESE
CARTS AT ANY GROCERY STORE.
THEY ONLY
COST A QUARTER.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THEY CAN
AFFORD TO STAY IN BUSINESS.
OKAY, I GOT THE
GROCERY CART WHEELS
MOUNTED ON THE BOTTOM OF
MY SECOND LOVE SEAT,
AND I ROLLED
HER INTO PLACE.
I TELL YOU, BERNICE IS GOING
TO FLIP OUT WHEN SHE
SEES THIS BABY.
YOU SEE, NOW IT'S
A LOVE SEAT,
WHERE SHE CAN SIT AND
DO HER NEEDLEPOINT
AND TELL ME WHAT
A GREAT GUY HER DAD IS.
BUT WHEN IT'S MY TURN,
I GET TO PUT MY FEET UP
AND STRETCH OUT.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
A MAN'S GOT TO DO
WHAT A MAN'S GOT TO DO.
[applause]
[quirky upbeat music]
YOU PROBABLY HEARD THEM SAY
THAT TO ERR IS HUMAN,
BUT TO REALLY MESS UP
YOU NEED A COMPUTER.
I'M ACTUALLY OLD ENOUGH TO
REMEMBER THE YEARS B.C...
BEFORE COMPUTERS.
BACK THEN THE ONLY USE FOR
SILICON WE KNEW ABOUT
WAS FROM LOOKING AT
PICTURES OF PIN-UP GIRLS,
WHICH WAS ALSO
OUR INTRODUCTION TO THE
CONCEPT OF VIRTUAL REALITY.
LIFE WAS A LOT SIMPLER
WHEN "BOOT UP" AND "LOG ON"
WAS SOMETHING YOU DID WHEN
YOU WANTED TO WARM YOUR
FEET BY THE FIRE.
SEE, COMPUTERS WERE
IN THEIR INFANCY THEN,
AND, LIKE ALL INFANTS, THEY
EVENTUALLY GROW UP TO
BE TEENAGERS
AND THEN TAKE
OVER YOUR LIFE.
AND IN THE
LAST FEW DECADES,
COMPUTERS HAVE
SLOWLY BUT SURELY
TAKEN OVER EVERY
ASPECT OF OUR EXISTENCE.
AND THERE HAVE BEEN
A BUNCH OF US
WHO HAVE FOUGHT IT
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY
FROM PUNCH CARDS TO P.C.s.
WELL, I SALUTE THE EFFORT,
BUT I'M HERE TO TELL YOU
THE BATTLE IS OVER
AND WE LOST, BABY.
WE LOST BIG TIME.
THE PALM PILOTS
HAVE LANDED.
LAY DOWN YOUR ARMS AND GET
CARPEL-TUNNEL SYNDROME
LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE.
THE ENEMY IS
AT THE GATES.
HECK, THE ENEMY MAY
EVEN BE NAMED GATES.
REMEMBER, I PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
IF YOU'VE GOT A SEPTIC
THAT SPUTTERS AND SPRAYS;
IF IT SMELLS LIKE CATTLE
THAT'VE BEEN ROUND TO GRAZE;
ROTHSCHILD'S WILL FIND YOUR
HOUSE THROUGH THE HAZE.
WE COME IN A TRUCK
AND LEAVE IN A DAZE.
WELL, THE BOY SCOUTS
ARE ALL HERE.
ABOUT 100 OF THEM WANDERING
AROUND THE LODGE,
TELLING US EVERYTHING
WE'RE DOING WRONG.
IT'S A DREAM COME TRUE.
[whistles and applause]
YOU ALL SET?
YEAH,
I THINK SO.
OKAY!
C'MON IN, BOBBY.
THIS IS YOUR
TABLE RIGHT HERE.
OKAY, IF THE CONTESTANTS
ARE ALL SET AND READY
TO PLAY --
GET ON WITH IT,
HAROLD.
OKAY. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
MEMORY IS A VERY IMPORTANT
SURVIVAL TOOL, ALL RIGHT?
SO OUR FIRST EVENT WILL BE
A MEMORY CHALLENGE.
ALL RIGHT,
UNCLE RED, BOBBY,
YOU HAVE TEN SECONDS TO
MEMORIZE EVERYTHING
ON THIS BOARD.
TIME'S UP.
OKAY. UNCLE
RED, YOU GO FIRST.
ALL RIGHT, UH,
I BELIEVE THERE WAS A
PICTURE OF A YOUNG LADY.
AND, UH...
A BIKINI.
AND THEN THERE WAS...
A PINK BIKINI,
I THINK IT WAS.
VERY GOOD.
VERY IMPRESSIVE.
BOBBY.
A COMPASS,
A FISHING LURE,
A PAIR OF SCISSORS, A KNIFE,
A COMB, A WHISTLE
AND A GIRL
IN A BATHING SUIT,
AND I THINK HER NAME
WAS JENNIFER ENGLAND.
YES!
OH, VERY GOOD!
YES. THE SCORE NOW IS
FIVE POINTS FOR BOBBY,
ONE FOR UNCLE RED.
NO, NO, NO,
I SHOULD GET TWO,
BECAUSE I GOT THE MODEL
AND THE BIKINI.
ALL RIGHT.
ONE.
ALL RIGHT, OUR NEXT EVENT,
WHAT I WOULD LIKE YOU TO DO,
YOU'VE GOT TWO PIECES OF
ROPE ON YOUR TABLE.
PLEASE TIE THEM
INTO A REEF KNOT.
AND GO.
[HAROLD hums
theme to
jeopardy]
OH, EXCELLENT!
YES. VERY GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
BOBBY HAS A REEF KNOT
AND SIX POINTS.
UNCLE RED?
[laughter and applause]
UNCLE RED HAS ONE POINT
AND A BALL OF TWINE.
ALL RIGHT, OUR NEXT
EVENT WILL BE,
I WANT YOU
TO START A FIRE,
BUT ONLY USING THE WOOD
THAT IS ON YOUR TABLE.
AND BEGIN!
[applause begins]
NO. NO. NO. NO. NO!
JUST WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS IS RED GREEN.
YEAH. YEAH.
WELL, HAROLD, THIS IS
NOT IMPORTANT ANYWAY.
IF YOU WANT
A REAL COMPETITION,
LET'S HAVE IT OUT IN THE
BUSH WHERE IT COUNTS, OKAY?
THE MEN OF
POSSUM LODGE
CHALLENGE YOU BOYS SCOUTS
TO A RACE, OKAY,
FROM THE LODGE UP TO
ROCK REEF POINT AND BACK.
NO BOATS,
NO VEHICLES,
NO SHOOTING GUYS
OUT OF CANNONS.
JUST, YOU KNOW, COMPASSES
AND A POCKET KNIFE.
THAT'S IT!
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S FINE.
THEN WE ACCEPT
YOUR CHALLENGE.
BOBBY, GO TELL
THE OTHERS.
WE'RE GOING TO BEAT
YOU SO BAD.
WHICH WAS IS
ROCK REEF POINT?
JUST FOLLOW US,
HAROLD.
Red:
WALTER AND I NEEDED
TO SPLIT UP SOME WOOD.
THE WEATHER WAS GETTING
A LITTLE COLDER, SO --
WE JUST HAD THE ONE AXE,
SO WE'D KIND OF TAKE
TURNS ON THERE.
SO I SAID,
I'LL GO FIRST.
THIS IS HOW YOU DO IT.
YOU JUST COME DOWN,
THERE'S YOUR SPLIT.
AND NOW WALTER'S TURN.
WALTER, HE'S A MUSCULAR
YOUNG FELLOW.
BUT HE DIDN'T NOTICE THIS
ONE HAD A FEW EXTRA
KNOTS IN THERE.
SO WHEN IT WENT IN, BOY,
SHE STUCK RIGHT IN THERE.
AND COULDN'T GET IT OUT,
AND NOW WHAT DO YOU DO?
AND HE'S TRYING
TO HORSE HER OUT
AND I'M THINKING, THERE'S
TWO WAYS TO GO WITH AN AXE...
IF IT WON'T COME OUT, YOU GOT
TO DRIVE IT FARTHER IN.
SO I GET THE SLEDGE HAMMER.
NOW, HOLD HER LOOSE, WALTER,
DON'T HOLD IT TIGHT.
THAT'S GOTTA --
THERE'S A LOT OF --
THOSE ARE NOT GOOD
VIBRATIONS.
SO I THOUGHT IF YOU CAN'T
GET THE AXE OFF THE LOG,
WHY DON'T YOU PULL
THE LOG OFF THE AXE.
SO I DUCT TAPED THE AXE
HANDLE TO THE TREE,
AND I WRAPPED THE
CHAIN AROUND THE LOG.
SO THE IDEA, JUST PUT THAT
AROUND THE HITCH THERE,
AND I COULD JUST
PULL HER  OFF --
PULL THE LOG RIGHT
OFF THE AXE.
UNFORTUNATELY, I PROBABLY
SHOULD HAVE TIED THE
KNOT ON THE HITCH,
AND WALTER NOTICED THAT THE
CHAIN WAS ACTUALLY
STARTING TO SLIP
NOW ON THE BALL.
AND HE RAN OUT
TO KIND OF FIX THAT
SO IT WOULDN'T JUST COME
IGHT OFF AND GO LOOSE.
AND HE GOT HER SNUGGED UP
JUST IN TIME AND
AND WHAT HAPPENED THERE --
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT --
THE DUCT TAPE LET GO.
AND COMING RIGHT
AT ME -- OH!
AND BY GOLLY, HE'S AWAY.
SO I TURN AROUND AND
I SPOT HIM, BUT TOO LATE.
HE DID A KIND OF
CRACK THE WHIP THING,
AND HE WENT
RIGHT UP A TREE.
SO I FIGURE I'D PULL HIM
DOWN WITH THE CHAIN,
BUT JUST THE CHAIN
CAME DOWN.
OH, THERE HE IS.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
AND NOW, OF COURSE,
THE AXE IS STARTING TO
COME OUT OF THE LOG
AND... OH, BOY.
THAT'S GOTTA HURT.
AND HERE COMES THE LOG,
AND WE GOT HER SPLIT!
[applause]
[quirky upbeat music]
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM
THESE DAYS
SAYS THAT SIZE
DOESN'T MATTER.
WELL, IF THERE'S TWO
WORDS I DON'T RELATE TO,
IT'S CONVENTIONAL
AND WISDOM.
SO FOR GUYS LIKE ME,
SIZE DOES MATTER,
IN CARS, HOUSES,
TELEVISIONS
AND YES, EVEN WAFFLES.
... FIVE, SIX, SEVEN,
EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
OKAY.
ALL WE NEED TO ADD
NOW IS THE MAPLE SYRUP.
FOR OUR CLIMATE,
I RECOMMEND...
10-W-30.
IT'S TIME FOR THE EXPERTS
PORTION OF THE SHOW,
WHERE WE EXPLORE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
THAT'S RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
TODAY'S LETTER READS
AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"I AM REALLY BUGGED
BY MY NEIGHBOURS.
"THEY MAKE NOISE
NIGHT AND DAY,
"AND THEY'RE ALWAYS
HAVING LOUD ARGUMENTS.
"THEY DON'T CLEAN THEIR YARD
OR EVEN CUT THE GRASS
"AND NOW THEY'RE SELLING CAR
PARTS ON THE FRONT LAWN.
"WHAT CAN I DO?"
WELL, I THINK WE'VE GOT TO
ASK OURSELVES TWO QUESTIONS.
FIRST OF ALL, WHAT EXACTLY
ARE THE CAR PARTS?
AND WHAT DOES THE GUY
WANT FOR THEM?
HE DOESN'T SAY.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU CAN DO ABOUT
THE NOISE,
AND AS FOR THE ARGUMENTS,
YOU KNOW, I SAY
LET THEM BE.
SURE, ARGUMENTS
CAN BE THERAPEUTIC.
ARGUING IS ABOUT THE ONLY
COMMUNICATION I HAVE
WITH ANN MARIE.
YOU KNOW, EXCEPT FOR
THE APOLOGIZING
AND THEN THE BEGGING
AND THE TALKING TO
MYSELF IN THE GARAGE.
YOU KNOW, I THINK OUR
LETTER WRITER NEEDS TO
TAKE A MATURE APPROACH
AND JUST SIMPLY CALL THE
NEIGHBOUR AND ASK HIM NICELY
IF HE WOULD MIND BEING A
LITTLE MORE THOUGHTFUL.
WELL, I DON'T AGREE WITH YOU
GUYS AT ALL ON THIS ONE.
I THINK A MAN FIGHTS
FIRE WITH FIRE ON THAT.
I MEAN, IF HE'S LETTING HIS
LAWN GO FOR THREE WEEKS,
YOU LET YOURS GO
FOR SIX WEEKS.
IF HE'S GOT
CHAIN SAWS RUNNING,
YOU RENT A PILE DRIVER.
IF HE'S PARKING
ON HIS LAWN,
GET YOURSELF A SCHOOL BUS
WITH THE KIDS STILL IN IT.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
THAT, RED.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES
YOU CAN BE A LITTLE
CONFRONTATIONAL.
EVERYONE GETS
THEIR BACK UP.
I'M IN THE SEWAGE BUSINESS,
AND I KNOW WHAT A BACKUP IS.
IT'S LIKE A SEPTIC TANK.
YOU WANT TO RELIEVE
THE PRESSURE,
NOT INCREASE THE PRESSURE,
'CAUSE ONE DAY SHE'LL BLOW,
AND THEN EVERYBODY'S GOT
EGG ON THEIR FACE.
YOU KNOW, IT DEPENDS
WHO YOU TALK TO.
SOME PEOPLE ARE REASONABLE
AND OPEN TO CHANGE.
I'VE NEVER MET HIM.
SOUNDS LIKE THIS
GUY'S NEIGHBOUR
COULD BE PRETTY
SET IN HIS WAYS.
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT I WOULD DO.
I WOULD GET SOME OF
THOSE GREEN GARBAGE BAGS,
AND I WOULD PUT ALL
OF MY JUNK INTO THEM,
ALL MY GARBAGE
AND EVERYTHING.
AND I'D GO UP ON THE
ROOF OF MY PLACE
AND JUST PITCH 'EM RIGHT
THROUGH THE WINDOWS OF
THAT GUY'S PLACE.
THAT'D WAKE HIM UP.
RED, THE GUY'D PROBABLY
GO TO JAIL FOR THAT.
AND HE AIN'T GONNA LIKE
HIS NEIGHBOURS THERE.
WELL, YOU KNOW, WINSTON,
MAYBE SO IN THE CITY,
BUT IN THE COUNTRY YOU'D
PROBABLY GET AWAY WITH IT.
WHERE DOES THE
GUY LIVE, ANYWAY?
OH, THERE'S
NO RETURN ADDRESS.
LOCAL POSTMARK,
THOUGH.
[laughter and applause]
[applause]
OH, YES! OH, YES!
I GUESS YOU CAN TELL WHO WON
THE RACE TO ROCK REEF POINT.
I'M GOOD, HAROLD.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
YOU BROUGHT THIS ON
YOURSELF, UNCLE RED.
HEY, I GOT LUCKY.
THEY KEPT WITH OTHER GUYS
THERE FOR OBSERVATION.
I'LL TELL YOU
SOMETHING, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW, TECHNICALLY,
WE WON THE RACE.
WE WERE BACK TO THE LODGE
BEFORE YOU GUYS WERE.
YOU WERE IN AN
AMBULANCE.
YOU GUYS ARE JUST TOO
OLD AND OUT OF SHAPE
TO BE CLIMBING
ROCK REEF POINT.
ROCK REEF POINT
WASN'T A PROBLEM.
IT WAS MERCURY CREEK.
OUR MAN-MADE BRIDGE
COLLAPSED.
WE HAD TOO
LITTLE SUPPORT
AND TOO MUCH
MOOSE THOMPSON.
WELL, I HOPED YOU
LEARNED SOMETHING.
I DID. I DID.
I LEARNED THAT DUCT TAPE
DOESN'T STICK TO BARK.
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, OKAY, HAR --
HOW CAN ME HAVE A MEETING
IF ALL THE GUYS ARE
IN THE HOSPITAL?
I INVITED
THE BOY SCOUTS.
OH, GREAT.
YEAH, OKAY.
I'LL BE DOWN
EVENTUALLY.
OKAY, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND HAROLD'S RIGHT.
I DID ACTUALLY LEARN A
COUPLE OF THINGS TODAY.
NUMBER ONE, YOU CAN'T TEACH
AN OLD DOG NEW TRICKS,
AND NUMBER TWO, YOU REALLY
CAN'T TELL THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN HARDWOOD
AND SOFTWOOD TREES
WHEN YOU LAND ON THEM AT
ABOUT 100 MILES AN HOUR.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheers and applause]
HERE HE COMES.
DON'T LAUGH.
HE WORKED HARD.
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
[ STIFLING A LAUGH ]
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT... MEN,
BOW YOUR HEADS FOR
THE... SCOUTS' PRAYER.
I'M A SCOUT,
BUT I CAN LIGHTEN UP,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.