Red: YOU KNOW, WE GET REAL
COLD WINTERS UP AT THE LODGE,
AND THE CHALLENGE IS TRYING TO
KEEP THE PLACE WARM ENOUGH TO
SUPPORT HUMAN LIFE.
BUT I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
INSTEAD OF CRANKING UP THE
THERMOSTAT OR CLEAR-CUTTING A
FOREST JUST SO YOU CAN KEEP
COZY, THE TRUTH IS, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO HEAT THE WHOLE BUILDING.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE TO HEAT THE
WHOLE ROOM.
ALL YOU HAVE TO HEAT IS YOUR OWN
BODY.
THAT'S WHAT THE ASTRONAUTS DO.
SO LET'S BE LIKE ASTRONAUTS.
GET YOURSELF ONE OF THESE BIG
GARMENT BAGS.
I DON'T NEED THIS.
I DON'T HAVE CLOTHES THAT I
DON'T WEAR.
AND THEN ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS
CUT YOURSELF A COUPLE ARMHOLES
AND LEGHOLES.
OKAY, WE'RE ALL SYSTEMS GO.
NOW I JUST PLUG IN MY HAIR
DRYER, WHICH IS SET ON HIGH, AND
I'LL BE LAUGHING.
DON'T YOU WISH YOU WERE?
[hair dryer whirring]
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
NO, NO.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
WELL, IT'S A BIG WEEK AT THE
LODGE THIS WEEK.
HAROLD'S PUTTING ON A FISHING
DERBY.
YEAH, HE'S PUTTING A PRIZE FISH
INTO POSSUM LAKE THERE, AND
WHOEVER CATCHES IT GETS 1,000
BUCKS.
I MEAN, THIS WILL BE THE BIGGEST
INFLUX OF CASH AT THE LODGE
SINCE WE TOOK BACK OUR EMPTIES.
[laughter]
Harold: UNCLE RED...
CAN YOU HELP ME OUT?
I GOT TO TAG THE PRIZE FISH.
Red: WOW.
WHAT IS IT, ANYWAY?
Harold: HEAVY.
Red: OH, YEAH.
Harold: CAN YOU JUST TAG IT
FOR ME SO I CAN RELEASE IT INTO
POSSUM LAKE?
Red: HAROLD, WHAT KIND OF
JELLY ARMS DO YOU HAVE?
CAN'T YOU JUST HOLD THE ONE HAND
AND TAG IT WITH THE OTHER?
Harold: WELL, YEA-- OH, NO.
NO, I CAN'T.
ALEX, ALEX!
ALEX!
Red: OKAY, WHAT DO YOU WANT
ME TO DO, HAROLD?
Harold: I JUST WANT YOU TO
REACH INTO MY POCKET AND GET THE
TAG AND THE CRIMPING TOOL.
Red: THIS POCKET HERE?
Harold: YES, I THINK SO.
Red: OKAY.
I THINK I GOT -- IS THAT THE
TAG?
Harold: NO, THAT'S MY CARAMEL
CHEWY CANDY.
Red: OH, YEAH.
Harold: I LIKE THOSE.
Red: THOSE ARE GOOD.
Harold: THEY ARE GOOD.
THEY ARE, YEAH.
Red: YOU EAT A FAIR NUMBER OF
THEM, DON'T YOU?
Harold: MAYBE UP TOP.
GOT IT?
Red: I GOT THE TAG, BUT THEN
THERE'S NO CRIMPING TOOL.
Harold: OH, IT'S IN MY PANTS
POCKET.
Red: OH, HAROLD, HAROLD,
HAROLD, WE'RE GONNA DO IT BY
HAND.
JUST BRING THE FISH OVER HERE,
OKAY?
Harold: OKAY.
Red: WILL YOU HOLD IT STILL?
Harold: I'M TRYING, BUT HE
KNOWS YOU'RE COMING!
Red: ALMOST GOT IT.
I ALMOST GOT IT.
Harold: WATCH MY FINGER.
OW! OH, OH, OH!
Red: OH!
Harold: [yelping]
Winston: IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
TODAY'S WINNER RECEIVES A COUPON
FOR A FREE VEGETABLE WAXING FROM
INGA'S HOUSE OF RUBBING.
COME ON IN AND HAVE INGA POLISH
YOUR TURNIP.
WINNERS MUST BE 18 YEARS OF AGE
OR OLDER.
OKAY.
DALTON, COVER UP YOUR EARS.
RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS TO GET
DALTON HUMPHREY TO SAY THIS
WORD.
HEAVEN.
Red: ALL RIGHT, WINSTON.
Winston: AND GO!
Red: OKAY, DALTON, WHEN
YOU'RE REALLY GOOD, YOU GET TO
GO HERE.
Dalton: THE BEDROOM.
Red: OKAY.
WHERE DO THE SAINTS GO?
Dalton: MARCHING IN?
Red: NO, OKAY.
THIS STARTS WITH "H," OKAY?
IT WAS A MOVIE...
SOMETHING "CAN WAIT."
Dalton: HUSBANDS.
Red: NO. OKAY, DALTON.
WHERE DO YOU WANT TO GO WHEN YOU
DIE?
Dalton: FLORIDA.
Winston: OKAY, RED, YOU'RE
ALMOST OUT OF TIME HERE.
Red: DALTON, THIS IS A PLACE
WHERE PEOPLE GET TO SPEND
ETERNITY.
Dalton: THE SENATE.
Red: NO, NO, NO.
WHERE DOES GOD LIVE?
Dalton: WELL, NOT IN MY
NEIGHBORHOOD.
THE WHOLE AREA STINKS TO HIGH
HEAVEN.
Red: THERE WE GO!
Winston: YOU DID IT!
Red: YOU KNOW, IN THE LAST
FEW YEARS, A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE
GIVEN UP ON SAVING THE WORLD OR
TRYING TO BE A SUCCESSFUL
BUSINESSPERSON OR A GOOD PARENT
AND ARE CONCENTRATING INSTEAD ON
TRYING TO MAKE A HALF-DECENT CUP
OF COFFEE.
THEY START WITH A BLEND OF
COFFEE BEANS FROM THE SOUTH
AMERICAN MOUNTAINS THAT HAVE
PICKED UP A LITTLE EXTRA FLAVOR
FROM THE SWEAT OF THE DONKEYS'
BACK.
AND THEN THEY GRIND THEM ALL UP
IN ONE OF THESE FANCY
NOISEMAKERS.
[whirring loudly]
WHAT THE HECK?
OH.
WONDERED WHERE THAT WRENCH GOT
TO.
THEN THEY TAKE THE GROUND-UP
COFFEE BEANS, PUT THEM INTO THIS
SPECIAL POT -- THAT'S WATER IN
THERE.
YOU BOIL THAT ALL UP.
THEN THEY TAKE ONE OF THESE
PLUNGER UNITS.
GOES DOWN INSIDE THERE.
AND YOU SQUEEZE ALL THE FLAVOR
OUT OF THE COFFEE.
ODD TO SEE A PLUNGER ON THE
INPUT SIDE OF THE EQUATION,
ISN'T IT?
[chuckles]
AND THEN THEY HAVE THEIR CUP OF
COFFEE.
BUT MAYBE YOU CAN'T AFFORD ALL
THESE SPECIAL APPLIANCES.
MAYBE YOU'VE ALREADY SPENT YOUR
DISPOSABLE INCOME ON COLLEGE
TUITION OR BAIL.
YOU NEED A CHEAPER WAY TO MAKE
COFFEE.
ALL YOU NEED IS A LAWN MOWER
WITH A GRASS CATCHER ON IT.
THEN WHAT YOU DO IS YOU TAKE
YOUR COFFEE BEANS, YOU MAKE A
PILE OF THEM ON SOME SMOOTH,
HARD SURFACE LIKED PAVED
DRIVEWAY OR A SIDEWALK OR THE
ROOF OF YOUR CAR.
THEN YOU SET THE BLADE AS LOW AS
SHE'LL GO.
GIVE THE BEANS A QUICK BUZZ.
I'M SURE THEY'LL RETURN THE
FAVOR LATER.
OKAY, NOW, WE TAKE OUR COFFEE
GROUNDS AND POUR THEM INTO OUR
COFFEEPOT.
AND THEN COMES THE BEST PART --
PLUNGING.
THAT'S BECAUSE WE DON'T HAVE TO
DO IT BY HAND.
SEE?
THE PISTON AND CYLINDER OF AN
INTERNAL COMBUSTION ENGINE USE
EXACTLY THE SAME MECHANICAL
PRINCIPLES AS A COFFEE PLUNGER.
WAIT A SECOND, WAIT A SECOND.
LET ME PUT MY COFFEE MUG UNDER
THE EXHAUST PIPE FIRST.
THE COFFEE WILL GO THROUGH THIS
THING PRETTY FAST.
WE'VE ALL BEEN THERE, HAVEN'T
WE?
ALL RIGHT, NOW YOU JUST POUR THE
COFFEE INTO THE CARBURETOR.
POUR IT SLOW.
IF YOU STALL THIS THING, IT'S A
PIG TO GET HER GOING AGAIN.
ANOTHER BONUS WITH THIS IS YOU
CAN SAY TO YOUR GUESTS, "WHO
WANTS MORE [mower] COFFEE?"
GET IT?
MOWER.
YEAH.
AND HERE'S ANOTHER BONUS...
WITH THE CARBON MONOXIDE MIXED
IN THERE, THIS COFFEE WON'T KEEP
YOU AWAKE.
REMEMBER, IF WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
YOU KNOW, AS I GET OLDER, I FIND
THAT A LOT OF THINGS IN LIFE
KIND OF FOLLOW A SIMILAR
PATTERN.
FOR EXAMPLE, MY WIFE AND I JUST
COME UP TO OUR 35th ANNIVERSARY,
AND IT SEEMS TO ME THAT MARRIAGE
IS LIKE A LONG GAME OF POKER.
SOME DAYS YOU HAVE THE CARDS,
AND SOME DAYS YOU DON'T.
SO YOU GOT TO LEARN HOW TO BE A
GOOD LOSER, OCCASIONALLY HOW TO
BE A GRACIOUS WINNER.
MAINLY YOU GOT TO KNOW HOW TO
BLUFF.
YOU GOT TO KNOW WHEN TO PRESS
YOUR LUCK AND WHEN TO HEAD FOR
THE HILLS.
IT'S LIKE THAT KENNY ROGERS
SONG...
ALTHOUGH AFTER FIVE OR SIX
MARRIAGES, HE'S OBVIOUSLY BETTER
AT FOLDING THEM THAN HE IS AT
HOLDING THEM.
[laughter]
BUT THE MAIN OBJECTIVE IS TO
KEEP PUTTING YOUR ANTE IN THERE
EVERY HAND, EVERY DAY.
IT'S JUST A GAME AFTER ALL, AND
IT WILL GET BETTER.
A FULL HOUSE USUALLY STARTS OUT
AS JUST A PAIR, RIGHT?
SO YOU JUST HANG IN THERE.
PLAY THE HAND YOU'RE DEALT.
YOU KNOW THAT SHE'S ULTIMATELY
GONNA WIN THE POT, BUT IF YOU
PLAY YOUR CARDS RIGHT, SHE MAY
BUY YOU SOMETHING FRILLY.
[laughter]
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[cheers and applause]
WELL, WE'VE BEEN OUT THERE
FISHING FOR FOUR HOURS, AND
NOBODY'S CAUGHT THE PRIZE FISH.
IN FACT, NOBODY'S CAUGHT ANY
FISH.
I THINK THE ONLY THING LIVING IN
POSSUM LAKE IS OUR BAIT, AND I
DON'T LIKE ITS CHANCES, TO BE
HONEST WITH YOU.
Harold: UNCLE RED, DID YOU
WANT TO TALK TO ME?
Red: YEAH, HAROLD.
I WAS LOOKING AT THE RULES HERE,
AND I HAD A COUPLE OF QUESTIONS
FOR YOU.
Harold: DID YOU PAY THE $10
ENTRANCE FEE?
Red: OH, HAROLD, I JUST SAID
I HAD QUESTIONS.
YOU DON'T RESPOND WITH ANOTHER
QUESTION.
THAT'S VERY, VERY, VERY
DISRESPECTFUL.
Harold: I'M SORRY.
SORRY.
SO, DID YOU PAY THE $10 ENTRANCE
FEE?
Red: I'M GOOD FOR IT, HAROLD,
OKAY?
WHEN I CATCH THE $1,000 FISH,
JUST GIVE ME $990 OF IT.
OKAY, NOW, IN THE RULES HERE, IT
DOESN'T LIMIT THE FISHERMEN TO
USE ANY KIND OF SPECIAL BAIT OR
FISHING ROD OR ANYTHING.
Harold: NO, NO, NO.
WE'VE LEFT THAT UP TO THE
INDIVIDUAL FISHERMAN...
AS LONG AS HE'S PAID THE $10
ENTRANCE FEE.
Red: SO I CAN CATCH THIS FISH
ANY WAY I WANT.
Harold: NO, NO, NOT YOU...
UNLESS YOU PAY THE $10 ENTRANCE
FEE.
Red: ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
BUT IF YOU TAKE MY 10 BUCKS,
THEN ANY WAY I WANT TO CATCH
THIS FISH IS FAIR GAME.
IS THAT RIGHT?
IS THAT IT?
Harold: YEAH, OKAY, FINE.
Red: GREAT. GREAT, GREAT.
NOW, HAROLD, REMEMBER YOU HAD
THAT BADMINTON TOURNAMENT AND
YOU HAD ALL THOSE GEEKY KIDS
FROM THE COMPUTER SCHOOL?
Harold: WAS THAT NOT GREAT?
WAS THAT NOT GREAT, HUH?
25 GAMES OF BADMINTON GOING ON
ALL AT THE SAME TIME.
YOU WANT TO TALK EXCITING?
Red: OH, YEAH. OH, YEAH.
Harold: THAT WAS BADMINTON
THERE.
Red: OH, YEAH.
YEAH, EVERYBODY HAD A BIRD.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
BUT...
I'M JUST WONDERING, WHAT DID
YOU DO WITH THE BADMINTON
EQUIPMENT WHEN YOU WERE DONE?
Harold: I JUST PUT IT IN THE
ATTIC OF THE BOATHOUSE.
Red: THANKS, HAROLD.
Harold: YOU BE CAREFUL WITH
THOSE RACKETS.
THEY WERE EXPENSIVE.
Red: I'M NOT GONNA USE THE
RACKETS, HAROLD.
Harold: OH, OKAY.
THE NET.
THE NET!
NO, NOT THE NET.
Red: DON'T YOU HATE IT WHEN
YOU'RE DRIVING IN HEAVY TRAFFIC
IN THE WINTER AND YOU RUN OUT OF
WINDSHIELD-WASHER FLUID?
'CAUSE THE WIPERS WON'T DO A
THING WITH NO MOISTURE ON THERE.
SO YOU END UP TAILGATING TRACTOR
TRAILERS TRYING TO CATCH THEIR
VAPOR TRAIL.
I'VE BEEN KNOWN TO LEAN OUT THE
WINDOW AT 75 KLICKS JUST TO
THROW MY COFFEE ON THE
WINDSHIELD.
WELL, THAT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN
TO ME AGAIN...
'CAUSE, FRIENDS, YOU HAVE JUST
WITNESSED THE LAST WASHER REFILL
I'M EVER GONNA HAVE TO MAKE.
FROM NOW ON, I'M GONNA RECYCLE
MY WINDSHIELD-WASHER FLUID.
THAT'S WHAT THIS FUNNEL'S FOR.
"HOW'S THAT GONNA WORK?" YOU'RE
PROBABLY ASKING...
AMONG OTHER THINGS.
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU HOW IT'S
GONNA WORK.
CAN YOU SAY "EAVES TROUGH"?
[panting]
HI, GORD.
ON YOUR WAY TO A SANITY HEARING?
Gord: NO.
NO, NO. NOT YET.
BUT THIS IS PERFECT.
I FOUND AN OLD BOOK OF MAGIC
TRICKS, AND I NEED A VOLUNTEER.
SIT DOWN.
Red: YOU'RE NOT GONNA TIE ME
UP, ARE YOU?
Gord: COME ON, RED, COME ON.
YOU KNOW I'M NOT ALLOWED ROPE UP
HERE ANYMORE.
NOW...
PICK A CARD.
ALL RIGHT.
DON'T SHOW ME WHAT IT IS.
Red: ALL RIGHT.
Gord: MEMORIZE IT. ALL RIGHT?
Red: YEAH.
Gord: OKAY, NOW PUT IT BACK
IN THE DECK.
Red: OKAY.
DONE.
Gord: DONE? ALL RIGHT.
NOW I MIX THE DECK UP A LITTLE
BIT.
PREPARE TO BE AMAZED AS I TURN
OVER THE NEXT CARD TO REVEAL
YOUR...JACK OF SPADES.
Red: NO.
Gord: WELL, THEN IT'S A QUEEN
OF DIAMONDS.
Red: NO.
Gord: COMMUNITY CHEST?
Red: YOU HAVE NO IDEA, DO
YOU, GORD?
Red: COME ON, RED, LIGHTEN
UP, OKAY?
LOOK, IT'S AN OLD MAGICIANS'
GAG -- MAKE THE AUDIENCE BELIEVE
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
DOING.
Red: BOY, DOES IT EVER WORK.
Gord: OH, WELL.
HAVE YOU SEEN WHAT'S UNDERNEATH
MY HAT?
[laughs]
Red: OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S A RABBIT.
Gord: OH, IS IT, RED?
IS IT A RABBIT?
Red: YEAH, YEAH.
Gord: [laughs]
Red: ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, THAT'S FLOWERS.
Gord: OH, FLOWERS?
Red: YEAH.
OH!
OKAY, OKAY!
THAT'S ANNOYING.
Gord: OH, WELL, THEN ALLOW ME
TO LEND YOU MY HANDKERCHIEF.
[laughs]
Red: OKAY, GORD, YOU KNOW
WHAT?
THIS IS NOT HOW IT WORKS, OKAY?
YOU DON'T JUST KEEP CHANGING THE
TRICK, EH?
YOU FINISH THE TRICK THAT YOU
STARTED WITH.
THAT'S HOW THE WHOLE DEAL WORKS.
Gord: [sobs]
YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHO AM I KIDDING?
I'M NOT A MAGICIAN.
I'M A LOSER.
MY LIFE IS ONE BIG PILE OF
UNFULFILLED DREAMS...
MISSED OPPORTUNITIES...
AND THE OCCASIONAL RESTRAINING
ORDER, RIGHT?
I DON'T BLAME YOU FOR NOT LIKING
ME.
Red: NO, NO.
IT'S NOT THAT I DON'T LIKE YOU.
IT'S JUST THAT I JUST WANTED TO
SEE MY TWO OF CLUBS.
Gord: OH! OH!
YOU MEAN...THIS TWO OF CLUBS?
[laughs]
Red: YEAH.
YEAH, THAT'S IT. YEAH.
WAY TO GO. WAY TO GO.
Gord: THERE'S MORE WHERE THAT
CAME FROM.
[laughs]
Red: MIKE AND I MET OUT ON
THE RINK THERE BEHIND THE LODGE
TO HAVE A LITTLE GAME OF
CURLING.
AND WE BROUGHT OUR ROCKS AS WE
ALWAYS DO, AND THE BROOMS WERE
LIKE NEW BECAUSE THEY WERE FOR
CLEANING THE LODGE.
AND, UH, MIKE HAD BROUGHT A
GALLON OF PAINT.
HE WANTED ME TO GO UP AND, UH --
IN CURLING, THEY HAVE SOMETHING
THAT'S CALLED A HOUSE.
IT'S LIKE A DOT IN THE MIDDLE,
AND IT'S GOT RINGS AROUND THE
OUTSIDE, SO...
SOMETIMES IT'S TOUGH TO FIGURE
OUT HOW TO PAINT A CIRCLE,
ESPECIALLY ON THE ICE, BUT
LUCKILY I HAD COME WITH AN EAVES
TROUGH NAIL ACTUALLY IN MY
POCKET.
SO I PIKE THAT DOWN THROUGH THE
CAN OF PAINT, THEN FLIP HER
OVER...
FLIP HER RIGHT OVER QUICK.
AND THERE'S YOUR CIRCLE.
OKAY, THAT'S THE DOT IN THE
MIDDLE.
NOW YOU GOT TO JUST BRING HER
OUT, AND YOU START DOING THE
RINGS WITH IT.
AND ROUND AND ROUND SHE GOES.
IT'S A PRETTY EFFECTIVE WAY
TO -- BEFORE YOU KNOW IT --
YOU THINK THEY PUT HOUSES UP
FAST WHERE YOU LIVE?
I BUILT THAT ONE IN ABOUT TWO
SECONDS.
SO NOW WE'RE READY TO GO.
SO MIKE -- HE PLAYS LEAD, BUT WE
HAVE A KIND OF SMALL TEAM, SO
YOU GOT TO DO YOUR OWN SWEEPING.
AND, UH, HE'S OUT THERE, AND
AWAY HE GOES.
I WASN'T PAYING AS MUCH
ATTENTION AS I SHOULD HAVE
BECAUSE MIKE DOESN'T DO
EVERYTHING JUST RIGHT BY THE
BOOK, YOU KNOW.
OKAY, SO -- SO NOW I GOT TO
THROW IN MY TAKEOUT ROCK, AND
I'M PRETTY FAMILIAR WITH TAKEOUT
AS A GENERAL RULE, BUT...UH, I
DIDN'T GET -- I MISSED.
ALL RIGHT, I MISSED.
OKAY, SO...
SO NOW MIKE FIRES ANOTHER ONE IN
THERE, AND THEN HE GETS THE
SWEEPER GOING AGAIN.
HERE AGAIN, YOU KNOW, I THINK I
NEEDED SOMEONE ELSE OR SOME TYPE
OF A REFEREE BECAUSE, UH, MIKE
IS NOW JUST GETTING BLATANT WITH
THE WAY HE'S CHEATING, AS FAR AS
I'M CONCERNED.
SO I FIGURE I GOT TO GO TO THE
NEXT LEVEL.
FORGET THE ROCK.
I'M GONNA PUSH MY CAR.
AND, UH...
THAT SHOULD TAKE OUT A -- THIS
IS ACTUALLY MY TAKEOUT CAR, AND,
UH, COMING IN THERE, LOOKING
GOOD.
THAT ONE'S OUT, AND THAT ONE'S
GONE.
OH, BABY!
DEAD CENTER.
SO THEN MIKE -- HE FIRES HIS,
AND HE GIVES IT A LITTLE SPIN.
AND HE'S GONNA TRY TO CURL HER
IN THERE.
IT'S A KIND OF A -- OH, LOOK
OUT, MIKE!
OHH, BABY!
AND...OH, MY GOODNESS.
YOU GET THE BIG WIN THERE, MIKE.
LOOKS LIKE YOUR END CAME THROUGH
AGAIN.
HOW IS YOUR END FEELING, ANYWAY?
NOT THAT GOOD, HUH?
THIS IS THE REPAIR-SHOP PART OF
THE SHOW WE CALL "IF IT AIN'T
BROKE, YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
SO, MIKE, WHAT DO YOU GOT FOR US
TODAY?
Mike: IT'S A CAR RADIO.
IT DOESN'T WORK.
Red: I FIGURED THAT, MIKE,
BUT THIS IS A GREAT BECAUSE WITH
ELECTRONIC EQUIPMENT, THERE'S
ACTUALLY A STEP-BY-STEP
PROCEDURE THAT A REAL HANDYMAN
GOES THROUGH, OKAY?
STEP ONE -- TURN IT ON.
Mike: SHOULDN'T IT HAVE A
POWER SOURCE OR SOMETHING?
Red: OH! YEAH.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
STEP MINUS ONE -- PLUG HER IN.
Mike: WELL, IT'S A CAR RADIO.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE A PLUG.
IT KIND OF CONNECTS UP TO THE
BATTERY.
Red: YEAH, I GOT ONE.
I GOT ONE HERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THREW ME OFF,
MIKE?
THAT'S A VERY FANCY RADIO.
I NEVER SEEN ONE LIKE THAT
BEFORE.
IS THAT A FOREIGN UNIT?
Mike: IT'S MADE IN TEXAS.
Red: WELL, THERE YOU GO.
OH, LOOK.
THE LIGHT CAME ON.
Mike: WELL, THAT'S ABOUT AS
FAR AS I GOT, TOO.
Red: DID YOU TRY TURNING IT
OFF, THEN TURNING IT RIGHT BACK
ON AGAIN?
Mike: YEAH, I DID THAT.
Red: DID YOU JIGGLE IT?
Mike: UH-HUH.
Red: DID YOU TRY HITTING IT?
Mike: YEP.
Red: DID YOU TRY TURNING IT
OFF AND THEN, LIKE, LET HER JUST
SIT FOR 10 MINUTES, BUT THEN
EVERY 20 SECONDS, YOU WENT BACK
AND DID THE SAME DARN ROUTINE
ALL THE WAY THROUGH ALL OVER
AGAIN?
Mike: ABOUT A DOZEN TIMES,
YEAH.
Red: THEN I THINK WE'RE
SCUPPERED HERE, MIKE.
THE ONLY OTHER ALTERNATIVE IS TO
LOOK AT THE MANUAL, AND I'M NOT
GONNA BE GOING THERE.
WE'RE DONE.
Mike: SHOULDN'T IT HAVE LIKE
A SPEAKER ATTACHED TO IT?
Red: IT, UH -- I WAS JUST
COMING TO THAT.
WE'RE GONNA HOOK THE SPEAKER
UP TO IT NOW, MIKE.
THAT'S THE NEXT -- JUST TO HELP
US.
HOW MANY OF YOU WERE AHEAD OF US
ON THAT?
[laughter]
BULL.
[radio static]
Mike: WE'RE GETTING
SOMETHING.
Red: YEAH. COME IN, RANGOON.
[laughs]
ROGER, SERGEANT, WE COPY.
Red: SOUNDS LIKE THE COPS.
YEAH, BE ON THE LOOKOUT FOR A
SUSPECT CARRYING A POLICE
SCANNER.
Mike: THANKS, MR. GREEN.
I GOT TO GO.
Red: ONE OF THE HAZARDS OF
WINTER IS GETTING TOO MUCH SNOW
BUILT UP ON YOUR ROOF.
YOU CAN HAVE AN AVALANCHE JUST
COMING OUT YOUR OWN FRONT DOOR.
AND, BELIEVE ME, IT'S A REAL
SHOCK TO THE SYSTEM TO SUDDENLY
HAVE 30 POUNDS OF SNOW SHOW UP
IN YOUR UNDERSHORTS.
NOW, FOR BIG MOUNTAINS LIKE THEY
HAVE IN SWITZERLAND OR ON "THE
WALTONS," THEY CONTROL THE
AMOUNT OF SNOW BUILDUP BY FIRING
OFF A CANNON.
THE EXPLOSION BREAKS UP ALL THE
SNOWDRIFTS SO THEY KIND OF ROLL
DOWN THE HILL WITHOUT TURNING
ANY CROSS-COUNTRY SKIERS INTO
FROSTED FLAKES.
THEY BASICALLY HAVE A BUNCH OF
SMALL AVALANCHES TO AVOID HAVING
A BIG ONE...
LIKE THE WAY YOU HAVE THOSE
SMALL DAILY DISAGREEMENTS WITH
YOUR WIFE TO AVOID HAVING THE
BIG ONE WHERE YOU END UP LIVING
IN YOUR CAR.
UNFORTUNATELY, I CAN'T FIRE A
CANNON TO GET THE SNOW OFF MY
ROOF BECAUSE THE LODGE CANNON
APPARENTLY WILL NOT BE RETURNING
TO US UNTIL AFTER THE TRIAL.
SO INSTEAD, I'M GONNA MAKE A
CANNON-LIKE NOISE BY FILLING MY
ENGINE HERE WITH HAIR SPRAY.
GUYS MY AGE DON'T NEED HAIR
SPRAY ANYWAY, UNLESS IT HAS
PAINT IN IT.
ALL WE DO NOW IS START THE
ENGINE AND LET NATURE TAKE ITS
COURSE.
[engine turns over]
[panting]
[laughs]
THOSE BADMINTON NETS WORKED
GREAT.
I BELIEVE I CAUGHT MY LIMIT.
Harold: IT'S DISGUSTING.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE A FISHING
DERBY, NOT A SALVAGE EXPEDITION.
Red: HAROLD, WHEN YOU'RE IN A
CONTEST, YOU GOT TO USE YOUR
INGENUITY.
I'M A CREATIVE GUY.
Harold: YOU'RE A DESTRUCTIVE
GUY.
DID YOU EVER HEAR OF
SPORTSMANSHIP?
YOU THINK THIS IS WHAT THE
GREEKS HAD IN MIND WHEN THEY
DEVELOPED THE OLYMPICS?
Red: NOW, HAROLD, THE GREEKS
USED TO COMPETE NUDE.
I DON'T THINK THAT WOULD WORK SO
GOOD FOR A FISHING DERBY.
BAD PLACE TO SNAG A LURE.
Harold: OH, YEAH.
AW, DON'T DO THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
YOU TRIED TO WIN BY CHEATING.
YEAH, WELL, THANKFULLY ALL YOU
ENDED UP DOING WAS CLEANING UP
THE LAKE.
[laughs]
AND SINCE THERE WAS NO ACTUAL
WINNER, WE'RE GONNA TAKE THE
PRIZE MONEY, AND WE'RE GONNA
RESTOCK IT WITH HEALTHY FISH.
Red: WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "NO
PRIZEWINNER," HUH?
[laughs]
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
EH?
Harold: THAT'S MY CARAMEL
CANDY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
Red: NO, WAIT.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS WHAT I MEANT.
DOES THAT LOOK FAMILIAR,
HAROLD, HUH?
Harold: YEAH, OKAY, OKAY.
THAT'S THE TAG, BUT THERE'S NO
ACTUAL FISH ON THERE.
Red: I KNEW YOU WERE GONNA
SAY THAT.
TAKE A LOOK AT THAT PICTURE.
WHAT DO YOU SEE THERE, HUH?
Harold: [laughs]
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
Red: UP ON THE BRIDGE.
THE FISH JUMPED OUT OF
POSSUM LAKE, RAN ACROSS THE
BRIDGE...
AND DOVE INTO MERCURY.
SEE THAT CARIBOU?
HE HAD HIM THERE STOPPING
TRAFFIC.
SO LET'S COUGH UP THE 1,000
BUCKS, HUH?
Harold: YOU DON'T GET THE
PRIZE MONEY.
YOU DIDN'T BRING IN THE ACTUAL
FISH.
Red: I BROUGHT IN A PICTURE
OF THE FISH, HAROLD.
THAT'S CLOSE ENOUGH.
Harold: OKAY, WELL,
CONGRATULATIONS.
Red: NO, NO, HAROLD.
I WANT MY MONEY.
Harold: WELL, THAT'S A
PICTURE OF 1,000 BUCKS.
CLOSE ENOUGH.
[pig oinking]
OH, OH, AND IT'S MEETING TIME.
Red: OKAY.
MY WIFE IS WATCHING.
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND SOMEBODY GOT THAT SAYING
WRONG...
OKAY, A PICTURE IS WORTH A
THOUSAND WORDS, BUT THEY'RE
FOUR-LETTER WORDS.
THE REST OF YOU, THANKS FOR
WATCHING ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
HAROLD AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE.
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE, HUH?
[cheers and applause]
[indistinct conversations]
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, EVERYBODY.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
All: QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS
MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS FOR THE MAN'S
PRAYER.
All: I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN
CHANGE IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
Red: OKAY, MEN, WE MANAGED TO
DREDGE UP AN OLD SNOWMOBILE OUT
OF POSSUM LAKE.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S BEEN DOWN THERE
MAYBE A COUPLE SEASONS OR A
LITTLE MORE, SO IS THERE ANYBODY
HERE WHO MAYBE DROPPED A
SNOWMOBILE THROUGH THE ICE OVER
THE LAST FIVE YEARS?