[quirky upbeat music]
[gunshots, explosion]
>> THE EXCITEMENT
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
SO GET READY TO BE EXCITED,
BECAUSE, WELL, IT'S GONNA
HAPPEN.
THAT MUCH I KNOW FOR SURE, SO
BECAUSE, BELIEVE ME YOU, I KNOW
EXCITEMENT.
HERE HE IS, THE WORLD'S GREATEST
UNCLE.
WELL, OKAY, AS FAR AS I KNOW,
ANYWAY.
I MEAN, AS AN EMPLOYER,
HE'S ALWAYS BEEN FAIR.
ANYWAY, HERE'S THE STAR
OF THE RED GREEN SHOW,
MR. RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU, HAROLD.
HELLO.
THANK YOU.
AND WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
AND A VERY SPECIAL HELLO TO ALL
THE SECURITY GUARDS OUT THERE
WHO'VE CHOSEN TO WATCH US RATHER
THAN THE LOBBY MONITOR.
AND YOU SHOULD'VE BEEN UP AT THE
LODGE HERE LAST NIGHT.
WE HAD A LITTLE TALENT SHOW, YOU
KNOW, JUST A BUNCH OF US.
STINKY PETERSON WENT FIRST,
ACTUALLY.
WHAT HE DID WAS, HE SWALLOWED
AIR FOR ABOUT 12 OR 13 MINUTES.
AND THEN HE TURNED AROUND AND
BELCHED MACARTHUR PARK.
IT WAS FABULOUS.
WE WERE KIND OF AFRAID TO ASK
FOR AN ENCORE.
ACTUALLY, HAROLD AND I HERE EVEN
DID A LITTLE--OH, I'M SORRY.
I HAVEN'T INTRODUCED HAROLD.
HAROLD, COME ON IN HERE A SEC.
HAROLD IS THE PRODUCER,
DIRECTOR, AND ANNOUNCER OF THE
SHOW.
PLUS, WE'RE HELPING HIM GET
THROUGH PUBERTY, IN CASE HE
LOSES THE MAP OR ANYTHING, YOU
KNOW.
>> AND DON'T FORGET THIS.
[laughs]
I DO ALL THE SPECIAL EFFECTS.
>> YEAH, HAROLD, I WAS JUST
TELLING THEM ABOUT
THE TALENT SHOW.
>> YES, I WAS JUST RELIVING
THOSE MOMENTS MYSELF.
YOU KNOW, AND IT GAVE ME THE
MOTIVATION AND OPPORTUNITY TO
QUEUE UP THE NEXT SEGMENT.
SO, UNCLE RED, WHY DON'T WE
JUST, LIKE, YOU KNOW, SKIP RIGHT
ON OVER TO THAT?
AND THEN WE CAN COME BACK TO YOU
DREDGING UP THE PAST LATER.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, IF THERE'S
TIME.
>> WELL, HAROLD, I WANTED TO
KIND OF CONTINUE WITH WHAT I WAS
SAYING.
>> OH, BOY.
UNCLE RED, I WISH YOU'D TOLD ME
THAT.
OH, I'M--
OH, JEEPERS, I'M SORRY.
>> THERE'S A FUNNY
LITTLE DITTY
[whistles]
IT'S CALLED THE HUMMING SONG
THE HUMMING SONG IS PRETTY
[whistles]
BUT I DON'T KNOW IT.
THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA BE TALKING ABOUT VCRs,
WHICH STANDS FOR, UH--
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
BEFORE I PURCHASED THIS UNIT, I
READ ALL THE MAGAZINES ABOUT IT.
AND I SPOKE TO THE PRODUCTION
PERSONNEL HERE
AT THE RED GREEN SHOW.
AND THEY ADVISED ME TO
GET ONE OF THESE BETA UNITS.
AND EVEN THE SALESMAN AT THE
STORE SAID, "BOY, THEY DON'T
MAKE THEM LIKE THIS ANYMORE."
SO I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU, BUT
WHENEVER I GET A NEW CAR OR A
LAWNMOWER, WHAT HAVE YOU, I LIKE
TO JUST TAKE IT APART, CHECK IT
OUT MYSELF, KIND OF TUNE IT UP
FOR MY OWN PARTICULAR
REQUIREMENTS.
AND I'M GONNA DO THE SAME WITH
MY BETA UNIT HERE,
ESPECIALLY SINCE MY RAMBO TAPE
IS JAMMED IN THERE.
I CAN'T SEEM TO GET IT OUT.
SO I'VE JUST GOT ONE MORE SCREW
TO POP OFF HERE.
OKAY.
KIND OF SET FOR SCREWING IN
WHICH DOESN'T HELP.
ANYWAY, THIS SHOULD POP OFF OF
HERE NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
LET'S SEE WHAT WE GOT HERE.
YEAH, OH, YEAH.
WELL, I THINK THAT THERE
IS A WIRE.
AND THIS SEEMS TO BE SOME TYPE
OF A PLASTIC.
AND I GUESS TO GET THE ACTUAL
CASSETTE OUT,
I'M GONNA NEED TO--
[muttering]
ALL RIGHT,
THERE SEEMS TO BE SOME SORT OF
A MALFUNCTION HERE.
AND I THINK THE ONLY WAY TO GET
THE CASSETTE OUT
IS TO CUT IT OUT.
AND I THINK I HAVE THE PERFECT
TOOL FOR THAT.
[whirring]
SO NOW WHAT WE HAVE IS A MOVIE
WITH AN INTERMISSION.
BUT SINCE I'VE GOT THE MACHINE
APART ANYWAY, MIGHT AS WELL TAKE
ONE LAST LOOK AT IT, MAKE SURE
THAT EVERYTHING'S--YEAH, YEAH.
EVERYTHING LOOKS OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT DOES SO
MIGHT AS WELL TAKE THOSE
OUT OF THERE.
KEEP IT SIMPLE IS MY MOTTO.
AND I'LL JUST GIVE HER JUST A
LITTLE CLEAN OUT HERE.
[hissing]
ALL RIGHT.
THAT SHOULD DO IT.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL, REALLY.
NO MATTER WHAT THEY MAKE, MAKE
IT A MICROWAVE OVEN OR A HAIR
DRYER OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT, IF
MEN MAKE IT, MEN CAN FIX IT.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME, REMEMBER, IF
WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OH, WAIT.
THERE'S AN EJECT BUTTON.
I DIDN'T SEE THAT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK
AFTER THESE MESSAGES.
AND I'LL FINISH MY STORY.
COUNT ON IT.
>> UNLESS I GET ANOTHER ATTACK
OF ENNUI.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU WILL,
NOT ON PAYDAY.
>> GOOD POINT.
>> YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
I WAS READING THERE THEY GOT
THESE ATOMIC BOMBS NOW.
WELL, THEY'VE HAD THEM
FOR A WHILE, I GUESS.
>> YOU'VE MENTIONED THAT, YEAH.
>> THEY WON'T SELL ME ONE,
THOUGH.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU'VE GOT NO PLACE
TO KEEP IT.
YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE AN ATOMIC
WAREHOUSE.
>> I WOULDN'T HAVE IT LONG.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT LIKE I'D NEED
TO STORE IT OVER A WINTER
OR ANYTHING.
BUT IT'S JUST TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT, YOU KNOW,
EXACTLY HOW THE BOMB WORKS.
NOW, AN ATOM, APPARENTLY,
IS QUITE SMALL.
>> YES.
>> AND WHEN YOU BREAK IT UP,
IT GOES UP BIG.
IS THAT IT?
>> EXACTLY.
IT EXPLODES BECAUSE IT GETS AWAY
FROM ITSELF REALLY QUICK.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> IT'S SORT OF LIKE...
>> both: A FAMILY REUNION.
>> EXACTLY.
EVERYONE JUST GOES, "THANK YOU.
BYE-BYE."
AND THEY LEAVE REALLY QUICK.
AND THERE'S A BIG
INTERNAL COMBUSTION.
>> OKAY, NOW, BUT THERE'S A--
NOW, THERE'S NEUTRON
AND A PROTON AND A ELECTRON.
THE ELECTRON, I BELIEVE, IS
IONIZING AROUND THE NUCLEUS.
AND IS THAT IT?
>> EXACTLY.
>> THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
AND THEN I THINK THE ELECTRON
COMES INTO THE NEUTRON ON, SAY,
LIKE, A FRIDAY NIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> AND THERE'S A COLLISION
THERE.
AND THE PROTON--
>> SAYS HE DIDN'T SEE A THING.
>> NO, EXACTLY.
AND NOW THE NEUTRON IS EXCITED.
>> YEAH.
>> AND OF COURSE,
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT IS CENSORED.
>> [laughing]
>> "IT IS WINTER.
A CAR DRIVES PAST,
RUSHING TO SOMEWHERE.
THE PEOPLE INSIDE DO NOT FEEL
THE GLOW OF THE WINTER SUN.
THEY DO NOT FEEL THE SNOW ON
THEIR TONGUE OR THE GENTLE
BREEZE ON THEIR CHEEKS OR THE
HUGE WAVE OF SLUSH THAT COVERS
ME FROM HEAD TO FOOT
AS THEIR CAR DRIVES PAST,
ON ITS WAY TO AN ACCIDENT
IF THERE'S ANY JUSTICE."
WELL, AS I WAS SAYING,
WE WERE HAVING A REAL HOOT WITH
THE TALENT SHOW THING.
YOU KNOW, MOOSE THOMPSON DID HIS
VERSION OF DIRTY DANCING
WITH A COUPLE OF TRUCK TIRES
AND A GREASE GUN.
AND THEN OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
PLAYED HIS MUSICAL SAW.
BUT HE GOT A LITTLE CARRIED AWAY
DURING THE FLIGHT
OF THE BUMBLEBEE
AND ENDED UP CUTTING THE CROTCH
OUT OF HIS HIP WADERS.
HE WASN'T HURT, THOUGH.
CLOSE BUT NO CIGAR.
>> IS THAT IT, UNCLE RED?
IS THAT THE END
OF THE TALENT SHOW STORY?
'CAUSE IF IT IS, WE CAN JUST GO
ON TO THE NEXT SEGMENT.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, IF THAT'S IT.
>> NO, THAT'S NOT IT, HAROLD.
I'LL TELL YOU
WHEN IT'S FINISHED.
>> UH-OH.
JEEPERS, I WISH YOU'D TOLD ME
THAT BEFORE I PUSHED THIS
BUTTON.
>> WHICH BUTTON?
>> JUST A SEC.
THAT ONE.
>> YOU DID THAT ON PURPOSE,
HAROLD.
>> SORRY, I HAD AN ATTACK OF
ENNUI.
>> HI, RED.
I THOUGHT IT WAS YOU.
>> YEAH?
>> I RECOGNIZED THE SOUND OF
YOUR TRUCK COMING UP THE LANE.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I WAS JUST MAKING SOME TEA.
YOU WANT SOME?
ORANGE PEKOE, RABBIT'S FOOT,
TREE BARK, OR MOOSE PATTY.
>> WELL, I THINK I'LL STICK WITH
THE ORANGE PEKOE.
>> OKAY, GREAT.
>> CAN I GIVE YOU A HAND THERE?
I'LL HOLD THIS FOR YOU.
>> THIS IS GREAT.
I'M MAKING TEA.
MAKING TEA FOR ME AND RED GREEN.
>> YEAH.
>> I HAVEN'T MADE TEA
IN 38 DAYS.
>> FOR GOSH SAKE.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I JUST WANTED TO
HAVE YOU TELL US ABOUT FIRE
SAFETY, 'CAUSE YOU'RE KIND OF
THE EXPERT IN THAT AREA.
>> WELL, I SHOULD BE.
I'VE BEEN UP HERE FOR 13 YEARS.
>> OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> 13 LONG, LONELY YEARS.
[wailing]
>> NO, NO, NO, NO.
>> YOU KNOW, IT WOULDN'T BE SO
BAD IF THERE WAS A FIRE NOW AND
THEN, YOU KNOW, ANYTHING, A
SMALL FIRE, A CONTROLLED BURN,
AN ARTIFICIAL FIREPLACE LOG.
I DON'T CARE, ANYTHING.
>> WELL, YOU CAN'T MEAN THAT,
GORD.
>> NO, I GUESS NOT.
>> NO, YOU KIDDER, HUH?
>> YEAH.
>> [laughs]
>> NOT WHEN IT'S BEEN AS DRY
AS IT HAS BEEN, YOU KNOW.
IT HASN'T BEEN THIS DRY IN THE
WHOLE TIME I'VE BEEN UP HERE.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, IT'S VERY, VERY DRY.
>> DO YOU GET A LOT OF LIGHTNING
UP HERE?
I WAS WONDERING ABOUT THAT.
>> WELL, YEAH.
BUT IT ONLY HITS MY TOWER.
>> OH.
>> YEAH, I'VE GOT THE ONLY METAL
FOR 50 SQUARE MILES AROUND.
SO ANY LIGHTNING THAT COMES DOWN
WILL GO THROUGH ME.
>> RIGHT HERE?
>> YEAH.
>> BOY.
>> I CAN'T TELL YOU THE NUMBER
OF TIMES I'VE HAD MY EYEBROWS
BLOWN OFF.
YOU KNOW, I CAN'T REMEMBER
ANYTHING BEFORE THE AGE OF 14.
IT'S THE LIGHTNING THAT DID IT,
I THINK.
>> YEAH?
YEAH.
WELL, COULD YOU GIVE OUR VIEWERS
AS KIND OF A SAFETY THING--LIKE,
SAY, IT'S IN A LIGHTNING STORM.
IS THERE ANY KIND
OF SAFETY THING?
>> SURE.
>> WHERE SHOULD THEY GO
IN A LIGHTNING STORM, SAY,
FOR EXAMPLE?
>> WELL, ANYWHERE
BUT THIS TOWER.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> AND ANOTHER GOOD SAFETY TIP
IS, WHEN YOU'RE LIGHTING A
CAMPFIRE, MAKE SURE YOU UNPLUG
THE ELECTRIC CHARCOAL STARTER.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
THAT'S VERY GOOD.
OKAY, WELL, WE GOT TO GET GOING,
GORD.
SO WE'LL SEE YOU NEXT TIME
AROUND, EH?
>> OH, YOU'RE NOT GOING ALREADY,
ARE YOU?
COME ON.
>> I REALLY HAVE TO--
>> YOU HAVEN'T HAD
YOUR ORANGE PEKOE.
I HAVEN'T HAD MY MOOSE PATTY.
>> NO, WELL, MAYBE SOME OTHER
TIME, EH?
>> YOU CAN'T GO YET.
BUT WHERE'S THE FIRE?
AS WE SAY.
[laughs]
>> WHAT DO YOU SEE
WHEN YOU LOOK AT A TREE?
ARE YOU SCARED OF THE BARK
OR THE WAY IT'S ALL DARK?
WHAT DO YOU SEE
WHEN YOU LOOK AT A TREE?
IF YOU SEE ME
STANDING UP TO A TREE
DON'T MAKE A SOUND
TILL I'M DONE
>> UNCLE RED, THIS IS MY
FAVORITE PART OF THE SHOW, WHERE
YOU ANSWER THE VIEWERS' MAIL,
'CAUSE I GET TO BRUSH UP ON MY
READING SKILLS, AND IT'S AN
INEXPENSIVE PRODUCTION FILLER.
[laughs]
LETTER NUMBER ONE.
"DEAR RED, WE'RE GOING MOOSE
HUNTING SOON.
AND I WONDERED HOW DO YOU TREAT
A GUNSHOT WOUND IN AN EMERGENCY
SITUATION?"
>> OH, THAT'S INTERESTING.
I WOULD'VE THOUGHT ANY GUNSHOT
WOUND IS AN EMERGENCY SITUATION.
UNLESS MAYBE YOU'RE SHOT
BY A DOCTOR IN A HOSPITAL.
>> WHY WOULD A DOCTOR
SHOOT A PATIENT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE SOME KIND OF
A MAKE-WORK PROJECT.
>> WELL, LET'S ASSUME THAT THE
GUNSHOT WOUND HAPPENED IN AN
OPEN FIELD, IF I MIGHT
INTERPULATE TO THAT OF WHICH THE
VIEWER HAS ALLUDED.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, FIRST OFF,
YOU HAVE TO DETERMINE
WHERE THE GUNSHOT WOUND IS.
IF IT'S IN THE DUCK OR THE DEER
OR THE MOOSE, WELL, YOU DON'T
TREAT IT AT ALL, 'CAUSE THAT'S
WHERE IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE.
BUT IF IT'S IN ONE OF YOUR
HUNTING COMPANIONS, THEN THE
FIRST THING YOU HAVE TO DO IS
STANCH THE FLOW.
>> OH, "STANCH THE FLOW,"
THAT SOUNDS NEAT.
WHAT IS THAT?
>> STOP THE BLEEDING.
AND THEN YOU HAVE TO DETERMINE
HOW BAD THE WOUND IS.
>> SO, LIKE, YOU MIGHT SAY,
LIKE, "HOW DO YOU FEEL?"
OR SOMETHING?
>> YEAH, YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
AND IF HE SCREAMS, "I'M DYING,"
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
IF HE MUMBLES, "I'M DYING,"
THAT'S ACTUALLY WORSE.
SO THE NEXT THING YOU TRY TO DO
IS MOVE THE PATIENT
IF HE CAN BE MOVED.
BUT IF YOU MOVE HIM AND THE LEG
DOESN'T MOVE WITH THE BODY,
THEN YOU REALLY HAVE TO RETHINK
THE TRANSPORTATION METHOD.
>> RIGHT, RIGHT.
SO THE PERSON AND THE LEG SHOULD
MOVE TOGETHER.
THAT WOULD BE GOOD.
I MEAN, THAT WOULD BE BETTER,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH, THAT'S MUCH BETTER.
AND THEN WHAT YOU DO IS, YOU GET
THE GUY TO THE HOSPITAL.
AND THEN YOU GO RIGHT BACK TO
HUNTING, BECAUSE OTHERWISE,
YOU'LL LOSE YOUR NERVE.
>> OH, LOSE YOUR NERVE FOR
HUNTING ALTOGETHER, YOU MEAN?
>> GIVE IT UP.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, I'VE SEEN IT HAPPEN
TO GUYS.
>> THAT WOULD BE TRAGIC.
>> WELL, IT'S THE DOWNSIDE OF
GETTING SHOT.
THIS WEEK ON ADVENTURES WITH
BILL, HE'S GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW TO ERECT--
THAT'S A TENT, I GUESS IT IS.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN BILL REACHES
INTO HIS PANTS.
NOW THIS, TO ME, IS NOT A
TECHNIQUE THAT I THINK HE
THOUGHT THROUGH TOTALLY,
'CAUSE THOSE PEGS
AND EVERYTHING WENT--
THEY WENT ALL OVER THE PLACE.
AND WE WERE THERE FOR A GOOD
TWO, THREE DAYS JUST FINDING THE
LITTLE ATTACHMENTS THAT GO ON
THE END OF THE WHIRLIGIGS THERE.
ANYWAY, I'M HOLDING THE PEG, AND
HE'S GONNA HAMMER IT IN.
AND I THINK THAT HAMMER
LOOKS--YEAH.
I THINK BILL UNDERESTIMATED THE
SOFTNESS OF THE GROUND
AT THIS TIME OF YEAR.
AND HE DRILLED THAT BABY DOWN A
FOOT AND A HALF, TWO FEET.
BUT, YOU KNOW, BILL SOLVES HIS
OWN PROBLEMS.
THAT'S ABOUT--
AND SOLVES THEM IN HIS OWN WAY.
BUT NOW--WHAT THE DEAL?
HE WANTED ME
TO PUT THIS TENT UP.
BUT IT WOULDN'T REACH.
I WAS JUST GONNA
STRETCH IT UP THERE.
BUT BILL HAD ANOTHER PLAN.
AND HE'S RESOURCEFUL.
YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE HIM THAT.
YOU KNOW, BILL'S A LOT STRONGER
THAN HE SMELLS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT EXACTLY
THAT ACCOMPLISHED.
BUT IT SEEMED TO MAKE BILL
HAPPY.
AND THEN THE TWO OF US KIND OF
GOT INTO--AND THIS IS NOT ALWAYS
GOOD, TO BE WORKING AT OPPOSITE
ENDS OF A TENT.
YOU NEED KIND OF A COMMUNICATION
THING HAPPENING.
AND IT'S FINE.
HE'S FINE.
BILL, HERE--
I GOT A LITTLE SUSPICIOUS.
THIS DOESN'T LOOK LIKE A NORMAL
KIND OF A TENT LOOK.
AND I WAS TRYING TO DO MY BEST
TO HELP.
YOU KNOW, I'M THERE AS A
SUPPORTER, REALLY.
AND LITERALLY, ACTUALLY,
IN THIS CASE.
THAT CAN HAPPEN.
AND HE'S WRESTLING AROUND
IN THERE.
AND OF COURSE, WHAT ARE YOU
SUPPOSE HE COMES OUT WITH?
THE INSTRUCTIONS.
AND I'M UNDER THE TENT THERE,
BILL.
I'M UNDER THE--OH, GREAT, GREAT.
THAT'LL WORK WELL.
BILL CAN GET SCARY ON YOU.
YOU KNOW, YOU GOT TO--
OH, HE'S A HAPPY GUY, ISN'T HE?
SO NOW WE--SINCE THE POLE GOT A
LITTLE BENT, HE DECIDES HE'S
GONNA TIE HER TO A TREE AND KIND
OF PROP HER UP THAT WAY AND--
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
WELL, I DO APPRECIATE THAT,
BILL.
THANK YOU VERY, VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU FOR INCLUDING ME
IN YOUR LIFE.
THIS IS AN OLD INDIAN TECHNIQUE
THAT BILL FINALLY RESORTED TO
FOR PUTTING UP TENTS.
IT'S A LITTLE TRICKY.
AND YOU GOT TO SMOKE A REALLY
WEIRD PIPE BEFORE YOU CAN DO
THIS.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I'VE SEEN BILL DO
THIS A FEW TIMES.
AND I'VE NEVER BEEN TOTALLY ABLE
TO FIGURE OUT HOW THE HECK
HE DOES IT.
YOU HAVE TO WALK FUNNY TO MAKE
IT WORK REAL WELL.
BUT THIS ONE NOW, HE SAID HE'S
GONNA DO A REAL WHOOP-DE-WHOOPER
HERE.
AND LOOK,
HE THROWS THE LINES OUT.
AND IF YOU WATCH HIM, HE KIND OF
FLOPS HER IN THE AIR A BIT.
IT'S KIND OF A BELLY FLOP THERE.
IT LOOKS LIKE A BIG BOWL OF
JELL-O TENT THERE.
BUT BY GOLLY, SHE WORKS,
DOESN'T SHE?
AND, WELL, HE'S PROUD OF IT.
NICE WORK, BILL.
SO HE'S ALL SET THERE
AND GOT HER ALL SET UP.
OF COURSE, IT'S ABOUT TIME FOR
ME TO HEAD BACK TO THE LODGE.
SO I HAD TO SAY GOOD-BYE TO BILL
THERE.
AND SEE YOU NEXT TIME.
SORRY, BILL.
"IT IS WINTER.
A LITTLE RUM IN YOUR COFFEE,
A LITTLE WHISKEY IN YOUR TEA,
A LITTLE ALCOHOL IN THE CAR
WINDSHIELD WASHER FLUID,
THAT SHOULD KEEP
EVERYONE WIPED."
YOU KNOW,
WE'VE HAD SOME COMMENTS
THAT THE SHOW DOESN'T HAVE
MUCH OF AN EDGE TO IT.
WELL, HERE'S SOMEBODY EDGY.
>> OKAY.
I WONDER WHAT THE PLURAL TO
GRILLED CHEESE IS.
WELL, ANYWAY, HOUSEHOLD CHORES.
THE OTHER DAY, MY MOM ASKED ME
TO CLEAN UP MY ROOM.
[chuckles]
YEAH, SO ANYWAY, SHE SAYS,
"HAROLD, GO CLEAN UP YOUR ROOM,"
RIGHT?
AND I SAID, "MOM, HOW CAN YOU
EXPECT ME TO CLEAN UP MY ROOM
WHEN IT WAS YOUR GENERATION THAT
DESTROYED THE ENVIRONMENT,
CREATED MILLIONS OF H-BOMBS AND
M-BOMBS AND A-BOMBS?
HUH?
HOW ABOUT THAT?
AND DRUGS AND OPEN MANHOLE
COVERS AND HATRED AND GREED AND
INTOLERANCE, SOMETHING WHICH I
PERSONALLY CANNOT STAND.
HUH?
MOM, HOW CAN YOU DO THAT?
DO YOU NOT SEE ANY
INCONSISTENCIES IN THIS AT ALL?"
[chuckles]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I LEARNED SOMETHING THAT DAY.
ACTIONS SPEAK LOUDER THAN WORDS.
'CAUSE SHE JUST, LIKE,
CLOUTED ME, RIGHT?
SO I RACED UP TO MY ROOM, AND I
SWEPT EVERYTHING UNDER THE BED.
[chuckles]
WHICH IS OKAY, 'CAUSE THAT'S
WHERE I KEEP STUFF.
GRILLED CHOOSE.
OH, THAT'S NEAT.
GRILLED CHOOSE,
THAT WOULD BE PLURAL.
[chuckles]
OKAY, SORRY, I WAS WRONG ABOUT
THAT TALENT SHOW STORY.
I KNOW HOW EXCITED WE ARE TO
HEAR THE END OF IT.
SO COME ON BACK
RIGHT AFTER THESE MESSAGES.
CAN I HAVE MY PAYCHECK NOW?
THANKS.
OH, IT'S NOT SIGNED.
>> SORRY.
I WAS HAVING AN ATTACK OF ENNUI.
>> YOU KNOW, SO MANY TIMES,
ONCE YOU GET TO BE AN ADULT,
YOU FORGET WHAT IT WAS
LIKE TO BE A--
TO BE A KID.
AND YOU REALLY SHOULD, I THINK,
TAKE A LITTLE BIT OF TIME,
SPEND SOME TIME WITH A CHILD.
GOOD FOR YOU, GOOD FOR THE KID,
WHETHER IT'S A NEIGHBOR'S KID OR
MAYBE A NEPHEW THAT'S NOT LIKE
HAROLD, OR MAYBE, YOU KNOW, JUST
THROUGH A STROKE OF BAD LUCK,
YOU HAVE A KID OF YOUR OWN.
ANYWAY, TODAY I'M GONNA SPEND A
LITTLE BIT OF TIME WITH ONE OF
MY GOOD CHILDISH FRIENDS HERE.
>> MAX.
MAX AND I ARE GONNA DO A LITTLE
ONE-ON-ONE OF THE OLD
BASKETBALL, THE OLD HOOPS, THE
OLD HITTING THE SLOTS UP ON THE
BOARDS.
I'M PRETTY BAD WITH THE
BASKETBALL.
SO, MAX, WHAT WE'RE GONNA START
WITH HERE IS--SEE, 'CAUSE I LIKE
TO JUST TEACH THEM, TOO.
I DON'T WANT TO JUST FOOL
AROUND.
THIS HAS GOT SOME
EDUCATIONAL--MAXIE, YOU TRY TO
DEFEND ME THERE.
AND NOW WHAT I'M GONNA DO IS,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU SOME OF MY
MOVES, OKAY.
AND I'M GONNA COME IN AND GO FOR
THE BASKET.
OKAY, YOU READY?
YOU READY?
OKAY.
OKAY, OKAY, READY?
TIME OUT.
TIME'S STILL OUT.
TIME IS STILL OUT.
SOMEONE DIDN'T CENTER THIS HOOP.
PROBABLY HAROLD.
THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, TIME'S BACK IN.
OKAY, NOW YOU TRY IT.
OKAY?
SEE OF YOU CAN GET BY ME.
OKAY, COME ON.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
GIVE IT A GOOD SHOT.
HEY, WAIT.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
HAVING A GOOD TIME?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
COME ON, THEN.
COME ON, COME ON.
NOW SEE, IF THERE WAS A REF,
THAT WOULD BE ILLEGAL.
OH, GET THE BALL, WILL YOU, MAX?
YOU KNOW, THE THING IS, I CAN'T
TELL YOU HOW MUCH FUN THEY HAVE.
I JUST WANTED TO GET MAX OUT OF
HERE FOR A SEC, BECAUSE, YOU
KNOW, THEY ENJOY IT SO MUCH.
AND THEY GO HOME, AND THEY TELL
ALL THEIR FRIENDS THAT THEY
SPENT SOME TIME WITH A, YOU
KNOW, A TELEVISION PERSONALITY,
I GUESS YOU CALL IT.
YOU WANT TO GET THAT, MAX?
AND THEN, YOU JUST, TO ME, IT
JUST KIND OF MAKES THEIR DAY.
THROW IT IN HERE.
NO, NO.
PUT IT IN MY HANDS, OKAY?
AND THEY GET SOME EXERCISE.
THEY'RE OUT IN THE SUNSHINE.
PUT IT RIGHT IN HERE.
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
NO, NO, NO.
YOU'RE GETTING CLOSER.
AND THE YOUNG LEGS AND THE--MAX,
I'M KIND OF TIRED.
ONE MORE, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, JEEZ.
THAT'S A--GO GET THAT.
HURRY UP.
HURRY UP, HURRY UP.
I GOT THINGS TO DO.
BUT IF ANY OF YOU WOULD LIKE TO
SPEND SOME TIME WITH A CHILD,
GO FIND ONE.
YOU KNOW?
GOD BLESS YOU.
HERE WE GO.
TIME OUT.
WAS THAT SARCASM THERE?
WELL, YOU KNOW, I DON'T LIKE TO
BRAG, NO MATTER HOW MANY
OPPORTUNITIES I GET
TO DO JUST THAT.
BUT I DO HAVE TO SAY THAT THE
HIGHLIGHT OF THE TALENT SHOW
HAD TO BE HAROLD AND I
DOING OUR SONG.
AND I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE AN
IDEAL WAY TO FINISH OFF
TONIGHT'S SHOW TO JUST DO A KIND
OF A REPEAT PERFORMANCE.
HAROLD, COME ON OVER HERE.
>> DO YOU HAVE A PEN?
>> YEAH, GET OVER HERE.
SO THANKS A LOT FOR WATCHING.
AND ON BEHALF OF HAROLD AND
MYSELF AND THE WHOLE GANG UP AT
THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
AND IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING, YOU
MIGHT WANT TO FIRE THE VCR ON
AND CATCH THIS.
PUT IT ON THAT CASSETTE THAT I'M
BUILDING UP FOR DICK CLARK.
OKAY, NOW YOU GOT TO PICTURE
THIS.
WE WERE ABOUT HALFWAY THROUGH
THE TALENT SHOW.
STINKY PETERSON HAD JUST
FINISHED JUGGLING BOWLING BALLS.
AND HE WAS ON HIS WAY TO THE
HOSPITAL.
AND EVERYBODY'S FIGHTING OVER
POTATO CHIPS.
AND SUDDENLY, THE MUSIC BEGINS.
[both hum]
>> both: I'M COMING HOME
I'VE DONE MY TIME
AND I'VE GOT TO KNOW
IF MY PET APE IS FINE
IF YOU SAW MY LETTER
SAYING DIE TO ENNUI
SIMPLE LITTLE WORDS
IS ALL I NEED TO SET ME FREE
THAT I WROTE
AND TOLD HER PLEASE
>> LISTEN TO THIS PART.
LISTEN TO THIS PART.
>> both: TIE A YELLOW GIBBON
ROUND THE OLD OAK TREE
IT'S BEEN THREE LONG YEARS
HOW'S MY PET MONKEY?
IF I DON'T SEE
THAT YELLOW GIBBON
ROUND THE OLD OAK TREE
I'LL STAY ON THE TRUCK
AND SAY
>> CAREFUL HERE, HAROLD.
THE BLAME ON ME
>> NO, WE'RE GONNA DO IT.
>> both: IF I DON'T SEE
A YELLOW GIBBON
ROUND
>> BIG FINISH.
>> both: THE OLD OAK TREE