A LOT OF MEN DON'T
TAKE MUCH INTEREST
IN CLOTHES.
THEY'LL WEAR ANYTHING
ANYTIME OR THE SAME
THING ALL THE TIME.
BUT WE'RE VERY
PROTECTIVE WHEN IT
COMES TO OUR PANTS.
I MYSELF WEAR
SUSPENDERS AND A BELT.
AND THIS IS NOT A
FASHION STATEMENT,
IT'S MORE PRIMAL
THAN THAT.
WE EVEN KEEP OUR HANDS
IN OUR POCKETS FOR
EXTRA SECURITY.
DON'T KNOW WHY.
I MEAN, WOMEN WILL
HAVE A PAJAMA PARTY AT
ONE OF THEM SORORITY HOUSES
AND THEY'RE HAPPY
TO WALK AROUND IN
THEIR UNDERWEAR,
AT LEAST I THINK THEY
ARE ACCORDING TO ALL
THOSE TEENAGE COMEDY FILMS.
BUT WHEN MEN GET
TOGETHER, THEY'RE
JUST NOT COMFORTABLE
UNLESS THEY HAVE
THEIR PANTS ON.
DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
MAYBE THEY'RE ASHAMED
OF THEIR LEGS.
A LOT OF GUYS
WON'T EVEN WEAR SHORTS.
BUT WHEREVER YOU GO
ALL OVER THE WORLD,
YOU'LL FIND MEN
TREASURE THEIR PANTS,
EXCEPT IN SCOTLAND,
BUT THEY HAVE A LOT
OF BOOZE THERE.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT MAKES US
WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
ON TODAY'S SHOW,
WINSTON ROTHCHILD'S HERE
BILL'S GOT A SNAKE
WHICH HE'S APPARENTLY
WILLING TO SHARE.
DOUGIE'S GOING TO SHOW
OFF HIS FLOSS JOB,
AND I'M GOING TO
DIVE INTO MY PANTS MORE
THAN ONE LEG AT A TIME.
IF MOTHER NATURE
EVER HAD A FATHER,
WHICH IS A FATHER
TO THAT MOTHER,
PLEASE WELCOME MY
FATHER'S BROTHER,
MY MOTHER'S BROTHER-IN-LAW,
YOUR FRIEND
AND MY UNCLE,
RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
AND PLEASE WELCOME EVERY
FATHER'S NIGHTMARE,
MY LITTLE MOTHER
OF A NEPHEW, HAROLD.
WELL, WE HAD A REAL
WING DING UP THE
LODGE LAST NIGHT.
AND SURVEYING THE
DAMAGE THIS MORNING,
WE MUST HAVE HAD A
PRETTY GOOD TIME.
A LOT OF THE GUYS
HAD HANGOVERS
BUT OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
HAD A LITTLE SOMETHING
EXTRA TO CONTEND WITH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE
STILL DRINKS TO EXCESS.
HE SHOULD START
ACTING HIS AGE.
IF OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
ACTED HIS AGE, HE'D
BE TEN YEARS DEAD.
ANYWAY, HE WOKE UP
AND HE FINDS HE'S GOT
A LIVE BADGER
IN HIS PANTS.
A BADGER?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, LIKE
ONE OF THOSE LITTLE NASTY,
HAIRY FURRY
THINGS WITH TEETH?
YEAH, NOT UNLIKE OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK HIMSELF,
EXCEPT FOR
THE TEETH PART.
WE FIGURE THE BADGER
CRAWLED IN THERE
TO SLEEP.
UNCLE RED, BADGERS
SLEEP IN HOLES
IN THE GROUND.
HOW DID ONE GET IN
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S
BEDROOM?
NO, OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
WAS SLEEPING IN A HOLE
IN THE GROUND.
HE WOKE UP, HE STARTED
WALKING IN TOWARDS
THE LODGE,
AND HE NOTICED A LUMP
IN HIS PANTS THAT WAS
TWITCHING AND WIGGLING.
ALMOST EVERYBODY
GUESSED BADGER.
NOW WE GOT TO FIGURE
OUT A WAY TO GET
IT OUT THERE
WITHOUT STARTLING HIM.
BOY, THAT MUST BE REALLY
FRIGHTENING FOR HIM.
YEAH, AND THE SAME
GOES FOR OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK.
YOU KNOW, BEING ISOLATED
UP HERE I REALLY
MISS TELEVISION.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
WHAT'S HAPPENING ON
WELCOME BACK KOTTER.
IS HORSESHACK
MARRIED YET?
I HOPE SO.
OH, THE TWINS CAN
SLEEP ON THE TABLE
AND AUNT HELEN CAN
SLEEP IN THE CHAIR
UNCLE TOBY JUST
SUCKED DOWN MY BEER
SO HE CAN SLEEP PRETTY
NEAR ANYWHERE AS FAR
AS I'M CONCERNED
JOYCE IS CAMPED OUT
IN THE BOATHOUSE
FRITZ HAS THE
KITCHEN FLOOR
AND THAT BRAND
NEW LITTLE BABY
IS LOOKING KIND
OF DANGEROUS
SO HE CAN SLEEP IN
THE SILVERWARE DRAWER
NOW, MY SISTERS CAN
BUNK IN WITH MOM
I WILL SLEEP IN
AN ORANGE CRATE
AND FRED AND JOHN
AND BRUCE AND LORNE
AND AL AND TOM
AND JOE AND DON
CAN SLEEP IN THE
CAR AND ASPHYXIATE
IT'S OKAY TO
RENT A COTTAGE
BE IN THE SUNSHINE
DOWN BY THE LAKE
BUT TELLING ALL YOUR
FRIENDS AND RELATIVES
BELIEVE ME IS
A BIG MISTAKE
WELL, YOU GOT TO KNOW
SHE'S GOING TO GO NUTS
WHEN YOU TELL
HER WHAT YOU DID.
ABSOLUTELY.
AND I GOT TO TAKE
MY HAT OFF TO YOU.
I DON'T THINK YOU'VE
EVER DONE ANYTHING
THIS STUPID BEFORE.
YOU KNOW, SHE
WAS SCRIMPING AND
SAVING THAT MONEY
FOR A SPECIAL
OCCASION.
SOMEHOW I DON'T THINK
THE OCCASION SHE
HAD IN MIND
WAS YOU LOANING THAT
MONEY TO YOUR BUDDY
SO HE COULD GO AND
PAY FOR A NEW CAP
AND A LINER
FOR HIS TRUCK.
AND YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO TELL HER
AND YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO TELL HER SOON.
THE BANK STATEMENT
COMES OUT EVERY MONTH.
DO IT, DO
IT QUICKLY,
BECAUSE THIS IS NOT
THE MOMENT FOR
YOU TO SHOW
YOU'RE THE LEAST BIT
SCARED OR INDECISIVE.
TAKE HER HANDS,
SIT HER DOWN,
LOOK HER STRAIGHT
IN THE EYE
AND... LIE.
LIE
THE BIGGEST
FIB YOU CAN WRAP
YOUR LIPS AROUND.
YEAH.
WELL, THAT WILL BUY
YOU A LITTLE BIT
OF TIME I GUESS.
YEAH, WELL, OF COURSE
YOU KNOW THE TRUTH
RIGHT NOW
WOULD JUST CLOUD
THE ISSUE.
YOU'VE GOT TO LIE
THROUGH YOUR TEETH.
I WOULD TRY SOMETHING
LIKE CLOSE FRIENDS
OF OURS, HON,
I DON'T WANT TO
SAY THEIR NAMES,
AND THEY DIDN'T EVEN
WANT ME TO KNOW BUT
I FOUND ABOUT IT,
AND I JUST GAVE THEM
THE MONEY JUST THE
WAY YOU WOULD,
YOU KNOW, BUT THEY
MADE ME PROMISE
NOT TO TELL YOU
ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
AND IT HAS A
SENTIMENTAL TWIST.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW?
YOU SAY SOMETHING
LIKE THAT,
SHE'S GOING TO THINK
YOU ARE SO SENSITIVE.
BUT IT WILL ONLY
BUY YOU TIME FOR A
LITTLE BIT OF TIME,
SO YOU GOT
TO MOVE FAST.
TIME FOR TIME, AND TIME
TO GO TELL YOUR BUDDY,
HEY, CALL THAT LOAN
BACK AND GET HIM TO
PAY IT BACK QUICK.
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND SAY YOU'LL
NEVER, NEVER, NEVER,
NEVER DO ANYTHING
THIS STUPID OR SELFISH
OR UNDERHANDED AGAIN.
UNLESS OF COURSE
YOU CAN COME UP
WITH AN EVEN BIGGER
AND BETTER LIE.
WELCOME TO
HANDYMAN CORNER
WHERE EVERYTHING
OLD IS NEW AGAIN.
YOU KNOW, OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK'S BADGER PROBLEM
HAS GIVEN ME AN IDEA
FOR AN INEXPENSIVE
ANIMAL TRAP.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW FOR STARTERS
YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED ONE OF
THESE HOSES HERE,
WHICH THEY USE TO CONNECT
FROM THE DRYER TO
THE OUTSIDE VENT
AND YOU'RE GOING TO
NEED THE OUTSIDE VENT.
YOU'RE IN LUCK, THOUGH,
BOTH OF THESE THINGS
ARE AVAILABLE
IN MOST HOME
LAUNDRY ROOMS.
I WOULD SUGGEST THAT
YOU WAIT A FEW MINUTES
BECAUSE THESE THINGS
HAVE A WAY OF BUILDING UP
A CERTAIN
AMOUNT OF HEAT,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE
DOING SAY A LIVING
ROOM RUG
OR YOUR WINTER UNDERWEAR
IN THERE ON THE HEAVY
DUTY CYCLE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, THE FIRST
THING YOU GOT TO DO
IS YOU GOT TO
CUT THE HOSE IN HALF,
WHICH ACTUALLY YOU
CAN DO BY BITING.
YOU MAY FIND THAT
THERE'S A WIRE IN THERE,
SO I WOULD SUGGEST
THAT TO AVOID BEING
PERMANENTLY FLOSSED,
YOU EITHER USE SOMEBODY
ELSE'S TEETH
OR MAYBE SOME
SNIPS OF SOME KIND.
THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, IF YOU GOT ONE
OF THESE WELCOME MATS
OUT IN FRONT OF YOUR HOUSE,
GET THAT OUT OF THERE
BEFORE IT DOES
ANYMORE DAMAGE.
AND YOU'RE GOING
TO ROLL THAT UP
BECAUSE THAT IN FACT
IS GOING TO BECOME
THE CAGE
TO HOLD THE
TRAPPED ANIMALS.
KIND OF THE WAY WELCOME
MATS ARE USED AT THE HOMES
OF LIFE INSURANCE SALESMEN.
NOW TAKE YOUR
OUTSIDE VENT THING HERE,
YOU WANT TO HOOK THAT UP
TO ONE OF THE HALVES
OF THE DRYER HOSE.
AND THE WAY YOU CAN
CONNECT THOSE IS
KIND OF INTERESTING,
THEY HAVE THESE LITTLE
PLASTIC HOSE CLAMPS,
THEY'RE
UNBELIEVABLE THINGS.
THEY JUST SLIDE --
ONE SLIDES --
THESE SLIDES IN TOGETHER,
YOU PULL THAT UP
RIGHT THERE
AND BY GOLLY
THAT IS SOLID.
YOU JUST WRAP THAT
AROUND THE HOSE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S JUST
OPEN THAT UP A LITTLE BIT
ALL RIGHT, I'M THINKING
MAYBE THIS IS NOT
THE BEST WAY
TO ATTACH THE WHOLE
UNIT TOGETHER.
NO.
I DECIDED TO USE THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET
WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
SO THERE'S OUR TRAP
PRETTY MUCH BUILT.
BUT YOU CAN'T JUST
HAVE IT SITTING OUT
IN THE WOODS LIKE THAT.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE SNEAKY
LIKE THOSE GUYS FROM
THE TAX DEPARTMENT.
SO I'VE DECIDED
TO TAKE A PAGE OUT OF
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S BOOK,
HIDE THE WHOLE TRAP
INSIDE A PAIR OF PANTS.
THERE WE GO.
COME ON OLD FELLA.
LET'S GO.
AND THE ANIMALS AREN'T
GOING TO BE SUSPICIOUS
BECAUSE A PAIR OF PANTS
LYING IN THE WOODS
AROUND POSSUM LODGE IS
A PRETTY COMMON SIGHT.
HOWEVER, THEY ARE
GOING TO NEED SOME SORT
OF A CULINARY INCENTIVE
TO COME UP
THE PANT LEG.
SO I WOULD SUGGEST
THAT YOU SWIPE AN
HOR D'OUVERS TRAY
FROM THE NEXT SOCIAL
FUNCTION THAT YOUR
WIFE DRAGS YOU OVER TO
AND PICK ONE OF
THESE UNITS UP
AND SEPARATE THE
TOOTHPICK FROM THE
HOR D'OUVERS ITSELF.
THEN YOU TAKE THE
PANT LEG, AS I'VE
DONE HERE
AND STICK THE HOR
D'OUVERS UP INSIDE
AND YOU PUSH THE TOOTHPICK
DOWN THROUGH, THROUGH
THE PANT LEG,
THROUGH THE HOSE AND
INTO THE HOR D'OUVERS.
IF YOU DO ONE OF
THOSE EVERY FEW INCHES,
THEN THE ANIMAL WILL
WORK HIS WAY ALL
THE WAY UP
UNTIL YOU GET TO
THE DANGER AREA,
WHICH IS THE CROTCH
OF THE PANTS,
'CAUSE THAT'S WHERE THE
WELCOME MAT CAGE IS.
AND YOU WANT TO USE
MEN'S PANTS ON THIS
BECAUSE IF YOU HAPPEN
TO CATCH AN ANIMAL
THAT YOU DON'T WANT,
YOU CAN JUST
UNZIP THE FLY,
LIFT THE WELCOME FLAP
AND LET THE LITTLE
GUY GO,
LIKE THEY DID IN
THAT MOVIE FREE WILLY.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME,
HAPPY HUNTING.
AND REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
EXCUSE ME.
RED GREEN:
AND SPEAKING OF TRAPS,
WE'RE LIKE THE VON
TRAPP FAMILY HERE,
RANGER GORD HAS GOT
A BADGER TRAP
AND BILL'S GOING TO MAKE
HIMSELF A SNAKE TRAP.
I WANT TO TALK YOU
TO YOU MIDDLE AGE
GUYS OUT THERE.
YOU HEARD ANY GOOD RADIO
STATIONS LATELY?
STATIONS THAT PLAY
GOOD DRIVING MUSIC?
WELL, THERE AREN'T ANY.
IT'S ALL YACKETY-YACK NOW,
NEWS, TALK SHOWS,
RAP MUSIC.
DOESN'T IT MAKE
YOU WONDER,
WHAT HAPPENED
TO OUR MUSIC?
WHERE DID IT GO?
WHERE DID THE MUSIC
THAT DEFINED OUR
GENERATION GO?
WELL, I KNOW
WHERE IT WENT
AND IT'S GOOD
NEWS FOR A CHANGE.
OUR MUSIC IS ALL
SITTING IN THE
CLEARANCE BIN
DOWN AT THE LOCAL
HARDWARE STORE.
YOU CAN ZIP DOWN
THERE RIGHT NOW
AND PICK UP FIVE
MAYBE SIX TAPES
FOR THE PRICE OF
ONE OF THEM CD THINGS.
AND IT'S GREAT MUSIC
WITH WORDS YOU CAN
HEAR AND UNDERSTAND.
WORDS THAT TELL A
STORY WITHOUT A VIDEO.
WHERE WOMEN SING
SONGS ABOUT MEN,
AND MEN SING SONGS
ABOUT WOMEN
AND SURFING
AND HOT RODS.
I KNOW IT'S DEPRESSING
TO SEE THE MUSIC
OF YOUR LIFE
STACKED BESIDE THE
DISCOUNT SHAMPOO
AND THE TWO-FOR-ONE
LIGHTBULBS.
BUT ON THE BRIGHT
SIDE ISN'T IT GREAT
WHEN THE TRULY REWARDING
THINGS IN LIFE
ARE GEARED TO A
PENSIONER'S INCOME?
REMEMBER, I'M
PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, THAT BADGER
IS STILL UP OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK'S PANT LEG.
EVERY TIME IT TWITCHES
THE OLD FELLA GETS TICKLED
SOMETHING FIERCE.
CAN'T YOU GET IT OUT?
WELL, WE TRIED, HAROLD.
DO YOU THINK WE WERE
JUST STANDING THERE
LAUGHING AT HIM
NOT DOING ANYTHING?
WELL, YOU WERE
FOR THE FIRST HOUR.
I KNOW, BUT THEN
HE OFFERED A REWARD
FOR ANYBODY WHO COULD
GET THE BADGER OUT
OF HIS PANTS
WITHOUT STARTLING
IT SO THAT IT
TURNS ON HIM.
SO JUNIOR SINGLETON
THREADED THE BOAT HOOK
UP HIS PANT LEG THERE
AND KIND OF GRABBED
ON AND TRIED TO
PULL IT OUT,
BUT ALL HE GOT WAS OLD
MAN SEDGEWICK'S
UNDERWEAR.
WRECKED OUR
BEST BOAT HOOK.
OH, OH, UNCLE RED,
OH, I GOT AN IDEA.
I WOULD TRY
TO LURE IT OUT.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
WE DID THAT HAROLD.
BUSTER HADFIELD
CAUGHT A FEMALE
BADGER
AND HE SET THAT UP JUST
OUTSIDE OF THE LEFT PANT
LEG OF OLD MAN SEDGEWICK.
THE TWO OF THEM STARTED
MAKING SOUNDS TO
EACH OTHER
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
THE FEMALE RUNS RIGHT
UP THE RIGHT PANT LEG.
SO NOW HE'S GOT LIKE
TWO BADGERS UP
HIS PANTS?
YES, AND HE ISN'T
GLAD TO SEE US.
BOY, THIS HAS
GOT TO END SOMEHOW.
WELL, WE'LL RUN OUT
OF ANIMALS EVENTUALLY.
WINSTON ROTHCHILD HERE
OF ROTHCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES,
REMINDING YOU, IF YOU
CAN'T BANK ON YOUR TANK,
WE'LL TAKE IT
FROM RANK TO SWANK.
WE'RE UP HERE
AT FIRE TOWER 13
WITH RANGER GORD,
A MAN LOOKING WHO'S
BEEN LOOKING OUT
OVER THE FOREST
FOR A LONG,
LONG TIME.
16 YEARS ON THE
JOB, RED, AND NOT
A SINGLE DAY OFF.
NOT ONE SICK DAY,
NOT ONE VACATION DAY
AND NOT ONE THANK YOU
FROM ANYONE, ANYWHERE,
ANYTIME, EVER.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
FAIR ENOUGH.
WELL, THEN, GORD, ON
BEHALF OF EVERYONE,
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
OUT OVER THE FOREST.
YOU'RE MOST WELCOME.
OH, ALL RIGHT
THEN.
YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.
NO, THAT'S FINE.
THAT'S FINE.
I SAID THAT'S FINE.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, TODAY IN HONOUR
OF OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S
PANTS,
I THOUGHT I WOULD
TALK ABOUT BADGERS.
NOW I'VE GOT A BADGER
OVER HERE THAT I
TRAPPED LAST WEEK.
THOUGHT YOU MIGHT LIKE
TO TAKE A LOOK AT HIM.
NO KIDDING.
YEAH.
WOW.
EXCELLENT.
YEAH.
COME ON UP HAROLD.
NOW A FULL GROWN
BADGER CAN GROW UP
TO TWO FEET LONG.
OH, LOOKS LIKE HE GAVE
YOU THE SLIP THERE, GORD.
OH, NO, THERE HE
IS RIGHT THERE.
I'VE NAMED HIM TIGER.
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A BADGER.
DON'T WORRY HE
WON'T HURT YOU.
NO, NO, NO, I DON'T
THINK THAT'S A
BADGER AT ALL.
LOOK AT HIM.
LOOK AT HIM!
LOOK AT HIM
TRYING TO ESCAPE.
LOOK AT HIM.
HUH?
IS THAT
FUN OR WHAT?
HEY, YOU KNOW, I WAS
THINKING OF STARTING
A BADGER CLUB,
LETTING YOU GUYS JOIN,
AND YOU CAN HAVE ALL
YOUR CONVENTIONS
UP HERE, HUH?
HERE WE GO.
THERE'S WHAT A
BADGER LOOKS LIKE.
A BADGER?
OH, YEAH, THAT'S A
BADGER RIGHT THERE.
THEN I MUST HAVE
CAPTURED A WOLVERINE.
STAND BACK!
GET BACK HAROLD!
GET BACK!
POTHOLES BY ME.
POTHOLES, POTHOLES
EVERYWHERE,
EVERYWHERE I GO.
IN THE CEILING UP ABOVE
AND IN THE FLOOR BELOW.
IT SEEMS THAT I SEE
POTHOLES EVERYWHERE
I LOOK.
MY WIFE SURE
TAKES IT BADLY
WHEN YOU TELL HER
SHE CAN'T COOK.
RED GREEN:
EVERYBODY RELAX,
IT'S TIME FOR
ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
WHAT THE HECK IS
HE DOING TODAY?
OH MY GOSH.
LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF THAT THING.
OH BOY.
IT'S NOT BILL --
BILL, DON'T HURT IT.
DON'T HURT IT.
WELL, MAYBE HE'LL
GET THE LAWN CUT.
OH, I SEE.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS ONE OF
THOSE INTERESTING
SNAKE TRAP THINGS
THAT THEY'RE NOT AS
DANGEROUS AS THEY LOOK.
WHAT HE DOES IS
HE GOT THE BOARD UP
AGAINST THE STOOL THERE
AND THEN YOU GOT
THAT LITTLE PIECE
OF EAVESTROUGH.
AND WHAT HAPPENS IS
THE SNAKE COMES UP
THE BOARD, ALL RIGHT,
AND HE GOES UP AND HE
GOES INTO THE PIECE
OF EAVESTROUGH
AND HE CRAWLS ALONG
IN THERE
AND ONCE HE GETS PAST
THE ROPE,
HIS OWN WEIGHT WILL
TIP THE EAVESTROUGH
AND THE WHOLE SNAKE
AND THE WHOLE DEAL
WILL FALL DOWN
INTO THE GARBAGE CAN
AND YOU CAN'T
GET OUT OF THERE
AND YOU GOT 'EM.
NOW THE TRICK IS YOU
GOT TO PUT SOME KIND
OF BAIT IN THERE
FOR THE SNAKE,
SOMETHING TO ATTRACT HIM.
NO SNAKE WOULD GO IN --
THERE IT IS,
THERE'S YOUR
SNAKE BAIT.
TO GET HIM TO
GO IN THERE.
NOW TO ME THIS LOOKS
LIKE A DOZEN LARGE EGGS
BUT THEN THEY CAN'T
CHARGE 15 BUCKS FOR A
DOZEN LARGE EGGS, CAN THEY?
MAKE THAT 11.
MAKE THAT 10.
MEANWHILE WE DIDN'T
NOTICE THIS,
BUT THE SNAKE IS
ON HIS WAY UP.
SO I TELL YOU THAT SNAKE
BAIT WORKS, DOESN'T IT?
WE WERE TRYING TO
GET ONE OUT OF THERE
WE CAN PUT INTO THE PIPE.
MEANWHILE THE SNAKE IS
GETTING RIGHT UP CLOSE
TO THE STOOL THERE.
AND OH, OH, I THINK
BILL'S GOT ONE.
THERE WE GO.
OH.
AND HE PUSHES THE ROPE
OFF AND NOW WE GOT --
OH BOY.
I GOT THE SNAKE BAIT.
ALMOST CALLED IT AN EGG.
BUT BILL PICKED UP
THE SNAKE THINKING
IT WAS THE ROPE
AND HE TRIES TO TIE
THAT ON THERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND
OF A KNOT YOU WOULD
USE WITH A SNAKE,
I NEVER WENT THAT FAR
IN BOY SCOUTS,
BUT I DO KNOW ONE THING,
I WOULDN'T MESS AROUND --
BILL, THAT'S A SNAKE.
BILL, SNAKE.
YEAH.
NO.
NO, DON'T WANT IT.
DON'T WANT IT.
WHERE DID IT GO?
WHERE IS IT?
OH, THERE IT IS.
HERE IT IS.
OH IT'S SAFE, IT'S GONE
TO A WARM DARK PLACE, BILL.
WOW, LOOK AT THAT,
THAT'S SOME INTERESTING
MOVES FOR A MAN HIS AGE.
HERE IS SOMETHING I'VE
ALWAYS WANTED TO DO.
GO FOR IT RED.
RED GREEN: STAY TUNED.
WINSTON IS COMING UP
WITH HIS BIG HOSE
AND HAROLD WILL
BE HERE DOING WHAT
HAROLD DOES BEST.
WELL, THINGS HAVE GONE
FROM BAD TO WORSE
WITH THE BADGERS IN OLD
MAN SEDGEWICK'S PANTS.
YOU MEAN THEY
STARTED TO MATE?
NO, HAROLD, BUT
THAT'S OUR FAULT.
YOU KNOW, WHEN WE SENT
THAT FEMALE UP THERE,
WE THOUGHT THE FIRST
ONE WAS A MALE.
SO NOW WHAT WE
GOT IS TWO FEMALE
BADGERS IN HIS PANTS
HAVING A KNOCK 'EM DOWN
DRAG 'EM OUT FIGHT
AND OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
IS CAUGHT IN THE MIDDLE.
OH BOY, UNCLE RED,
HE MUST BE GOING MENTAL.
WELL, OKAY,
MORE MENTAL.
WELL, HE'S NOT
SAYING TOO MUCH
BUT HE IS MAKING THE
MOST UNUSUAL FACIAL
EXPRESSIONS
I HAVE EVER SEEN.
[ LAUGHING ]
AND I'VE SEEN SOME
HUMMERS, TRUST ME.
ANYWAY, AT THIS POINT
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK IS
GETTING PRETTY UPSET.
WOW HE MUST REALLY BE
AT THE END OF HIS ROPE.
WELL, THE BADGERS ARE
AT THE END OF HIS
EVERYTHING.
HERE IS A NEW JOKE
I JUST MADE UP.
KNOCK KNOCK.
WHO'S THERE?
NO ONE.
NO ONE WHO?
JUST NO ONE.
EVER.
[ LAUGHING ]
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE PROGRAM.
CLAIMING TO BE AN
EXPERT THIS WEEK
WITH MY UNCLE RED
IS MR. DALTON
HUMPHREY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
OUR FIRST LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS:
IT'S FROM
PORTLAND, OREGON.
DEAR EXPERTS, WHAT WOULD
BE AN APPROPRIATE GIFT
FOR MY WIFE ON OUR
25TH ANNIVERSARY?
I WOULD RECOMMEND AN
OLYMPIC MEDAL FOR ENDURANCE.
IT WOULD HAVE
TO BE A SILVER MEDAL
BECAUSE THE 25TH
ANNIVERSARY IS SILVER.
GOLD IS ACTUALLY 50
AND THEN 60 IS A DIAMOND
AND 100 I BELIEVE
IS KRYPTONITE.
YEAH, I'D SUGGEST
A TOASTER.
A TOASTER
MR. HUMPHREY?
YOU'D CELEBRATE LIKE
A QUARTER CENTURY
OF WEDDING BLISS
WITH A TOASTER?
WELL, I'M TALKING
A FOUR SLICER.
YOU KNOW, THAT SEEMS
A TAD CHINTZY TO
ME, DALTON.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THIS
GIFT HAS GOT TO BE
RIGHT UP THERE
WITH THE WEDDING RING.
YOU DID GET HER
A WEDDING RING,
DIDN'T YOU MR. HUMPHREY?
NO, I COULDN'T.
NO, NO, MONEY WAS
TIED UP IN INVENTORY.
THE BYTHEWEE MOTEL
CLOSED UP
AND I BOUGHT ALL THEIR
STOVES, WASHERS, DRYERS
AND BAR FRIDGES,
SO I GAVE
ANNE-MARIE A WASHER.
A WASHING MACHINE IS
NOT A VERY ROMANTIC
WEDDING GIFT.
NO, NO, NO, NO, A
WASHER FROM A GARDEN HOSE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
NO, NO, NO, I TOLD HER,
I SAID ANNE-MARIE
THIS IS JUST AN
IMITATION RUBBER WASHER,
IT'S OLD AND IT'S
CRACKED BUT FOR NOW
IT'S OUR WEDDING RING
AND SOME DAY I WILL GET
YOU A PROPER ONE WHEN
I'M SUCCESSFUL.
SO SHE'S STILL
WAITING, HUH?
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN,
THOUGH, ACTUALLY,
BECAUSE YOU ARE
SUCH A SUCCESS,
YOU KNOW, AND THE HUMPHREY
EVERYTHING STORE
IS DOING SO WELL, OH,
YES, CONGRATS, YES.
HAROLD, I AM A MAN
OF MY WORD, HAROLD.
AND ON OUR 20TH ANNIVERSARY
I GOT ANNE-MARIE A BRAND
NEW WASHER,
PAINTED GOLD
AND EVERYTHING.
AND WHAT DID
SHE SAY TO THAT?
WELL, NOTHING.
IT KINDA SURPRISED ME, TOO.
SHE JUST BURST INTO
TEARS AND RAN UPSTAIRS.
OH COURSE WOMEN CRY
WHEN THEY'RE HAPPY.
SHE DOESN'T SOUND
TOO HAPPY TO ME
ABOUT THIS RUBBER WASHER
WEDDING RING-THING.
OH, NO, NO, SHE WAS.
THE NEXT DAY SHE
CLEANED OUT OUR
BANK ACCOUNT
AND BOUGHT HERSELF A
BRAND NEW CAR TO MATCH IT.
THEN IT WAS YOUR TURN
TO BURST INTO TEARS.
WELL MEN CRY WHEN
THEY'RE HAPPY, RIGHT?
WE'RE HERE WITH
ENTREPRENEUR WINSTON ROTHCHILD
TO GET HIS BUSINESS ADVICE
FOR THE SMALL BUSINESSMAN.
NOW, WINSTON, WHAT'S
THE BEST WAY TO GET
LOYAL CUSTOMERS?
OH, HONESTY RED.
YEAH.
TOTAL HONESTY AND
COMPLETE SINCERITY.
REALLY?
NO.
HAH, HAH, HAH,
HAH, HAH.
BOY YOU HAD ME
GOING THERE.
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
NO, ACTUALLY WHAT YOU
WANT TO DO IS YOU WANT
TO PICK UP ONE
OF THOSE HELP
YOURSELF BOOKS.
IT'S CALLED HOW TO HAVE
MORE OF EVERYTHING
BY WALLY HIMLER.
AND IN THERE YOU
LEARN THE SECRET,
THE NICH-EE PHILOSOPHY.
OH, SURE, NEITZSCHE,
THE GERMAN PHILOSOPHER.
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NICH-EE.
LIKE WHEN YOU GOT
A PARTICULAR NICH-EE
AND YOU WANT
TO FILL IT.
NO, NO, THAT'S
NICHE MARKETING.
NICHE?
YEAH.
I THOUGHT IT
WAS NICH-EE.
NO.
OH, WELL, I GUESS NEXT
TIME I SHOULD GET
THE AUDIO TAPES.
WHAT IT MEANS IS YOU
GOT TO SPECIALIZE, EH?
YOU GOT TO ADD EXTRA
THINGS TO YOUR SERVICE.
YOU KNOW, DO THINGS
THAT NO ONE OUT
THERE IS DOING,
I MEAN, IF RUNNING
A SUCCESSFUL SEWAGE
SUCKING SERVICE
WAS AS SIMPLE AS
JUMPING DOWN SOME DARK
STINKY HOLE WITH A HOSE,
EVERYBODY WOULD BE
DOING IT, WOULDN'T THEY?
OH, YEAH, ONE GIANT
LEAP FOR MANKIND.
LIKE, FOR INSTANCE,
I'M THE ONLY ONE
IN THE AREA
WHO OFFERS EXTRA
SERVICES, EH?
LIKE, FOR INSTANCE,
DID YOU KNOW THAT I
WILL REMOVE DEAD ANIMALS
FROM YOUR DRAINAGE
SYSTEM FREE OF CHARGE?
WOW.
OH, YEAH.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE HOW
MANY CUSTOMERS FIND THAT
ATTRACTIVE, EH?
WAIT A MINUTE.
I'M JUST THINKING
HERE, WINSTON.
HAVE YOU EVER REMOVED
A BADGER FROM A
DRAINAGE SYSTEM,
SAY FROM A PIPE THE
SIZE OF A PANT LEG?
OH, THAT'S NOTHING.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I ONCE SUCKED A DEAD
MOOSE OUT OF A
CHEMICAL TOILET.
BUILT MY REPUTATION
ON THAT ONE.
SORT OF STICKS IN
PEOPLE'S MINDS,
YOU KNOW?
I WOULD THINK
SO, YEAH.
I'M WONDERING IF MAYBE
YOU CAN TAKE A DETOUR
PAST OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK'S PLACE.
I THINK HE MIGHT HAVE
A LITTLE JOB FOR YOU.
OH, NO PROBLEM.
YOU SEE, NOW THAT'S
HOW I GET MY JOBS, EH,
I FILL A NICHE.
NO, THIS IS MORE
OF A NICH-EE.
WELL, WE MANAGED TO GET
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK SAFELY
AWAY FROM THOSE BADGERS.
HE WAITED UNTIL
THEY FELL ASLEEP
AND HE JUST SLIPPED
THE PANTS OFF.
WELL, HOW DID HE DO THAT
WITHOUT DISTURBING THEM?
WELL, THEY WERE
IN THERE SO LONG,
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK LOST
A LOT OF WEIGHT.
HE WENT FROM SKIN
AND BONE TO JUST BONE.
WELL, THAT'S EXCELLENT.
BECAUSE NOW THE BADGERS
CAN ASSIMILATE THEMSELVES
BACK INTO THE WOODS
AND JOIN THE REST OF
THE ANIMAL KINGDOM.
THAT COULD TAKE
A WHILE HAROLD.
THE SIGHT OF OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK WITH NO
PANTS ON
PRETTY MUCH CLEARED
THE AREA OF WILDLIFE.
WELL, OF COURSE YOU KNOW,
UNCLE RED, NONE OF THIS
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED
IF YOU WERE PARTYING
RESPONSIBLY.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH MEETI TIME, UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN
A LITTLE WHILE, HAROLD.
OKAY.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND AFTER WHAT HAPPENED
TO OLD MAN SEDGEWICK,
I THINK MAYBE WE SHOULD
THROW OUT SOME OF MY
OLD BELL BOTTOM PANTS.
I GOT A PAIR THERE
THAT A RHINO COULD
GET INTO.
HEY, THERE'S AN IDEA,
WE'LL GIVE THEM
TO YOUR SISTER.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
STAND UP.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
ALL RIGHT, MANY OF YOU
MAY NOW THAT WE'VE BEEN --