WELL, I MEAN EVERYBODY WHO
PREFERS SPORTS TO, SAY,
CONVERSATION.
THE PROBLEM IS THEY'RE
SO DARNED EXPENSIVE.
WHAT IF I COULD SHOW YOU
THAT YOU COULD HAVE
A BIG SCREEN TV
FOR UNDER $10.00?
LIKE, SAY, $9.95.
THAT'S HOW MUCH IT COSTS FOR
A SET OF THESE CASTORS.
NOW YOU JUST JAM THESE BABIES
INTO THE BOTTOM OF YOUR
FAVOURITE CHAIR.
MIGHT WANT TO PUT A LITTLE
GREASE ON THERE FIRST,
BECAUSE IF THEY
SQUEAK AT ALL,
YOUR MOTHER'S GOING TO FORCE
YOU TO TAKE A LITTLE
CASTOR OIL.
NOW, YOU MAY BE SITTING
THERE THINKING,
HOW DOES A SET OF CASTORS
GET ME A BIG SCREEN TV?
WELL, THAT TELLS ME I HAVE
TWO THINGS THAT YOU
DON'T HAVE...
IMAGINATION...
AND A CROOKED FLOOR.
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE THAT.
BIG, BIG CHANGES UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
YOU PROBABLY NOTICED HOW NEAT
AND TIDY EVERYTHING IS.
THAT'S BECAUSE WE'RE NOT
JUST A LODGE ANY MORE.
HAROLD'S ALSO TRYING TO TURN
US INTO A BED AND BREAKFAST.
HE'S CALLING IT THE SLEEPY
POSSUM BED AND BREAKFAST.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S GONNA WORK.
I WOULD BE VERY WARY
OF EATING BREAKFAST
AT ANY PLACE THAT HAD THE
WORD POSSUM IN THE NAME.
[bell ringing]
OH, FRONT, FRONT.
OUR FIRST GUEST
HAS ARRIVED.
WHY ARE YOU TELLING
ME, HAROLD?
I'M NOT YOUR FRONT MAN.
C'MON, UNCLE RED.
IF THIS IS
GOING TO WORK,
WE NEED TO HAVE
PROFESSIONAL SERVICE.
YOU NEED TO HAVE
PROFESSIONAL HELP.
WE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT RUNNING A BED
AND BREAKFAST.
IT'S EASY.
YOU JUST HAVE
TO LIKE PEOPLE.
OH, GREAT.
IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE GOING TO PRACTICE.
I'VE GOT
A GUINEA PIG.
OUR FIRST GUEST IS
GOING TO BE à la maison.
AL WHO?
A la maison --
mais --
HE'S STAYING FOR FREE.
OH, MIKE.
BONJOUR, MONSIEUR.
AND WELCOME TO THE
POSSUM BED AND BREAKFAST.
YOUR ROOM AWAITS.
WHAT A DUMP!
GET MY BAG!
OH, BOY,
GET HIS BAG!
HIS BAG,
GET HIS BAG.
HIS BAG.
OKAY,
I'LL GET IT.
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
TODAY'S WINNER RECEIVES AN
ASSORTMENT OF LOOSE CHANGE
FROM McGINTY'S
TRAMPOLINE PARK
WHERE EVERYTHING BOUNCES,
INCLUDING THE CHEQUES.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
THINGIES, WINSTON.
OKAY, MR. GREEN,
YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET WINSTON TO SAY
THIS WORD...
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND... GO!
OKAY, WINSTON,
THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT YOU GO ON,
ON A SATURDAY NIGHT.
A PUMP-OUT.
OKAY, NO, THIS IS
WHEN YOU GO OUT
AND YOU'RE DRESSED UP,
MAYBE TAKE SOME FLOWERS.
FUNERAL?
NO. OKAY, NO.
IF A WOMAN AGREED
TO GO OUT WITH YOU,
THAT WOULD BE
CALLED A...
MIRACLE.
I KNOW!
YOU'VE GOT A
CALENDAR IN YOUR SHOP.
WHAT'S ON IT?
A PICTURE
OF MIKE'S MOM.
ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
MR. GREEN.
OKAY, WINSTON,
TODAY IS THE SIXTH.
YOU COULD ALSO
THE SIXTH IS...
OH, MY ANNIVERSARY!
YEAH, IT WAS 12 YEARS AGO
TODAY I GOT MY SEPTIC TRUCK.
IT WAS A DATE
WITH DESTINY.
THERE WE GO!
[quirky upbeat music]
TODAY ON TALKING
ANIMALS,
LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER, ED FRID,
HAS BROUGHT IN A
SURPRISE ANIMAL FOR US.
C'MON UP HERE, ED.
COME ON. COME ON.
WELL, OKAY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WHAT WE HAVE HERE
IS THE SINGLE MOST
DANGEROUS ANIMAL
IN THE WORLD.
WOW!
KIND OF A SMALL
CAGE, ISN'T IT?
IS THIS THING ANY MORE
DANGEROUS THAN A CROCODILE?
OH, YEAH.
MORE DANGEROUS
THAN A COBRA?
YEAH, I KNOW ALL
THE ANIMALS, RED.
I DON'T JUST MAKE
ARBITRARY CHOICES
AND TRY TO BACK THEM UP WITH
OUTRAGEOUS CLAIMS, YOU KNOW?
NO. I'M NOT
SAYING THAT --
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
BEING AN ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICER
BEFORE YOU START SHOOTING
OFF YOUR MOUTH, HUH?
YEAH, MAYBE AFTER YOU'VE
BEEN MAULED BY A PUMA.
YOU EVER BEEN
MAULED BY A PUMA?
THAT'S NOT THE
POINT, RED!
THE POINT IS, AT ANY TIME,
I COULD BE
MAULED BY A PUMA
AND DRAGGED
INTO ITS CAVE.
WELL, WE ALL
HAVE PROBLEMS.
I OFTEN GET DRAGGED
INTO A MALL.
JOKES DON'T WORK
IN THE ANIMAL
KINGDOM, RED.
OKAY, FINE.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU
JUST SHOW US WHATEVER
YOU'VE GOT HERE.
OKAY, WELL, THAT'S
WHAT I'M TRYING TO DO.
I DIDN'T DRAG THIS
DANGEROUS ANIMAL
ALL THE WAY OVER HERE
TO NOT SHOW IT TO YOU.
SO STAND BACK
AND, YOU KNOW, DON'T
MAKE ANY SUDDEN MOVES.
LOOK OUT!
ED, THAT'S A
HAMSTER.
OH, I KNOW.
YOU'RE SAYING HAMSTERS
ARE DANGEROUS?
OTHER ANIMALS PICK
THEM UP AND THROW
THEM AT YOU?
YOU KNOW,
WHEN I WAS A CHILD,
I HAD A HAMSTER.
MISTER WINKLEBOTTOM
WAS VERY CUTE.
OKAY. I SEE.
YOU BLAME YOUR HAMSTER
FOR YOU BECOMING AN
ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER.
AND ISN'T IT
NICE FOR YOU
TO BE ABLE TO
PUT EVERYONE'S LIFE
INTO A NICE, NEAT
LITTLE COMPARTMENT
LIKE THAT, HUH?
SO YOU BLAME YOUR
HAMSTER FOR YOU
BECOMING AN --
OKAY. YES. YES.
YES! YES!
AND PARENTS, DON'T GET
YOUR CHILDREN HAMSTERS.
GET THEM AN EDUCATION.
GET THEM
AN OFFICE JOB.
A THERAPIST.
DON'T YOU JUST HATE
GETTING SPEEDING
TICKETS?
THEY COST YOU MONEY.
MAKES YOU LATE FOR WHEREVER
IT WAS YOU WERE GOING.
THAT MAKES YOU
SPEED EVEN MORE.
THEN THEY NAIL YOU AGAIN,
AND THE FINES GO
HIGHER AND HIGHER.
FINALLY, YOU LOSE
YOUR LICENSE
AND END UP SPENDING
30 DAYS IN THE SLAMMER.
YOU KNOW, IT'S ALMOST
ENOUGH TO MAKE YOU
WANT TO SLOW DOWN.
SO I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
YOU CAN GET A WAY
WITH SPEEDING
AS LONG AS THE GUY IN FRONT
OF YOU IS ALSO SPEEDING.
SPEEDING IS THE EXACT OPPOSITE
OF A WEDDING NIGHT...
YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE FIRST.
SO WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS GET YOURSELF A BUNCH OF
LARGE CARDBOARD BOXES,
MAYBE FROM A REFRIGERATOR
OR A THIGH-MASTER
OR WHATEVER.
MAKE YOURSELF A FAKE
CAR OUT OF IT, HUH?
THEN YOU CAN PAINT IT
ANY COLOUR YOU WANT
AND THEN HOLD IT TOGETHER
WITH THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON,
WHICH ALSO DOUBLES
AS CHROME.
AND GEAR THE
TYPE OF CAR
TO YOUR PERSONAL
ARTISTIC ABILITY...
IF YOU'RE USELESS,
MAKE IT A RUSSIAN CAR;
IF YOU'RE GOOD,
MAKE IT A FRENCH CAR.
THE CAR WON'T RUN,
SO ACTUALLY BRITISH
IS A PERFECT CHOICE.
NOW, THIS MAY NOT LOOK
LIKE A CAR TO YOU AND I,
BUT LUCKILY, WE ONLY
HAVE TO FOOL THE COPS.
BESIDES, THE CAR
WILL BE SPEEDING,
SO IT'S GOING TO BE
HARD TO TELL.
AND THE WAY WE'RE
GOING TO MAKE IT SPEED
IS BY SITTING IT ON
TOP OF THIS PLATFORM
THAT I GOT HOOKED UP ON
TOP OF THE POSSUM VAN.
SO THE CAR'LL BE GOING THE
SAME SPEED THAT I DO, SEE?
ONLY IT'LL BE THE
ONE THAT GETS PULLED OVER.
OKAY, NOW,
THE PULLING OVER PART,
THAT'S A LITTLE TRICKY.
I GOT THIS PUSHBAR SECURED
TO THE ONE END THERE
SO IT WILL PIVOT
AND PUSH THE CAR OFF.
AND THIS LATCH HOLDS
IT BACK LIKE A GATE
UNTIL THE TIME COMES.
I JUST GOT TO DECIDE
WHAT SIZE SPRING TO USE
THAT'LL HAVE ENOUGH JAM TO
PUSH THE CAR OFF THERE,
BUT NOT SEND HER INTO
THE NEXT COUNTY.
NOW, I'M SURE THERE'S A
MATHEMATICAL FORMULA
FOR FIGURING THAT OUT,
BUT I PREFER
TRIAL AND ERROR.
IT'S QUICKER,
IT'S MORE FUN,
AND IT'S REALLY
ONE OF THE UPSIDES
OF HAVING
SOCIALIZED MEDICINE.
OKAY, I'VE DECIDED
TO GO WITH
THE MEDIUM SIZED
COIL SPRING THERE.
I'VE ALSO SET
HERE NOW THOUGH.
AND I CONTROL
THE PUSHBAR
WITH THIS HIGH-TECH
LATCH RELEASE, EH?
NOW WHEN I COME
SPEEDING OVER THE HILL,
THE COPS'LL WAVE
THE CAR OVER.
ALL'S I DO IS
PULL ON THE STRING.
THEY GET A LOAD
OF CARDBOARD,
AND I GET OUT OF DODGE.
THIS MAY BE MY
SMARTEST IDEA YET.
OR MAYBE IT'S JUST
TOO CLOSE TO CALL.
TAILGATING.
[laughter and applause]
[quirky upbeat music]
I NEEDED SOMETHING FROM THE
HARDWARE STORE THE OTHER DAY,
SO I ASKED MY WIFE
IF SHE'D LIKE ME
TO PICK UP ANYTHING
FOR HER WHILE I WAS OUT.
SHE SAID,
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I'LL GO WITH YOU.
OKAY.
SO THE NEXT
THING YOU KNOW,
WE'RE WELL IN TO
OUR SECOND HOUR
AT THE MALL,
LOOKING FOR SHOES.
NOW, THERE WAS A
TIME IN OUR MARRIAGE
WHEN I WOULD'VE
SAID SOMETHING NEGATIVE
ABOUT HOW A MAN WHO
ONLY NEEDS DRYWALL SCREWS
ENDS UP GIVING OPINIONS ON
20 OR 30 PAIRS
OF SLING-BACK PUMPS
THAT ALL PRETTY MUCH LOOK
IDENTICAL TO HIM.
WELL, I DON'T DO
THAT ANYMORE.
NO, I JUST FOLLOWED
ALONG QUIETLY,
THINKING WHAT
A GREAT GUY I AM
TO BE SHOPPING
WITH MY WIFE
AND NOT EVEN
COMPLAINING ABOUT IT.
BUT APPARENTLY
I WAS WRONG.
SHE TOOK ME ASIDE
BY THE WIENIE WAGON
AND POINTED OUT
THAT MY ATTITUDE
WAS DESTROYING THE ENTIRE
SHOPPING EXPERIENCE.
SHE SAID, THIS IS SUPPOSED
TO BE FUN, ISN'T IT?
AND I NODDED INSTEAD
OF TELLING THE TRUTH.
AND THEN IT
HIT ME, OKAY.
WHEN YOU HAVE
A LIFE PARTNER,
IT'S NOT ENOUGH
TO DO THINGS WITH THEM.
YOU HAVE TO WANT
OTHERWISE IT'S JUST
NOT GONNA WORK.
SO IT'S NOT ENOUGH THAT
I GO SHOPPING WITH MY WIFE;
I HAVE TO WANT
TO SHOPPING WITH MY WIFE.
I UNDERSTAND THAT NOW,
AND THAT'S WHY I SIGNED UP
FOR ACTING LESSONS.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
WHEN SEPTICS GO BAD,
IT'S NOBODY'S FAULT.
IT JUST MEANS YOUR SEWAGE
HAS COME TO A HALT.
CALL ROTHSCHILD'S.
WE'LL GIVE IT
OUR FULL-SCALE ASSAULT.
AND UNLOCK THE TREASURE THAT'S
TRAPPED IN YOUR VAULT.
WELL, THE BED AND BREAKFAST
ISN'T WORKING OUT SO GOOD.
I THINK HAROLD
MAY HAVE BITTEN OFF
MORE THAN HE CAN CHEW,
EVEN WITH THOSE TEETH.
UNCLE RED!
I'VE GOTTA GO
BACK INTO TOWN
AND GET SOME MORE
GROCERIES FOR MIKE.
YOU'D THINK A GUY
WHO EATS HIS MEALS
OFF A TIN TRAY
WOULDN'T BE SO
DEMANDING.
AM I SUPPOSED
TO LOOK AFTER MIKE
WHILE YOU'RE GONE?
I'LL JUST BE
A FEW MINUTES.
I GAVE HIM THE BELL TO RING
IN CASE HE WANTS ANYTHING.
BUT I DON'T THINK
HE'LL BOTHER YOU.
[bell ringing]
BYE.
OH, THANK YOU,
HAROLD.
DIDN'T YOU HEAR
ME TINKLING?
[laughter]
I TRY NOT TO
LISTEN, MIKE.
WHAT KIND OF AN
ESTABLISHMENT IS
THIS ANYWAY?
I THOUGHT THIS WAS
A FOUR-STAR HOTEL.
IF YOU DON'T GET
A LONGER BATH ROBE,
IT'LL BE FOUR
STARS AND A MOON.
I EXPECT
EXCELLENT SERVICE,
AND I'M GONNA STAY
HERE TILL I GET IT.
[bell ringing]
NO! NO!
GIVE ME THE BELL!
STOP BEING
A DINK.
AH, GEEZ.
IT'S FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
I MEAN, THIS IS
AN EXPERIMENT
TO SEE IF YOU'VE
GOT WHAT IT TAKES.
AND IF I ENJOY
THE EXPERIENCE,
I WILL INFORM MY FRIENDS.
YOUR FRIENDS?
THIS IS A
BED AND BREAKFAST,
NOT A HALFWAY HOUSE.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT HAROLD?
I MEAN, HE'S PUT
HIS HEART AND SOUL
INTO MAKING THIS
BED AND BREAKFAST WORK.
AT LEAST WE SHOULD
GIVE A TRY FOR HIM,
DON'T YOU THINK?
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
BUT IT'S A BED
AND BREAKFAST, OKAY?
YOU GO BACK TO BED,
AND I'LL GO MAKE
SOME BREAKFAST.
CAN I HAVE
THE BELL?
DO YOU PROMISE
NOT TO RING IT?
I SWEAR.
OKAY.
YOU'RE NOT
GONNA RING IT?
NOPE.
YOU BETTER
NOT RING IT.
BETTER NOT.
I WON'T.
HE'S RIGHT, YOU KNOW?
Red (voiceover):
YOU YOUNGSTERS MIGHT
WANNA WATCH THIS BECAUSE --
STAY AWAY IF YOU SEE YOUR
DAD WORKING ON SOMETHING.
LIKE I SAY, WALTER SHOULD
STAND OFF TO THE SIDE.
BUT INSTEAD --
I WAS ADJUSTING THE CHOKE,
HE'S GOTTA GET
RIGHT DOWN.
AND HERE, AGAIN,
YOU WANNA STAY BACK.
SO THEN HE GETS THE IDEA
MAYBE HE'LL PULL START IT.
MIGHT BE A LITTLE SAFER.
WALTER'S GOT
THE BIG MUSCLES.
MAYBE TOO MANY MUSCLES.
OKAY, THAT'S NOT
REALLY HELPING.
DON'T WORRY.
WE'VE STILL GOT THE CORD.
I'M THINKING
ANOTHER WAY TO GO,
RATHER THAN PULLING
THE LAWN MOWER BY HAND,
IS IF WE COULD EXTEND
THE STARTER CORD
AND THEN ATTACH IT TO
A BUCKET FULL OF BRICKS.
AND WE LIVE ON THE EDGE
OF THE ESCARPMENT THERE.
THAT WOULD GIVE HER
A GOOD JOLT THERE.
YEAH. JUST --
OKAY, I'M ALL SET.
YEAH, FIRE HER OVER.
FIRE HER OVER.
THAT SHOULD
START HER UP.
BUT APPARENTLY DIDN'T
HAVE MY FOOT, UH,
HELD DOWN STRONG
ENOUGH ONTO THE MOWER,
AND THEN, OH, BOY.
OH, BOY. OKAY.
WALTER, GRAB THE --
GRAB THE LAWN MOWER!
GRAB IT! GRAB IT!
OKAY, SO --
OKAY. OKAY.
WE'LL TRY SOMETHING ELSE.
WALTER'S UP IN
THE TREE WITH THE MOWER.
GRAB THE HANDLE
AND DROP THE MOWER,
AND MAYBE THE GRAVITY
WILL HELP US THAT WAY.
AND THERE SHE GOES!
UH-OH!
OH! OH!
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE END JUSTIFIES THE MEANS.
THE LAWN MOWER'S RUNNING,
AND BOY, IT'S A LITTLE BIT
COOLER IN MY HAT.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL GO
FIX MY HAT,
AND WALTER, WHY DON'T
YOU GO CUT THE LAWN?
AWAY YOU GO.
[applause]
[quirky upbeat music]
NO, NOT QUITE READY
FOR YOU YET.
JUST GO UP TO THE
END OF THE LAKE THERE
AND COME BACK.
JUST GO ONE TIME.
OKAY? GOOD.
YOU KNOW,
IF THERE'S ONE THING
MIDDLE AGED GUYS DON'T DO
AS QUICKLY AS WE USED TO,
IT'S NONE OF
YOUR BUSINESS.
BUT IF THERE'S
TWO THINGS,
THE OTHER ONE IS RUNNING.
NOW, I'M NOT
A JOGGER MYSELF,
BUT IF I WAS,
I'D BE LOOKING FOR SOME
EXCUSE TO RUN SLOWER.
OH, NO, NO, NOT YET.
JUST GIVE ME ONE MORE.
ONE MORE, WALTER.
YEAH. THAT'D BE GREAT.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
SUPER. SUPER. GOOD.
OKAY, UH, THESE
ARE ANKLE WEIGHTS.
SEE, WHEN YOU
HAVE THESE ON,
NOBODY EXPECTS
YOU TO GO FAST.
THE PROBLEM WITH WEIGHTS IS
THEY TEND TO HAVE...
WEIGHT.
SO WHAT I'VE DONE IS
I TOOK SOME OF THESE
KIDS' WATER WINGS,
I BLEW THEM UP,
AND THEN WHAT I DID,
I COVERED THEM
WITH DUCT TAPE.
OKAY, THIS IS PERFECT.
PERFECT TIMING, WALTER.
GREAT.
WORKING OUT GREAT.
WALTER'S GONNA DEMONSTRATE
HOW GREAT THIS IS.
I MEAN, LOOK AT
THESE BABIES, EH!
THEY LOOK LIKE THEY WEIGH
ABOUT 50 POUNDS EACH,
WHEN IN FACT THEY'RE
LIGHTER THAN AIR.
WELL, NO, OKAY, THEY'RE
NOT LIGHTER THAN AIR.
THEY ARE AIR.
I MEAN, LET'S NOT MAKE A
BIG DEAL OUT OF IT, OKAY?
IT'S JUST AN EXPRESSION
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
OKAY, WALTER,
COME ON.
AWAY YOU GO NOW.
THAT'S GREAT.
AWAY YOU GO.
TAKE IT EASY.
YOU KNOW, WITH ANKLE
WEIGHTS THAT SIZE,
YOU HAVE PERMISSION TO GO
AS SLOW AS YOU WANT.
JUST ANOTHER
BRILLIANT CONCEPT --
[Walter yells,
water splashes]
OH, MAN.
[applause]
UNCLE RED, WE'RE AT THE
CRITICAL POINT OF OUR PROJECT.
WHETHER WE'RE GOING TO BE A
SUCCESSFUL BED AND BREAKFAST
COMES DOWN TO ONE THING,
AND ONE THING ONLY...
THE BREAKFAST.
ARE YOU READY TO GIVE
IT YOUR BEST SHOT?
WELL, I'M READY TO GIVE
SOMEBODY MY BEST SHOT, HAROLD.
BONJOUR!
OH, DON'T YOU LOOK STRIKING
IN THAT OUTFIT, SIR?
MIGHT I ASK,
IS THAT A RALPH LAUREN?
UH, NO, IT'S
A LEAVENWORTH.
VERY WELL.
YOUR SEAT, SIR.
COULD I INTEREST
YOU IN A DRINK?
FRESHLY SQUEEZED
GRAPEFRUIT JUICE.
OH, EXCELLENT CHOICE, SIR.
FLORIDA BIB BALL
AND DRAIN 'EM!
GRAPEFRUIT JUICE.
OH. OH.
THERE'S A SEED
IN MY JUICE.
THERE IS A SEED
IN MONSIEUR'S JUICE.
TERRIBLY SORRY.
IT'S NEVER HAPPENED BEFORE.
THANK YOU.
I WILL HAVE THE SCRAMBLED
EGGS ON THE TOAST.
EXCELLENT!
ADAM AND EVE ON
A RAFT AND WRECK 'EM!
AND I'LL HAVE A
LOW-FAT SOY CAPPUCCINO
WITH ARTIFICIAL SWEETENER.
LOW-FAT SOY CAP.
ART. SWEET!
GO NUTS.
IS SOMETHING
WRONG, SIR?
DO YOU WANT ME
TO EAT THAT?
NO.
I DO.
NO! NO! NO!
NO, FORGET THIS WHOLE
BED AND BREAKFAST PROJECT.
I'M CANCELLING
THE WHOLE THING.
UNCLE RED, YOU DON'T
HAVE WHAT IT TAKES FOR
CUSTOMER SERVICE.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
THAT MAY BE THE
NICEST THING
YOU'VE EVER
SAID TO ME.
WELL, THAT'S ALL
VERY WELL AND GOOD,
BUT I STILL THINK I
SHOULD GET MY MONEY BACK.
I AGREE.
HE DIDN'T PAY
ANYTHING!
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I'D MUCH RATHER BE AT
YOUR BED AND BREAKFAST.
NOBODY CAN COMPETE WITH YOUR
HOSPITALITY AND PRICES,
AND THAT'S JUST
THE BED PART.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF HAROLD AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheers and applause]
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE.
SIT DOWN. HAVE A SEAT.
EVERYONE SIT DOWN.
COME ON, TAKE A SEAT.
THERE WE GO.
EVERYONE SIT.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
THE SLEEPY POSSUM
BED AND BREAKFAST
EXPERIMENT IS OVER.
FROM NOW ON, IF YOU WANNA
HAVE BED AND BREAKFAST
WITH A STRANGER
STEAL A CAR.