THERE ARE LOTS OF OCCASIONS
WHERE A MAN HAS TO STAND
FOR LONG PERIODS OF TIME...
AT A PARADE OR
AT A FUNERAL
OR IN THE MALL WHEN YOUR WIFE
SAYS, "NOW, YOU JUST STAND
RIGHT THERE."
BUT AS YOU GET OLDER YOU FIND
YOU'RE A LOT HAPPIER
SITTIN' DOWN.
THAT'S BECAUSE THERE'S A LOT
LESS THEY CAN STAND FOR.
WELL, HERE'S A NIFTY TRICK.
GET YOURSELF A BARSTOOL WITH
A LITTLE BACK ON IT.
THEY'RE NOT EASY TO FIND.
I MUST'VE TRIED ON 100
BARSTOOLS BEFORE I
FOUND THIS BABY.
THEN WHAT YOU WANNA DO IS
MEASURE AROUND YOURSELF,
AROUND YOUR KNEES,
INCLUDING THE BACK.
THEN YOU GO DOWN TO YOUR LOCAL
FAT GUY CLOTHING STORE
AND GET YOURSELF MATCHING
CLOTHES IN THAT SIZE.
AND IF THE GUY ASKS YOU HOW
COME YOU NEED PANTS THAT BIG,
YOU TELL HIM BECAUSE THEY NEED
TO GO AROUND YOUR STOOL.
USE A BARREL HOOP AS A BELT
SO YOUR PANTS WILL KEEP
THEIR SHAPE.
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH
ALL THERE IS TO IT.
NOW YOU CAN LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE STANDING TALL,
WHEN IN FACT
YOU'RE SITTIN' PRETTY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
HAROLD'S DONE SOME DEAL WITH
ONE OF THE UNIVERSITIES,
McGILL-U OR CARLETON-U
OR WHO ASKED YOU.
I DON'T KNOW, SOMETHING.
ANYWAY, THEY'RE DOING THIS
EXPERIMENT WHERE WE ALL GOTTA
BE COMMUNISTS OR SOMETHING.
NOT TOO EXCITED ABOUT DRIVING
LADAS AND MAKIN' BEER
OUT OF POTATOES.
I MEAN, WHAT DO
YOU CALL IT, SPUD LITE?
UNCLE RED! UNCLE RED!
I HAVE YOUR COMRADE
UNIFORM RIGHT HERE.
YOU HAVE TO BE LIKE ME.
WELL, LUCKILY, HAROLD,
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
WE ALL HAVE TO
DRESS THE SAME.
IT'S IN THE RULES.
AH, HAROLD.
HOW DID YOU GET US
INTO THIS ANYWAY?
WELL, IT WAS THE
POLITICAL SCIENCE DEAN.
HE GOT A GRANT TO EVALUATE
DIFFERENT FORMS OF GOVERNMENT.
THIS IS A SOCIOLOGICAL
EXPERIMENT.
WELL, SO ARE YOU.
WHY DOES EVERYBODY
HAVE TO SUFFER?
NOT FOR FREE.
YEAH, WE'RE GETTING
COMPENSATED.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
IT'S REALLY VERY SIMPLE.
EVERYTHING'S BASED ON EVERYONE
BEING TREATED THE SAME,
FROM EACH TO FROM HIS
ABILITY TO EACH OF
HIS NEED.
SO YOU MEAN YOU GET
TREATED THE SAME
WHETHER YOU'RE A
BRAIN SURGEON OR
A BAT BOY?
YES! NO ONE IS JUDGED.
WELL, I CAN CERTAINLY
SEE WHY YOU'D LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T LIKE IT
WHEN EVERYBODY'S THE SAME.
WELL, THERE'S LOTS OF WAYS
PEOPLE CAN BE THE SAME.
YEAH, WELL, THERE LOTS
OF WAYS PEOPLE CAN BE
DIFFERENT.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY MIKE HAMAR
WILL BE PLAYING TO WIN
A FREE WEEKEND AT THE ELVIS
PRESLEY ROCK 'N' ROLL
FANTASY CAMP!
HOME OF ELVIS' FAVOURITE DISH,
CHICKEN A LA KING...
FOR PEOPLE
"WHO LOVE MEAT TENDER."
OKAY, COVER YOUR EARS, MIKE.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS TO
GET MIKE HAMAR TO SAY
THIS WORD...
ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, MIKE, THIS IS
SOMETHING THAT SITS IN
YOUR LIVING ROOM WINDOW,
AND YOU WATER IT
ONCE A WEEK.
GRANDPA?
NO, NO, I KNOW.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT HANGS
AROUND THE LAMPPOST DOWNTOWN.
OH, GRANDMA.
NO. NO. OKAY.
THIS IS LIKE WHEN YOU
DIG A HOLE IN THE BACKYARD
AND YOU PUT
SOMETHING IN IT...
NOBODY PROVED
ANY OF THAT.
OKAY, I KNOW, I KNOW.
YOUR UNCLE, YOU KNOW,
THE BIG GUY,
THINK OF HIS JOB,
RENDERING...
PEOPLE UNCONSCIOUS.
NO, OKAY. OKAY.
OKAY, I KNOW.
THIS WITHERS IN
THE COLD WEATHER.
SO DOES MINE!
UM, ALMOST OUTTA TIME, RED.
YEAH, OKAY.
MIKE, THIS IS SO SIMPLE.
WHAT DO YOU BUY FROM
THE FLORIST IN TOWN?
NOTHING.
HE'S NOT A REAL FLORIST.
HE'S AN UNDERCOVER R.C.M.P.
YOU KNOW,
KINDA LIKE A PLANT.
THERE WE GO!
TODAY ON
TALKING ANIMALS,
LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER, ED FRID,
HAS BROUGHT US
A WILD PARROT
FROM THE BRAZILIAN COAST.
ACTUALLY, RED, I LOOKED INTO
GETTING A WILD PARROT.
UH, TURNS OUT THEY'VE
GOT SHARP, UNTRIMMED CLAWS
AND, UH, UNPREDICTABLE
TEMPERAMENTS
AND SHARP,
UNTRIMMED CLAWS.
THAT ARE SHARP
AND UNTRIMMED.
ALL RIGHT, THEN WHERE
DOES THIS ONE COME FROM?
WELL, THIS ONE'S MY
GIRLFRIEND'S.
YEAH, SHE NAMED IT
OPRAH.
WELL, OBVIOUSLY
A TALKER, HUH?
WELL, RED, THAT'S
A COMMON MISCONCEPTION.
BUT INTERESTING
THING ABOUT PARROTS...
ALL PARROTS HAVE
HOLLOW BONES.
Parrot: LOSER!
DID YOU CALL
ME A LOSER?
JUST NOW, NO.
OKAY.
THE OTHER THING
ABOUT PARROTS IS, UH,
THEY'VE GOT THESE HOOKED
BEAKS THAT ARE GREAT
FOR DIGGING DIRT
AND OPENING SEEDS --
Parrot: LOSER!
OKAY, I GUESS YOU
THINK THAT'S FUNNY, HUH?
DO YOU THINK
THAT'S FUNNY?
YEAH,
I DO, ACTUALLY.
IT'S NOT ME,
OKAY, ED.
IT'S THE PARROT.
AND HE'S NOT CALLING
YOU A LOSER.
IT'S JUST A WORD
HE PICKED UP SOMEWHERE.
Parrot:
ED FRID IS A LOSER!
CAN'T COMMIT.
EMOTIONALLY IMMATURE.
OH, I KNOW
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
THE PARROT HAS PICKED UP
WORDS AND PHRASES THAT
YOUR GIRLFRIEND USES.
HOW SHE TALKS
ABOUT YOU.
[ CHUCKLING ]
-- OH.
WELL, THAT MAKES
ME FEEL BETTER.
WELL, LOOK.
MAKE IT WORK THE
OTHER WAY AROUND.
YOU CAN USES THE BIRD TO
RELAY MESSAGES BACK TO
YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
JUST LEAVE A MESSAGE
AFTER THE BEAK.
WELL, OKAY.
WHAT DO I SAY?
WELL, IT SOUNDS TO ME
LIKE SHE'S LOOKIN' FOR
A COMMITMENT,
LIKE, I WOULD SAY
A MARRIAGE PROPOSAL.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT
THE AUDIENCE WANTS TO HEAR.
AM I RIGHT?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
GREAT.
HONEY,
W-W-W-OULD YOU --
W-W-W-OULD YOU
MARRY ME?
Parrot: NOT UNTIL
YOU GET A BETTER JOB!
[ APPLAUSE ]
DEPENDING ON WHERE YOU LIVE,
YOUR TOWN MAY PICK UP
YOUR GARBAGE ONCE
OR MAYBE TWICE A WEEK.
THE PROBLEM IS
THEY WON'T TAKE IT,
UNLESS YOU HAUL YOUR CAN ALL
THE WAY DOWN TO THE END
OF THE DRIVEWAY,
WHICH MEANS YOUR TRASH STARTS
PILING UP FASTER THAN
YOUR EXCUSES.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
THE NEIGHBOURS ARE
COMPLAINING,
YOUR WIFE IS EMBARRASSED,
AND THE RACCOONS
HAVE TURNED YOUR YARD
INTO A DRIVE-THRU.
OH, YEAH, SURE, I SUPPOSE YOU
COULD TAKE THE GARBAGE OUT
EVERY WEEK.
BUT I NEVER IT
CALL IT SUCCESS
WHEN I TAKE
SOMETHING I DON'T LIKE
AND FIND A WAY
TO DO IT MORE OFTEN.
WOULDN'T IT BE BETTER IF
WE COULD CRAM FOUR WEEKS
OF TRASH INTO ONE CAN?
WE'D ONLY HAVE TO TAKE THE
GARBAGE OUT ONCE A MONTH.
SO TODAY ON HANDYMAN CORNER
WE'RE NOT JUST TALKIN' TRASH,
WE'RE TALKIN'
TRASH COMPACTOR.
I STARTED BY FILLING THIS
GARBAGE CAN WITH CEMENT.
NEXT STEP...
GENTLY REMOVE THE
HARDENED CONCRETE.
OKAY, NOW THIS WHOLE ASSEMBLY
IS GOING TO DO THE COMPACTING.
THAT'S WHY I USED
A COMPACT CAR.
SEE, ACTUALLY, THE CEMENT
IS ALREADY HEAVY ENOUGH,
BUT THEN YOU HOOK IT
ONTO A VEHICLE,
THAT GARBAGE IS GOING TO BE
FEELING AS MUCH DOWNWARD
PRESSURE
AS MOOSE THOMPSON'S FEET.
AND OF COURSE, THE WHOLE
PROCESS IS MECHANIZED;
OTHERWISE, IT WOULD
REQUIRE MANUAL LABOUR,
AND AS YOU KNOW, I HAVE NO USE
FOR ANY KIND OF MANUAL.
I'VE ATTACHED THE GARBAGE
CAN TO THE GARAGE DOOR
WITH THIS HOOK
I GOT OFF A TOW TRUCK.
YOU CAN GET
THESE PRETTY CHEAP.
JUST SLAM ON YOUR BRAKES
WHILE YOU'RE BEIN' TOWED.
NOW ALL'S WE DO IS TOSS THE
GARBAGE BAGS INTO THE CAN.
LOOK FULL TO YOU?
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
AND THERE'S THE END OF IT.
SO REMEMBER: IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OH, BOY.
JUST FOR THE RECORD...
18 BAGS IS THE LIMIT.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE A
THEORY THAT MAN'S LIFE
IS A LONG LIST OF
SANDWICHES.
LIKE, WHEN YOU'RE A KID,
YOU'RE PEANUT BUTTER AND JAM.
LIFE IS SWEET,
NO CRUSTS.
THEN YOU GET
TO BE A TEENAGER,
YOU'RE A TOASTED CLUBHOUSE.
YOU GOT A LITTLE
BACON GOIN' FOR YOU,
BUT THE GIRLS STILL STAY AWAY
BECAUSE EITHER THEY'RE CHICKEN
OR YOU'RE A TURKEY.
THEN AS A YOUNG MAN,
YOU BECOME A HAM AND CHEESE --
MORE HAM THAN CHEESE,
BUT THAT WILL REVERSE
AS YOU GET OLDER.
BUT MAYBE NOW YOU'VE REACHED
THE NOT SO HEALTHY SANDWICH
YEARS, HUH?
THE BIG, FAT, GREASY
CORNED-BEEF-ON-A-KAISER YEARS.
THINGS ARE HANGING OUT
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
YOU'RE LOOKIN' KINDA ROUGH.
YOU'VE BIGGIE
SIZED YOURSELF.
YOUR FAT CONTENT
IS THROUGH THE ROOF.
AND IF YOU DON'T START
SAVING SOME BREAD SOON,
YOU COULD
END UP OPEN-FACED.
OKAY, THIS IS WHEN
YOU NEED YOUR WIFE'S HELP.
YOUR WIFE IS THE SPOONFUL OF
COLESLAW THAT CAN SAVE
YOUR LIFE.
YOU BE NICE TO HER,
BECAUSE IF SHE LEAVES,
YOU'VE HAD THE BUN.
AND YOU ARE WAY TOO OLD
TO BE HOLDIN' THE PICKLE.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
VENI, VIDI
VACUUM...
WE CAME, WE SAW,
WE SUCKED.
WELL, THIS WHOLE COMMUNIST
EXPERIMENT ISN'T
GOIN' TOO BAD.
I'M GETTIN' PAID
FOR DOIN' NOTHIN',
SO IT'S NOT THAT
MUCH OF AN ADJUSTMENT.
ACTUALLY THINKIN' ABOUT
CHANGIN' THE NAME OF THE LODGE
TO RED GREEN SQUARE.
UM, UNCLE RED.
WE MIGHT HAVE
A BIT OF A PROBLEM.
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW,
UNDER THE COMMUNIST SYSTEM
ALL INDUSTRY IS OWNED
BY THE GOVERNMENT.
SO, UH, TECHNICALLY,
THIS SHOW BELONGS TO
THE GOVERNMENT.
WELL, I'M SURE THEY'LL
CHANGE THEIR MINDS ONCE
THEY SEE IT, HAROLD.
YES, BUT NO INDIVIDUAL
IS ALLOWED TO REAP
CAPITAL GAINS,
SO THEREFORE, YOU HAVE
TO TURN OVER ALL YOUR
PROFITS FOR THE SHOW.
WHAT, YOU MEAN
FOR ALL 13 SEASONS?
WELL, THIS IS
A KILLER, HAROLD.
CAN YOU
CHANGE A 20?
OKAY, GREAT.
MR. GREEN,
THIS IS NOT WORKING!
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
MIKE?
YOU SEE EVERYBODY DRESSED
IN THE GREYS AND YOU
GET HOMESICK?
NO!
NO, IT'S JUST WHEN
EVERYBODY OWNS EVERYTHING
THEN NOBODY'S GOT
ANYTHING WORTH STEALIN'.
IT'S THE END OF THE
WORLD AS WE KNOW IT.
I'M IN THE
SAME BOAT, RED.
EVERYONE'S AFTER ME
TO PUMP OUT THEIR SEPTICS,
AND ACCORDING TO THE RULES,
I CAN'T CHARGE ANYTHING,
AND THEY CAN'T
PAY ANYTHING.
GEEZ, IT'S LIKE WORKIN'
FOR YOUR RELATIVES.
YEAH,
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
HAROLD, WINSTON AND I
ARE QUITTING.
WINSTON'S PARKED HIS
TRUCK NEXT TO MY STORE,
AND FOR US IT'S BACK TO
BUSINESS AS USUAL.
OH, NO!
YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
NO, YOU CAN'T HAVE
A POCKET OF CAPITALISM
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF A
COMMUNIST TERRITORY.
OH, IT'S
NO PROBLEM, HAROLD.
WE BUILT A WALL
AROUND OUR SECTION.
YEP, BUILT IT OUT
OF WRECKED CARS.
WELL, I'D LIKE
TO SEE THAT.
THAT'S A
SCRAP IRON CURTAIN.
Red: WALTER WAS
OUT BEHIND THE LODGE.
HE WANTED TO DO
A LITTLE DRYWALL WORK,
AND I HAD THE
INSTRUCTIONS THERE
THAT I WAS FOLDING
INTO AN AIRPLANE,
AND I HAD THE
PLANS THERE AS WELL.
UH, WALTER'S PRETTY STRONG.
I DIDN'T FIGURE HE NEED --
JUST PUT DOWN ON THE SAW --
EASY NOW.
EASY. EASY. EASY.
YOU'RE GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, I JUST
FIRED THE PLANE AT HIM.
THERE WE GO.
[ RED CHUCKLES ]
LOVE GLIDERS.
LOVE THE PAPER AIRPLANES.
NOW I'M MAKIN' A BIGGER ONE
OUT OF THE ACTUAL PLANS,
AND I'M NOT PAYIN' A LOT
OF ATTENTION TO WALTER.
LOOKIT, THAT'S
A BEAUTIFUL THING.
THAT LOOKS KINDA
LIKE THE CONCORDE.
AND I MADE HER
SO SHE CURVES RIGHT AROUND,
AND WATCH YOURSELF THERE.
OH, BOY!
SEE WHAT KIND OF
FUN THAT IS, WALTER?
THAT'S MORE FUN THAN --
NOW WALTER'S GETTIN' AN IDEA.
WAIT A SECOND.
IT'S JUST A BIG RECTANGULAR
SHEET THAT YOU FOLD
INTO A PAPER AIRPLANE,
AND DRYWALL IS KINDA A BIG
RECTANGULAR SHEET
THAT WHEN YOU SCORE IT,
YOU CAN FOLD --
I DIDN'T KNOW QUITE
WHAT WAS GOIN' ON,
BUT HE'S MAKIN' ALL KINDS OF
MARKS AND EVERYTHING.
WHEN HE ACTUALLY GRABBED THE
ONE SIDE AND STARTED TO
FOLD HER OVER,
I KINDA GOT THE FEELIN' --
OH, THAT LOOKS
KINDA WINGLIKE, DOESN'T IT?
AND HE MADE JUST AN
UNBELIEVABLE HUGE GLIDER
AIRPLANE THERE.
SHE IS A BEAUTY.
THAT'S A -- THAT'S LIKE
THE 747 OF GLIDERS THERE.
AND LET HER GO...
AND OH, BOY.
OH, BOY, BUT HEY, SHE'S
AIRBORNE, BABY.
OH! BEAUTIFUL.
SHE'S A GOOD --
WALTER, SHE'S COMIN' --
WALTER, SHE'S
COMIN' THIS WAY.
WALTER, WALTER.
AWAY YOU GO. AWAY YOU GO.
OH, BOY! OH, BOY!
MAKE A WISH, WALTER.
OH!
AND THEN I SEE HIM COMIN'
AND I'M THINKIN',
IF I CAN GET HIM
TO LAND INSIDE THE VAN
IT WOULD KINDA
BREAK THE FALL.
AND I'M LOOKIN'
FOR A COUPLE OF FLASHLIGHTS,
YOU KNOW, LIKE THEY
USE AT THE AIRPORT,
TO KINDA SIGNAL THE BIG --
SO THERE YOU GO.
I GOT A HAMMER
AND A PIPE WRENCH.
THAT'S GONNA HAVE TO --
THAT'S GONNA HAVE TO DO.
AND HE'S GETTIN'
AWFUL CLOSE,
AND HE JUST --
OH, BOY!
OH!
ALL RIGHT, NOW, FOR YOU
YOUNGSTERS OUT THERE,
IT'S A REAL IMPORTANT
SAFETY LESSON.
IF SOMEONE IS EVER INJURED,
YOUR MAIN JOB
IS TO STAY CALM AND
GET THEM TO THE HOSPITAL
AS QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THIS IS THE EXPERTS
PORTION OF THE PROGRAMME
WHERE WE ADDRESS
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
OKAY, AND HERE'S
OUR LETTER...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"MY WIFE HAS A LOT
OF FEMALE INTUITION.
"SHE CAN LOOK AT ME
AND KNOW WHAT I'M THINKING.
"HOW DOES SHE DO THAT?
"I NEVER HAVE A CLUE
WHAT SHE'S BEEN UP TO."
BOY, I CAN
RELATE TO THAT.
YEAH, ESPECIALLY THE NEVER
HAVING A CLUE PART.
NO!
I MEANT THE WAY THAT WHEN
ANN MARIE LOOKS AT ME,
SHE KNOWS EXACTLY
WHAT I'M THINKING.
WOMAN ARE JUST --
THEY'RE GOOD AT THAT!
NO, IT'S NOT
JUST WOMEN.
I MEAN, I CAN TELL,
EVERY TIME SOMEBODY
LOOKS AT ME,
WHAT THEY'RE THINKIN':
"THAT'S THE GUY!"
NAH, WOMEN DON'T HAVE ANY
KIND OF SPECIAL INTUITION.
MEN GIVE THEMSELVES AWAY WITH
THEIR BODY LANGUAGE,
THAT'S ALL.
YOU MEAN LIKE WALKIN'
THROUGH THE DOOR WITH
YOUR HANDS UP?
WELL, YEAH.
NO, I MEAN, YOU KNOW, WE'RE
PRETTY SIMPLE MACHINES.
WE'RE NOT HARD
TO FIGURE OUT.
WE'RE LIKE BULLDOZERS,
YOU KNOW?
LOTS OF POWER,
LOTS OF GAS,
WE MOVE THINGS
FROM PLACE TO ANOTHER,
DON'T REALLY CHANGE
ANYTHING, YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW, WOMEN,
THEY'RE MORE COMPLICATED.
THEY'RE LIKE COMPUTERS.
YOU CAN SEE WHAT'S
GOIN' ON ON THE SCREEN,
BUT YOU KNOW BY ALL
THE HUMMING AND WHIRRING
THAT THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
GOING ON IN THE BACKGROUND.
IS THAT WHY WOMEN ARE
SO HARD TO UNDERSTAND?
YOU EVER SEEN HOW BIG A
COMPUTER MANUAL IS, MIKE?
YEAH, YOU SEE, WOMEN
HAVE GOT THE SOFTWARE,
AND THEY'VE GOT
THE GRAPHICS PACKAGE,
AND THEY GOT THE
HUGE MEMORY BANKS.
THAT'S MEMORY
WITH AN "E."
AND YOU GOTTA PRESS
THE RIGHT BUTTONS,
OR THEY'LL FREEZE UP ON YOU.
YEAH, AND ALL THEIR DADS
ARE LOOKIN' AT 'EM
AND TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHETHER THEY SHOULD
GET A NEWER MODEL
WITH A FASTER
OPERATING SYSTEM
OR JUST UPGRADE THE
ONE THEY'VE ALREADY GOT
AND RUN THE RISK OF GETTING
INTO BED WITH YESTERDAY'S
TECHNOLOGY.
NO. NO. NO.
NO WAY.
OKAY, SO YOU'RE SAYING THIS
VIEWER DOESN'T HAVE A
GHOST OF A CHANCE
OF FIGURING OUT THE
WHOLE FEMALE INTUITION THING
BECAUSE SHE'S AS
COMPLEX AS A COMPUTER?
YEAH, IF HE'S THINKING OF
GETTING A NEWER MODEL
OR UPGRADING,
SHE'LL BE ONTO HIM IN
A PORT ASBESTOS MINUTE.
OH, YEAH. YEAH.
YOU START FOOLIN' AROUND
WITH A WOMAN COMPUTER,
YOU'RE GONNA FIND OUT WHAT
"BOOT UP" REALLY MEANS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW THERE'S
AN OLD SAYING,
INTO EVERY MEAL
A FEW VEGETABLES MAY FALL.
HERE THEY GO NOW.
THAT WAS EASY, BUT WHAT
HAPPENS IF YOUR WIFE'S THERE?
YOU KNOW SHE SEES RED
IF YOU DON'T EAT YOUR GREENS.
WELL, HERE'S A SIMPLE
SOLUTION TO THE PROBLEM...
GET YOURSELF A RAT TRAP
AND AN OLD SIDE VIEW MIRROR
YOU DON'T USE ANYMORE.
CAULIFLOWER MAY BE
CLOSER THAN IT APPEARS.
NOW I JUST ATTACH
THE MIRROR FACE DOWN
TO THE SPRING MOUNT
ON MY RAT TRAP, SEE,
AND THEN WHEN
I TAP THE RELEASE,
I'LL RIG HER SO SHE
JUST COMES UP TO 90°,
WHICH WILL HIDE MY VEGGIES
AND MAKE THE
PLATE LOOK CLEAN.
DAVID COPPERFIELD,
EAT YOUR HEART OUT.
BETTER YET, EAT MY
WIFE'S TURNIP CASSEROLE.
LET'S DEMONSTRATE THIS IN A
FULL DINNER SETTING, SHALL WE?
AS YOU CAN SEE, I'VE MOVED
ALL MY UNDESIRABLES
TO ONE HALF OF THE PLATE,
AND ON THE OTHER HALF,
I CAN ENJOY THE REST
OF MY MEAT ENTREE.
MM-MM-MM!
NOW I JUST ROTATE THE PLATE SO
THAT THE MIRROR IS FACING
TOWARDS BERNICE,
AND THEN I SUBTLY HIT THE
RELEASE WHEN SHE'S
NOT WATCHING.
AND I'M READY FOR DESSERT.
NEVER COULD KEEP
MY VEGGIES DOWN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
LOCK THE DOOR!
I THINK WE LOST 'EM.
OKAY, WELL, WE'VE JUST
WITNESSED THE COLLAPSE
OF OUR COMMUNIST REGIME.
OH, UNCLE RED, I'M SO
SORRY ABOUT THIS MESS.
IT WASN'T REALLY
YOUR FAULT, HAROLD.
WHAT AM I SAYING?
I MEAN, AT LEAST
WE GOT PAID, RIGHT?
RIGHT!
AT LEAST WE
GOT PAID, RIGHT?
R-R-RIGHT --
WELL, NOT PAID IN
A SENSE OF MONEY
PER SE.
NOT MONEY I COULD PUT IN MY
WIFE'S PURSE, SAY?
EACH OF US GETS 25% OFF ANY
POST-GRADUATE COURSE
WE WANNA TAKE.
OH, NO!
WHAT DO THEY WANT?
I ALREADY ANNOUNCED WE
WERE GONNA TURN DOWN
THE GOVERNMENT.
I THINK I KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE AFTER, HAROLD.
[ MEN SHOUTING ]
SETTLE DOWN!
HERE YOU GO!
[ APPLAUSE ]
YES, SIR.
FIRST RULE OF
POLITICS, HAROLD...
GIVE THE PEOPLE
WHAT THEY WANT.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD,
COMRADE.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
OKAY.
OKAY, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND, UH, THE COMMUNIST
THING IS OVER,
BUT WE CAN STILL PARTY, HUH?
WITH THE DIFFERENCE
BEIN' I WON'T BE RUSHIN',
AND I'M HOPIN'
YOU WON'T BE STALLIN'.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHIN'.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG AT
POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THE MEETING'S ABOUT TO BEGIN.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, THE COMMUNIST THING
DIDN'T REALLY WORK OUT SO GOOD.
SO I THINK WE SHOULD GO BACK
TO THINKING AND ACTING
AS INDIVIDUALS.
ALL IN FAVOUR...
OPPOSED...
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.