(Chainsaw revving)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
NOW, HERE'S THE MAN WHO SAID,
"STOP THE WORLD --
I WANT TO GET A HOT DOG!",
YOUR HOST, MY UNCLE...
RED GREEN
(Applause and cheering)
(Whistling)
(Singing)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANKS FOR COMING.
THIS IS AN EXCITING TIME
AT POSSUM LODGE THIS WEEK
BECAUSE TONIGHT IS
MEN'S NIGHT ON THE MOUNTAIN.
HAS ANYBODY TOLD THE MOUNTAIN?
DON'T LISTEN TO HIM.
THIS IS A FANTASTIC TIME.
IT'S TIME TO CUT LOOSE.
WE FORGET OUR REONSIBILITIES
AND GO RIGHT UP THE MOUNTAIN.
REAL OLD TRADITION --
DATES BACK
HUNDREDS OF YEARS WHEN,
IN THE SPRING,
MEN WOULD GO UP ON TOP
AND WATCH OUT OVER THE RIVERS
TO MAKE SURE
THERE WAS NO FLOODING
FROM THE SPRING RUNOFF.
THERE'S A MALE BONDING SIDE
TO IT.
IT'S JUST MEN
UP ON THE MOUNTAIN,
LOOKING OUT OVER
A RAGING RIVER.
IT'S A BUNCH OF YOU GUYS,
SITTING ON ROCK REEF POINT,
STARING AT MERCURY CREEK?
NOT A REAL MOUNTAIN,
NOT A REAL RIVER, NOT REAL MEN.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD,
IF IT'S NOT REAL MEN,
I GUESS YOU'LL BE ABLE TO COME.
REALLY? YEAH, REALLY?
I CAN GO?
WELL, OK, ALL RIGHT.
MY USUAL DISDAIN
FOR YOUR DESTRUCTIVE
TESTOSTERONE-INDUCED
CRAZINESSES
SEEMS TO BE OVERRIDDEN
BY MY INCREDIBLE DESIRE
TO BE ACCEPTED BY THE GROUP.
MAYBE YOU ARE A REAL MAN.
PUT THIS ON.
(Applause)
(Horns honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): WE GOT
SOME NEW STUFF TO SHOW YOU.
GARTH HARBLE, ANIMAL CONTROL.
I'M GONNA MAKE SOMETHING
OUT OF A SHOPPING CART.
WE GOT A NEW GAME CALLED
"TWO ON A MATCH" YOU'LL ENJOY.
DON'T FORGET, IT'S MEN'S NIGHT
ON THE MOUNTAIN.
MEN'S NIGHT ON THE MOUNTAIN
WAS A HUGE SUCCESS, AS USUAL.
HARD ON THE BACK,
BUT I'M NOT AS YOUNG AS I WAS.
JUST HAD ONE INCIDENT.
HAROLD FELL OFF THE CLIFF
WEARING MY BACKPACK.
I WAS AFRAID THERE WOULD BE
SOME SERIOUS INJURIES.
WE WERE LAUGHING THAT HARD.
(Audience laughing)
YEAH.
(Laughing)
COME ON IN.
DID YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME,
THERE, YOUNG FELLA?
NO!
ONLY THE WORST TIME OF MY LIFE.
COME ON, HAROLD, DOESN'T GET
ANY BETTER THAN THIS.
THIS IS OUR ONE NIGHT
TO GO CRAZY.
CRAZY? IT WAS BORING!
BORING?
BORING, BORING, BORING!
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE GOT 12 FEET UP THE HILL
AND EVERYBODY WAS TOO TIRED
TO GO ANY FURTHER.
BUSTER HADFIELD WENT HOME
AND GOT HIS MEDICATION.
NO ONE COULD GET THE FIRE LIT.
WELL, SPRING RUNOFF, HAROLD.
SPRING RUNOFF,
YEAH, SPRING RUNOFF!
EVERYTHING'S WET.
IT WAS SO BORING.
IT WAS INCREDIBLY TERRIBLE.
EVERYBODY'S COMPLAINING
ALL THE TIME.
"IT'S TOO DARK," "IT'S
TOO DAMP," "I GOT A SOAKER."
COME ON!
MOOSE THOMPSON
WAS ASKING EVERYBODY
IF THEY BROUGHT
AN EXTRA SWEATER.
IT WAS BORING --
IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
NO DIRTY JOKES,
NO SCARY STORIES.
JUST MIDDLE-AGED FAT GUYS
SITTING AROUND A DEAD FIRE
ON HEMORRHOID CUSHIONS.
I'M SORRY, BUT YOU ALWAYS SAY,
"TELL ME WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND."
NO, "TELL ME WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOUR MIND."
OH.
(Applause and cheering)
(Red): LOOK OUT BELOW!
AHHHH!
BILL'S PRACTISING
FOR A NEW EVENT
FOR MEN'S NIGHT ON
THE MOUNTAIN -- CLIFF-DIVING.
HE'S JUST GETTING WARMED UP.
YOU OK, BILL?
OKEY-DOKEY,
THIS IS THE BIG ONE,
FOR A FREE WASH AND HOT WAX
AT LARRY'S BARBERSHOP.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. HUMPHREY
TO SAY THIS WORD.
THIRTY SECONDS, AND GO.
ALL RIGHT, UH...
AWARE.
SOBER?
TOUCHY.
FEELY.
TOUCHY-FEELY.
RICHARD SIMMONS?
(Audience laughing)
COMPARED TO YOU,
YOUR WIFE IS MORE...
OVERWEIGHT.
EMOTIONALLY,
SHE'S MORE...
WEEPY, WEEPY.
SHE'S WEEPY!
NO, NO, NO, NO, I'M SAYING
SHE NOTICES THINGS MORE
BECAUSE SHE'S...
PICKY.
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YOU WOULD NEVER TELL YOUR WIFE
THAT SHE'S PICKY, OVERWEIGHT,
OR WEEPY BECAUSE...
CASTRATION?
(Audience laughing)
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
DALTON.
THE VERTICAL HOLD
ON YOUR
TELEVISION SET...
SENSITIVE.
THAT'S IT!
(Strums guitar)
OH, DUFFY'S JOINTS
WERE LOOSE AND LOUD
YOU'D SWEAR
THEY ALL WERE BREAKIN'
HE'D TWIST HIS KNUCKLES
AND CRACK HIS KNEES
HE SOUNDED LIKE
A POPCORN MAKER
HE'D SNAP HIS BACK
AND RIPPLE HIS SPINE
DO IT ALL
WITH A BIG STUPID GRIN
THEN HE SLIPPED AND FELL
300 FEET ON A ROCK
AND THAT WAS THE LAST CRACK
WE HEARD FROM HIM
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL,
WITH A TIP ON HOW TO DEAL
WITH A COMMON HOUSEHOLD PEST.
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
COME ON IN HERE, RED.
(Laughing)
VERY FUNNY, VERY FUNNY.
GARTH, YOU GOT
NO SERIOUS INJURY TODAY.
SLOW WEEK, HUH?
WELL, YEAH, SEE, RED,
I'VE TAKEN SICK LEAVE.
OH.
YEAH, YEAH,
AFTER THAT SPIDER BITE,
I STARTED FALLING DOWN
ALL OVER THE PLACE
AND I MANAGED TO FLATTEN
A LITTLE PARAKEET.
WHEN THE BOSS FOUND OUT,
HE SENT ME HOME FOR THE WEEK.
POOR LITTLE PARAKEET.
YOU HAVE A TIP FOR US AT ALL?
HUH?
YOU HAVE A TIP FOR US TODAY?
OH, YES, YES.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT A VOLE IS?
YES, IT'S LIKE A LITTLE MOUSE,
I BELIEVE.
EXCEPT THAT THE VOLE HIDES
UNDER YOUR LAWN
AND HE EATS THE ROOTS
OF YOUR GRASS AND YOUR PLANTS.
OH, YEAH?
I'VE LOCATED THE TWO ENTRANCES
INTO THE VOLE'S TUNNEL.
I SHOVE A PAPER BAG
INTO THE FIRST HOLE.
I SEE THAT NOW.
INTO THE SECOND HOLE,
I'VE GOT PLASTIC TUBING.
WHAT DO I DO NEXT?
I WOULD THINK YOU'D PUMP IN
THE METHANE AT THIS POINT.
I'LL PRETEND
I DIDN'T HEAR THAT, RED.
NO, I DON'T DO THAT.
NO, I'M GONNA BLOW VERY HARD
INTO THIS TUBING,
SO THAT THE VOLE WILL POP OUT
THE OTHER SIDE INTO THAT BAG.
ISN'T THAT GREAT?
WELL, NOW, THAT IS GREAT.
RUN OVER THERE, AND WHEN THE
VOLE COMES OUT, YOU SNATCH IT.
HEY, THIS IS FUN.
VOLE SNATCHING COULD CATCH ON
AT THE LODGE.
REALLY?
ALL RIGHT, BLOW AWAY.
WE'LL GIVE 'ER A BLAST!
ALL RIGHT.
(Vole
squeaking)
AHHH!
WELL, YOU MUST HAVE IT, GARTH.
WHAT?
OH!
THIS IS FUN.
OH, BOY.
ANOTHER SUPER DAY.
(Burping)
HAROLD DOESN'T
UNDERSTAND
THAT YOU GET
TO A CERTAIN AGE
WHERE YOU'RE
NOT PREPARED
TO GIVE UP THE
CREATURE COMFORTS.
I THOUGHT I'D TAKE
THIS WEEK'S "HANDYMAN CORNER"
AND SHOW YOU
HOW YOU CAN SATISFY
MAN'S TWO BASIC
FUNDAMENTAL NEEDS.
NUMBER ONE, A COMFY CHAIR
TO SIT ON,
AND NUMBER TWO, JUNK FOOD.
GO TO YOUR GROCERY STORE
AND PICK UP
YOUR FAVOURITE SNACKS...
... JUST LIKE THIS.
MAKE SURE YOU BRING
THE CART WITH YOU, TOO.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT TAKING IT.
THE STORE DOESN'T MIND.
THEY FACTOR THE COST --
WHOA, COME BACK HERE --
INTO THE PRICE
OF THEIR GROCERIES.
BESIDES, IF THEY--
MY GOSH, FLOORS ARE UNEVEN
AT THE LODGE.
IF THEY FILL THE CART
WITH GROCERIES,
THEY DON'T EXPECT YOU
TO CARRY THE WHOLE THING HOME.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, STEP TWO,
WE WANT TO CUT DOWN THE SIDES
SO WE CAN FOLD THAT THING DOWN.
JUST GRAB A SAW, HERE,
AND GET AT THAT.
(Blade breaking)
(Grunting)
THERE WE GO.
THAT'S THE COMFORT ASPECT
TAKEN CARE OF.
NOW WE CAN TAKE A LOOK
AT SAFETY.
WE GOT THIS-- WHOA, WHOA!
GOT THIS OZONE HOLE
FROM PEOPLE WHO THINK
EVERYTHING GOOD
IS SPRAYED OUT OF A CAN.
WE GOTTA WORRY ABOUT--
WHOA! -- ABOUT THAT.
I GOT THIS-- MAN!
I GOT THIS WINDOW HERE,
WHICH I'M GONNA MOUNT
ON TOP OF THE UNIT.
GOT A BLIND ON THERE
SO IT NOW BECOMES
A VARIABLE-ANGLE
U.V. DEFLECTOR.
GOT A SCREEN ON HERE
TO KEEP THE BUGS OUT.
SO I'LL JUST MOUNT--
I'LL JUST MOUNT THIS RIG
ON HERE WITH THESE 2 x 2's.
OH!
JUST GET YOUR SNACKS
HUNG ON THERE.
YOU FOLD THESE THINGS
FOR TRAVELLING,
BUT WHEN YOU ARRIVE
WHERE YOU WANT TO BE,
SWING 'EM OPEN
AND GET COMFORTABLE.
OHH...
NOT THAT EASY TO DO.
THERE YOU ARE, HUH?
SITTING PRETTY WITH LIFE'S
TREASURES AT YOUR FINGERTIPS.
YOU GET THIRSTY, YOU SAY?
HOOK UP ONE
OF THESE PLASTIC HOSES
TO A BOTTLE
THAT'S ABOVE YOUR HEAD
AND IT'S EVEN A GRAVITY FEED.
WHEN PEOPLE SAY, "YOU SUCK,"
YOU CAN PROVE OTHERWISE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I'LL HAVE SOMETHING TO EAT
WHILE I'M WAITING
FOR THE AMBULANCE.
(Crash)
IF YOU WANT REASONS
NOT TO GO BUNGEE-JUMPING,
STAY TUNED FOR BUZZ SHERWOOD.
OUR NIGHT ON THE MOUNTAIN
GOT US THINKING.
I HATE TO ADMIT HAROLD'S RIGHT,
BUT IT'S POSSIBLE
THAT WE'VE LOST OUR MANHOOD,
THROUGH MARRIAGE OR SOME OTHER
ACCIDENT IN THE WORKPLACE.
WELL, YOU DON'T NEED
FOOLISH STUNTS
TO PROVE YOU'RE A MAN.
JUST ACT RESPONSIBLY
TOWARDS FELLOW HUMAN BEINGS.
GET SERIOUS, HAROLD.
SO NOW
WE'RE GOING
TO DO SOMETHING REALLY MANLY.
YOU MEAN BEING GOOD FATHERS,
GOOD HUSBANDS,
BEING GOOD PROVIDERS?
WHERE DO YOU GET THIS STUFF?
NO, WE
WERE THINKING
OF MAYBE GOING WHITE-WATER
RAFTING ON MERCURY CREEK.
THE PROBLEM IS, THE
WHITE-WATER'S CHEMICAL FOAM.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
IN DEAD MAN'S WHIRLPOOL
AND HAVE THE RIVER EAT
THE RUBBER OFF YOUR PONTOONS.
GANDHI WAS A GREAT MAN
AND SO WAS ALBERT SCHWEITZER.
THEY DIDN'T NEED STUNTS
TO PROVE THEY WERE MEN.
THEY WEREN'T LODGE MEMBERS,
ALL RIGHT?
WE DECIDED TO GO CLIFF-DIVING
OFF ROCK REEF POINT.
I GOT THE APPLICATION FORM
RIGHT HERE.
REALLY ONLY TWO RULES.
YOU GOTTA PROMISE
TO GO RIGHT OFF THE TOP.
YOU GOTTA DO YOUR BEST
TO HIT THE WATER.
WANT ME TO SIGN YOU UP?
NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
NO, NEVER, NEVER, NO, NO.
GOOD, GOOD, THAT PROVES
IT'S FOR MEN ONLY.
PROVES IT'S FOR MEN
LIKE
YOU
ONLY.
WE'RE A DYING BREED, HAROLD.
COINCIDENCE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL,
REMINDING YOU THAT
WILD ANIMALS CAN SMELL FEAR.
OF COURSE,
IF IT SMELLS BAD ENOUGH,
WHY, THEY WON'T EAT YOU.
HEY, I'M ALIVE.
YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR THIS
UNTIL THE MOON PASSES CHINA.
SHE COMES HOME FROM WORK,
STRESSED TO TEARS,
AND BLUBBERS OUT THE FIVE WORDS
THAT NO MAN UNDERSTANDS:
"I JUST WANT TO BE HELD."
JUST BECAUSE THEY WERE COMING
TO THE END OF THE BREAK
BETWEEN "WHEEL OF FORTUNE"
AND "JEOPARDY",
YOU TRIED TO SUBSTITUTE A HUG
FOR A "HELD".
A FIVE-SECOND HUG?
DON'T YOU KNOW 15 SECONDS
IS THE ABSOLUTE MINIMUM
FOR "I JUST WANT TO BE HELD"?
THAT EXTRA 10 SECONDS
WILL BE THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN THE COUCH
AND THE GARAGE.
FORGET ALL ABOUT THE BED.
YOU COULD HAVE HELD HER
FOR 15 SECONDS
IF YOU'D JUST USED YOUR HEAD.
ALL YOU HAD TO DO WAS
TILT HER TO THE SIDE
AND THEN YOU COULD HAVE SEEN
"JEOPARDY" OVER HER SHOULDER.
YOU COULD HAVE WATCHED
THE WHOLE HALF HOUR
BUT YOU WEREN'T THINKING.
IT'S TIME FOR A QUICK FIX.
CLAIM THAT YOU FEEL
A LITTLE SOMETHING COMING ON
AND YOU DIDN'T WANT TO PASS
THE BUG ON TO HER.
IF YOU THINK YOU'RE UP
TO THE ACTING CHALLENGE,
JUMP BACK WITH A STARTLED LOOK
AND SAY,
"HAVE YOU LOST WEIGHT?"
WHATEVER YOU DO
IN THE GREAT OUTDOORS,
ALWAYS REMEMBER, SAFETY FIRST.
RIGHT, BUZZ?
YOU GOT
THAT RIGHT.
JUST BECAUSE YOU
SAW SOMEBODY ON T.V.
DOING SOMETHING
LIKE BUNGEE-JUMPING,
DOESN'T MEAN
YOU CAN DO IT YOURSELF.
TELL THE VIEWERS
WHAT YOU THINK
THE PROFESSIONAL
BUNGEE-JUMPER WOULD DO FIRST.
THEY'D GO OUT
AND FIND
SOMETHING REALLY
STABLE FOR JUMPING OFF.
LIKE MAYBE
THAT GIANT PINE TREE THERE?
IN HINDSIGHT,
YOU'D THINK THAT,
BUT I FOUND OUT
THAT GIANT PINES
AREN'T THAT GREAT
FOR BUNGEE-JUMPING.
WHAT ABOUT POWER LINES?
YOU MAKE SURE
THERE'S NONE OF THEM AROUND.
OH, FOR SURE.
I THOUGHT
I COULD CLEAR THOSE
BUT ME AND GRAVITY
NEVER DID GET ALONG.
DON'T MAKE
YOUR BUNGEE CORD
OUT OF STUFF
AROUND THE HOUSE.
DON'T GO USING
OLD SUSPENDERS
OR SPANDEX BIKE
PANTS OR ELASTICS OR...
WHAT ELSE
DID I USE, RED?
WELL, I SEE PANTYHOSE,
POLO PYJAMAS, AND JOCK STRAPS.
DON'T USE
ANY OF THOSE.
IF YOU WANT TO GO
BUNGEE-JUMPING,
GO WHERE T@Y HAVE
BUNGEE-JUMPING, RIGHT?
WHERE THEY HAVE
THE RIGHT EQUIPMENT
AND PROFESSIONAL SUPERVISION.
YEAH, WELL,
WE'LL SAY THAT NOW.
ALWAYS REMEMBER, SAFETY FIRST.
SAFETY FIRST,
SAFETY FIRST.
CAN YOU CUT ME
DOWN NOW, RED?
HAVE THEY TURNED
THE POWER OFF YET?
(Electricity zapping)
NOPE.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE
TELEPHONE WIRES.
I'M THINKING,
"HOW MUCH ELECTRICITY'S
"IN A TELEPHONE
WIRE?"
(Laughing)
SO, UNCLE RED, HOW MANY PEOPLE
HAVE SIGNED UP
FOR THE CLIFF-DIVING CONTEST?
NONE OF THE MEN
WERE MOTIVATED TO SIGN UP
UNTIL I ADDED
A SPECTATOR GALLERY
AND GAVE FREE TICKETS
TO THE WIVES AND GIRLFRIENDS
AND THE CONTESTANTS
FOR THE "MISS TEEN" PAGEANT.
WHAT?
A-A-ALL
T-T-THE B-B-BABES--
ALL THE "MISS TEEN" PAGEANT
PEOPLE-- GIRLS WILL BE THERE?
YEAH, EXCEPT FOR
MISS CONGENIALITY.
SHE WAS A LITTLE TOO BUBBLY
FOR OUR CROWD.
YOU KNOW, KNOWING THAT
THE WOMEN WERE GONNA BE THERE
REALLY GOT THE MEN INTERESTED
IN SHOWING OFF THEIR MANHOOD.
ANYBODY WHO IS NOT CLIFF-DIVING
IS PROBABLY NOT A REAL MAN.
HEY, HANDYMEN!
I KNOW A LOT OF TOOLS
COME WITH A BUTTON ON THE SIDE
TO LOCK 'EM
IN THE "ON" POSITION,
BUT I WOULDN'T ADVISE IT!
WELL, AS I TRIED TO WARN YOU
EARLIER IN THE SHOW,
THIS WEEK'S
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL",
BILL'S GONNA TRY
AND WORK HIS WAY--
YEAH, NICE DIVE, BILL.
BILL'S WORKING HIS WAY UP
TO THE CLIFF-DIVING CONTEST.
HE THOUGHT HE'D TRY DIVING
OFF THE DOCK.
MUST HAVE HIT SOMETHING
THAT HE'D EATEN.
HE THOUGHT HE'D GET UP
ON THE CHAIR AND DIVE.
THAT'S A FAMILY HEIRLOOM
THAT'S BEEN IN MY FAMILY
SINCE THE TRAILER BURNED DOWN.
I WONDER WHY HE NEEDED ME
TO HOLD THE--
OH!
WELL, THANK YOU, BILL.
BILL? BILL?
OH, BOY.
GOING WELL, AS USUAL.
I GOT THE CHAIR FIXED.
THAT WAS A WASTE OF TIME.
SO NOW WHAT BILL'S GONNA DO...
NEXT STEP UP, PHASE THREE,
I GUESS,
IS TO GO OFF THE LADDER.
TO ME, I'M NOTICING
HE'S GOT THAT LADDER CLOSE
TO THE EDGE, AND WE TRY TO BE
A BIT SAFETY-CONSCIOUS,
AS YOU KNOW,
OR AT LEAST CONSCIOUS,
HERE AT THE LODGE.
I'M SAYING,
"GET IT RIGHT BACK,"
BUT THE THING WITH SAFETY IS
YOU CAN BE ACTUALLY TOO SAFE.
OHHH!
I'M THINKING WE MAY HAVE
PULLED 'ER BACK TOO FAR.
OH, YEAH.
BUT ANYWAY,
FOR WHATEVER REASON --
MAYBE 'CAUSE HE BANGED
HIS HEAD --
HE'S DECIDED HE'S READY
TO ATTACK THE CLIFF,
SO HE'S GONNA NEED THE ROPE
AND HE WANTS ME...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
I WANT TO SEE HOW IT TURNS OUT,
AND I HOPE YOU DO, TOO.
ROCK REEF POINT IS
A BEAUTIFUL PIECE OF GEOGRAPHY.
IT'S GOT THE INSIDE
OF THE REEF.
I WAS A LITTLE TIRED.
THERE'S THE ROCK AND THE REEF
AND THERE'S A POINT.
YOU DON'T SEE THE POINT
UNLESS YOU GET A CLOSE-UP
OF BILL'S HEAD.
THE IDEA IS, THROW THIS--
THE LOOP WAS TOO SMALL.
WE'RE TRYING TO USE THE ROPE
TO PULL OURSELVES UP,
BUT EVERY ROPE HAS TWO ENDS.
ON THE OTHER END
IS A BIGGER LOOP.
THIS IS GONNA WORK,
AND BILL'S GOOD WITH THE ROPE.
THERE WE GO -- LOOK AT THAT.
SO HE'S ALL SET AND UP WE GO
AND I'M STARTING TO SEE
WHY MOUNTAIN CLIMBING
IS SO DANGEROUS.
WE GET UP THERE.
THAT WAS A HECK OF A CLIMB.
I THOUGHT I SHOULD PULL
THAT ROPE UP
AND GET THAT OUT OF HIS WAY.
WHAT I'D FORGOTTEN WAS,
YOU SEE,
THAT THE ROPE STILL HAD
THAT SMALL LOOP ON THE END.
OH! OH!
BILL HAS KIND OF AN UNORTHODOX
APPROACH TO HIS DIVES.
NOW HE'S READY,
AND UNFORTUNATELY,
HIS FOOT WENT INTO
THAT SMALL LOOP AND NOW
THE ROPE IS NOT AS LONG
AS HIS DIVE!
ON THIS WEEK'S EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW, WE HAVE EXPERTS.
MY UNCLE RED AND HIS
GOOD FRIEND, EDGAR MONTROSE.
(Applause and cheering)
FIRST LETTER GOES AS FOLLOWS:
"DEAR EXPERTS, I TOOK
MY CHILDREN TO A MOVIE RECENTLY
"AND I WAS DISGUSTED
BY THE LANGUAGE AND THE NUDITY,
"AND THAT WAS JUST
IN THE CAR BESIDE US."
(Audience laughing)
"THE MOVIE WAS
"FAR TOO VIOLENT FOR CHILDREN
OR SENIORS
"OR ANYONE
WHO HADN'T SPENT TIME
"IN EITHER PRISON OR THE NAVY.
"HOW CAN WE GET HOLLYWOOD
TO CLEAN UP ITS ACT?
"SIGNED, OFFENDED."
I AGREE WITH THIS VIEWER.
MY WIFE, BERNICE, DRAGGED ME
OUT TO SEE THAT "MARY POPPINS".
MAN, TALK ABOUT OFFENSIVE!
I THOUGHT
I WAS GONNA GET DIABETES!
THEY STARTED SINGING
THAT "SUPERCALI-NARCOLEPTIC-
EXTRA-HALITOSIS",
I JUST ABOUT LOST
MY LICORICE "NIBS".
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT'S WRONG
WITH MOVIES.
THEY GIVE THE KIDS
A FALSE SENSE OF REALITY.
LIKE
THAT MOVIE
"SPEED", WHEN THE BUS BLEW UP.
YOU NEVER GET THAT MUCH FLAME.
(Laughing)
THEY SHOWED IT
AS A BIG FIREBALL
BUT A REAL BUS EXPLOSION
IS ALL SMOKE AND MIRRORS.
I KNOW -- I WAS THE MECHANIC
AT A BUS COMPANY
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
I CAUTION
OUR VIEWER,
THERE HAVE BEEN
SOME GREAT MOVIES
THAT ARE BOTH EDUCATIONAL
AND UPLIFTING.
YEAH, LIKE "THE BRIDGE
OVER THE RIVER KWAI".
DID YOU SEE THAT BABY GO UP
AT THE END?
AND THE TRAIN
WENT CRASHING INTO THE RIVER?
WON AN OSCAR FOR BEST PICTURE.
BUT THAT ONE NOW...
UH, "BRIDGES
OF MADISON COUNTY".
I WAITED FOR ONE OF THOSE
BRIDGES TO GO UP, BUT NOTHING.
(Audience laughing)
I WASN'T THE ONLY ONE
DISAPPOINTED.
EVERYBODY IN THE THEATRE
WAS CRYING BY THE END.
(Laughing)
MOVIES TODAY
JUST DON'T DELIVER.
THERE HAVE BEEN
SOME GREAT FILMS MADE,
LIKE "FOREST GUMP",
"THE PIANO",
"DANCES WITH WOLVES".
I SAW THAT ONE.
(Laughing and applause)
NOW, THE NATIVE GUY WAS OK...
(Laughing)
SHOULD HAVE GOT THE OSCAR.
BUT THE REST OF IT WAS A YAWN.
NOW, WHAT THEY NEEDED THERE IS
ONE OF THOSE BUFFALO
TO GET BACKED UP WITH METHANE.
(Laughing)
HE'LL CATCH HIS HOOF
ON A PIECE OF FLINT
AND GO OFF LIKE
A BIG FURRY GRENADE.
KABOOM!
TALK ABOUT YOUR BURGERS TO GO.
(Laughing)
HAROLD, COME HERE.
GIVE ME THAT MANUAL.
LOOK AT THAT.
"ALL-TERRAIN VEHICLES:
SAND, GRAVEL, LAKES."
WHAT?
"FROZEN LAKES."
AH, FROZEN.
I MIGHT HAVE JUMPED THE GUN
A BIT ON THAT.
WHAT TIME DO WE HAVE TO GET IT
BACK TO THE RENTAL PLACE?
A LITTLE ADVICE FOR ANY OF YOU
PLANNING SOME KIND OF EVENT
FOR YOUR NEXT FAMILY REUNION.
DON'T MAKE IT
A CLIFF-DIVING CONTEST.
(Audience laughing)
THESE ARE REAL MEN.
WANT TO KNOW WHAT REAL MEN DO?
THEY CLIMB ROCK REEF POINT
IN A SELECTION OF BATHING SUITS
YOU DO NOT WANT TO SEE
ON A FULL STOMACH,
AND EVERY ONE OF THEM
CHICKENED OUT.
A BUNCH OF THE WOMEN CLIMBED UP
AND STARTED DIVING OFF
TO SHOW UP
THE MEN.
I KNEW WE WERE IN TROUBLE
WHEN MOOSE THOMPSON'S MOTHER
DID A BELLY-FLOP FROM THE TOP.
IT BROUGHT THE HOUSE DOWN,
AND PART OF THE LODGE.
BOY, DID SHE HIT
THE WATER!
PORT ASBESTOS HASN'T HAD
THAT MUCH RAIN IN 12 YEARS.
IT PROVES THERE'S NO REAL MEN
LEFT IN THESE PARTS.
THERE ARE, BUT LOTS OF THEM
ARE WOMEN, UNFORTUNATELY.
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
YOU GO GET DRIED OFF.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
MAYBE YOU CAN MAKE
THE NEIGHBOURS
COME OVER ANOTHER NIGHT.
MAYBE I'M NOT A REAL MAN
BUT I'M REAL TIRED
AND NOT REAL INTERESTED
IN BEING REAL SOCIABLE.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): OK, ALL RISE.
ALL RISE.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN.