[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN
IN TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD HAS
A PHONE IN SEX SHOW,
BILL GOES HAND GLIDING,
AND I TURN A CANOE INTO A SWING.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: AND NOW HERE'S
A MAN WHO CUTS HIS OWN
WOOD, CHANGES HIS OWN OIL,
MAKES HIS OWN CHEESE
AND ALL AT THE SAME TIME
MY UNCLE, YOUR HOST,
MISTER RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
THAT'S THE KIND OF INTRO
YOU JUST DREAM UP ESPECIALLY
IF YOU EAT A LOT OF GARLIC.
>>HAROLD: IT'S MY WAY OF
DELIVERING THE UNEXPECTED
>>RED: DELIVERING THE UNEXPECTED
HAROLD YOU'D HAVE A
HARD TIME TOPPING YOUR
MOTHER'S OBSTETRICIAN.
IT'S BEEN KIND OF A BAD WEEK
UP AT POSSUM LODGE THIS WEEK
IT STARTED OUT MONDAY MORNING
WITH THE BREAKFAST CHALLENGE.
>>HAROLD: OH NOW THE BREAKFAST
CHALLENGE THAT'S WHERE ALL YOU
GUYS ALL JUMP UP FROM THE
BREAKFAST TABLE JUMP IN YOUR
BOATS AND ROAR AROUND THE
LAKE FOR LIKE 10 MINUTES?
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH, THE BREAKFAST
CHALLENGE IS THAT THE LAST GUY
TO RUN OUT OF GAS IN HIS
BOAT HAS TO DO ALL THE
BREAKFAST DISHES.
>>HAROLD: GOT THEIR ENGINES
WIDE OPEN, THEY'RE ZOOMING
AROUND THERE IT WAS TERRIBLE
7 O'CLOCK IN THE MORNING
ALL THAT NOISE ROARING!
THAT'S PLEASANT ISN'T IT?
>>RED: WELL NOBODY REALLY MINDS
THERE'S NOBODY OUT THERE
MAYBE A FEW FISHERMEN.
THEY DON'T MIND AT ALL
IN FACT I THINK FISH ARE EASIER
TO CATCH WHEN THEY'RE STAMPEDING
UNFORTUNATELY THIS MONDAY
WE MET UP WITH A BUNCH OF
YUPPIES OUT ON A CANOE TRIP.
>>HAROLD: I HOPE 'MET UP'
DOESN'T MEAN SMASHED INTO YOU
KNOW MOST YUPPIES ARE LAWYERS.
>>RED: WELL THEY'RE SURE NOT
SWIMMERS I CAN TELL YOU THAT.
TOOK US OVER AN HOUR TO GET
THE WATER OUT OF THE FAT GUY.
IF ANYBODY SHOULD BE SUING
ANYBODY WE SHOULD BE SUING THEM
I MEAN THE CEDAR STRIP CANOES
AREN'T TOO BAD BECAUSE THEY
KIND OF SPLINTER UP WHEN
YOU RAM THEM
YOU SHOULD SEE THE DAMAGE THAT
A LOON CANOE CAN DO TO A PROP
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU'RE DOING
FULL TILT IN HER THERE.
>>HAROLD: I'M NOT SAYING THAT
I'M A PSYCHIC OR ANYTHING HERE
UNCLE RED I'M JUST GOING TO
SAY WHAT I THINK AND I THINK
THAT VERY SHORTLY SOMEBODY
IS GOING TO BE HANDING YOU
A LEGAL DOCUMENT THAT'S GOING
TO BE CHANGING THE QUALITY
OF YOUR LIFE.
>>RED: WELL YOU'RE WRONG HAROLD
IT'S ALREADY HAPPENED.
>>HAROLD: AH HA!
>>RED: THIS IS A LEGAL PETITION
THAT STINKY PETERSON STARTED
AND WE'RE ALL GOING TO SIGN IT
AND GET ALL THOSE WUSSES AND
THEIR CANOES OFF THE LAKE.
>>HAROLD: I DON'T THINK YOU
SHOULD MAKE JUDGMENTS
LIKE THAT UNCLE RED.
>>RED: IT'S NOT A JUDGMENT
HAROLD IT'S JUST
A STATEMENT OF FACT.
>>HAROLD: WELL YOU DID
CALL THEM WUSSES.
>>RED: YEAH WELL THAT'S
ROUGHLY WHAT THEY ARE HAROLD
A WUSS IS ANYBODY THAT DIDDLES
AROUND IN A CANOE AND THEN
WHINES WHEN THEY'RE T-BONED
BY A LODGE MEMBER.
>>HAROLD: THAT IS YOUR OPINION.
>>RED: FINE.
>>HAROLD: AND THAT'S WHAT
MAKES IT A JUDGMENT AND
THAT'S MY OPINION.
>>RED: IT'S NOT A JUDGMENT
HAROLD, I DON'T JUDGE PEOPLE
AND ANYBODY WHO SAYS I DO IS
A CROSS-EYED, PENCIL-NECKED,
RUBBER-HEADED GEEK.
WHEN HUNTING SEASON'S OVER
NOBODY'S ON A BENDER
WE'RE TOO BUSY WITH
ROPES AND DUCT TAPE
TYING CARCASSES TO FENDERS
A BULL-LINE OR A CLOVE HITCH
IT'S EASY TO GET IT WRONG
LIKE ONE TIME A GUY TIED
A MOOSE TO HIS FRONT WHEEL
LOOKED PRETTY FUNNY
SPINNING AWAY OUT THERE
BUT IT WAS SAFE UNTIL
HE TRIED TO PASS A CYCLIST
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE
GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW TO
TURN AN OLD CANOE INTO
SOMETHING THAT WILL NOT ONLY
GET YOUR NEIGHBOURS TALKING
IT MAY EVENTUALLY LEAD
TO A FOR SALE SIGN
ON THEIR FRONT LAWN.
NOW I'M SURE A BUNCH OF YOU
HAVE HEARD THE JOKE ABOUT
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
A CANOE AND A LODGE MEMBER?
A CANOE TIPS...
WELL ACTUALLY CANOES AND LODGE
MEMBERS HAVE A HECK OF A LOT
IN COMMON, THEY BOTH ARE ALL
FULL OF DENTS AND STUFF
(CRASHING & BANGING)
BUT OTHER THAN THAT THERE'S
QUITE A DIFFERENCE.
BUT YOU KNOW PEOPLE WOULD LOOK
AT AN OLD CANOE LIKE THIS
AND THEY'D JUST SAY WELL
THAT'S JUST A LEAKY OLD BOAT
MORE HOLES THAN ANYTHING ELSE
AND BUT THE HANDYMAN HE SEES
THIS AS POTENTIAL BECAUSE YOU
COULD TURN THIS INTO SOMETHING.
YOU COULD MAKE IT, WELL YOU
COULD MAKE IT A REALLY BIG
DINNER BELL OR A FIRM HAMMOCK
OR YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE YOU COULD
MAKE OUT OF ONE OF THESE
IS A PORCH SWING.
YEAH, YEAH, A PORCH SWING.
OKAY STEP ONE YOU GOT TO CUT
ONE OF THE SIDES PORT OR
STARBOARD WHICHEVER ONE HAS
THE MOST DENTS IN IT
RIGHT ABOUT EXACTLY RIGHT HERE.
(BANGING & CRASHING)
(HACKSAW RASPING)
(CIRCULAR SAW WHINING)
(THUD OF AXE HITTING)
(CRASH OF TABLE FALLING)
(CHAINSAW BUZZING)
>>RED: BY GOLLY ONCE THEY
GET THE FUNGUS INTO THE
FIBERGLASS THERE IT'S A REAL
PIG TO GET A BLADE THROUGH.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT MUCH BUT
ANYWAY ONCE YOU'VE GOT THE
SIDE CUT OUT WHAT DO YOU
DO NEXT, OH YOU'RE DONE THAT'S
IT YOU'RE DONE THEN AND WHAT
YOU DO IS YOU TAKE YOUR BOW ROPE
AND YOU TAKE YOUR OTHER ROPE
ON THE OTHER END YOU KNOW
ACTUALLY MAYBE THAT'S THE BOW
AND YOU JUST TIE THESE UP TO
THE BEAM ACROSS YOUR
FRONT PORCH.
REMEMBER A FEW WEEKS AGO
WE SHOWED YOU HOW TO MAKE
A FRONT PORCH OUT OF OLD
ICE CREAM TUBS
WELL USE A DIFFERENT PORCH
NOW ISN'T THAT A BEAUTIFUL
PIECE OF AMERICANA?
AND WE'LL JUST ADD SOME LIFE
JACKET CUSHION TYPE DEALS
HERE FOR THE SEATS
IT'S ALSO A GOOD IDEA IN CASE
THE MARINE POLICE HAPPEN
TO CRUISE BY...
AND TO ME WHEN YOU'RE
SITTING IN A UNIT OF THIS
NATURE YOU'RE GOING TO WANT TO
HAVE YOUR FAVOURITE BEVERAGE
WITHIN THE VICINITY OF YOUR
RIGHT HAND SO I WOULD SUGGEST
YOU STICK THE COOLER RIGHT UP
INTO THE CANOE IT'LL KEEP YOUR
DRINKS SHAKEN NOT STIRRED.
(SNAP OF ROPE BREAKING)
ALL RIGHT NOW THE QUESTION THERE
IS DID THAT ROPE BREAK OR
DID JUST THE KNOT SLIP?
I THINK IT WAS JUST THE KNOT
(SNAP OF ROPE BREAKING)
NO I GUESS IT WAS THE ROPE.
WELL I THINK I GOT HER NOW
AND YOU KNOW WHAT WITH A HEAVIER
ROPE I TOOK THE DRAWSTRING OUT
OF THE FLAP ON MOOSE THOMPSON'S
PYJAMAS THAT'S ONE OF THE
GREAT THINGS ABOUT BEING UP
HERE AT THE LODGE IF SOMETHING
BREAKS YOU JUST USE SOMETHING
ELSE INSTEAD.
(LOUD CRASH)
THAT'S THE GREAT THING ABOUT
THE LODGE WHEN SOMETHING BREAKS
YOU JUST USE SOMETHING
ELSE INSTEAD.
WELL TIME FOR ME TO GET BACK
TO THE SWINGIN' 60'S.
(LOUD CREAKING)
>>RED: I'LL TELL YOU WE ARE
RUNNING OUT OF GREAT THINGS
ABOUT THE LODGE.
>>HAROLD: IT'S THAT PART
OF THE SHOW AGAIN WHERE
WE EXPOSE THOSE 3 LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO DIFFICULT
TO SAY 'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT
IS ONE MORE TIME IS MY
UNCLE RED AND HIS GOOD
FRIENDS MR. GLEN BRAXTON
AND MR. BOB STUYVESANT.
>>HAROLD: THERE'S
A CHRISTMAS CARD.
ALL RIGHT, 'DEAR SIRS I DRIVE
A VAN, IT'S A GREAT VEHICLE
EXCEPT FOR ONE MAJOR
DESIGN FLAW REAR VISIBILITY.
EVEN WITH THE EXTRA LARGE SIDE
MIRRORS AND A REAR VIEW MIRROR
THERE'S A BLIND SPOT AT THE
BACK OF MY VAN THAT'S BIG
ENOUGH TO HIDE A SAINT BERNARD.
A DOG COULD FALL ASLEEP BEHIND
THE VAN AND YOU'D NEVER SEE IT
UNTIL YOU PULLED AWAY.
ANYWAY MY QUESTION IS
HOW DO YOU TELL A CHILD
THEIR PET IS DEAD?'
>>RED: WELL I THINK YOUR BEST
ROUTE THERE IS JUST TO LIE
JUST TELL HIM THAT THE DOG
HAS RUN OFF AND JOINED A CIRCUS
AND WILL BE BACK IN A FEW YEARS.
>>BOB: YOU KNOW I LOST A PET
ONCE WHEN I WAS 9 YEAH,
THE GARDENER FROM OUR FAMILY
ESTATE RAN A LAWN TRACTOR
OVER FIFI MY MINIATURE
FRENCH POODLE, I LOVED HER.
BUT YOU KNOW MY MOTHER AND
MY FATHER NEVER SAID A WORD
NO THEY JUST WENT RIGHT OUT
AND PURCHASED ANOTHER PUREBRED
POODLE IT LOOKED THE SAME
THEY JUST CALLED HIM FIFI.
>>HAROLD: THAT'S LIVING
IN DENIAL.
>>BOB: IT IS?
>>HAROLD: YES IT IS,
THAT'S CALLED LIVING IN DENIAL.
>>BOB: I DIDN'T KNOW THAT
OKAY I GUESS I WOULD RECOMMEND
LIVING IN DENIAL.
>>HAROLD: MR BRAXTON HOW
ABOUT YOURSELF, YOU HAVE KIDS.
>>GLEN: WELL WHAT NORMALLY
DELORES AND I DO IS WE BRING
THE GIRLS IN WHEN WE'VE LOST
A PET AND WE SIT THEM DOWN
AND WE TELL THEM THAT GOD'S
COME TO OUR HOUSE AND HE'S
GONE TO A BETTER PLACE
FOR A GREATER PURPOSE.
>>RED: BOY THAT SOUNDS
REAL NICE.
>>HAROLD: THAT'S VERY NICE.
>>GLEN: YEAH BUT NOW THE GIRLS
HATE GOD, SO CAN'T WIN.
>>HAROLD: OKAY ALL RIGHTY
AH WELL THERE YOU HAVE IT
3 EXPERTS AND 3 OPINIONS
BUT YOU KNOW IF YOU WANT TO KNOW
MY OPINION I'D SAY JUST HONESTY
IS THE BEST POLICY.
>>RED: OH REALLY HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: YES.
>>RED: WELL REMEMBER
THAT HAMSTER YOU HAD?
>>HAROLD: YEAH.
>>RED: RAN OFF TO JOIN
THE CIRCUS?
>>HAROLD: OH NO!
SHE FELL OFF THE HIGH WIRE?
>>RED: IT IS WINTER
I PRESS THE ACCELERATOR
TO THE FLOOR AND HOLD IT
AS I WAIT FOR MY SPINNING TIRES
TO MELT THEIR WAY DOWN
TO SOMETHING HARD
THEN A LOUD POP
SO THAT'S WHERE I
LEFT THE GARDEN RAKE.
>>RED: GOING TO TAKE A FEW
MINUTES AND GO AND SEE
RANGER GORD 'CAUSE I WORRY
ABOUT HIM STUCK UP IN
THAT TOWER, YOU OKAY GORD?
>>GORD: SURE YOU KNOW SOMETIMES
I FEEL LIKE I'M THE LUCKIEST
GUY ON THE PLANET.
>>RED: OH THAT'S GREAT.
>>GORD: OR THE ONLY GUY
THE ONLY GUY IN THE UNIVERSE.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
>>GORD: THERE'S STILL
A WORLD OUT THERE HUH RED?
PEOPLE STILL FALL IN LOVE
AND HAVE BABIES HUH?
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH.
>>GORD: THEY STILL WATCH TV
AND PLAY RUBIC'S CUBE?
>>RED: YEAH.
>>GORD: BOY I MISS
BATTLESTAR GALLACTICA AND
STARSKY AND HUTCH.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>GORD: YEAH BOY OH BOY
YOU KNOW WHEN I GET BACK
TO CIVILIZATION I'VE GOT THIS
IDEA IT'S A PATENT SHH!
I'M GOING TO MAKE THIS
MACHINE THAT'S GOING TO BE
ABLE TO TAPE RECORD TV SHOWS.
>>RED: OH YEAH A VIDEO
CASSETTE RECORDER.
>>GORD: LIKE AN 8-TRACK CAN
TAPE MUSIC BUT THIS IS
GOING TO TAPE TV SHOWS.
>>RED: YEAH IT'S A
VIDEO CASSETTE RECORDER.
>>GORD: YEAH, YEAH!
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH, A V.C.R.
>>GORD: YOU KNOW THAT NAME?
>>RED: YEAH SURE.
>>GORD: V.C.R. GREAT
YEAH EXACTLY THAT'S WAY BETTER
THAN WHAT I WAS GOING
TO CALL IT.
>>RED: WHAT WERE YOU
GOING TO CALL IT?
>>GORD: BETA.
>>RED: WELL THIS CANOE VERSUS
POWER BOAT THING HAS TURNED
INTO AN ALL OUT WAR.
>>HAROLD: I DON'T WANT TO
DISAPPOINT YOU UNCLE RED
BUT MY CONSCIENCE WILL NOT
ALLOW ME TO SIGN THAT PETITION.
>>RED: IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS
HAROLD WHATEVER GOES ON IN YOUR
MIND IS BETWEEN YOU AND YOUR
PARAPSYCHOLOGIST/PUMP REPAIR MAN
AND BESIDES, THIS IS NOT EVEN
A PETITION THIS IS AN OFFICIAL
NOTIFICATION FROM THE GOVERNMENT
THAT POSSUM LAKE IS BEING
CONSIDERED AS A NON-POWER
BOAT LAKE.
>>HAROLD: NON-POWER BOAT
OH THAT'S SO GREAT!
IMAGINE POSSUM LAKE WITHOUT
ANY SMOKE AND SCREAMING
DIRTY ENGINES,
MAN THAT WOULD BE EXCELLENT!
>>RED: YEAH HAROLD THAT'D
BE REAL GOOD YOU KNOW EXCEPT
FOR A FEW MINOR ADJUSTMENTS
LIKE FOR EXAMPLE ALL OF OUR
MOTORS WOULD BE USELESS
WE HAVE TO GET RID OF 12,000
GALLONS OF PREMIUM UNLEADED
EVERYBODY WOULD QUIT THE LODGE
AND I'D BE OUT OF BUSINESS
BUT HEY ONCE WE'RE OVER THOSE
LITTLE SPEED BUMPS I THINK
IT WOULD BE AS YOU
SAY EXCELLENT.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED YOU DID
BRING THIS ON YOURSELF
I MEAN YOU COULD HAVE SAT DOWN
AND TALKED TO THOSE CANOEISTS.
>>RED: HAROLD WE HAD A MEETING
WITH THEM RIGHT OUT IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE LAKE.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH WHO COULD
EVEN HEAR ANYTHING JUNIOR'S
THROTTLE WAS JUST SCREAMING
THERE LIKE 8 ZILLION R.P.M.'S.
>>RED: WE DID HAVE A LITTLE
LINKAGE JAMMING PROBLEM
I'LL ADMIT THAT.
>>HAROLD: LINKAGE JAMMING
HOW COME IT ONLY GOT JAMMED
WHEN THEY WERE SPEAKING?
IT SEEMED TO SETTLE RIGHT
DOWN WHEN YOU WERE
SPOUTING OFF.
>>RED: I DON'T KNOW WHY HAROLD
I'M NOT A MARINE MECHANIC
ALL RIGHT.
>>HAROLD: YOU WERE RUDE AND
BEING COUNTER PRODUCTIVE
AND NOW YOU'RE BEING
PUNISHED FOR IT.
>>RED: BOY HAROLD THAT SOUNDS
KIND OF JUDGMENTAL TO ME.
>>HAROLD: OH NO, NO, NO, NO,
YOU SEE I AM NOT JUDGMENTAL
NOR AM I TEMPERAMENTAL.
>>RED: WELL YOU'RE
SOME KIND OF MENTAL.
>>HAROLD: IT'S NOT
EASY BEING ME.
>>RED: WHO ELSE WOULD EVEN TRY?
OH HONEY
I'M VERY FOND OF YOU HONEY
DON'T YOU KNOW IT'S TRUE
HONEY ON TOAST
OR HONEYDEW
BUT HONEY ON THE
TOILET SEAT IS TACKY
>>RED: BILL TOLD ME TO COME UP
AND FIND HIM IN HIS PUP TENT
SO THAT'S WHAT I DID.
HE SAID PUP TENT BUT
I THINK HE MEANT POP TART.
ANYWAY BILL GOT SOME KIND OF
YEAH OKAY BILL RELAX GOT SOME
KIND OF ADVENTURE OH A LITTLE
HANG GLIDER IN HIS PANTS
THERE SOME KID'S TOY
OH, OH, OH, I WORRY ABOUT
BILL SOMETIMES, THE IDEA IS
I GUESS HE HAD A HANG GLIDER
IN HIS TENT, I DON'T
SEE ANYTHING IN THERE.
AND HE'S SAYING NO, NO,
THERE'S NOT A HANG GLIDER
IN THE TENT THE HANG GLIDER
IS THE TENT GOING TO CONVERT
THIS VERY STRANGE BUT I'M
NOT GOING TO DO IT
SO I'M ALL FOR IT.
SO HE PILES HER A LITTLE HIGH
THERE BILL GOING TO BE A LITTLE
DIFFICULT TO SEE JUST EXACT
BUT IT'S A NICE DAY FOR A WALK
OH HE'S GOING TO COME
BACK AND GET ME.
NOW HE'S TRYING TO GUIDE
ME AND I'M NOT SURE
THIS WAS THE MOST BRILLIANT
THING WE'VE DONE ALL DAY
BUT THAT WOULD BE A CHALLENGE.
OH I SAW HIM GO DOWN AND
I'M USING ALL THOSE TENT POLES
SO I JUST HANDED THAT TO HIM
WHAT I'D FORGOTTEN OF COURSE
WAS THAT THEY WERE A SECTIONAL
THING AT THIS POINT I THOUGHT
HE WAS JUST ENJOYING HIMSELF
SO I LET GO OF THE LAST BIT
AND THEN HE HOLDS ONE AND
UP HE COMES THERE WE GO OKAY
FINE NOW WHAT WE GOT TO DO
IS START TAKING THAT TENT AND
CONVERTING THAT INTO A HANG
GLIDER AND THE FIRST THING
HE DOES IS GET THE BACKPACK
SECTION AND IT'S REALLY JUST
THE FRAME OF THE BACKPACK
OH GOT SOME TAPE ON HIM
OH WELL, OH WELL PORTIONS
OF THE THE RED GREEN SHOW
WERE TAPED EARLIER.
>>BILL: AHH!
>>RED: I REALLY FELT
BAD ABOUT THAT...
SO WE TAKE THE TENT POLES
AND RESHAPE THEM AND THEN PUT
THE CANVAS OVERTOP AND WHAT
HAVE YOU AND YOU'VE GOT
YOURSELF KIND OF A OH, OH,
HE FELT REALLY BAD ABOUT THAT.
YOU'VE GOT KIND OF A IT'S KIND
OF MORE OR LESS A BIG KITE
AND THEN BILL PUTS THE BACKPACK
FRAME ON THERE HOOKS THAT ON
TO A SEATBELT TYPE OF A RIG
AND THEN I'M GOING TO HOOK
THE KITE ONTO THE BACKPACK
AND YOU CAN SEE IT STARTING
TO TAKE SHAPE AND WE'RE LOOKING
PRETTY GOOD BUT IT LOOKS
KIND OF DANGEROUS
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU'RE
STANDING ANYWHERE, OW! OW!
ANYWAY AWAY SHE GOES
BON VOYAGE HAPPY FLYING BILL
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH MY GOSH!
HOME IS ANYWHERE YOU HANG
YOUR GLIDER.
>>RED: THIS IS THE PART OF
THE SHOW WHERE HAROLD GETS
TO TALK TO THE YOUNG PEOPLE
OF OUR COUNTRY, HOPEFULLY
THEY WON'T LISTEN.
>>HAROLD: GOOD EVENING
AND WELCOME TO DR. HAROLD'S
TEEN PHONE IN SEX SHOW
WHERE TEENAGERS CAN PHONE IN
AND ASK QUESTIONS AND GET
ANSWERS FROM SOMEONE JUST
LIKE THEMSELVES.
SO IF YOU KNOW YOU'RE A TEENAGER
WHATEVER COOL OR WHATEVER
IT DOESN'T MATTER JUST PHONE
IN AND TALK TO ME DR. HAROLD
THE NUMBER HERE IS 2-2- SORRY!
555-5555 I'LL GIVE YOU A MINUTE
TO JOT THAT DOWN AND THEN JUST
CALL IN AND WE'LL SPEAK OPENLY
AND FRANKLY ABOUT SEX.
LINES ARE OPEN.
SO YOU WANT TO PHONE IN
JUST FEEL FREE IT'S
555-5555 PLEASE.
(COUGHING)
PHONE IN, I'M HERE TO TALK TO
(PHONE RINGING)
YES, HELLO, HI.
TALK TO ME.
OH HI MOOSE, IT'S MOOSE THOMPSON
OH NO SORRY, SORRY, ANONYMOUS.
ANONYMOUS GO AHEAD TALK TO
ME BECAUSE I'M A PROFESSIONAL
NO WAY! (GIGGLES)
YEAH (GIGGLES) NO WAY! NO WAY!
YEAH GET OUT! NO YOU DON'T
YOU NO THAT'S GOOD,
A LOT OF PEOPLE DO THAT WELL
I DO YEAH, LIKE NO THAT'S FINE
YOU'D BE SURPRISED YEAH WELL
I DON'T KNOW V.H.S. OR BETA
DEPENDS WHATEVER YOU WANT
TO USE...
WELL, WELL, WELL, SOMEBODY
HAS A PROBLEM WITH S-E-X.
>>RED: THE QUICKEST WAY FOR
ME TO GET TO THOSE YUPPIE
CANOEISTS WAS BY WATER WHICH
UNFORTUNATELY MEANT I HAD TO
USE HAP'S WATER TAXI BUT
I HAD SOME MESSAGES
I WANTED TO DELIVER TO THEM.
>>HAP: OH YEAH SOME KIND
OF INJUNCTION IS IT?
>>RED: NO WAY,
ANONYMOUS THREATS.
>>HAP: NOW RED IF THERE'S
ANYTHING I LEARNED IN MY YEARS
ON THE SUPREME COURT
IT'S THAT MOST CONFLICTS
CAN BE AVOIDED BY A LITTLE
DOSE OF COMPROMISE.
>>RED: SUPREME COURT HAP?
>>HAP: YEAH I WAS THIRD
ON THE RIGHT.
>>RED: THAT BLACK WOMAN?
>>HAP: YEAH.
ORIGINALLY I WAS COURT CLERK
BUT A JUDGE DIED SO
I STEPPED IN.
>>RED: COURT CLERK HAP?
I CAN'T PICTURE YOU ASKING
ANYONE TO TELL THE TRUTH,
NOTHING BUT THE TRUTH.
>>HAP: OH THERE WAS ONE
VERY CONTROVERSIAL CASE
MCENROE VERSUS CONNER
I GOT BOTH PARTIES TO SIT DOWN
GOT THEM TO COMPROMISE A WEE BIT
AND YOU KNOW AFTER THAT QUEBEC
DECIDED TO STAY PART OF CANADA.
>>RED: OH YEAH.
>>HAP: YEAH AND THEN I WAS
MAHATMA GHANDI'S RIGHT HAND MAN
I TAUGHT HIM THE ART OF
COMPROMISE I TAUGHT HIM TO
CALM DOWN, TAUGHT HIM HUMILITY,
TAUGHT HIM MODESTY.
>>RED: OH THOSE ARE
IMPORTANT LESSONS HAP.
>>HAP: BUT IF YOU WANT A REAL
DEMONSTRATION OF THE POWER OF
COMPROMISE LET ME TELL YOU
ABOUT HOW I GOT NIXON
TO GO QUIETLY.
>>RED: HAP IS THERE ANY
CHANCE THAT WE CAN GO QUIETLY?
>>RED: WELL THIS COMPROMISE
THING SEEMS TO BE WORKING OUT
PRETTY WELL, THE CANOEISTS HAVE
AGREED TO ALLOW US TO HAVE
OUTBOARD MOTORS AS LONG
AS THEY ARE LIMITED
TO 10 HORSEPOWER.
>>HAROLD: THAT'S A PRETTY
SMALL MOTOR.
>>RED: YEAH BUT YOU CAN
GET 4 OR 5 OF THEM ACROSS
THE BACK OF THE BOAT.
IN FACT MOOSE THOMPSON BOLTED
A BUNCH OF PARK BENCHES AT
THE END OF HIS BOAT THERE
AND HE'S GOT ABOUT 6 OF THEM
ON EACH BENCH SO I BELIEVE HE
HAS ABOUT 30 MOTORS ON THERE.
>>HAROLD: THAT DOESN'T
SOUND VERY SAFE.
>>RED: OH IT'S SAFER HAROLD
HE CAN HAVE 29 MOTORS CONK OUT
AND STILL MAKE IT HOME.
HEY YOU GOT A LOT OF POWER THERE
MIND YOU BY THE TIME HE PULL
STARTS THEM ALL HE'S SO CRAMPED
UP HE CAN'T STEER.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED THAT'S
CHEATING, THAT'S VIOLATING
THE SPIRIT OF THE AGREEMENT.
>>RED: WELL HAROLD THAT'S ALL
THE ART OF NEGOTIATING YOU KNOW
AND THEY CAME OUT OKAY TOO ALL
RIGHT BECAUSE WE AGREED TO FIX
ALL THE CANOES AND THE PADDLES
AND WE'RE GOING TO BUY ONE
OF THOSE YUPPIES A NEW SHIRT
I GUESS THE ALLIGATOR DROWNED.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: MEETING TIME.
>>RED: YEAH YOU GO AHEAD HAROLD
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
>>RED: SO THIS IS A SITUATION
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY
EVERYBODY WINS,
WE GOT OUR MOTORS BACK AND
WE'RE BACK IN BUSINESS AND
THE CANOES ARE GOING TO BE
BETTER THAN NEW BECAUSE THEY'RE
GOING TO LOOK GREAT WITH THAT
SHINY SILVER DUCT TAPE
ALL OVER THEM.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
I LEARNED A LOT ABOUT JUDGING
AND COMPROMISE TONIGHT AND
I'M GOING TO BE COMING HOME
STRAIGHT AFTER THE MEETING AND
I WAS KIND OF LOOKING FORWARD
TO A ROMANTIC EVENING IN
A COMPROMISING POSITION
IN A NON JUDGMENTAL SETTING.
AND EVERYBODY ELSE ON BEHALF
OF MYSELF AND HAROLD AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>ALL: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT BEFORE WE GET
STARTED OLD MAN SEDGEWICK TOLD
ME THAT HE HAD NOTHING TO SAY.