I’M LOOKING FOR A
BETTER WAY
PUTTING WINDOW TINTING
ON MY VEHICLE
WHEN I GOT THINKING
SUNGLASSES ARE LIKE WINDOW
TINTING FOR HUMANS.
THEY MAKE YOU LOOK
INTIMIDATING, MYSTERIOUS,
OR JUST PLAIN COOL.
IF SUNGLASSES CAN
DO THAT FOR PEOPLE,
WHY CAN'T THEY ALSO
DO IT FOR MY TRUCK?
BECAUSE YOU GET THOSE HOMEMADE
DO-IT-YOURSELF WINDOW
TINTING KITS,
AND THEY NEVER GO ON EVEN.
AFTER A FEW WEEKS IT STARTS TO
LOOK LIKE LAWRENCE WELK NIGHT
AT THE SENIORS' HOME,
ALL BUBBLES AND WRINKLES.
AND THEN AT NIGHT, THERE'S
NOT ENOUGH LIGHT TO SEE
WHERE YOU'RE GOIN'.
WHEREAS, WITH THE HANDYMAN
WINDOW TINTING SYSTEM,
YOU'RE IN CONTROL.
YOU JUST FLIP UP YOUR TINT
FOR MAXIMUM VISIBILITY.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HEY, I APPRECIATE THAT.
I GOT BIG NEWS.
WE HAD WHAT YOU CALL A
HORTICULTURAL BREAKTHROUGH
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
I'VE GOT A PRODUCT THAT
I THINK EVERY HOMEOWNER
IS GONNA WANT TO BUY.
I'VE GOT A NEW KIND
OF GRASS SEED HERE.
SEE? HUH?
ACTUALLY IT WAS
CREATED BY ACCIDENT,
BUT WHO WASN'T?
YEAH, WHAT HAPPENED WAS I
KNOCKED OVER A SHELF
IN THE TOOL SHED
A LITTLE WHILE AGO,
AND SOME OF THE GRASS SEED
MIXED DOWN WITH SOME OF THE
PAINT AND THE CHEMICALS
AND SO ON
ON THE DIRT FLOOR.
I DIDN'T THINK
ANYTHING OF IT.
BUT SIX MONTHS LATER,
LOOK AT THIS.
THE GRASS GREW THIS HIGH,
AND THEN IT STOPPED GROWING.
IS THAT PERF --
I HAD A LOOK AT
THOSE LAWN MOWERS OF YOURS,
AND THEY'RE
NOT WORTH MUCH.
YOU GOT THE THE MISMATCHED
WHEELS AND THE BROOM HANDLES.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TROUBLE
SELLIN' THOSE, RED.
I'VE NEVER SEEN A WRENCH USED
AS A LAWN MOWER BLADE
BEFORE EITHER.
DALTON, I DON'T CARE
IF YOU HAVE TO SELL
THEM BY THE POUND.
I DON'T NEED
'EM ANYMORE.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT GETTING
A RIDING MOWER?
NO, NO.
LOOK AT THIS, DALTON.
I GOT A NEW KIND
OF GRASS.
IMAGINE A LAWN THAT
ONLY GROWS THAT HIGH.
OH, BOY, WHAT'D YOU
PUT ON THAT?
SHORTENING?
[ LAUGHTER ]
FINE.
NOW, YOU KNOW --
NOW, PERSONALLY, I COULD
LISTEN TO THAT KIND OF
HUMOUR ALL DAY.
BUT LUCKILY THIS
ISN'T THE DAY,
SO I'M GONNA TAKE
THE GRASS SEED,
I'M GONNA RE-SEED THE
WHOLE LODGE PROPERTY.
RED, IF WE'VE GOT GRASS THAT
ONLY GROWS A COUPLE INCHES,
WE COULD BE SITTIN'
ON A GOLD MINE, YOU KNOW.
WE SHOULD PUT OUT
A BIG ANNOUNCEMENT.
YEAH, OKAY.
BUT LET'S WAIT TILL
WE SELL THE LAWN MOWERS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I'M HERE TO GIVE YOU
SOME ADVICE
ON DOING YOUR FIREWORKS
DISPLAY THIS YEAR.
NOW, MY SUGGESTION IS TO FORGET
ABOUT THE FIRECRACKERS,
AND BLOW UP SOME OLD
FURNITURE WITH DYNAMITE.
NOW, GIVEN THE CHOICE,
WOULD YOU RATHER SEE SOME
PATHETIC LITTLE SPARKY LIGHT
SHOOTING UP THROUGH
THE AIR AND GOING POP --
VERY QUIETLY I MIGHT ADD --
OR CHUNKS OF DIRT AND WOOD
FLYING UP INTO THE AIR
ACCOMPANIED BY A
THUNDEROUS EXPLOSION?
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
NOW, THROUGH
THE MAGIC OF TELEVISION
AND THIS HANDY
REMOTE DETONATOR,
I AM GOING
TO LET YOU WATCH
MY EXPLOSIONS DISPLAY
FOR THIS YEAR.
NOW, WHAT I'VE DONE,
FOR YOUR VIEWING PLEASURE,
IS I'VE NAMED EACH EXPLOSION,
JUST LIKE THE DIFFERENT
FIRECRACKERS
ARE NAMED ACCORDING TO THEIR
PARTICULAR PROPERTIES.
NOW, THIS ONE I CALL
THE EXPLODING DRESSER.
AND THIS ONE I CALL THE
EXPLODING COMPUTER TABLE.
AND THIS ONE,
THE EXPLODING BOOKSHELF.
UH, I HAVEN'T GOT
A NAME FOR THIS ONE YET,
BUT IT'S MY FAVOURITE.
AND JUST LIKE
THE REAL FIREWORKS,
I'VE SET IT TO MUSIC.
[ SMOOTH JAZZ ]
THIS THING ISN'T WORKING.
LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER,
ED FRID, WILL BE IN
ANY MINUTE NOW.
I THINK HE'S GOING TO BRING
A BIRD OF SOME KIND.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT KIND.
HE HAS SO MANY TYPES OF --
HERE HE IS.
WHAT DO YOU --
OH, HE'S GOT
A FALCON.
OH, GREAT, YOU GOT
THE FALCON.
THAT'S TERRIFIC.
SH-H-H.
NOT SO LOUD, RED.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO,
MAKE IT MAD OR SOMETHING?
YOU TRYING TO SCARE IT
INTO A FRENZY, OR WHAT?
WELL, SORRY.
I MEAN IT'S --
IT'S TAME,
ISN'T IT?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
IT USED TO BE QUITE TAME,
BUT IT'S GETTIN'
A LITTLE OLDER NOW
AND A LITTLE BITTER.
WE'RE LOOKIN' AT
A VERY VIOLENT BIRD HERE.
WHY DIDN'T YOU BRING
A DIFFERENT FALCON?
WELL, I WANTED TO,
BUT I COULDN'T GET
THIS ONE OFF MY ARM.
OH, BOY, HE'S DUG RIGHT INTO
YOUR BARE WRISTS THERE, EH?
SHOULDN'T YOU HAVE ONE OF
THOSE PROTECTIVE GLOVES ON?
YOU MEAN
LIKE THIS?
YEAH.
YES, I WOULD DEFINITELY
RECOMMEND THAT.
DOES THAT
HURT AT ALL?
VERY MUCH SO.
YEAH.
INTENSELY PAINFUL.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S NOT BLEEDING.
NO, NO, NO,
BUT I THINK ONCE THE
TALONS COME OUT OF MY SKIN,
SOME BANDAGES WOULD
COME IN MIGHTY HANDY,
MAYBE A FEW
BLOOD DONORS.
I'M A TYPE "A".
ALL RIGHT.
ED, WHY DON'T YOU JUST
TAKE THE LITTLE HOOD OFF?
THEN HE'LL JUST FLY
AROUND A LITTLE BIT.
ARE YOU OUT
OF YOUR MIND!
NO, I'M JUST THINKIN'
IF HE FLIES AWAY,
HE'LL, YOU KNOW,
LET GO OF YOUR ARM.
WELL, MAYBE MOST
OF IT, YEAH.
BUT I'M NOT IN A BIG HURRY
TO TEST THAT THEORY.
THIS IS A VERY
DANGEROUS BIRD.
WELL, HE LOOKS
PRETTY CALM TO ME.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT
HE WANTS YOU TO THINK,
OH, YEAH.
BUT ALL THE WHILE
HE'S SITTING THERE,
THINKING UP NEW
TECHNIQUES FOR ATTACK
AND KILL.
THAT'S ALL THESE
BIRDS THINK ABOUT IS
KILL, KILL, KILL.
ALTHOUGH, YOU MAY
BE RIGHT.
HE SEEMS TO HAVE LOOSENED
HIS GRIP A LITTLE BIT.
I THINK
HE'S RELAXING.
MAYBE IF WE JUST GIVE HIM
A COUPLE MORE MINUTES.
HOW MUCH MORE
TIME DO WE HAVE?
ABOUT TWO MINUTES,
I THINK.
OH.
OH, UH,
UNLESS THAT WAS
A MOOD SWING,
I THINK YOUR FALCON
IS DECEASED.
YEAH, WELL --
I GOTTA GO GET
A BIRD REMOVED.
LET'S HEAR IT
FOR ED FRID.
THANK YOU, ED.
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
GOOD STUFF.
SEE YOU AROUND.
YOU KNOW WATCHING TELEVISION
IS KIND OF THE BIRTHRIGHT
OF ALL MALES,
AND THE LATEST DEAL ARE THESE
BIG SCREEN TVs WITH THE
SURROUND SOUND
THAT'LL SET YOU BACK
A COOL 10 GRAND.
WELL, IF YOU'VE GOT
THAT KINDA MONEY,
YOU'RE PROBABLY NOT WATCHING
THIS KIND OF SHOW.
SO TODAY ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW TO TAKE
A SIMPLE BLACK AND WHITE,
NINE-INCH TV
AND TURN IT INTO A BIG SCREEN
SURROUND SOUND SYSTEM
THAT'LL ROCK YOUR WORLD.
NOW, THE FIRST
CONSIDERATION IS COMFORT.
GET YOURSELF COMFORTABLE,
AND THEN DECIDE
WHERE TO PUT THE TV.
I THINK I SEE A SPOT.
OKAY, NOW WE'RE READY
TO FACE OUR FIRST PROBLEM,
WHICH IS HOW DO YOU MAKE A
NINE-INCH SCREEN LOOK BIG?
WELL, THE SAME WAY YOU MAKE THE
HORSES AT THE TRACK LOOK BIG
OR THE NEIGHBOUR
IN THE BIKINI LOOK BIG,
WITH A PAIR OF BINOCULARS.
NOW WE NEED A WAY TO MOUNT THE
BINOCULARS ONTO THE THE TV
SO THAT IT'S
ALWAYS IN FOCUS.
HOW ABOUT USING
A BROOM, HUH?
THAT'LL WORK GREAT,
ESPECIALLY DURING
SWEEPS WEEK.
[ CHUCKLING ]
I'LL PROBABLY BE RECOGNIZED BY
THE ACADEMY FOR THIS NEXT STEP.
WHAT DO 3-D GLASSES HAVE
THAT MAKES THEM WORK?
THAT'S RIGHT.
COLOUR.
SO IF I JUST DUCT TAPE THESE
3-D GLASSES TO THE EYEPIECES
OF MY BINOCULARS,
WHAT EFFECT'S THAT GONNA HAVE
ON MY BLACK AND WHITE TV?
I'M GOING TO BE GETTING TWO
VIDEO EFFECTS IN ONE.
I SMELL AND EMMY.
THAT MEANS I CAN NOW CONCENTRATE
ON THE AUDIO COMPONENT OF OUR
HOME THEATRE SYSTEM.
NOW WITH THE SURROUND
SOUND SPEAKERS,
THAT'S NO GOOD 'CAUSE YOU'VE GOT
SPEAKERS ALL OVER THE PLACE,
AND THERE'S NO
ROOM FOR YOU.
I SAY, WHY DON'T YOU
GO ANOTHER WAY WITH IT?
WHY DON'T YOU MOUNT
THE SPEAKER IN SUCH A WAY
THAT THE SOUND
WILL COME TO YOU?
[ CHUCKLING ]
THE SOUND'LL SURROUND
YOU, ALL RIGHT,
AT ANY SPEED YOU WANT.
AND TO MAXIMIZE MY RECEPTION
HERE, I ADDED A SATELLITE DISH.
ACTUALLY, IT'S JUST ONE OF
THOSE METAL COLANDERS YOU
USE TO STRAIN PASTA,
BUT I'D RATHER BE STRAINING
MY EYES THAN STRAINING
MY FETTUCINI.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OH, MAN, I'M AIMING
AT THE WRONG SATELLITE.
I WANNA TALK TO YOU OLDER
GUYS WHO GET IN TROUBLE
WHEN YOU TRY TO HELP.
I'M TALKING ABOUT WHEN YOU
SEE YOUR WIFE OR YOUR KIDS
STRUGGLING TO DO SOMETHING,
AND YOU BUTT IN AND SAY,
HERE, GIVE ME THAT.
THEY THINK YOU'RE TRYING TO
SHOW-OFF, BE A KNOW-IT-ALL,
TRYING TO INFLATE YOUR EGO.
NOTHING COULD BE
FARTHER FROM THE TRUTH.
YOUR EGO IS UNDER
SO MUCH PRESSURE,
THE LAST THING YOU WANT
TO DO IS INFLATE IT.
AND YOUR WIFE, OF COURSE,
HAS THAT EGO PIN THAT
SHE KEEPS HANDY.
NO, NO, WHEN YOU SAY,
HERE, GIVE ME THAT,
YOU'RE TRYING TO SAVE THEM FROM
THAT PAINFUL LEARNING CURVE
YOU'VE GONE THROUGH.
YOU KNOW THAT WHEN
SOMETHING'S STUCK
OR DOESN'T FIT
OR ISN'T STRAIGHT,
YOU JUST HAVEN'T HIT
IT HARD ENOUGH YET.
AT OUR AGE THERE'S ALMOST
NOTHING THAT WE HAVEN'T
DROPPED, HAMMERED, ROLLED,
DRIVEN THROUGH, SMASHED,
CUT TOO SHORT,
OR BURNED.
WE HAVE THIS VAST
KNOWLEDGE TO SHARE,
AND WE WANNA SAVE OUR LOVED
ONES FROM THE PAIN AND INJURY.
YOU SEE, ON THEM A CUT OR A
BRUISE IS AN UNSIGHTLY BLEMISH.
ON US IT'S JUST ONE MORE
KNOTHOLE ON AN ALREADY
BLEMISHED TREE.
SO JUST TELL YOUR FAMILY
THE NEXT TIME YOU SAY,
HERE, GIVE ME THAT,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING
TO BE THE STAR.
YOU'RE JUST OFFERING
TO TAKE ONE FOR THE TEAM.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLIN'
FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
MAN, I DON'T GET IT.
THE SAME GRASS THAT GREW ONLY
TWO INCHES LONG IN THE SHED
IS A FOOT LONG
OUT IN THE YARD.
AND IT HASN'T EVEN RAINED
SINCE WE PLANTED IT.
MIND YOU THE GRASS IS KIND OF
WET AND STICKY ALL THE TIME.
SMELLS LIKE PAINT
OR KEROSENE
OR NUCLEAR WASTE,
I THINK.
GOOD NEWS, RED.
I SOLD ALL
THE LAWN MOWERS.
OH, MAN, DALTON,
THAT'S TOO BAD.
I'M GONNA HAVE
TO GET 'EM ALL BACK.
OH, NO, NO,
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
LOOK. LOOK.
I GOT 100 BUCKS
FOR 'EM.
HOLY HANNA.
WHO GAVE YOU THAT
MUCH FOR THOSE UNITS?
SOME MORON
FROM THE CITY.
[ LAUGHING ]
NO, NO, NO.
HAVE YOU GOT
HIS PHONE NUMBER?
YEAH, YEAH.
RIGHT HERE.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO CALL HIM BACK
AND TELL HIM
THE DEAL'S OFF.
SORRY.
WHAT?
YEAH.
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU THINK YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YEAH, I KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING.
BOY,
IT'S ROUGH, HUH?
YEAH, I KNOW.
NICE LAWN.
YEAH.
WHAT, DID YOU GUYS
PUT IN NEW SEPTICS
AND DIDN'T GIVE ME
A CHANCE TO BID ON THEM?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
WE PUT IN A
WHOLE NEW LAWN.
OH.
YEAH.
'CAUSE I'LL
TELL YA,
BUSINESS HAS BEEN PRETTY SLOW
FOR ME LATELY BECAUSE OF
THE DROUGHT.
AND TO TOP IT ALL OFF,
THE COUNTY GAVE
SOME OTHER GUY
THE PUMPIN' JOB TO CLEAN
OUT THEIR SEPTICS.
I NEVER EVEN
GOT A SNIFF.
WHAT IS GOOD NEWS
IN YOUR BUSINESS?
RED, I'VE GOT
THE GUY ON THE PHONE.
HE SAYS WE CAN
HAVE LAWN MOWERS,
BUT HE WANTS HIS
100 BUCKS BACK,
PLUS ANOTHER 50!
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S FINE.
WE GOT A DEAL.
TELL HIM IT'S FINE.
RED, RED, RED.
WE'LL BE DOWN
50 BUCKS.
NOT IF HE
TAKES A CHECK.
[ LAUGHING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
OH, RED GREEN.
THIS IS GREAT.
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME FOR MY
SECOND ANIMATED FEATURE.
DID YOU GET
MY NOTICE?
WELL, I'M HERE,
SO, NO.
THIS ONE'S
MUCH BETTER.
I'VE IMPROVED
THE DRAWINGS.
I THINK I'VE CAPTURED THE
CHARACTER VOICES
MUCH BETTER TOO.
VERY REMINISCENT OF
WALT DISNEY'S EARLY
PROGRESS, I THINK.
A LITTLE MORE GOOFY,
A LITTLE LESS MICKEY MOUSE?
NO, IT'S MORE
EDUCATIONAL.
THIS ONE'S ALL ABOUT
SUN PROTECTION.
HERE WE GO.
OH, WOULD YOU LIKE SOME
POPCORN BEFORE WE START?
YEAH, SURE.
I LIKE IT AFTER
IT'S POPPED.
SUIT YOURSELF.
OH, DO YOU WANNA USE
THE BATHROOM FIRST?
NO, BUT I WOULDN'T
MIND USING THE EXIT.
NO, NO,
DOWN IN FRONT.
NO TALKING.
HERE WE GO.
[ CHEERY KIDS MUSIC ]
LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN,
SUN SAFETY
IS IMPORTANT.
KNOW THAT THE SUN
IS YOUR ENEMY
AND YOU MUST PROTECT
YOURSELF AGAINST ITS
HARMFUL DEATH RAYS.
DO EITHER OF YOU KNOW HOW WE
CAN FINALLY DESTROY THE SUN
ONCE AND FOR ALL?
UH, I REALLY DON'T THINK
WE NEED TO DESTROY SUN,
RANGER GORD.
I THINK --
THINK AGAIN.
SOME PEOPLE WOULD HAVE YOU
BELIEVE THAT THE SUN IS
SIMPLY A BIG HARMLESS BALL
BURNING WOOD AND DEAD LEAVES.
WELL, THEY'RE WRONG.
THE SUN IS A LIVING BEING
SET ON DESTROYING MANKIND.
SO WE MUST ABOLISH
THE SUN FROM THE SKY.
HERE, TAKE THESE
RAY GUNS.
WE'LL SHOW THAT SUN.
WITH THESE RAY GUNS WE CAN
GIVE AS GOOD AS WE GET.
UH, GORD, I DON'T
THINK WE NEED TO
BLAST THE SUN.
IT'S CRAZY.
I'LL JUST PUT ON
SOME SUNBLOCK LOTION,
AND I'LL BE FINE.
WELL, THAT'S JUST
PEACHY, LITTLE RED.
YOU CAN JUST SIT BACK
COVERED IN YOUR
FANCY LOTION
AND PLAY DEFENCE FOR
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE,
NEVER ONCE STANDING
UP TO THE SUN.
MEANWHILE, LITTLE HAROLD
AND I WILL FIGHT THE SUN
TO THE DEATH
IF WE HAVE TO
TO SAVE MANKIND.
TO THE DEATH?
YOU'RE NOT RIGHT
IN THE HEAD, GORD.
OH, NO, THE SUN HAS BEEN
EAVESDROPPING ON US.
IT KNOWS WHAT
WE'RE UP TO.
THERE'S NO TIME.
WE MUST DESTROY IT NOW!
RANGER GORD, YOU FOOL,
YOUR INCREDIBLE SUPERHUMAN
POWERS AND GOD-LIKE BODY
ARE NO MATCH FOR ME.
AND YOUR PATHETIC LITTLE FRIENDS
CAN'T HELP YOU EITHER.
HA HA HA!
HA HA HA HA.
JOKE'S ON YOU.
THEY WERE PATHETIC
AND LITTLE, YES,
BUT THEY WEREN'T
MY FRIENDS.
COME ON, DROP IT.
DROP YOUR GUN.
HEY, OW,
COME ON, STOP IT.
STOP IT, GORD.
AW, PLEASE DON'T
DESTROY ME.
DO YOU PROMISE NOT TO SHOOT
DEATH RAYS AT PEOPLE ANYMORE?
YEAH.
SAY IT.
I PROMISE NOT TO
SHOOT DEATH RAYS
AT PEOPLE ANYMORE.
IT'S A DEAL.
FOLKS, YOU HEARD THE SUN.
THANKS TO ME, WE NO LONGER
LIVE IN FEAR OF THE SUN'S
HARMFUL DEATH RAYS.
I SURE LEARNED MY LESSON.
NOW EVERYONE CAN SPEND HOURS
AND HOURS IN THE SUN
WITHOUT A CARE
IN THE WORLD.
WELL, EVERYONE BUT
THOSE TWO.
HA HA HA.
HA HA HA HA!
[ APPLAUSE ]
HUH?
AND AS YOU CAN SEE,
I HAVE A GUEST ON
THE SHOW TODAY.
WELL, HE'S NOT
REALLY A GUEST.
IT'S JUST HAROLD.
BUT I CAN
EXPLAIN THAT.
TODAY WE'RE
CELEBRATING CAREER DAY.
SO NATURALLY WE NEEDED
SOMEBODY WITH A CAREER
ON THE SHOW,
BUT AROUND HERE,
THAT'S NOT SO
EASY TO FIND,
SO THAT'S WHERE
YOU COME IN, HAROLD.
THANK YOU, MIKE.
I DON'T REALLY KNOW IF IT'S
MUCH OF A CAREER YET, YOU KNOW.
I'M STILL TRYING TO LEARN AND
GROW AND BE BETTER AT MY JOB
AND REAP THE REWARDS THAT COME
WITH TAKING RESPONSIBILITY
FOR YOURSELF.
SEE, HE'S WEIRD
LIKE THAT.
IT'S GREAT.
SO WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A JOB AND
A CAREER?
WELL, OKAY,
TO ME, PERSONALLY, UM,
A JOB IS SOMETHING
THAT'S TEMPORARY.
YOU KNOW, YOU STICK AT IT
FOR A LITTLE WHILE UNTIL
YOU QUIT OR GET FIRED.
OR ESCAPE.
OR ESCAPE, YES.
YES, ALL RIGHT.
UM, BUT ON THE
OTHER HAND,
A CAREER IS SOMETHING THAT
YOU PLAN ON STICKING AT
FOR A LONG TIME,
YOU KNOW, AND CLIMB UP THAT
LADDER UNTIL YOU RETIRE.
SO A JOB IS LIKE
DRAWING ONE TO TWO,
AND A CAREER IS BASICALLY
A LIFE SENTENCE?
SIMILAR.
SO TELL ME ABOUT
YOUR JOB, HAROLD.
UM, WHAT DID YOUR
LAWYER GET YOU?
WELL, I'M AN ASSISTANT ACCOUNT
EXECUTIVE AT MULTI-CORP
INTERNATIONAL INC.
AND WHAT
DO THEY DO?
WELL, UH, MIKE --
THEY'RE VERY BIG.
THEY'RE HUGE.
THEY'RE HUGE, MIKE.
GOOD ENOUGH.
AND WHAT DO
YOU DO IN IT?
I WORK WITH FILES.
AND A FILING CABINET.
I DIDN'T BRING ONE ALONG TODAY
FOR SHOW AND TELL OR NOTHING
BECAUSE ONE GUY TRIED
THAT ONE TIME,
AND HE GOT FIRED.
IT'S DOG EAT DOG
OUT THERE.
YEAH, NO,
YOU'RE RIGHT, IT IS.
BECAUSE, LIKE, WHEN I DO
HAVE WORK TO TAKE HOME ON THE
WEEKEND OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
I'VE LIKE A MINI
FILING CABINET.
IT'S CALLED AN
ATTACHE CASE.
AND MY BOSS, IF HE EVER WANTS
TO GET IN TOUCH WITH ME,
THEY GAVE ME
A CELLULAR PHONE.
SO YOU --
SO YOU WORK
ALL ALONE
ALL DAY IN A
WINDOWLESS CUBICLE,
AND THEN YOU TAKE MORE WORK
HOME WITH YOU AT NIGHT,
AND THEN IF YOUR BOSS
HAS ANY OTHER IDEAS,
HE CAN CALL YOU UP
WHENEVER HE WANTS?
YEAH, THAT'S MY JOB.
AND YOU'RE LOOKING
AT DOING THIS FOR LIFE?
DO THEY GIVE YOU
THREE SQUARES A DAY?
NO.
WELL, I HAVE LEARNED
SO MUCH TODAY.
I USED TO THINK A
JOB WAS PRETTY BAD,
BUT A CAREER REALLY
SUCKS, DOESN'T IT?
THANKS FOR COMING
ON THE SHOW, HAROLD.
NO, I THINK YOU MISSED
THE IDEA OF THE
WHOLE CONCEPT.
[ CELL PHONE RINGING ]
OH, EXCUSE ME.
IT'S PROBABLY
THE WARDEN.
SH-H-H!
THANKS FOR BEING
ON THE SHOW.
AND PLEASE, DON'T LET
THIS HAPPEN TO YOU.
WELL, WE'VE HAD A
COUPLE OF SETBACKS.
THE GRASS IS
FIVE FEET HIGH,
THE LAWN MOWERS WON'T CUT IT,
THE TOXIC FUMES MAKE
YOU LIGHTHEADED,
AND THE DARNED STUFF
TURNS EVERYTHING GREEN.
YOU KNOW, I'M STARTIN' TO THINK
THIS NEW GRASS SEED WASN'T
SUCH A GREAT IDEA.
Winston: OW!
WHAT THE HECK?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
Winston: RED IS THAT YOU?
OW!
WINSTON, THE DOOR'S OVER
HERE TO YOUR LEFT.
THERE YOU GO.
OH, GEEZ.
WOW.
I WAS GETTING CLAUSTROPHOBIC
OUT THERE.
YOU CAN'T SEE
THE BUILDINGS
OR ANY OF THE SCRAP WATER
HEATERS OR ANYTHING.
ACTUALLY, THE LODGE
NEVER LOOKED BETTER.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S
WEIRD, THOUGH?
EVERYBODY ELSE'S GRASS IS DEAD
BECAUSE THERE'S BEEN NO RAIN,
BUT WE GOT BLADES IN SPADES.
TROUBLE, RED.
TROUBLE.
WHAT? WHAT?
IT LOOKS LIKE RAIN.
LOOK HOW DARK IT IS OUTSIDE.
HOLY SMOKE.
WE BETTER GET
UP ON THE ROOF.
THE GRASS MIGHT
GROW 30 FEET HIGH.
NO, NO, IF IT GROWS THAT HIGH,
IT'LL JUST FALL OVER, WON'T IT?
WELL, YOU NEVER KNOW.
SOME THINGS CAN
DEFY GRAVITY.
REMEMBER TAMMY
FERGUSON'S HAIRDO?
OH, BOY.
WELL, I WANNA KNOW WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN WHEN IT RAINS
'CAUSE I'LL TELL YOU,
IN THE SEWAGE BUSINESS,
ONE THING YOU LEARN TO HATE,
AND THAT'S SURPRISES.
WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO?
WELL, I'M JUST GONNA THROW SOME
WATER ON THIS SAMPLE PATCH
OF LAWN HERE
AND SEE
WHAT HAPPENS.
I HOPE THE
ROOF HOLDS.
WHAT?
THIS GRASS DOESN'T
GROW IN WATER,
IT DISSOLVES
IN WATER!
THAT'S WHY IT DID SO
WELL DURING THE DROUGHT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
[ THUNDER ]
LOOK AT THAT,
WILL YA?
BOY, THAT GRASS
IS DISAPPEARING FASTER
THAN BREATH MINTS
AT A SINGLES' BAR.
LOOK AT THAT TOXIC RUN-OFF.
IT'S HEADING RIGHT
INTO THE LAKE.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA
DO ABOUT THAT?
AH!
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GUYS
GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
DON'T LET THE
GRASS GROW --
OH, NEVER MIND.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I LEARNED ONE THING TODAY,
JUST LET NATURE TAKE ITS COURSE.
AND WHEN I GET HOME TONIGHT,
I HOPE YOU'RE GONNA BE AWAKE,
AND I'M HOPIN' TO SHOW YOU
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND THE
WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
closed captioning performed
by INTERCAPTION CANADA
www.intercaption.com
SIT DOWN.
PUT YOUR BUTTS
IN THE BENCHES.
SIT HER DOWN.
OH, ALL RISE.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
REMEMBER, GUYS,
THE GRASS IS ALWAYS GREENER IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE LAKE.