(Explosion)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
BROADCAST LIVE
TO TAPE TO EDITING
TO SATELLITE FEED TO V.H.S.
BOOTLEG COPY, HERE HE IS,
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
(Whistling)
(Cheering)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
VERY MUCH.
PRETTY EXCITING THIS WEEK.
IT APPEARS THAT
A VERY IMPORTANT, BIG VISITOR
IS DRIVING THROUGH
THE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
LET ME GUESS, LET ME GUESS,
LET ME GUESS!
UH, SUPERMODEL
CLAUDIA SCHIFFER.
NO, IT'S NOT A PERSON.
IT'S A THING.
OH -- FABIO.
(Audience laughing)
NO, NO, NO, NO.
THE ROAD CREW'S
ON THE MAIN HIGHWAY.
THEY'RE WIDENING HER OUT
FOR A SUPER-TRANSPORT
CARRYING A BIG THING.
WHAT'S THIS
BIG THING CALLED?
HAD LOTS OF Q's AND L's IN IT.
DOESN'T MATTER --
IT'S NOT IMPORTANT.
WHAT MATTERS IS,
IT'S A
BIG THING.
THIS IS AN OCCASION
FOR ANY COMMUNITY.
THIS KIND OF THING
BONDS A TOWN,
BRINGS US ALL TOGETHER
FOR AN EVENT.
YOU'RE TALKING TAILGATE PARTY?
A KILLER.
(Audience laughing)
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): WE GOT A GREAT SHOW
FOR YOU.
I'M PUMPED.
MIKE WILL TRY TO SAY
THE WORD "REMORSE".
SPEAKING OF SORRY THINGS,
RANGER GORD IS WITH US.
THERE'S A FUNNY THING
NEAR THE END OF THE SHOW.
AND BRING CHARCOAL --
RIGHT, BYE.
JUNIOR SINGLETON FOUND OUT
THAT THIS BIG THING IS COMING
ON A CUSTOM-BUILT TRAILER.
THAT MEANS IT'S SPECIAL
AND REALLY BIG.
SO... SO WHAT?
YOU'LL BE COOKING UP
YOUR FAMOUS TAILGATE HOT-DOGS?
NO, I WANT TO DO SOMETHING
KIND OF SPECIAL.
BUSTER HADFIELD THOUGHT
WE COULD HONOUR THE BIG THING
BY HAVING BIG FOOD.
BIG FOOD FOR BIG MOUTHS.
NO, BIG FOOD IS TOO OBVIOUS.
IT'S TOO ON THE NOSE.
AND ON THE FACE AND THE CHIN
AND THE LAP...
IT'S GONNA BE
QUITE A THING, HAROLD.
EVERYBODY'S ALL REVVED UP.
EVERYBODY'S EXCITED, YOU KNOW?
THE BARBER SHOP'S BOOKED.
WOMEN HAVE BOUGHT
NEW TRACK SUITS.
(Audience laughing)
IT'S JUST A BIG THING.
WHY TURN EVERYTHING INTO
SUCH A...
... BIG THING?
YEAH!
HAVE YOU EVER CONSIDERED
YOU SHOULDN'T GO OUT THERE?
MAYBE IT'S FULL
OF TOXIC CHEMICALS.
THAT'S THE TICKET!
I'LL MAKE MY TAILGATE CHILI!
OHHHH!
(Applause)
(Red): BILL AND I WILL ASSEMBLE
A HIGH VIEWING STAND
SO HE CAN SIT
AND WATCH THE BIG THING.
HE'D ASKED ME TO COME OVER
AND HELP HIM.
I THOUGHT THE VAN
WOULD COME IN HANDY.
SORRY, BILL.
HOPEFULLY, HE HAS
ANOTHER PLAN.
HE NEEDS A MEDICAL PLAN.
OK, THIS IS THE BIG ONE!
FOR A PIZZA
WITH EVERYTHING ON IT,
COURTESY OF THE POSSUM LAKE
PETTING ZOO,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. HAMAR
TO SAY THIS WORD.
THERE YOU GO --
30 SECONDS AND BEGIN.
UH, ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
WHEN YOU FEEL SORRY
FOR SOMETHING,
THAT MEANS YOU HAVE...
... BEEN
CAUGHT.
NO, UH...
HAVE YOU EVER FELT BAD
ABOUT SOMETHING?
UM... PATROL CAR...
UH, HOLDING CELL...
DON'T GUESS.
HANDCUFFS,
SOLITARY...
MIKE, YOU'RE GETTING
ON MY NERVES.
OH, I'M SORRY, MR. GREEN.
YOU'RE SORRY --
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
WHEN YOU'RE FEELING SORRY,
YOU GO TO THE PERSON
AND YOU SAY YOU HAVE...
... A PLEA BARGAIN.
(Audience laughing)
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
I'M DOING
MY BEST.
NO, IT'S REALLY...
IT'S ME.
I'M JUST USELESS --
I CAN'T DO THIS.
I'M A PIECE OF GARBAGE.
I-I-I'M EMBARRASSED,
I'M SO BAD.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M SO BAD...
MERE WORDS CANNOT EXPRESS
THE DISSATISFACTION I FEEL,
MY DYSPEPSIA...
(Harold):
YOU'RE WRONG.
IT'S ALL OVER.
MY REMORSE.
(Ringing bell)
AW, RIGHT ON!
OH, THAT WAS CLOSE!
(Applause)
(Strums acoustic guitar)
OH, THERE'S A HAPPY
WHISTLING IN THE AIR
EVERYTHING'S BRIGHT
AND CLEAR
YOU BURNED THE HAIR
OFF BOTH OF YOUR ARMS
AND THERE'S A PIECE MISSING
FROM THE TOP OF ONE EAR
WHILE YOU'RE WAITING
FOR THE AMBULANCE
YOU REVIEW
THE THINGS YOU DID
AND THE NEXT TIME
YOU START TO BARBECUE
YOU'LL REMEMBER
TO OPEN THE LID
(Making
explosion sounds)
WITH THIS BIG THING
COMING THROUGH TOWN
AND EVERYBODY GETTING OUT THERE
TO TAKE A BOO AT IT,
I'LL USE "HANDYMAN CORNER"
TO SHOW HOW YOU CAN RISE
ABOVE THE CROWD... LITERALLY.
WHEN YOU GO TO PUBLIC EVENTS
LIKE A STOCK CAR RACE
OR A MOCK LYNCHING
OR A POST OFFICE FIRE,
YOU DON'T WANT TO STAND
FOR MINUTES AT A TIME.
HOW DO YOU GET YOUR CHAIR
SIX FEET OFF THE GROUND?
YOU GET YOURSELF
SOME OF THESE INNER TUBES,
LAY ONE DOWN ON THE FLOOR,
LAY ANOTHER ONE ON TOP,
AND ATTACH THEM,
USING RUBBER CEMENT
OR ELASTIC CORD OR --
THAT'S RIGHT --
THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
ONCE YOU GOT THE DUCT TAPE ON,
TAKE ONE OF THE INNER TUBES,
STICK HER RIGHT ON TOP, THERE.
YOU WANNA MAKE SURE
THAT YOU LINE THE VALVES UP.
THEN YOU GRAB ANOTHER ONE.
PUT IT RIGHT ON THERE.
AS I SAY,
GET THOSE VALVES ALIGNED,
AND GRAB ANOTHER ONE.
SAME DEAL, SAME
"NOTHING NEW HERE".
PUSH THAT DOWN.
AND NOW YOU TAKE YOUR CHAIR...
PUT THAT RIGHT ON TOP.
SEAL THAT UP.
ALL RIGHT.
SIT DOWN AND START PUMPING.
YOU'LL GET
A WHOLE NEW PERSPECTIVE.
NOW...
(Grunting)
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S GOT HER.
WE'LL JUST DISCONNECT
THAT ONE...
AND HOOK THE HOSE
ONTO THE NEXT...
(Air escaping)
I COULD PROBABLY
STAND UP AND DO THIS.
NO, THERE, WE GOT HER.
PUMP UP THE NEXT TUBE.
(Grunting)
OK, OK, YEAH, OK.
YOU SHOULD HAVE
THOUGHT OF THIS.
SEE WHAT'S WRONG HERE?
YOU SHOULD HAVE STARTED PUMPING
THE BOTTOM INNER TUBE FIRST.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
YOU'RE GONNA TAKE THE AIR OUT,
START ALL OVER AGAIN.
(Grunting)
AND DONE!
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I'LL BE ABLE TO SEE EVERYTHING.
NOTHING'S GONNA GET IN MY WAY.
I'M LOOKING OVER
PEOPLE'S HEADS.
I'LL SEE FOR MILES.
I'M UP HERE, COMFY AS HECK.
CAN EVEN PEEL A SNACK
WHILE I'M WAITING
FOR THE BIG THING.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OH!
UH-OH!
OOH!
OHHHH!
THERE'S NOTHING TO SEE HERE.
KEEP MOVING... OHHHH!
STAY TUNED -- I PROVE
THERE'S NOTHING FUNNY
ABOUT BEING AFRAID OF SPIDERS.
JUNIOR SINGLETON HEARD
THAT THE BIG THING
IS LESS THAN 24 HOURS AWAY.
THE BEST VIEW WILL BE
FROM LOVERS' LEAP.
THAT'S WHAT EVERYBODY THOUGHT.
HALF THE TOWN'S UP THERE.
THE WEIGHT WAS SO MUCH,
THE CLIFF COLLAPSED.
(Audience laughing)
LOVERS' LEAP
IS NOW LOVERS' LUMP.
I'LL GO TO THAT HILL JUST TO
THE WEST OF DALTON'S PLACE.
YOU KNOW THE... THE...
THE CEMETERY.
NO, THAT'S PACKED, TOO.
INSTEAD OF A TAILGATE PARTY, IT
LOOKS LIKE A TOMBSTONE PARTY.
LOOKS LIKE THE DEAD HAVE RISEN
AND ARE PICNICKING.
THERE'S STILL ROOM
BY THE MAUSOLEUM.
FINE, I MAY NOT HAVE
THE BEST VIEW,
BUT I'LL HAVE
THE BEST TAILGATE PARTY.
DID YOU BUY TICKETS
FOR THE BIG-THING POOL?
WHAT CAN YOU BET ON?
HOW MANY PEOPLE
WILL GET FOOD POISONING
BEFORE THE BIG THING ARRIVES?
NO, HAROLD, WE'RE BETTING
ON THE NUMBER OF TIRES.
I UNDERSTAND IT WEIGHS
30,000 POUNDS.
A NORMAL TIRE'S
30 POUNDS PRESSURE.
I'M GUESSING A THOUSAND TIRES.
EXCELLENT REASONING.
I'M GONNA MAKE MONEY.
WELL, I DEFINITELY WILL.
I'M GONNA VIDEOTAPE IT.
IT'S GONNA BE
A COMMEMORATIVE VIDEO.
THE ULTIMATE SOUVENIR.
YOU SAID THE BIG THING
WAS STUPID
AND MEANINGLESS AND IRRELEVANT.
IT IS -- IT'S PERFECT
FOR TELEVISION.
(Audience laughing)
HI, RANGER GORD AGAIN.
PEOPLE DON'T KNOW
THAT A FOREST FIRE
IS A NATURAL PART
OF A FOREST'S EVOLUTION.
IT CLEARS THE UNDERBRUSH,
AND IS THE ONLY WAY
MANY CONIFEROUS TREES
CAN START TO GROW.
MY JOB AS A FOREST RANGER IS
TO PREVENT FOREST FIRES.
FOR THE LIFE OF ME,
I CAN'T REMEMBER WHY.
(Chuckling)
IT'S "MALE CALL"!
(Applause and cheering)
(Whooping)
OK, HERE'S OUR FIRST LETTER,
FROM ALLAN BERTHA IN ALBERTA.
"DEAR RED GREEN,
WE ABSOLUTELY LOVE YOUR SHOW.
"EVERYONE WE'VE TURNED ON
TO THE SHOW
"HAS RAVED ABOUT
HOW GREAT IT IS.
"THEY'RE ALL RABID FANS.
"WHAT A FINE, FINE PROGRAMME."
WAAA-HAW-HAW!
"THE SHOW IS CLEVER,
THOUGHTFUL, AND INFORMATIVE.
"YOU'RE REALLY A WONDER
"IN CANADIAN TELEVISION.
"LONG LIVE
'THE NEW RED AND GREEN SHOW.'"
WELL, ACTUALLY, IT'S NOT
"THE NEW RED AND GREEN SHOW".
IT'S JUST
"THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW".
THERE'S NO "AND".
I MAY CHANGE MY MIDDLE NAME
TO "AND".
OH, LOOK, OK.
"MY SON'S FAVOURITE PART
IS WHEN YOU RACE YOUR BOAT."
RACE YOUR BOAT?
I KNOW WHAT HE MEANS.
REMEMBER THE WATER SKIING,
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL"?
OH, THAT'S, LIKE,
THREE SEASONS AGO.
WELL, THAT'S-- ALL RIGHTY.
"WE ALSO LIKE
WHEN YOU AND YOUR BAND SING."
(Audience laughing)
NO, THEY'RE TALKING
ABOUT THE CAMPFIRE SONGS.
YEAH, THE
CAMPFIRE SONGS.
I'M IN A BAND!
ALL RIGHT, UM...
"MY DAD'S FAVOURITE PART IS THE
SPORTS BLOOPERS" -- OK, WHAT?
(Audience laughing)
ALL RIGHT, I--
UH, YES, YES.
THERE IS A PART
WITH SPORTS BLOOPERS ON.
I CAN'T REMEMBER IT RIGHT NOW.
THANKS, I APPRECIATE THAT.
THE IMPORTANT THING IS
THAT THEY LIKE THE SHOW.
"AND WHEN YOU AND YOUR WIFE
AND DAUGHTER
"SING YOUR CLOSING SONG,
WE GET A TEAR IN OUR EYES."
(Audience laughing)
"KEEP UP THE GOOD WORK, OR,
AS RED AND GREEN ALWAYS SAY,
"'MAKE HAY
WHILE THE SUN SHINES.'"
(Audience laughing)
UH, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, UH, THANKS VERY MUCH,
YOU KNOW.
PROBABLY BE
MORE SPORTS BLOOPERS
COMING UP IN THE FUTURE.
WE'RE GONNA BACK OFF ON
SINGING WITH THE DAUGHTERS.
I SHOULD TELL YOU THAT.
UNTIL THEN, KEEP WATCHING
AND, UH...
MAKE HAY WHILE THE SUN SHINES.
(Applause)
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL.
THIS WEEK
WE'RE FEATURING INSECTS.
COME ON IN HERE, RED.
SOMETHING HAPPEN TO
YOUR HANDS THERE, GARTH?
OK, ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S A GOOD TIP
FOR YOU YOUNG PEOPLE.
IF YOU'RE OUT IN THE WOODS
AND A BEEHIVE,
OR, FOR THAT MATTER,
A HORNETS' NEST
SHOULD FALL OUT OF THE TREES,
DON'T TRY TO CATCH IT.
HOW MANY STINGS
DID YOU TAKE, GARTH?
GEE, I'D SAY 30, 40, 50,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
HAD BLURRED VISION
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
BOSS WOULDN'T LET ME
TAKE ANY TIME OFF,
JUST WOULDN'T LET ME
DRIVE THE TRUCK.
I LOVE THAT TRUCK.
SO, IS THAT YOUR TIP
FOR THIS WEEK?
HUH?
YOUR TIP?
OH, NO -- TODAY
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT SPIDERS.
DON'T LIKE SPIDERS.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
ARACHNOPHOBIA.
IT'S A COMMON FEAR.
BUT THERE'S NO REASON FOR IT,
BECAUSE 99% OF
THE WORLD'S SPIDERS
ARE A VALUABLE, HARMLESS PART
OF THE ECOLOGICAL CHAIN.
IT'S JUST THAT MOST PEOPLE
DON'T WANT THEM AROUND
THEIR HOUSE.
SO HERE'S A TIP.
TAKE A PIECE OF BREAD --
COULD BE RYE, PUMPERNICKEL,
AND SOAK THAT
IN WATER AND SUGAR.
PUT THAT IN A JAR
AND KEEP THE TOP OFF.
OH, GEE, THAT DOESN'T WANT TO
COME OFF.
GIVE ME A HAND WITH IT.
HOW MANY, UH,
HOW MANY YOU GOT IN THERE?
OH, GEE, I'D SAY, 1, 2,
I'D SAY 600 OR 700.
DON'T LIKE SPIDERS.
HELP ME WITH IT.
GO ON, GO ON, GO ON.
OH, CATCH IT!
OH, OH, NO!
OH, THERE HE GOES.
THEY LOOK ANGRY.
HE'S UP THAT WAY.
(Laughing)
ANOTHER SUPER DAY.
OOPS, THERE HE GOES.
RIGHT UP THERE.
(Laughing)
WELL, LESS THAN 12 HOURS
UNTIL THE BIG THING
COMES THROUGH ON THE HIGHWAY.
SPECULATION
IS GOING CRAZY AROUND HERE.
NUCLEAR REACTOR, SPACE SHUTTLE,
PIPELINE.
MAYBE IT'S JUST ALL THE COPIES
TO KEVIN COSTNER'S "WATERWORLD".
UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED!
THE TOWN'S EMPTY.
THE CEMETERY'S EMPTY --
EVERYBODY'S GONE.
IT'S LIKE THAT MOVIE
"BRAIN SUCKERS FROM MARS",
EXCEPT OUR TOWN'S DUMPIER.
THERE'S A RUMOUR
THAT THE BIG THING
IS TOO BIG FOR THE HIGHWAY,
SO THEY'RE BRINGING IT UP
ON THE RAIL LINE.
LET'S GO THERE.
NO -- EVERYBODY'S GONE.
SO WE CAN GO TO THE HIGHWAY
AND GET A GOOD SPOT
FOR OUR TAILGATE PARTY.
YOU STARTED THAT RUMOUR.
THAT'S DIRTY!
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
GRAB THE BAG.
YOU TOLD A FIB TO GET
A BETTER PARKING SPOT.
I DON'T LIKE LINE-UPS.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
POLICE LINE-UPS?
HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT MUG SHOTS?
WOULDN'T MIND TAKING
A SHOT AT YOURS.
(Audience laughing)
HI, THERE --
RANGER GORD AGAIN.
IN THE 16 YEARS I'VE BEEN
MANNING FIRE WATCHTOWER 13
I'VE OBSERVED ALL MANNER OF
EXOTIC ANIMAL BEHAVIOUR.
BUT THERE'S THREE THINGS
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND.
FIRST, WHY DO FOXES
CIRCLE TWICE
BEFORE THEY LIE DOWN?
WHY DO DEER STOP AND STARE
IF YOU SHINE A LIGHT
IN THEIR EYES?
THE THIRD THING IS,
WHY DO BEARS
ALWAYS SCRATCH THEMSELVES
AGAINST TREE--
OH.
OOH.
WELL, MAYBE THERE'S
ONLY TWO THINGS
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
(Red): MEANWHILE,
I'M BACK WITH BILL
TRYING TO MAKE THIS SCAFFOLD,
RAISED-UP-THING.
THIS IS A THREE-LEGGED LADDER.
IT'S USED FOR PICKING THINGS
OUT OF TREES.
BILL SHOULD HAVE PICKED
A BETTER LADDER.
THEN HE GETS AN IDEA.
TIE THAT OFF LIKE A TETHER,
LIKE THEY DO WITH A HORSE,
A THREE-LEGGED HORSE.
THEY TETHER THEM OFF
APPARENTLY.
WE'LL USE A THIRD LADDER
AS SCAFFOLDING.
KIND OF WORKING IN THREES.
IT'S A SCAFFOLD
MANEGE A TROIS.
THE LADDER WAS, UNFORTUNATELY,
A LITTLE LONG.
RATHER THAN TAKE THE TIME
TO MOVE THE LADDERS,
BILL DECIDED HE'D
HORSE HER IN THERE.
WHAT HAPPENED WAS --
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
OUT COME THE LEGS.
OUT COME THE TETHERS.
DON'T WATCH THIS, KIDS.
THIS GETS VIOLENT.
BOY, THAT'S GOTTA HURT.
THIS PART HERE'S
NO FUN EITHER.
SO WE REGROUP AND GET
THAT LADDER TIED UP THERE.
I'M GETTING OUT OF THERE.
BILL DECIDES HE'S GONNA...
BOY, OH, BOY.
AMAZING, ISN'T IT?
DON'T TRY THIS AT HOME,
IF YOU HAPPEN TO HAVE
SOME THREE-LEGGED LADDERS.
HE GETS HIMSELF UP THERE.
HE SAYS HE'S GOT
A GOOD PERSPECTIVE
TO WATCH THE BIG THING GO BY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
HUH?
OH, MY GOSH.
HE'S GONNA SIT
IN A LAWN CHAIR.
HE'S GOT HIS THERMOS.
WHAT'S IN THERE, BILL?
INTELLIGENCE?
LOOK AT HIM SITTING THERE.
MIND YOU, HE'D ADDED
A LOT OF WEIGHT.
BILL, DO YOU NOTICE SOMETHING
GOING TERRIBLY WRONG?
OH BOY, OH BOY,
OH BOY, OH BOY, OH, OH.
I TOLD HIM
THIS WOULDN'T WORK.
WAIT NOW.
WAIT A SECOND.
YEAH, THIS DOES GIVE ME
A BETTER VIEW OF THE PARADE.
FIND OUT HOW HAP GOT INTO
"THE GUINESS BOOK OF RECORDS".
MY UNCLE RED
CAN'T BE HERE RIGHT NOW.
HE'S AT THE HIGHWAY
WAITING FOR THE BIG THING.
THAT'S WHERE EVERYBODY IS.
THEY'VE GOT EVERYTHING
DOWN THERE.
THERE'S HOT-DOG STANDS
AND CHIP WAGONS.
PONY RIDES,
THEY GOT PONY RIDES.
THEY GOT PHONE BOOTHS
AND PORTABLE TOILETS.
IT'S LIKE WOODSTOCK,
BUT INSTEAD OF HAVING
THE BEST MUSIC,
THEY'VE GOT...
A REALLY BIG THING.
I WASN'T THE ONLY ONE
WHO HAD AN IDEA ABOUT
SELLING STUFF.
DALTON HUMPHREY HAS GOT THESE.
"I SAW THE BIG THING."
AND THERE'S, UH...
"BIG THING ON BOARD".
IT'S FOR UNCLE RED.
"MY FOLKS WENT TO SEE
THE BIG THING
"AND ALL I GOT WAS
THIS LITTLE THING."
HAROLD, WHERE WERE YA?!
YOU MISSED THE BIG CONTRAPTION
COMING DOWN THE ROAD,
TAKING OUT POLES,
TAKING OUT TREES,
TAKING OUT LINES.
THE BIG
THING CAME?!
NO, NO, NO,
MOOSE THOMPSON.
HE NAILED FIVE PICNIC TABLES
TO HIS TRUCK FOR HIS PARTY.
HE'S BARRELLING INTO TOWN.
BY THE TIME HE GOT THERE
IT WAS COVERED WITH
LAUNDRY AND PIECES OF BIRDS.
YEAH,
OH, YEAH.
WE GOTTA GO.
BERNICE IS HOLDING OUR SPACE.
YOU FOLKS WATCH THIS.
COME ON, HAROLD.
HERE WE ARE
WITH HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
WHAT ARE WE FISHING FOR?
SPECKLED TROUT.
THE CONDITIONS ARE GOOD.
I THINK I'M GONNA
HOOK A BIG ONE.
MIGHT GET INTO "THE GUINESS
BOOK OF WORLD RECORDS".
NO, NOT AGAIN.
LET SOMEONE ELSE
HAVE A TURN.
YOU'RE TELLING ME
THAT YOU'RE IN
"THE GUINESS BOOK
OF WORLD RECORDS"?
YEAH, A FEW TIMES.
HAVE A CATEGORY FOR B.S.,
DO THEY?
PROBABLY.
I'M IN IT FOR
THE WORLD'S LONGEST KISS,
THE WORLD'S STRONGEST MAN,
AND THE WORLD'S FATTEST MAN:
972 POUNDS.
AND I SET THE RECORD FOR
THE MOST WEIGHT EVER LOST
BY ONE PERSON: 801 POUNDS,
AND THE LONGEST BUNGEE JUMP.
THOSE LAST TWO RECORDS
WERE SET THE SAME DAY.
YOU'LL NEVER GUESS
WHAT I FOUND, HAP.
"THE GUINESS BOOK
OF WORLD RECORDS".
WHAT PAGE DID YOU SAY
YOU WERE ON?
ALL MY RECORDS
HAVE BEEN BROKEN BY NOW.
ESPECIALLY
THE WORLD'S FATTEST MAN.
I GUESS THIS NEW GUY
JUST WANTED IT MORE.
WITHOUT ANY PROOF, HAP,
IT MAKES A LOT OF THE THINGS
YOU SAY HARD TO BELIEVE.
I DON'T CARE WHETHER
YOU BELIEVE ME OR NOT.
I'M NOT OUT TO SET
ANY RECORDS.
I DON'T KNOW, HAP.
SOME OF THE STORIES YOU TELL,
YOU'VE GOT TO BE GETTING
PRETTY CLOSE.
YEAH, I GUESS HE'S RIGHT.
HEY, HANDYMAN,
HERE'S A TIP FOR YA.
IF YOU'RE TRYING TO PULL-START
A LAWN MOWER
AND IT DOESN'T GO
ON THE FIRST 117 TRIES,
GIVE IT UP.
OTHERWISE YOU'RE GONNA
PULL LIGAMENTS
THROUGH THIS AREA,
RIGHT UP INTO THE SHOULDER.
AND DON'T EVER KICK A MACHINE
WITH SOFT-SOLED SHOES ON.
(Engine starts)
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY!
HEY, HEY, YOU!
COME BACK HERE.
THE BIG THING WAS
A BIG BUST.
DIDN'T EVEN SHOW UP.
I THINK THAT ROAD CREW
WAS HAVING US ON.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
THE BIG THING CAME BY AT 9:25.
I DIDN'T SEE IT, HAROLD.
NONE OF THE LODGE MEMBERS
SAW IT.
OF COURSE NOT!
YOU WERE IN THE MINI-PUTT THING
ALL DAY.
THE REST OF THE GUYS WERE
LINE DANCING,
RIDING THE FERRIS WHEEL,
IN THE BEER GARDEN.
WAS IT BIG?
HUGE.
WHAT WAS IT, HAROLD?
YOU CAN FIND OUT
FOR MERELY $10, V.H.S.
OR $12, BETA.
(Audience laughing)
I HAD TO CLIMB OVER BRAMBLES
AND ROCK IN MERCURY CREEK
TO GET THESE SHOTS.
I HUNG BY A TREE BY MY FEET.
BUT I AM GOING TO BE RICH,
BECAUSE I AM THE ONLY ONE
WITH FOOTAGE OF...
THE BIG THING.
EVERYBODY'S GONNA
WANT ONE COPY.
OH NO, THEY'RE NOT, HAROLD.
EVERYBODY'S TALKING ABOUT
THE BIG THING FOR DAYS.
NOT THE BIG THING --
GOING TO THE BIG THING.
GOING ON RIDES,
PLAYING BINGO,
EATING BARBECUE,
HAVING THE BEER TENT.
THAT WAS THE FUN.
COURSE, YOU MISSED THAT,
BUT THAT'S NORMAL.
BUT I'M THE ONE WHO SAW
THE THING THAT WAS CARRYING
THE BIG THING,
I KNOW HOW MANY TIRES IT HAD --
59.
GREAT, I WIN.
NO WAY --
YOU SAID 1,000!
DIDN'T HAVE TO GET RIGHT ON--
I'M THE CLOSEST.
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME.
AWAY YOU GO, HAROLD.
OH, CHEER UP.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I'D LIKE TO GIVE YOU
MY PRIZE
BECAUSE YOU ARE THE BIG THING
IN MY LIFE.
I HOPE THAT MAKES UP FOR
WHAT I YELLED
ON THE ROLLER COASTER.
I WAS USING AN EXPRESSION.
I WASN'T REFERRING TO
YOUR MOTHER.
THANKS FOR WATCHING,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
(Snoring)
(Harold): ALL RISE.
(Red and Harold): QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS, MORITATI.