(Bottling plant sounds)
IT'S "THE NEW
RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE KEY MAN
OF POSSUM LODGE.
HE'S GOT ALL THE ANSWERS
AND ALL THE KEYS!
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause)
THANK YOU.
LOVELY, HAROLD, LOVELY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YOU GUYS MISSED
ALL THE EXCITEMENT THIS WEEK
DOWN AT THE POLICE STATION.
THE COPS PICKED UP
JIMMY GRISTLE.
JIMMY GRISTLE THE BOOTLEGGER?
I'M GLAD, BECAUSE
OPERATING A STILL IS ILLEGAL.
NOBODY DRANK THE STUFF.
WE USE IT
AS WINDSHIELD WIPER FLUID.
AIR WOULD FREEZE
BEFORE JIMMY'S BOOZE.
YOU'LL HAVE TO GO
TO HUMPHREY'S EVERYTHING STORE
AND BUY IT THERE.
AT TWO BUCKS A GALLON?
I DON'T THINK SO.
I'LL DRIVE WITH ZERO VISIBILITY
BEFORE I'LL DO THAT.
IF JIMMY CAN MAKE WIPER WASH,
SO CAN WE.
GO AHEAD AND OPERATE A STILL.
IF YOU HAVE QUESTIONS,
YOU COULD ALWAYS ASK JIMMY.
I TOLD YOU, JIMMY'S IN JAIL.
BUT IT'S A SMALL JAIL.
WITH LUCK, YOU'LL BE
IN THE SAME CELL.
(Audience laughing)
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): TODAY, WE HAVE
A LOT OF HAROLD,
WHICH IS REGRETTABLE,
BUT IT'S NOT THAT MUCH WORSE
THAN SPENDING AN AFTERNOON
WITH HAP.
THERE'S HAROLD AGAIN,
CREAMED BY CORN.
BEING A GOOF -- BOY!
WE'RE ON THE VERGE
OF MAKING MOONSHINE.
WE'VE DECIDED
WHERE TO PUT THE STILL.
WE CAN START GATHERING
THE STUFF TOGETHER.
YOU'RE GONNA OPERATE A STILL
AND RISK BURNING DOWN
THE LODGE,
TO SAVE $1.00 ON WASHER FLUID?
HAROLD, IT'S THE PRINCIPLE.
AND IT'S $2.00.
I REFUSE TO PAY
HUMPHREY'S PRICES.
HOW HARD CAN IT BE
TO MAKE WIPER FLUID?
ISN'T THAT SOMETHING YOU SAID
WHEN YOU MADE BEER
AND IT BLEW UP?
BUT THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT,
HAROLD.
THEN THERE WAS
THE HAWAIIAN LUAU NIGHT.
WHAT WAS WRONG WITH THAT?
YOU DUG THE FIRE PIT
OVER A GAS LINE.
BOY, THAT WAS A GREAT FIRE PIT.
(Audience laughing)
THAT PIG COOKED FAST,
DIDN'T IT?
I MEAN, BEFORE IT EXPLODED.
IT RAINED BACON BITS
FOR SIX DAYS.
THAT WAS REALLY FUN.
(Applause)
(Red): IN KEEPING WITH OUR PLAN
TO MAKE A STILL...
BOY, THAT HURT.
ANYWAY, BILL HAS GOT
AN ABOVE-GROUND SWIMMING POOL
TO SUPPLY WATER TO THE STILL.
THIS IS ONE
OF THESE CHEAPER MODELS.
YOU CAN HAVE A POOL INSTALLED.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT 5,000 BUCKS.
YOU CAN BUY ONE OF THESE THINGS
FOR ABOUT 500 BUCKS.
YOU TAKE A WHILE
SETTING THEM UP.
YOU REALIZE HOW UGLY THEY ARE.
YOU THROW THEM AWAY
AND BUY A $5,000 ONE.
THERE'S THE FIRST STEP.
"LEVEL THE POOL AREA."
LEVELLING AREAS IS KIND OF--
HERE, LOOK AT THIS.
THIS IS SOMETHING
YOU MAY NOT BE AWARE OF.
IN MANY PARTS OF THE COUNTRY,
YOU CAN RENT A BOBCAT
WITHOUT ANY PRIOR EXPERIENCE.
YOU DON'T NEED
A SPECIAL LICENCE.
YOU CAN GO ON UP THERE.
IF YOU HAVE
A WORKING VISA CARD
THAT BELONGS TO YOU OR PERHAPS
SOMEONE THAT YOU FOUND...
IF YOU'VE GOT THAT
AND THEY'RE COVERED,
YOU CAN JUST GO IN THERE.
THEY'RE NOT THAT HARD
TO OPERATE.
YOU CAN HAVE A GOOD TIME.
IT JUST GETS THE JOB DONE
THAT MUCH FASTER.
BY THE TIME YOU'RE FINISHED
WITH THE BOBCAT AND HAVE
ALL THE EQUIPMENT
GATHERED TOGETHER,
YOU HAVE ENOUGH TIME TO DO
THE JOB YOU WERE TRYING TO DO
BUT YOU'LL DO THAT
WITH JUST SHOVELS --
SOMETHING THAT YOU CAN HANDLE.
WE'LL BE BACK LATER
TO SHOW YOU
HOW THIS THING TURNS OUT.
GET REAL, BILL.
THIS IS MORE MANLY ANYWAY,
RIGHT?
THERE ARE MANY
SPEEDY VESSELS
LIKE SPEEDBOATS
AND SKI-BOATS AND THAT
EVEN A TIN BOAT
WITH A 25-HORSE
CAN GET THERE
IN NOTHING FLAT
SAILBOATS
TEND TO BE SLOWER
WHENEVER
THE SUMMER WIND STALLS
BUT A CANOE
CAN REALLY GET MOVING
WHEN YOU ACCIDENTALLY
TAKE HER OVER THE FALLS
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
WE'LL BUILD A MACHINE
THAT WILL RUN ON THE BOOZE
FROM JIMMY GRISTLE'S STILL.
I HAVE A LAWNMOWER.
YOU GUYS ARE THINKING,
"WHAT KIND OF MACHINE COULD YOU
MAKE OUT OF A LAWNMOWER?"
WELL, THINK ABOUT IT.
HMM...
IT'S OBVIOUS, ISN'T IT?
A ROBOT! OH, YEAH!
I'M GONNA MAKE
A HOOCH-POWERED ANDROID --
A "HOOCHENOID".
WHEN I WAS A KID,
USED TO GET THE
"POPULAR MECHANICS" MAGAZINES.
THEY'D TALK ABOUT
HOW ROBOTS IN THE FUTURE
WOULD CLEAN OUR HOUSES
AND FETCH EVERYTHING FOR US.
SO FAR, ALL THEY'VE DONE
IS STOLEN OUR JOBS.
I'M GONNA BUILD
MY VERY OWN C3-PU...
OR R2-DETOX...
SOMETHING THAT WILL DO
MY EVERY WHIM.
HEY, I'M GONNA NEED A WHIM.
I GOT THIS WOMAN'S
WIG HEAD HERE.
WE'RE GONNA MAKE
A WOMAN ROBOT.
YOU WANT TO PAINT HER GOLD.
SILVER -- YOU WANT
TO PAINT HER SILVER.
ROBOTS SHOULD ALWAYS BE SILVER.
JUST LAY IT ON GOOD AND THICK.
THERE WE GO,
AND JUST SET THAT ASIDE.
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO
IS MAKE A SPINE,
WHICH IS A BUNCH OF VERTEBRAE
OR DISCS
KIND OF ATTACHED TOGETHER.
FOR THAT, WE COULD USE
HOCKEY PUCKS
AND DRILL OUT THE CENTRE
FOR YOUR SPINAL CORD.
YOU COULD USE P.V.C. PIPE
AND MAKE A PLASTIC...
PLASTIC... ROBOT...
I FIND THE PLASTIC
HARD TO WORK WITH.
PERSONALLY, I PREFER
THE LOOK AND FEEL OF WOOD.
SO I'M GONNA BUILD
A WOODEN ROBOT
AND HAVE HER "LUMBER" AROUND.
LUMBER AROUND.
ALWAYS ROOM FOR HUMOUR
IN THE WORKSHOP.
YOU WANNA GET THE HEAD
AND SEE HOW BIG
THE SPINE SHOULD BE,
YOU KNOW,
IN PROPORTION TO THE...
BY GOLLY.
OK, THE LACQUER HAS KIND OF
EATEN THE HEAD AWAY.
WE HAVE A MUCH SMALLER HEAD.
NOT ROOM FOR A VERY BIG BRAIN,
SO WE'LL MAKE IT A GUY ROBOT.
ALL RIGHT, SO STACK UP YOUR...
YOUR VARIOUS PIECES OF WOOD...
TILL IT LOOKS
ABOUT IN PROPORTION.
BY GOLLY, THAT LOOKS HUMAN
ALREADY.
MORE THAN MOOSE THOMPSON DOES,
ANYWAY.
GET YOURSELF SOME NAILS
AND JUST START NAILING
ONE VERTEBRAE TO THE NEXT.
IT'S JUST REALLY THAT SIMPLE.
I'M GONNA USE
A DIFFERENT NAIL.
THAT WAS THE WRONG KIND.
THIS IS THE RIGHT KIND.
SEE THIS KIND OF NAIL?
THIS IS...
BY GOLLY.
WE'LL GET
A DIFFERENT KIND OF NAIL.
ALWAYS HAVE LOTS OF KINDS OF
NAILS AROUND IN YOUR WORKSHOP.
NO.
POINTY END DOWN.
THEY'RE PUT...
(Grunting)
YEAH...
ALL RIGHT.
BIGGER NAIL!
THERE'S THE PROBLEM.
HUH? ANOTHER SPINAL INJURY.
WAIT, I GOT A BETTER IDEA
FOR SOMETHING MECHANICAL
TO BRING ME MY DRINKS
AND GET ME STUFF.
(Machinery whirring)
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
OK, COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, WHOA, WHOA!
HAND ME THE TRAY, HAROLD.
POUR ME A DRINK.
(Machinery whirring)
OH, OH, OH, OH!
HAROLD, WATCH IT!
YOU'LL NEVER REPLACE A HUMAN.
COMING UP, WHERE THERE'S SMOKE,
THERE'S A FIRE EXTINGUISHER.
WANT TO TALK TO YOU GUYS
WHO ARE SITTING THERE,
UNATTACHED,
THE VICTIMS OF A DIVORCE
OR A JOINT CHEQUING ACCOUNT.
YOU'RE PROBABLY THINKING ABOUT
LOOKING UP THAT OLD GIRLFRIEND
YOU HAD IN HIGH SCHOOL,
THE ONE YOU TOOK
TO THE GRADUATION SOCK-HOP?
THERE MIGHT BE SOME APPEAL
IN RUSHING BACK
TO THE ONLY OTHER WOMAN
YOU EVER HAD A SLOW DANCE WITH,
BUT I'M TELLING YOU,
AS A FRIEND,
THINK ABOUT A COUPLE OF THINGS.
FIRST AND FOREMOST,
TIME HAS NOT BEEN KIND TO YOU.
TOO MUCH GRAVITY
AND TOO MUCH GRAVY
HAVE TAKEN THEIR TOLL.
(Audience laughing)
YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE YOU DID
ON PAGE 77 OF THE YEARBOOK.
NOW ZIP OVER TO HER PICTURE.
TRY ADDING 30 OR 40 YEARS
TO THAT.
SEE WHERE I'M COMING FROM?
START WITH A CLEAN SLATE.
DATE A WOMAN YOU DIDN'T KNOW
WHEN SHE WAS YOUNG.
YOU'LL BE ATTRACTED TO HER
FOR WHAT SHE IS RIGHT NOW.
THERE WON'T BE NAGGING PICTURES
FROM 30 YEARS AGO.
SHE'LL MAKE SURE OF THAT.
IT MIGHT BE A NICE GESTURE
IF YOU DID THE SAME FOR HER.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Audience laughing)
WELL, THIS IS THE LAST
OF THE STUFF
FROM JIMMY GRISTLE'S STILL.
WE STOLE-- I'M SORRY --
WE
SALVAGED
THE STUFF.
HOW ARE WE DOING AT THIS END?
I SHOULD REMIND YOU
THAT I'M AGAINST THIS.
I'M JUST HERE
FOR THE CHEMISTRY.
SAVE YOUR SPEECH FOR THE TRIAL.
I'M KIDDING YOU!
I'M JUST
KIDDING!
BUSTER'S GOT EVERYTHING GOING
IN THE KITCHEN.
HE'S GOT THE CAULDRON BOILING.
I FOUND SOME SUGAR.
WE NEED CORN FOR THE MASH.
SHOULD BE CANS IN THE KITCHEN.
SOME OF IT'S CREAMED CORN.
THAT SHOULD BE FINE.
WHEN JUNIOR SINGLETON
GETS HERE WITH HIS MOM'S LADA,
WE'RE READY TO START.
WHY USE HER CAR?
WE'LL PARK IT OUTSIDE.
WE'LL RUN A HOSE FROM
THE KETTLE TO THE ENGINE.
IT'S GONNA PROCESS IT.
IT'S GONNA PUMP IT, FILTER IT,
SKIM IT, PUREE IT,
AND DISPENSE IT
OUT THE HOLE OF THE RAD.
THAT'S THE THEORY.
IT CAN DO THAT?
UNCLE RED, IT'S A RUSSIAN CAR.
IT CAN DO ANYTHING.
EXCEPT START.
(Audience laughing)
WELL, HERE WE ARE
WITH HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
WE'RE TROLLING FOR TROUT.
HAP CAUGHT HIMSELF
A BEAUTY LAST WEEK.
SHOULD HAVE SEEN
THE ONE THAT GOT AWAY.
EVERY FISHERMAN SAYS THAT.
I SAID IT FIRST, RED.
OH, REALLY?
ALWAYS HAD A FLAIR
FOR THE ONE-LINERS.
"MAKE LOVE, NOT WAR.
"DON'T DO ANYTHING
I WOULDN'T DO.
"HAVE A NICE DAY."
THEN THERE WERE MY POEMS.
"MARY HAD A LITTLE LAMB".
YOU CAME UP
WITH ALL THAT YOURSELF?
YOU KNEW THAT, DIDN'T YOU?
NO.
I WROTE BOOK AFTER BOOK.
SNAPPY SAYINGS, QUIPS, POEMS,
PHRASES, NURSERY RHYMES...
"LITTLE JACK HORNER", "LONDON
BRIDGE IS FALLING DOWN"...
"THREE LITTLE PIGS"...
"JACK AND THE BEANSTALK",
"LITTLE JACK HORNER"...
YOU ALREADY SAID
"LITTLE JACK HORNER".
THIS WAS THE SEQUEL.
YOU KNOW, HAP, I DON'T REMEMBER
EVER SEEING ANY OF THOSE BOOKS.
I'VE NEVER USED MY OWN NAME,
HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
I'M NOT ONE TO TAKE
A LOT OF CREDIT FOR STUFF.
THAT WOULD LEAD
TO LEGAL ACTION.
I USED A PEN NAME.
THE NAME I CHOSE
WAS ARNOLD NONYMOUS --
A. NONYMOUS FOR SHORT --
SO I DIDN'T GET ANY CREDITS.
ALL THOSE NURSERY RHYMES
AND PHRASES AND POEMS...
I'VE BEEN QUOTED MORE OFTEN
THAN SHAKESPEARE,
BUT WHO WOULD BELIEVE IT?
I CAN'T THINK OF ANYONE.
IF I HAD A NICKEL
FOR EVERY TIME I WAS QUOTED,
I'D BE A BILLIONAIRE.
IF YOU DON'T MIND ME SAYING SO,
IF IFS AND BUTS
WERE CANDIES AND NUTS,
WE'D ALL HAVE
A GREAT CHRISTMAS.
WELL, THERE YOU GO.
GIVE ME A NICKEL.
OK, THIS IS THE BIG ONE
FOR A GRAND PRIZE
YET TO BE DETERMINED.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. STUYVESANT TO SAY
THIS WORD.
THIRTY SECONDS, GO.
UM... OBLIGATION.
MOTHER.
APPOINTMENT.
PROCTOLOGIST.
(Laughing)
WHEN YOU TELL SOMEBODY
YOU'LL BE THERE, THAT'S A...
LIE.
WHEN YOU CARE ABOUT SOMETHING,
IT'S BECAUSE YOU'VE MADE A...
BET?
I KNOW, I KNOW.
IF YOU GIVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND
AN ENGAGEMENT RING
YOU'RE MAKING A...
MISTAKE.
WE MAY HAVE
DOWN-PLAYED THE DANGER
OF MANUFACTURING
A FLAMMABLE LIQUID
IN AN ENCLOSED SPACE
UNDER PRIMITIVE CONDITIONS
NEAR AN OPEN FLAME
IN A WOODEN BUILDING
ON A SHAKY STOVE.
BUT THE FIRE'S OUT NOW, AND
I THINK THE INITIAL EXPLOSION
DID NOT DO TOO MUCH
STRUCTURAL DAMAGE.
THERE'S CREAMED CORN
EVERYWHERE!
EVERYWHERE CREAMED CORN.
IT'S LIKE SOMEBODY
BLEW UP IOWA.
IT'S OK --
THE FIRE IS OUT.
THAT CAR'S STILL BURNING.
BUT I THINK IT LANDED
FAR ENOUGH AWAY FROM THE LODGE
THAT WE'LL LET NATURE
TAKE ITS COURSE.
WHAT ARE THE OTHER GUYS DOING?
THEY'RE IN THE KITCHEN
LICKING CORN OFF THE CUPBOARDS.
I'M SORRY, BUT
YOU HAVE TO FORGET
ABOUT DISTILING
YOUR WASHER FLUID STUFF.
THE STILL'S DESTROYED,
AND I QUIT.
HA-HA-HA-HA-HA.
YOU'LL HAVE TO
SWALLOW YOUR PRIDE
AND BUY YOUR WASHER FLUID
AT HUMPHREY'S EVERYTHING STORE.
REAL MEN
DON'T SWALLOW THEIR PRIDE.
WE JUST FAKE IT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WE'LL DO.
ALL WE'VE GOT LEFT
IS THE EMPTY BOTTLES.
OH, OH, AW!
I GOT-- OH, I KNOW!
THIS IS INCREDIBLE.
WE CAN BOTTLE THE SPRING WATER
FROM POSSUM HILL.
WE CAN JUST BOTTLE THE WATER.
SPRING WATER.
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO BUY
SPRING WATER, HAROLD?
YEAH, ALL THE TIME.
OK,
ALL RIGHT,
YOU'RE GONNA FILL BOTTLES
WITH SPRING WATER
AND PEOPLE WILL PAY FOR IT.
THAT COULD WORK.
MR. PERRIER ISN'T DOING SO BAD.
COME ON, HAROLD.
WHAT KIND OF GOMER'S
ARE GOING TO PAY MONEY
FOR WATER
THAT COMES OUT OF THE GROUND?
CITY PEOPLE.
OH WELL.
OH YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
(Red): WITH US SWITCHING
TO BOTTLED WATER
THE ABOVE-GROUND POOL
MAKES EVEN MORE SENSE.
LUCKILY, WE HADN'T
COMPLETELY BUILT IT YET,
'CAUSE IT HAD ONLY BEEN
SEVEN DAYS.
IF YOU EVER GET
ONE OF THESE THINGS,
TRY TO LIVE IN A NEIGHBOURHOOD
WITH A LOT OF PEOPLE IN IT
SO THAT YOU CAN AFFORD
TO LOSE A FEW FRIENDS.
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
HERE'S SOMETHING
FOR YOU TEENAGERS.
BE CAREFUL WHAT YOU STRADDLE.
IT CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE TO
YOUR ENTIRE ADULT LIFE.
COME ON, BILL, UP YOU GO.
OH BOY.
WE'VE GOT TO PUT
THIS POOL LINER ON HERE.
IMAGINE MAKING A BED
WITH THIS GUY.
ANYWAY, WE GOT HER ON,
AND GOT A LITTLE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON
SNUCK INTO THE PROJECT.
WHERE IS HE?
HOW DID HE DO THAT?
TUNNEL OUT, BILL,
LIKE THEY DID
IN "THE GREAT ESCAPE".
OR STAY THERE.
IT MIGHT MAKE
AN INTERESTING DESIGN
IN THE BOTTOM OF THE POOL.
OH MAN, WHAT DID HE HAVE
FOR BREAKFAST?
THIS IS THE PUMP.
IT'S A SMALL UNIT.
IT'S MADE TO PUMP WATER,
AND WE DIDN'T HAVE WATER.
THE AIR WAS UNBELIEVABLE
COMING OUT OF THAT THING.
I THOUGHT BILL WOULD
DO THOSE TRICKS
WHERE HE MAKES ANIMALS.
NOW, HERE... NOW, THIS...
OK, OK, GOODBYE, SEE YA.
BILL TRIES TO MAKE IT WORK,
AND THEN REALIZES --
NO, BILL.
IT LOOKS LIKE ON OF THEM
POPCORN MAKERS, DOESN'T IT?
BILL RUNS AND THEN TRIPS,
AND THE LADDER
HAS A SPRING EFFECT.
AND HE LANDS.
THEN BILL GETS THE IDEA
TO PUSH A HOLE THROUGH.
EVERYBODY OUT OF THE POOL.
OH MY GOSH.
OH!
AND, UH, WHAT HAVE WE GOT HERE?
WELL, IT WAS JUST ANOTHER DAY
AT THE LODGE.
TWO GUYS WASTING TIME AND MONEY
ROLLING AROUND ON THE GROUND,
BEING GOOFY,
ENDING UP WRAPPED IN PLASTIC.
MAN.
DOUGIE'S GOT ADVICE
FOR YOU GUYS IN TROUBLE.
WELL, DALTON HUMPHREY
TAKES THE CAKE.
TRY TO DO SOMETHING GOOD
FOR LOCAL COMMERCE,
WHAT DOES IT GET YA?
IF YOU WANT TO DO SOMETHING,
WHY NOT SETTLE YOUR BILLS?
THIS ISN'T ABOUT PAYING BILLS.
I TOOK A BUNCH OF
POSSUM SPRING WATER DOWN THERE
TO SEE IF THEY COULD SELL IT,
AND THEY SAY
"IT'S GOT TO BE TESTED."
TURNS OUT IT'S GOT
SO MANY MINERALS IN IT,
THE ICICLES POINT NORTH.
SO NOBODY WANTS IT?
THE CENTRE FOR DISEASE CONTROL
ORDERED A COUPLE OF CASES.
I GUESS THE MORAL FOR TODAY IS
IF YOU WANT WASHER FLUID,
BUY IT.
YOU GOT OFF EASY
CONSIDERING THERE WAS
ONLY ONE EXPLOSION,
ONE KITCHEN FIRE,
AND THAT CAR'S BURNING.
LOOKS LIKE AN OIL FIRE
IN KUWAIT.
I CAN'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
I'M STUCK WITH 2,000 BOTTLES
WITH NOTHING IN 'EM.
THAT'S NOT TRUE --
THERE'S AIR IN THEM.
WELL, THAT'S ALMOST NOTHING.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
IT'S NOT JUST ANY AIR.
IT'S THE AIR OF POSSUM HILLS.
WE COULD START A TREND HERE.
POSSUM AIR?
THIS IS THE PERFECT
YUPPIE PRODUCT.
FAT-FREE, CHOLESTEROL-FREE,
SUGAR-FREE, SALT-FREE,
NO ADDITIVES, NO CALORIES.
WE'LL CALL IT "POSSUM LIGHT".
SHE HAD THAT CHAT WITH YOU
ABOUT HOW SHE GETS STUCK
DOING ALL THE HOUSEWORK.
YOU TOLD HER YOU'D HELP
A LITTLE MORE, DIDN'T YA?
YOU SAID YOU'D PICK UP
AFTER YOURSELF.
NOW SHE'S CALLING YOU
INTO THE BEDROOM.
AND IT'S NOT FOR
WHAT YOU HOPE IT IS.
AT HER FEET IS A HUMUNGOUS PILE
OF YOUR USED UNDERWEAR.
DON'T TRY SAYING SOMETHING
STUPID LIKE
"I'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR THEM."
BE CLEVER AND
TURN THE TABLES ON HER.
LOOK DOWN AND GO
"THOSE AREN'T MINE.
"HAVE YOU BEEN SEEING SOMEONE?"
NO -- DWELL ON THE POSITIVE.
SAY "STORING USED UNDERWEAR
IN THE BOTTOM OF THE CLOSET
"IS GOOD FOR THE ENVIRONMENT
"'CAUSE YOU USE
LESS LAUNDRY DETERGENT."
AND BRING UP THE POINT,
AT LEAST YOU'RE NOT LEAVING IT
AROUND THE KITCHEN ANY MORE.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW.
THIS WEEK'S EXPERTS ARE
MY UNCLE RED
AND HIS FRIEND,
MR. DALTON HUMPHREY.
(Applause and cheering)
OUR LETTER GOES AS FOLLOWS.
"DEAR EXPERTS"
AH-AH-AH.
"MY CAR IS A WRECK.
"WHAT DO YOU DO WITH A CAR
THAT'S TOO WRECKED TFIX?"
OBVIOUSLY, YOUE GOT TO
SELL THE PIG.
THAT SOUNDS A LITTLE UNETHICAL,
MR. HUMPHREY.
SELLING A CAR THAT'S
UNSAFE AND WORTHLESS.
YOU WOULDN'T SELL IT
TO ANYBODY YOU KNOW.
YEAH, I WOULD.
NO, NO, NO,
DON'T GET ME WRONG.
MY FRIENDS AND NEIGHBOURS
ARE A TREASURED
AND WONDERFUL PART OF MY LIFE.
I TRULY VALUE EACH OF THEM.
I HAVE TO SAY THAT I AM BLESSED
TO HAVE
SO MANY OF THEM IN MY LIFE.
BUT, WELL, HEY,
A BUCK'S A BUCK.
I THINK A LOT OF IT IS
THE WORDING OF THE AD.
YOU'VE GOT TO SAY, LIKE,
"FOR SALE, AS IS, WHERE IS."
OR "CAR FOR SALE,
"STOPS AND GOES,
MOSTLY STOPS."
OR, "GREAT VEHICLE FOR
PEOPLE WHO HATE TRAVELLING."
THAT'S NOT LYING.
THAT'S JUST GOOD SALESMANSHIP.
SAY THE FLOORBOARD'S RUSTED.
SAY THAT'S GOT
A CLASSIC INTERIOR.
CLASSIC?
LIKE THE FLINTSTONE'S CAR.
SEE, NOW THAT'S NOT LYING.
THAT'S
PERJURY.                THAT'S
SALESMANSHIP.
HAROLD, DIDN'T
I SEE YOU
TALKING TO THAT COUNSELLOR,
TRYING TO GET A DATE?
HOW DID YOU
DESCRIBE YOURSELF?
HA-HA-HA-HA-HA.
HA-HA.
I MIGHT HAVE SAID SOMETHING
ABOUT, YOU KNOW,
SOMETHING ABOUT BEING
TALL, DARK AND HANDSOME.
RATHER THAN TALL,
DORK AND USELESS.
THAT'S ABOUT AS HONEST AS
OUR CAR SALES PITCH, ISN'T IT?
NOT REALLY --
THE GIRL DIDN'T BREAK DOWN.
YOU SHOULD LOOK AT SOMETHING
WITH MORE MILES ON HER.
(Laughing)
I THOUGHT WE WERE
ONTO SOMETHING.
SHOWS WHAT I KNOW
ABOUT YUPPIES IN LOS ANGELES.
LOS ANGELES?
YOUR AIR WAS TURNED DOWN
BY LOS ANGELES?
YEAH, THEY SAY
IT SMELLS FUNNY.
I THINK WE MADE A MISTAKE
PUTTING THAT DEAD POSSUM
ON THE LABEL.
YOU COULD HAVE RINSED
THE BOTTLES OUT FIRST.
DOESN'T MATTER --
I TOOK THE BOTTLES BACK.
I GOT ENOUGH MONEY TO BUY
12 GALLONS
OF WINDSHIELD WIPER FLUID.
THIS WINTER I'LL BE LETTING HER
FLY ANY TIME I FEEL LIKE IT.
THERE'S A LESSON FOR YOU.
NOT TO MAKE A STILL
OUT OF A RUSSIAN CAR
OR BOTTLE WATER OR CAN AIR
DURING MANURE SEASON,
WHEN ALL YOU WANT
IS WASHER FLUID?
NO -- THE LESSON IS,
WHEN YOU GET TO MY AGE
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO LET
A LITTLE SQUIRT GO
ANY TIME YOU FEEL LIKE IT.
(Possum
squeal)
MEETING TIME.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
WHEN OUR NEIGHBOURS SEE
HOW CLEAN OUR WINDSHIELD IS
THEY'LL THINK WE HAVE
SO MUCH MONEY
WE'VE STOPPED BUYING
SELF-SERVE GAS.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF HAROLD,
MYSELF AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): OK.
ALL RISE.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN, GUYS.
(Harold): WE SHOULD BEGIN BY
READING THE MINUTES
OF LAST WEEK.