[garbage cans crashing]
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE REASON
GOD CREATED BODIES
THAT CAN HEAL THEMSELVES,
THE SALT OF THE EARTH
IN A SALT-FREE WORLD,
MY UNCLE, MR. RED GREEN!
AH HA HA HA!
[applause and whistling]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YOU'LL BE GLAD YOU TUNED IN
BECAUSE WE HAVE A PROBLEM
THAT YOU CAN TURN INTO
AN OPPORTUNITY.
I LIKE THAT ONE.
JUST THE OPPOSITE OF YOU,
EH, HAROLD?
[laughing]
ANYWAY,
WE'VE RECEIVED NOTICE THAT
WE HAVE TO CLEAN UP THE LODGE
BECAUSE THESE COLLECTABLES
ON THE FLOORS AND WALLS
ARE GETTING IN THE WAY OF US
GETTING THINGS LIKE
FIRE INSURANCE, LIFE INSURANCE,
AND GETTING FROM
ONE ROOM TO THE OTHER.
HERE'S WHERE IT GOES
OVER THE TOP.
UNCLE RED'S GIVING YOU
THE OPPORTUNITY TO BUY IT.
AREN'T YOU THRILLED?
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT BE.
HE'S A BORN SALESMAN.
WATCH THIS, HAROLD.
GIVE US A CALL.
MAKE AN OFFER.
JUST DIAL 555-
"C" FOR COLLECTABLE,
"R" FOR RARITY,
"A" FOR ANTIQUE,
"P" FOR PECULIARITY.
THAT'S 555-CRAP.
DIAL 55...
OPERATORS ARE STANDING BY.
555-CRAP.
GIVE US A CALL.
CALL IN NOW, I GUESS.
NO SENSE PUTTING IT OFF.
THIS STUFF WILL JUST GO
LIKE...
555-C.R.A.P.
THE PHONE WORKING, HAROLD?
I DON'T HEAR ONE.
YOU WILL IN A MINUTE.
[horns honking]
[geese honking]
[quacking]
[Red]: ON TODAY'S SHOW,
GARTH HAS A COUGAR,
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE
A GARBAGE COMPACTER,
EDGAR HAS A PROBLEM,
AS USUAL, WITH DYNAMITE,
AND WE GOT RECYCLED GEMS.
THAT NUMBER IS 555-272P.
[telephone ringing]
WE HAVE A CALLER.
WHERE'S THE PHONE, HAROLD?
IT'S UNDER THE JUNK,
LIKE EVERYTHING ELSE.
DON'T HANG UP.
HERE WE GO, HERE WE GO!
[telephone ringing]
WHAT DO YOU WANT AND
HOW MUCH YOU WILLING TO PAY?
HUH?
THEY WANT YOU, HAROLD.
ANY OFFER TAKES HIM.
HELLO, HAROLD GREEN SPEAKING.
OH, YEAH, OK.
IT'S THE GARBAGE COLLECTION
AGENCY.
I PHONED THEM TO COME FOR
THIS STUFF.
THEY CAN'T TAKE THIS.
PARDON ME, WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT --
THEY'RE REFUSING IT.
HEY, BUDDY BOY, IT'S MY CHOICE
WHETHER YOU CAN GET IT.
YOU'RE GARBAGE MEN.
I SAY "THAT'S GARBAGE."
YOU GET IT.
ARE YOU STARTING TO GRASP
THE NATURE OF OUR RELATIONSHIP?
HUH? -- WELL FINE.
DON'T CALL BACK.
THEY HUNG UP ON YOU,
DIDN'T THEY?
RIGHT AFTER I SAID
"BUDDY BOY."
[laughing]
[Red]: SPEAKING OF BUDDY BOY,
HERE'S MY BUDDY BOY,
ESPECIALLY THE BOY PART.
HE'S GOING TO PLAY
FRISBEE FOR US TODAY.
YEAH, THAT'S EXCITING, BILL.
BILL CAN GET A FRISBEE TO DO
PRETTY MUCH WHATEVER HE WANTS.
ONCE IN A WHILE I CAN GET
A FRISBEE TO DO WHAT I WANT.
[laughing]
ALL RIGHT, THEY TELL ME
THIS IS THE BIG ONE,
FOR FOUR HOURS OF AROMA THERAPY
AT BAXTER'S BEANERY.
HAROLD, YOU GOT
AROUND 30 SECONDS
TO GET DOUGIE FRANKLIN
TO SAY THIS WORD.
ALL RIGHT, GO.
YOUR MONSTER
TRUCK IS
MANLY.
ALL RIGHT, IF IT HAD A MUFFLER,
IT WOULD BE LESS...
FUN?
IT'S FUN AND MACHO
AND MASCULINE AND MANLY
BECAUSE IT'S...
MADE IN
AMERICA.
[laughing]
WELL, OK, UH,
BUT THE ENGINE IS...
FULLY SUPERCHARGED.
ALMOST OUT OF TIME HERE,
HAROLD.
OH, OK, ALL RIGHT,
REMEMBER THAT TIME,
YOU WERE PEELING OUT DOWNTOWN,
THE STREETS WERE ON FIRE.
YOUR RADIO WAS CRANKED UP.
THAT'S BECAUSE IT WAS...
MY
BIRTHDAY.
[laughing]
THIS IS EDGAR MONTROSE
SAYING THAT
IF YOU'RE CLOSE ENOUGH
TO HEAR THE DYNAMITE HISSING,
YOU'RE TOO DARN CLOSE.
OH, THE SUN
HAS TURNED GREEN
THE TREES ARE
UPSIDE DOWN
EVERYTHING IS SHAKING
WHILE EXPLOSIONS
CONTINUALLY POUND
YOU COWER
IN YOUR BEDROLL
AFRAID
YOU'RE GOING TO DIE
BUT IT ISN'T
THE END OF THE WORLD
IT'S JUST A REALLY
IMPRESSIVE HANGOVER
[laughing]
NOW THAT WE'VE GOT GARBAGE
BUILDING UP AROUND THE LODGE
FASTER THAN
IT USULY BUILDS UP,
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE
YOUR OWN GARBAGE COMPACTER
USING THE LAW OF THE LEVER,
WHICH ISN'T "IF YOU
DON'T LOVE HER, LEAVE HER,"
OR IN STINKY PETERSON'S CASE,
"IF YOU DO LOVE HER,
LEAVE HER."
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING.
A LEVER IS KIND OF LIKE
THE MAIL SERVICE.
YOU'VE GOT YOUR FIRST,
SECOND AND THIRD CLASS.
SOMETIMES
IT DOESN'T GET THERE AT ALL.
NOW THIS HERE,
THIS IS YOUR FIRST CLASS.
AND THEN WHEN YOU SET HER UP
LIKE THIS,
LIKE THAT,
THAT'S YOUR SECOND CLASS.
AND THIS, I BELIEVE,
IS A THIRD CLASS LEVER.
AND THIS IS A FOURTH CLASS
TWO-BY-FOUR.
I THINK I'LL LEAVE HER.
I'M GOING TO USE THIS LADDER
AS A LEVER
IN MY GARBAGE COMPACTER.
TO MAKE THAT WORK,
I HAVE TO CUT A SLOT
IN THE SIDE OF THIS OIL DRUM
FOR THE LADDER TO FIT INTO
AND COMPRESS THE GARBAGE.
TO DO THAT,
ALL I NEED IS A HACKSAW.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO HAVE
THIS SIDE OF THE DRUM
FACING AWAY FROM THE STREET,
'CAUSE IT'S NOT
THAT ATTRACTIVE.
NOW YOU LOAD YOUR GARBAGE
IN THERE.
MAKE YOURSELF A REAL HIGH STACK
BECAUSE YOU'LL COMPRESS THIS
DOWN SO THIN
IT WILL SLIDE UNDER
YOUR NEIGHBOUR'S FRONT DOOR.
NOW YOU TAKE YOUR LADDER AND
STICK IT ON TOP OF THE PILE,
AND LINE IT UP SO THE LADDER
WILL GO INTO THE SLOT.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS
APPLY SOME DOWNWARD PRESSURE.
HMM?
HAROLD,
IS MOOSE THOMPSON AROUND?
ALL RIGHT, I'LL USE
THE NEXT BEST THING.
[van door opening]
[engine starting]
THERE'S YOUR GARBAGE
COMPRESSED TO A SIZE
THAT WILL FILL YOU WITH PRIDE.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OK, MAYBE I DIDN'T
QUITE COMPRESS IT.
I MORE OR LESS
DROVE IT INTO THE GROUND.
THIS IS WHERE WE HAVE TO REVERT
BACK TO THE LAW OF THE LEVER.
IF YOU MAKE A MISTAKE...
LEAVE 'ER.
BUZZ LOST HIS PLANE.
I KNOW WHERE TO LOOK.
YOU GUYS ARE TRYING TO LOOK
20 AGAIN.
I'M ASKING AS A FRIEND:
STOP DOING THAT, ALL RIGHT?
YOU'RE WEARING
THE SNAPPY CLOTHES,
YOU'RE EXERCISING,
YOU'RE DIETING,
MAYBE GETTING YOURSELF
A $10 HAIRCUT.
[laughing]
HERE'S A BULLETIN.
IT'S NOT WORKING.
STOP DOING THAT.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
YOU'VE GOT A CAREER.
YOU'VE GOT A LITTLE MONEY.
YOU KNOW HOW TO TALK TO WOMEN.
YOU'RE A MAN OF THE WORLD.
UNFORTUNATELY,
IT'S TAKEN 25 YEARS,
A WIFE AND THREE KIDS
TO GET THERE.
BE HONEST ABOUT
HOW OLD YOU ARE.
YOU'LL ACCEPT IT.
STOP LOOKING IN MIRRORS
AND BUY PANTS WITH
ELASTIC WAISTBANDS.
IF THAT DOESN'T MAKE YOU HAPPY,
LOOK AT A PICTURE OF YOURSELF
WHEN YOU WERE 20.
LOOK AT THE HAIR, THE SHIRT,
THE PANTS, THE SHOES.
YOU WANT TO LOOK
LIKE THAT AGAIN?
I DIDN'T THINK SO?
REMEMBER, WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
HI, I'M EDGAR MONTROSE.
I'M AN EXPERT IN EXPLOSIVES.
THE ONLY WAY TO BECOME
AN EXPERT
IS THROUGH YEARS OF EXPERIENCE
AND CONSTANT EXPERIMENTATION.
LET'S SEE,
FIVE STICKS OF DYNAMITE
KEPT IT IN THE AIR
FOR 60 SECONDS.
LET'S TRY SIX.
I'VE PULLED OFF A BEAUTY
THIS TIME.
COME ON, HAROLD.
NOW, THE STUFF WAS NOT SELLING,
GRANTED.
THE GARBAGE MEN
REFUSED TO TAKE IT.
WAIT TILL THEY SEE
WHAT I THROW OUT FOR THEM
DURING CARP SEASON.
THEN I CALLED
THE WASTE MANAGEMENT PEOPLE.
THEY WANTED TO CHARGE ME
TO TAKE THIS AWAY.
BUT I PULLED OFF A MAJOR COUP.
HE'S AGREED TO LET THEM USE
10 ACRES OF LODGE PROPERTY
AS A LANDFILL SITE.
WE'VE GOT TO SORT THROUGH
THE GARBAGE,
PUT IT IN CONTAINERS.
WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
IF THE LAVA LAMP IS
ANIMAL OR MINERAL.
BUT IT'S FREE, HAROLD.
WE GET RID OF THIS STUFF
AND IT DOESN'T COST US A CENT.
YOU CAN'T CALL IT
A LANDFILL.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE IT CERTIFIED,
APPROVED, ZONED.
IT'S ALL DONE, HAROLD.
THEN 10 ACRES OUT BACK,
THAT'S BEEN ZONED
A PUBLIC LANDFILL.
PUBLIC?
PUBLIC MEANS THAT
ANYBODY CAN PUT STUFF THERE.
I DON'T THINK SO.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YES!
PUBLIC LANDFILL,
JUST LIKE PUBLIC BEACH.
THAT MEANS ANYBODY CAN USE IT.
WELL THEN, GREAT.
THAT MEANS WE'LL GET PEOPLE
COMING TO THE LODGE.
YOUR GENERATION JUST
DOESN'T GET IT, DO THEY?
NOPE --
SO FAR SO GOOD.
WHEN IT COMES TO SAFETY,
NO ONE IS MORE FAMILIAR
WITH THE LEGAL RAMIFICATIONS
THAN MY PAL...
BUZZ SHERWOOD.
MAN, IS NOTHING SACRED
ANY MORE?
NO, I DON'T THINK SO, BUZZ.
WHERE IS YOUR AIRPLANE?
SOMEBODY RIPPED IT OFF, MAN.
THEY VIOLATED MY DOCK,
MY SPACE.
TOOK MY ONE TRUE LOVE.
FIRST JERRY GARCIA,
NOW THIS.
THINK ABOUT IT THIS WAY.
IF THEY FLEW OFF
IN YOUR PLANE,
THEY PROBABLY LEFT
A TRAIL OF PARTS.
YEAH.
SO EVENTUALLY...
EVENTUALLY, IF HE FLIES IT
LONG ENOUGH,
WE'LL GET THE WHOLE PLANE BACK!
[laughing]
THAT WOULD BE GREAT!
THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
HERE'S A LESSON FOR YOU.
SAFETY ALSO MEANS SECURITY.
YEAH, SAFETY, SECURITY,
THEY'RE LIKE THAT.
IT'S THE '90's.
IT'S THE '90's,
SO WATCH YOUR STUFF.
IT'S NOT THE '60's ANY MORE
WHERE WE LIVED IN
PEACE AND BROTHERHOOD.
THE BIG MAN
THAT RAN THE GOVERNMENT,
HE DIDN'T LIKE THAT.
SO THEY'VE TURNED US
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
THEY'VE GOT THE POLICE,
AND THAT'S THE POWER, MAN.
WE'RE JUST DROIDS.
BUZZ, BUZZ!
WHAT, MAN?
I THINK I FOUND THE PLANE.
MY PLANE!
OH, WOW, LOOK HOW CLEAN IT IS!
YOU MIGHT THINK ABOUT PLUGGING
THE HOLES IN THE PONTOONS.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
AND MAYBE STOP FLYING
THROUGH THE RIFLE RANGE.
OH YEAH, OK, YEAH, THAT'S GOOD.
YEAH, THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
BOY, OH BOY,
THIS LODGE CLEAN-OUT
IS WORKING BETTER THAN
ANYBODY EXPECTED.
WE'RE FINDING STUFF
WE HAVEN'T SEEN IN YEARS.
INCOME TAX FORMS, GUM,
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S FALSE TEETH.
ACTUALLY,
THEY WERE WITH THE GUM.
THE LODGE SEEMS BIGGER NOW.
I KNOW IT'S NOT.
IT'S THE SAME SIZE.
BUT IT FEELS BIGGER 'CAUSE
THE STUFF IS GONE, SO BIGGER.
BUT IT SEEMS DIFFERENT,
LIKE, SPATIALLY.
YOU FEEL THE VOLUME?
THERE'S VOLUME IN THE ROOM.
THE SAME, YET DIFFERENT.
IT'S BIGGER, BUT SMALLER.
WITHOUT BEING SMALLER,
IT'S LARGER.
THAT'S THE WAY I FEEL --
THAT'S ME.
YOUR TAX DOLLARS ARE PAYING
FOR THAT EDUCATION, FOLKS.
THE WASTE DISPOSAL COMPANY
DUMPED EVERYTHING IN FRONT
'CAUSE THEY THOUGHT THE LODGE
WAS THE DUMP.
THERE WAS A LOT OF GOOD STUFF.
I GOT THESE SLIM WHITMAN ALBUMS,
A TOASTER THAT ALMOST WORKS,
AND THERE MUST HAVE BEEN
50 EGG CARTONS.
I GOT A GUMBY AND POKEY --
ONE LEG MISSING.
BY THE TIME WE TOOK
THE GOOD STUFF,
THERE WASN'T ENOUGH LEFT
TO FILL A WHEELBARROW.
ANOTHER TRUCK'S PULLING UP!
WE GOT TO MAKE SURE
THEY'RE NOT THROWING OUT
ANY GOOD JUNK.
IF THERE'S ANY POWER RANGERS,
CALL ME!
GO, GO!
OH, HEY, MAN!
I'M BUZZ SHERWOOD.
IF YOU GET TO BE A PILOT,
YOU CAN USE LANDMARKS
LIKE ROADS AND HIGHWAYS
TO STEER YOUR PLANE.
BUT REMEMBER,
STAY IN THE PASSING LANE.
OTHERWISE THE MOTORISTS
YELL AT YOU.
[laughing]
FOR ALL YOU HANDYMEN
WHO USE PAINTSPRAY CANS,
THERE'S AN ARROW ON THE TOP
THAT TELLS YOU WHICH WAY
THE PAINT WILL SPRAY.
I WOULD ADVISE
THAT YOU LOOK AT THAT
BEFORE YOU START SPRAYING.
THAT'S MY SUGGESTION ANYWAY.
MEANWHILE BACK AT
THE FRISBEE FARM --
OH, THANK YOU, BILL.
BILL WAS FIRING THAT FRISBEE
AROUND.
HE KNOCKED THE HUBCAP OFF.
PUT THE HUBCAP
BACK ON THE VAN.
NO, THE HUBCAP.
PUT THAT ON THE...
THAT'S THE...
OH, I SEE.
ALL RIGHT, OK.
WELL, THAT'S...
I'M HERE, BILL.
NO, BILL, I'M HERE.
AH, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU GO OUT THERE
FOR THE EXERCISE.
A LITTLE AFTERNOON SPORT.
HERE YOU GO, BILL.
HERE WE GO.
HEY, NICE GRAB.
THROW HER BACK.
CHUCK IT IN HERE, BABY.
YOU HEAR ABOUT THE VIOLENCE
OF THE SPORT,
BUT, TO ME,
IT'S WITH GOOD REASON.
YOU HAD IT COMING,
ALL RIGHT?
OK, WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW?
THAT'S MY HUBCAP.
THAT WAS MY HUBCAP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, THE GARBAGE CAN LID.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
OH MAN, THIS GUY.
OK, THROW IT IN HERE, BILL.
NO, IT'S UP AND...
OH MAN, OH DEAR.
IT'S A BOOMERANG-TYPE THING.
THERE YOU GO.
WHAT GOES AROUND
COMES AROUND, EH?
PUT THAT BACK ON THERE.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT, BILL?
WHAT THE HECK?
OH, IT'S ONE OF THOSE LITTLE,
WHAT DO THEY CALL THEM?
THE CONTACT LENS.
HA-HA!
IT'S A LITTLE FRISBEE TO BILL.
HE FIRES THAT IN THERE.
LET HER RIP.
LET HER GO.
BOY, THAT IS HARD TO SEE,
COMING THROUGH THE SUN.
AND... I GOT HER!
ALL RIGHT.
TRY THAT, BILL.
THERE YOU GO.
TOP THAT ONE IF YOU CAN.
OH MY GOSH, HE DID.
OH HO HO, BY GOLLY.
HE CAUGHT THAT
WITHOUT HIS GLASSES ON.
OH, I DON'T WANT TO
WATCH THAT.
OH, DO THAT IN YOUR OWN HOME.
GEE.
WHAT'S THAT?
THAT'S A SAW BLADE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
THROWING A SAW BLADE.
BILL, BILL.
OH, BO-BO-BO-BO!
OH!
WHAT WAS THAT?
LOOK AT THAT.
MY HAT.
I GOT OFF LUCKY.
A FLYING SAUCER THE KIDS USE
IN THE WINTER.
YOU CAN USE THEM
IN THE SUMMER.
OH, SORRY, BILL --
LOOK OUT!
IT'S GARBAGE DAY!
[laughing]
BYE.
STAY TUNED --
EDGAR'S AT THE END OF HIS FUSE.
THIS GARBAGE CLEAN-OUT
IS WORKING OUT GREAT.
WE'VE SALVAGED SO MUCH STUFF.
I'M SURE WE'LL GET AROUND TO
FINDING A USE FOR IT.
I HAVEN'T HAD THIS MUCH FUN
SINCE MY DAD
WORE HIS RUDE T-SHIRT
TO PARENT-TEACHER NIGHT.
THERE'S BEEN 30 LOADS
DUMPED OUT FRONT,
BUT STILL THE LANDFILL SITE
IS ALMOST EMPTY.
REGULAR RECYCLING PLANTS,
THEY TAKE GLASS,
METAL AND PAPER, THAT'S IT.
WE TAKE EVERYTHING.
THIS IS GOING TO MAKE
A COOL LAMP.
THE GUYS STAND IN THE LANEWAY
WAITING FOR THE NEXT LOAD.
MOST OF THE STUFF THEY PICK OFF
BEFORE THEY GET IT
OFF THE TRUCK.
MOOSE THOMPSON
MADE A GREENHOUSE
OUT OF TOILET SEATS.
WHEN THE SUN SHINES,
HE FLIPS THEM ALL UP.
BUSTER HADFIELD MADE
A COUCH OUT OF ORANGE RINDS.
IT'S AN EXCELLENT EXAMPLE
OF RECYCLING,
AND HE'LL NEVER HAVE TO BUY
ANOTHER AIR FRESHENER.
WE'RE THINKING OF EXPANDING
THE LANDFILL
TO INCLUDE
ALL OF LODGE PROPERTY.
THAT WAY WE CAN TAKE GARBAGE
FROM ALL OVER THE WORLD.
YOU'VE GOT TO THINK
INTERNATIONALLY.
POSSUM LODGE, HEAD OFFICE
TO THE WORLD'S GARBAGE.
THAT'S AN EXCITING VISION.
OH YEAH, YEAH.
MORE EXCITING IF
I DIDN'T HAVE A NOSE.
WELL, THAT CAN BE ARRANGED,
HAROLD.
[Explosion]
THIS IS EDGAR MONTROSE.
DID YOU KNOW THAT
FAST-BURNING FUSE
LOOKS EXACTLY LIKE
SLOW-BURNING FUSE?
I DIDN'T.
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL,
WITH ANOTHER TIP
THAT COULD SAVE YOUR LIFE,
OR EVEN YOUR CARPETING.
COME ON IN HERE, RED.
LAUNDRY DAY, GARTH?
NO, RED.
BADGER DAY.
[Mewing]
OH, OH, EASY THERE, FELLA.
YOU GOT A BADGER IN THERE?
EITHER THAT, RED, OR
A VERY UNDERDONE HAMBURGER.
[laughing]
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
YOU KNOW, RED, BADGERS ARE
THE PUNKS OF THE FOREST.
OH, PURE TROUBLE,
PURE TROUBLE.
IF YOU GET A BADGER
IN YOUR HOUSE,
SAY GOODBYE
TO ANYTHING OF VALUE,
UNLESS YOU CAN TRAP HIM
IN A SACK LIKE THIS.
THEY JUST FREEZE UP
IN THE DARK.
[Mewing]
I THINK THAT FELLA MAY BE
THAWING OUT A BIT.
HOW DID YOU GET HIM
INTO THE BAG?
I HEARD AN ANIMAL CRASHING
AROUND IN THE BASEMENT.
I FIGURED THAT'S EITHER
A COUGAR OR A BADGER.
COUGARS DON'T COME DOWN
FROM THE HILLS,
SO IT HAD TO BE A BADGER.
I HUNG A SACK
ON THE BASEMENT DOOR.
WITHIN A COUPLE OF SECONDS
I HAD MYSELF A BADGER.
HE'S DOCILE AS A KITTEN NOW.
OH!
GARTH, THERE'S BEEN SOME RUMOURS
THAT COUGARS HAVE BEEN
COMING DOWN FROM THE HILLS
AND KILLING COWS.
NO, COUGARS DON'T DO THAT.
WELL, I THINK MAYBE THEY DO.
UNLESS...
UNLESS THEY'RE RABID.
OK, OK.
OH BOY.
ANOTHER SUPER DAY.
OH, OH.
OHHH!
[Red]: IT DOESN'T GET
ANY BETTER THAN THIS.
I DON'T THINK THEY CAN SEE YOU,
UNCLE RED.
SORRY.
WE'VE DECIDED TO KEEP THE CRAP
AND GET RID OF THE INSURANCE.
TURNS OUT IT WAS
A $200 DEDUCTIBLE ANYWAY.
WE DON'T GET TO COLLECT
EVEN IF THE LODGE
BURNS TO THE GROUND.
WE'LL GET ANYBODY WHO COMES HERE
TO SIGN
A PERSONAL DAMAGES WAIVER.
I THINK IT'S UNDER THE BOX
OF FLAVOUR STRAWS, HAROLD.
OK.
I'LL GET IT LATER.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW LANDFILL
SITES CAN BE FILLING UP.
WE CAN'T KEEP
OUR TINY ONE FULL.
IT'S AMAZING WHAT PEOPLE
THROW AWAY.
ACETYLENE TANKS,
AIR CONDITIONERS,
HIGH-VOLTAGE TRANSFORMERS.
I GUESS ONE MAN'S GARBAGE
IS ANOTHER MAN'S
POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS
EXPLOSION.
THEY SAY YOU CAN JUDGE
CIVILIZATI BY ITS GARBAGE.
I WONDER WHAT
FUTURE ARCHAEOLOGISTS
WILL SAY ABOUT
OUR CIVILIZATION.
THEY'LL SAY IT WAS A BIG ONE.
AND IT SMELLED CHEESY.
[squealing]
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I'VE PICKED UP
SOMETHING FOR YOU.
THE STAINS ON THIS LAMPSHADE
GO PERFECTLY WITH
OUR LIVING ROOM WALLS.
CHEAPER THAN A COAT OF PAINT.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF, HAROLD,
AND THE GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
[possum squeal]
[Harold]: RISE.
[All]: QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
[Harold]: WE'RE HAVING
A BEER BOTTLE PLEDGE.