HERE'S A LITTLE TIP FOR THOSE
WHO LIVE WHERE THERE'S
LOTS OF SNOW.
AND WITH EL NINO, THAT'S
PRETTY MUCH EVERYBODY.
NOW, TO PROTECT
THE EAVESTROUGHS FROM GETTING
THE ICE IN ON THERE.
YOU CAN GET THESE EXPENSIVE
KIND OF SPECIAL COILS,
OR HEATING COILS, REALLY.
THEY GO RIGHT ONTO
THE ROOF LIKE THAT.
BUT I SAY WHY BOTHER
WHEN YOU ALREADY GOT
CHRISTMAS LIGHTS UP THERE, HUH?
AFTER NEW YEAR'S, GET UP THERE,
TAKE ALL YOUR CHRISTMAS LIGHTS
OUT AND REPLACE THEM
WITH PENNIES.
WHEN THESE THINGS HEAT UP,
IT'LL MELT ALL
THE ICE ANYHOW, HUH?
IT SAVES YOU DOLLARS
AND MAKES
CENTS.
YOU KNOW, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO CHECK THE FINE PRINT
ON YOUR FIRE INSURANCE POLICY
BEFORE YOU TRY THIS.
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW!
[cheering]
AND NOW, HERE HE IS, THE MAN
WHO'S GOT SO MUCH ON THE GO,
THAT IT GOT UP AND WENT.
YOUR HOST AND HERO,
BUT MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
[cheering]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
POSSUM LODGE IS ABOUT TO BE
DECLARED AN OFFICIAL RELIGION.
A R-R-R-RELIGION?
OH, PRAY TELL.
OH, COME ON, HAROLD.
HEY, IT MAKES SENSE, DOESN'T IT?
WE HAVE WEEKLY MEETINGS,
WE HAVE MEMBERS,
AND WE HAVE CERTAIN
UNIQUE BELIEFS
THAT SEPARATE US
FROM THE REST OF SOCIETY.
AND SOCIETY THANKS YOU FOR THAT,
BUT WHY...WHY DO YOU HAVE
TO BE A RELIGION?
BECAUSE THAT MAKES US
A REGISTERED
NON-PROFIT ORGANIZATION.
SEE, RELIGIONS CAN DO THINGS
THAT OTHER CLUBS CAN'T.
WHAT? PERFORM
WEDDINGS?
BINGO!
OH, NO!
NO, WHO WOULD WANT
TO GET MARRIED HERE?
WHAT, YOU CAN'T WALK UP
THE AISLE WITHOUT TRIPPING
OVER DEAD BEARS
AND OILY CAR PARTS.
WHAT? NO, DON'T.
NOT WEDDINGS, HAROLD,
BINGO, YOU KNOW, BINGO.
YOU'RE GOING TO PLAY BINGO?
BINGO. WE'RE GOING TO MAKE
A FORTUNE HERE, HAROLD.
YOU'LL CHARGE PEOPLE
TO COME HERE TO PLAY BINGO.
BINGO.
AND HE THOUGHT
I WAS STUPID.
BINGO.
IT'S TIME TO PLAY
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME,
AND TODAY'S GRAND PRIZE
ALLOWS YOU TO CALL
THE SEXIEST MOVIE STAR
YOU'VE EVER SEEN.
AND THAT GRAND PRIZE:
A SHINY NEW QUARTER.
AND PLAYING FOR THIS QUARTER
WITH MY UNCLE RED
IS MR. KEVIN BLACK, CITY
SLICKER TURNED POSSUM LAKER.
WELCOME.
[cheering]
OK, MR. BLACK, YOU HAVE
30 SECONDS TO GET
MY UNCLE RED TO SAY THIS WORD...
ALL RIGHT,
HAROLD.
OH, OK...AND GO.
OK, MR. GREEN.
UH, LET'S SAY
YOU BUY
A PIECE OF
REAL ESTATE.
OVERPAY.
NO, YOU'RE GOING TO SELL IT
FOR MORE THAN YOU PAID FOR IT.
NOW, WHAT IS THAT CALLED?
A MIRACLE?
NO, ALL RIGHT, LET'S SAY
YOU BUY SOMETHING,
AND THEN YOU SELL IT
FOR A PROFIT
BEFORE YOU EVEN HAVE
TO PAY FOR IT, WHAT'S THAT?
THE '80s.
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT
OF TIME, MR. BLACK.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT, UH, UH.
MR. GREEN, LET'S SAY
I BUY SOMETHING,
THEN I IMMEDIATELY SELL IT
FOR A PROFIT, WHAT HAVE I DONE?
UNDERMINED THE BASIC
FABRIC OF SOCIETY.
[laughing]
YOU'RE...YOU'RE QUITE HOPELESS,
BUT I THINK YOU KNOW THAT.
AND I BELIEVE THAT
QUARTER SHOULD BE MINE.
I'LL FLIP YOU FOR IT.
[ringing]
VERY GOOD.
UNDER THE "B"...CASH.
UNDER THE "I"...I'M RICH.
UNDER THE "N"...
N YOU THOUGHT I WAS STUPID.
UNDER THE "G"...
GEE, LOOK AT ALL THE MONEY.
AND UNDER THE "O"...OH, YEAH.
YOU MADE ALL
THAT MONEY FROM BINGO?
YEAH, HAROLD, WE ONLY HAD
TWO BINGOS CALLED,
SO WE GET TO KEEP THE POT.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK JUMPED UP
AND YELLED, "OGNIB!",
BUT HIS CARD WAS UPSIDE DOWN.
HOW ARE YOU DOING ON THE
REGISTRATION FORM, HAROLD?
OH, PRETTY GOOD,
OH, PRETTY GOOD.
THE GOVERNMENT ASKED
A FEW MORE QUESTIONS
ABOUT YOUR NEW RELIGION
FOR THEIR FILES.
ALL RIGHT.
UH, THEY WANT TO KNOW
IF YOU HAVE A NAME
FOR YOUR NEW RELIGION --
I SUGGESTED, "GOD HELP US".
I DON'T THINK SO.
HOW ABOUT THE SACRED
CHURCH OF THE POSSUM?
SACRED CHURCH
OF THE POSSUM.
DO YOU HAVE
A PATRON SAINT?
SAINT BERNARD.
AND HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT LIFE AFTER DEATH?
OH, I DON'T KNOW, HAROLD.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
I BELIEVE IN LIFE BEFORE DEATH.
SO, YOU JUST-- I DON'T CARE.
YOU FILL OUT ANY WAY YOU WANT.
YOU CAN MAKE YOURSELF
A SACRIFICIAL VIRGIN.
[ CHUCKLING ]
NO, NO, NO, I'M GOING
TO BE A DEACON.
YEAH, YEAH, 'CAUSE I-- YOU KNOW,
LIKE A SAINTLY PRESENCE.
LIKE AN ANGEL THAT SHINES
A LIGHT FOR ALL TO SEE.
A BEACON OF HOPE FOR THE MEEK
AND THE DOWNTRODDEN.
THAT'S GOOD.
YEAH, YEAH.
I'M GOING TO CALL MYSELF
DEACON BEACON.
OK?
HEY, YOU CAN ANSWER THE PHONE...
"DON'T BE FREAKIN', THIS IS
GEEKIN' DEACON BEACON SPEAKIN'."
BINGO.
THERE'S A DAMPNESS
IN THE MEADOW
WHEN THE OLD RED
ROOSTER CALLS
THERE'S A LOT
OF CONDENSATION
WHERE THE ROOF USED
TO JOIN THE WALLS
THERE'S A WETNESS
IN MY MATTRESS
AND PUDDLES ON THE DRESSER
THE LESSON HERE
IS DON'T MAKE BEER
IF YOUR TANK CAN'T
HOLD THE PRESSURE
OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, IN HIS LIFETIME,
MY DAD HAD A LOT
OF PRETTY DISTINCTIVE CARS:
THE OLD DeSOTO THERE WITH
THE BIG FINS ON HER, HA, HA.
OH, GOSH, YEAH, THE BIG HEAVY
STUDEBAKER, REMEMBER THEM?
POINTED AT BOTH ENDS,
JUST LIKE DAD, HA, HA.
OH, MAN, I LOVED THE CORVAIR.
IT HAD THE FANCY TRIM
ON THE SIDE.
ANOTHER DENT ON THE ROOF EVERY
TIME YOU FLIPPED HER, YEAH.
THESE THINGS, THE GAS MILEAGE
WAS BRUTAL ON THEM, THERE.
AND THE BODY WOULD RUST OUT
EVERY THREE YEARS ON HER,
AND ANY COLLISION OVER 10 MILES
AN HOUR, OF COURSE, WAS FATAL.
BUT YOU JUST DIDN'T CARE, HA.
OF COURSE, NOWADAYS, THE WAY
THEY'RE MAKING THE CARS,
THEY ALL LOOK THE SAME.
THIS IS 'CAUSE THEY GOT
COMPUTERS DESIGN THEM,
SO THEY'RE AERODYNAMIC AND FUEL
EFFICIENT AND ALL THAT STUFF.
BUT, HEY, AFTER YOU DO
A LITTLE BIT OF SHOPPING
OR MAYBE PACK FOR A TRIP
OR SOMETHING,
THAT THEORY GOES OUT THE WINDOW.
OF COURSE, THE FUNDAMENTAL
PROBLEM WITH THIS
IS THE MESSAGE THAT ALL
CARS SHOULD BE THE SAME.
HOW LONG IS IT GOING TO BE
BEFORE THEY START SAYING
THAT ALL PEOPLE
SHOULD BE THE SAME, EH?
THEN A LOT OF US ARE
IN TROUBLE, ESPECIALLY ME.
TO ME, PEOPLE ARE
DISTINCTIVE INDIVIDUALS
AND THEIR VEHICLES
SHOULD REFLECT THAT.
SO THIS WEEK,
ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW
YOU CAN CUSTOMIZE YOUR CAR,
SO THAT IT'LL STAND OUT
ON THE ROAD, IN THE PARKING LOT,
AND IN THE POLICE COMPOUND --
LET'S START WITH THE FRONT END.
SEE, I KIND OF GOT A PIECE
OF GARDEN HOSE--
THIS HAS BEEN SITTING ON HERE,
OUT IN THE SUN,
FOR ABOUT THREE DAYS.
AND IT HAS ACTUALLY
TAKEN ON THE SHAPE
OF THE FRONT END OF THE CAR.
SO, NOW THIS BECOMES
OUR PATTERN, EH, OUR JIG,
SO WE CAN CUT SOMETHING OUT,
MAKE A LITTLE PIECE OF TRIM
THAT WILL GO RIGHT ON
AND FIT PERFECTLY
ONTO THE FRONT END OF THE CAR.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO USE?
DON'T GET AHEAD OF ME NOW.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT MY PATTERN
ALL TRACED OUT ON THE CANOE NOW.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS CUT HER OFF.
AND FOR THAT, I'M GOING TO USE
ONE OF THESE FANCY
LITTLE COPING SAWS.
IT'S JUST IDEAL FOR
CUTTING CURVY LINES.
ALL RIGHT, THE SAW
SEEMS TO BE COPING
A LITTLE BETTER THAN I AM.
[chain saw starting]
AH, SHE'S REALLY STARTING
TO TAKE SHAPE, ISN'T SHE?
AND HOW ABOUT THIS LITTLE
NIFTY FEATURE, HUH?
HIDEAWAY HEADLIGHTS.
ACTUALLY, THESE ARE
JUST PAILS, YEAH.
YOU CUT THEM OUT AND LEAVE
THE BOTTOM IN THERE.
SEE, SO UNDER NORMAL CONDITIONS,
THE HEADLIGHT IS HIDDEN.
BUT AS YOU GET GOING,
THE WIND GRABS HERE AND JUST
LIFTS THIS BABY RIGHT UP
AND EXPOSES THE HEADLIGHT, SEE?
SO THE FASTER YOU GO,
THE BETTER YOU CAN SEE, HUH?
SO IF YOU'RE DRIVING AT NIGHT
AND THE VISIBILITY
IS NOT TOO GOOD, JUST SPEED UP.
BY THE WAY, THESE HINGES
ARE 100% DUCT TAPE,
AND IT'S CALLED
THE HIMMELMAN HINGE.
HIMMELMAN WAS ACTUALLY
A LODGE MEMBER.
HE WAS ACTUALLY BY THE LODGE
THE OTHER DAY,
BUT HIS ARTIFICIAL KNEES
HAVE NOT WORKED OUT SO WELL...
IN THE HOT WEATHER, THEY STICK
TO THE INSIDE OF HIS PANT LEGS.
ANYWAY, SPEAKING OF HIMMELMAN,
LET'S DO SOMETHING
FOR THE BACK END.
ALL RIGHT NOW, THIS IS ACTUALLY
JUST AN IRONING BOARD,
BUT I'M USING IT
AS A SPOILER, HUH?
HEH, HEH, HEH, I FEEL SPOILED.
WELL, SOMETHING'S SPOILED,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
AND YOU SEE THESE FINS?
CANOE PADDLES, HA, HA, HA.
THAT'S ALL THIS IS.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
SEE MY ROLLBAR HERE?
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS?
IT'S A KID'S SWING, HUH?
IT'S AMAZING
WHAT A PERSON CAN DO.
YOU KNOW SOMETHING THAT BUGS ME
TOO ABOUT THE NEW CARS?
THEY COME WITH
NO CHROME ON THEM, HUH?
FULLY LOADED, NO CHROME, NONE.
I DON'T GO FOR THAT.
SO I'M GOING TO ADD
SOME CHROME TO THIS BABY.
AND YOU CAN GET A TAPE
LIKE IT'S KIND OF A MYLAR.
I'M NOT EXACTLY SURE
WHAT IT'S CALLED,
BUT IT'S LIKE DUCT TAPE,
ONLY SILVERIER.
JUST LAY IT DOWN...
WELL, THERE'S NOTHING LIKE
CHROME TO CREATE AN IMAGE, EH?
I BET THIS IS BURNING A PRETTY
GOOD IMAGE INTO THAT TV CAMERA.
BUT THAT'S JUST HOW EASY IT IS
TO LET PEOPLE KNOW
THAT YOU'RE DIFFERENT.
YOU'RE NOT ONE OF THEM.
IT'LL MAKE YOU FEEL GOOD,
AND IT'LL MAKE THEM FEEL
EVEN BETTER.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME...
[engine sputtering
and finally starting]
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU GUYS
WHO ARE GOING TO FACE
A PROBLEM WHEN YOU GET OLDER.
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT
EXTRA EAR AND NOSE HAIR.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE INABILITY
TO REMEMBER SPECIAL OCCASIONS.
THE DAY WILL COME WHEN
SUDDENLY YOU REALIZE
THAT LAST YEAR YOU FORGOT
HER BIRTHDAY,
YOUR ANNIVERSARY,
VALENTINE'S DAY AND CHRISTMAS.
I KNOW, NOBODY REMEMBERS YOUR
SPECIAL OCCASIONS, DO THEY, EH?
OPENING DAY OF BASS SEASON.
ANYBODY BUY YOU A BAG OF WORMS?
YOU CAN LIVE WITH
THEIR INSENSITIVITY,
BUT THEY CAN'T HANDLE YOURS.
AND RIGHT NOW YOU'RE THINKING,
WASN'T IT ABOUT A YEAR AGO
YOU GOT INTO TROUBLE
FOR SOMETHING OR OTHER?
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
YOU GOT A SPECIAL OCCASION
COMING UP, DON'T YOU?
AND YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT IT IS, DO YOU?
WELL, NEITHER DO I.
BUT HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
GO OUT NOW AND BUY
A GIFT NOW, ALL RIGHT?
WRAP IT UP,
HIDE IT IN THE GARAGE NOW.
GET A FLOWERY CARD
THAT JUST SAYS
"I LOVE YOU" ON IT, ALL RIGHT?
NOW, JUST WAIT AROUND
FOR THE DAY IN QUESTION.
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO TELL BECAUSE
SHE'LL BE TICKED OFF WITH YOU.
SHE'LL GET INTO THE SIGHING,
TAPPING HER FOOT ON THE FLOOR,
SAYING STUFF LIKE,
"YOU KNOW, I COULD HAVE MARRIED"
"ANY OF YOUR FRIENDS."
WHAT YOU DO THEN,
GO GET THE GIFT,
BRING IT OUT,
JUST YELL, "SURPRISE!"
"SURPRISE," LIKE THAT. IT WILL
MAKE YOU LOOK LIKE A HERO.
YOU MIGHT EVEN GET TO SLEEP
IN YOUR OWN BED.
AND MAYBE NOT RIGHT AWAY.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
YOU ARE IN SUCH TROUBLE, MISTER.
JUST STAY CALM,
HAROLD, ALL RIGHT?
WE'RE CAUGHT ON A LITTLE
TECHNICALITY ON THE LODGE
BEING AN ORGANIZED RELIGION.
PROBABLY NEED TO BE
A BIT MORE ORGANIZED, I GUESS.
YEAH, GOVERNMENT SAYS
YOU'RE NOT EVEN A RELIGION.
SAYS YOU'RE NOT EVEN
A PAGAN RITUAL.
AND YOU GOT TO HAVE A GAMING
LICENCE TO RUN BINGO.
NOW WE ALL GOT TO GO JAIL
AND EAT BLAND FOOD
AND MARRY OUR OWN GENDER -- OH!
NO, NO, NO--
YES, YES!
HAROLD.
WHAT?
DON'T PANIC, OK?
WE'RE NOT DONE YET.
OHHH.
I HAD, I HAD A MEETING
WITH THE CHURCH ELDERS.
WE SACRIFICED A COUPLE OF BEERS.
AND, UH, WE CAME UP WITH A PLAN,
WHAT WE CALL OUR HOLY DOCTRINE.
THE GOVERNMENT BOYS
ARE COMING TONIGHT
TO LOOK AT OUR BINGO GAME --
WE MUST CONVINCE THEM
THAT IT'S ACTUALLY
A CHURCH SERVICE.
OH!
HOW ARE YOU GOING TO DO THAT?
WELL, WE GOT SINNERS.
THAT'S A GOOD START.
YEAH, WE
GOT THOSE.
WE FIGURE WE'LL HAVE
SOME CONFESSIONS.
YOU KNOW HOW THE GUYS
LOVE TO BRAG.
ALL WE NEED NOW IS JUST A
SERMON TO TOP THAT OFF, HAROLD.
YOU'RE NOT TELLING
YOUR STORY ABOUT
THE BIRD AND THE MANURE AGAIN?
OH, NO, NO, NOT ME, HAROLD.
YOU'RE THE DEACON.
YOU'LL BE DOING THE CEREMONY.
ME? NO WAY!
NO! UH-UH.
NO, NO.
YES, YES.
I'VE EXCOMMUNICATED
MYSELF FROM
THIS CULT.
NO, YOU SHOULD HAVE
THOUGHT OF THAT BEFORE
YOU TOOK YOUR VOWS, YOUNG MAN.
DON'T WORRY, I CAN HELP YOU.
WE'LL BE FINE.
WE WON'T BE ABLE TO FAKE OUT
THESE GOVERNMENT PEOPLE.
SURE WE ARE.
THEY'RE FROM THE TAX DEPARTMENT.
THEY'VE NEVER BEEN
TO CHURCH EITHER.
WELCOME TO THE
EXPERT PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THIS IS THE PART
OF THE PROGRAM WHERE WE EXAMINE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND HARD TO SAY.
I DON'T KNOW.
HA, HA, THAT'S GOOD.
AND JOINING MY UNCLE TODAY
IS RANGER GORD.
[cheering]
OK, HERE WE GO.
LETTER NUMBER ONE.
"DEAR EXPERTS, RANGER GORD IS
THE BEST PERSON ON YOUR SHOW."
"HE IS DOWN TO EARTH,
YET UNCOMMONLY BRILLIANT."
"ALL THE WOMEN IN POSSUM LAKE"
"MUST BE CRAZY FOR HIM."
AW, GORD DOESN'T NEED ANYBODY
TO BE CRAZY FOR HIM.
I THINK THERE'S
MORE THERE, HAROLD.
OH, UH, "THERE IS NO ONE
BETTER THAN RANGER GORD"
"ON THE SHOW, IS THERE?"
NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
UH, I DOUBT IT.
RED, WHAT'S
YOU'RE FEELING ON THAT?
WHO WROTE THAT LETTER, HAROLD?
OK, NOT REALLY THE PERFECT
CRIME, GORD.
MAYBE YOU
SHOULDN'T HAVE SIGNED IT.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S
NOT NECESSARILY MY LETTER, RED.
SOME DERANGED PERSON MAY HAVE
WROTE IT AND PUT MY NAME TO IT.
YEAH, THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I'M SAYING.
[red]: BOY, OH, BOY, THAT'S
A SCARY-LOOKING THING, ISN'T IT?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
WHAT YOU DOING, BILL?
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
LITTLE, UH--
THAT'S A FUNNY LITTLE HAMMER.
KIND OF A PICKAXE KIND OF A...
PAINTBRUSH. WHAT'S THAT FOR,
BILL? WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH, BOY.
YOU MUST GET UP EARLY
IN THE MORNING
TO GET DRESSED, I'M THINKING.
YOU HAD, UH...
BILL HAD, UH... WOW.
HOLY SMOKES. WHAT DO YOU GOT?
I DON'T QUITE UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE,
BUT I'M GOING TO STAND BACK
A LITTLE BIT.
WHAT DO YOU GOT THERE?
OH, MY GOSH, OH, JEEZ.
LOOK, HE PASSED A STOOL.
OK.
WHAT, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT IS THIS ALL ABOUT?
OH, I GET-- IT'S LIKE
AN ARCHEOLOGY-- YEAH, OK,
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
NO, THANKS.
I'M GOING TO-- I'M RELAXING.
OH, BOY, OH, BOY. THERE YOU GO.
THAT WILL BE MY JOB.
I'LL SIT IN THE CHAIR, BILL.
GO AHEAD.
I KNOW, YOU GOT TO DIG A HOLE --
YOU GO DIG A HOLE,
AND YOU CALL ME
WHEN THE HOLE'S DONE.
OH, HEY, HEY,
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
HAVE YOU DUG THE HOLE YET, BILL?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING THERE?
OH, MY GOSH.
HOLY COW.
HI, EVERYBODY.
LOOK, I DUG
A HOLE.
WOW, HOLY SMOKES.
OH, YOU'VE MARKED
ALL THE LAYERS.
THERE'S THE '90's, YES.
WHAT'S THAT? A CASSETTE.
THEY GOT A CASSETTE TAPE THERE.
THE '80's, YEAH,
I REMEMBER THE '80's.
THEN YOU HAVE THE '70's.
WHAT'S THAT? AN EIGHT-TRACK.
OH, GOD, OH, BOY, OH, BOY.
WOW, WOW, THE '60's.
YOU GOT A RECORD.
YOU GOT EVERYTHING.
YOU GOT ANY MORE STUFF THERE?
FUNNY HOW IT GOES IN LAYERS,
ISN'T IT?
WHAT DO YOU GOT? OR MORE STUFF.
ARE THESE REALLY ARTIFACTS,
DO YOU THINK?
A PIECE OF A BIKE.
OLD GAS CANS ARE NOT REAL--
THIS IS A JUNK PILE.
COME ON UP, COME ON UP,
AND I'LL COME DOWN.
ALL RIGHT.
BOY, OH, BOY, THIS IS,
THIS IS AN ODD FEELING
TO BE DOWN IN A--
OH, THAT HURT, THAT HURT.
OH!
COME LISTEN TO MY STORY--
OH, NO.
WHEN BILL THINKS THAT HE'S FOUND
SOME BONES OF SOME ANIMAL
OR SOMETHING,
IT'S JUST AN OIL CAN,
JUST AN OIL CAN.
THAT'S THE WAY MY LIFE
GOES SOMETIMES.
THERE WE GO.
NO, BILL, I DON'T THINK
THAT'S, NO.
IT'S NOT A PREHISTORIC ANIMAL,
IT'S JUST...
IT'S, NO, NO, I DON'T...
I DON'T THINK SO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
WATCH YOUR STEP.
OH, BOY.
YEAH, YEAH.
NOW, WE THOUGHT THAT WAS
PRETTY MUCH THE END OF THE DAY,
BUT WHEN HE LANDED, HE FOUND
SOMETHING KIND OF UNUSUAL.
HE MAY BE ONTO SOMETHING HERE,
MAYBE ONTO SOMETHING.
OH, MY GOSH,
IT'S A LICENCE PLATE THERE.
IT'S A LICENCE PLATE.
"YOURS TO DISCOVER."
WHAT WOULD THAT BE? MY GOD.
WHAT HAVE WE GOT OVER HERE?
OH, IT'S A HEADLIGHT, AND IT'S--
BOY, THERE'S SOMETHING,
SOMETHING UNDER...
ALL RIGHT, I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
LOOK OUT, DON'T CATCH ME.
DON'T HELP ME, BILL.
LOOK, LOOK, ANOTHER HEADLIGHT.
TWO HEADLIGHTS IN A...
WELL, THIS IS...
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK IT IS?
I THINK IT'S A CAR. YES, IT IS!
WELL, I GOT ALL
THE DIRT OFF THERE,
AND I GOT THE OIL
POURED INTO HER THERE.
AND HERE'S SOMETHING,
25 YEARS LATER,
THE ENGINE STILL RUNS,
TRANSMISSION STILL WORKS.
HERE'S SOMETHING WE LEARNED.
THE BRAKES ARE SHOT.
OH, BOY, OH, BOY, OH, DEAR.
I'LL GET IT, I'LL GET IT,
I'LL GET IT, I'LL GET IT.
CAREFUL, CAREFUL, THERE WE GO.
THIS IS A SPECIAL FEATURE
OF THE SHOW WE CALL
YOU AND YOUR ANIMAL,
HOSTED BY LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER ED FRID -- WELCOME, ED.
RED.
[cheering]
I'LL TELL YOU, THE, UH, THE
YOUNGSTERS LOVE THESE ANIMALS.
SO, WHAT DID YOU BRING
FOR US TODAY?
A COUPLE CREATURES.
UH, FIRST, A SNAKE.
WOW! HEY, I'M IMPRESSED, ED.
I THOUGHT YOU
WERE AFRAID OF SNAKES.
OH, YEAH.
BUT I DON'T LET ON, EH.
OK, SO THIS IS THE LARGEST SNAKE
WE GET IN NORTH AMERICA, OK?
THIS IS
AN INDIGO SNAKE, AND, BOY...
HAVE WE GOT A BIG SPECIMEN.
WAIT TILL YOU SEE
THE SIZE OF THIS BABY.
WELL, I GUESS I FORGOT
TO BRING HIM.
ED, THERE'S A...
SOMETHING MOVING UNDER
YOUR SHIRT, THERE.
IS THERE ANY CHANCE THE SNAKE
GOT INSIDE YOUR SHIRT AT ALL?
OHHH!
I DON'T LIKE THE WAY
THIS IS GOING.
YOU KNOW WHAT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE'LL USE A LITTLE BIT OF BAIT.
WHAT DO THEY EAT?
MICE.
LITTLE FURRY WARM MICE.
OK, I GOT A PIECE OF CHEESE.
I'LL PUT THAT DOWN --
NOW, LOOK, WE'LL GET HIM TO GO
DOWN OUT-- JUST STAY STILL --
CAN YOU STAND STILL?
YEAH, OH, YEAH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DIDN'T
NOTICE A SNAKE IN YOUR SHIRT.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU GET BUSY.
AND, UH, YOU KNOW,
I CAN'T BE CHECKING MY CLOTHES
FOR SNAKES EVERY FIVE MINUTES.
BUT I THINK I MIGHT START.
I GOT HIM,
I GOT HIM!
OH, GOD!
BR-R-R-R!
I GUESS, UH, I GUESS THAT'S
THE END OF THAT SEGMENT, IS IT?
NO.
I ALSO BROUGHT A TARANTULA.
OOH, OOH, OOH!
MAN, THAT WAS
RELIGIOUS PERSECUTION.
THERE'S NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.
UNBELIEVABLE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THE GOD-FEARING
LODGE MEMBERS
ATTACKED
A MAN OF
THE CLOTH.
WELL, YOUR SERMON
DIDN'T HELP, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T WARM UP
A CONGREGATION
BY CALLING THEM
THE SPAWN OF SATAN.
YOU DIDN'T HELP MATTERS EITHER
WITH YOUR PHONEY COMMANDMENTS.
"THOU SHALT NOT TIP."
I...I JUST THOUGHT THE
BINGO THING WAS A GREAT IDEA.
UNDER THE "R", WRONG.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD,
I WAS OUT OF LINE,
BUT YOU HAVE TO FORGIVE ME.
FOR-- WHY?
IT'S YOUR JOB.
YOU'RE THE FREAKIN' DEACON.
[squealing]
MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD, YOUR WORSHIP.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
OK.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING, I'LL BE
COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I THINK I'M IN NEED
OF A MIRACLE,
PERHAPS A LAYING ON OF HANDS.
FOR THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheering]