Red: THIS IS A MONUMENT
TO A FAMOUS BATTLE
THAT TOOK PLACE DURING
THE WAR OF 1812,
WHICH WAS ALSO THE SCORE...
WE GOT 18,
THEY GOT 12.
EVERY YEAR, DOZENS OF TOURISTS
COME TO VISIT THIS MONUMENT.
TODAY I'M ONE OF THEM.
AND LIKE EVERYONE WHO TRAVELS,
YOU WANNA GO HOME
WITH A PICTURE OF YOURSELF
STANDING IN FRONT OF
THE DARNED THING.
THE PROBLEM WITH THAT IS
YOU'VE GOT TO STOP A STRANGER
IN SOME PLACE YOU'VE
NEVER BEEN BEFORE
AND ASK THEM TO TAKE
YOUR PHOTOGRAPH.
AND BEFORE YOU CAN EVEN
TAKE THE PICTURE,
YOU'VE GOT TO TRAIN THEM
HOW TO OPERATE A PIECE
OF EQUIPMENT
THAT YOU BARELY
UNDERSTAND YOURSELF.
THEN YOU STAND THERE
LIKE A WEINER
WHILE THIS GOOF TAKES
A PICTURE OF YOUR FEET
WITH HIS THUMB
OVER THE LENS.
SO INSTEAD, I GOT BERNICE
TO TAKE A PICTURE OF ME
WAVING LIKE A TOURIST
AND THEN I JUST CUT
THIS THING OUT.
ISN'T IT BEAUTIFUL?
NOW YOU JUST CARRY
THIS WHEREVER YOU TRAVEL.
WHEN YOU SEE SOMETHING
YOU WANT YOUR PICTURE
TAKEN IN FRONT OF,
LIKE, SAY, THE TAJ MAHAL OR
FREDERICK'S OF HOLLYWOOD,
YOU JUST STAND YOURSELF
UP IN FRONT OF IT.
THEN ALL YOU DO IS
FRAME IT JUST RIGHT.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
I'VE GOT AN INVITATION HERE
TO SUBMIT A CONTESTANT
FOR A TV SHOW THEY'RE SHOOTING
UP IN THE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
IT'S ONE OF THOSE GAME SHOWS:
"WHO WANTS TO BE A SMART GUY?"
IT'S ONE OF THOSE TRIVIA DEALS
WHERE THEY TAKE SOMETHING
YOU DON'T CARE ABOUT
AND THEY TRY TO ATTRACT YOUR
INTEREST BY ADDING CASH
PRIZES.
KIND OF LIKE THE WAY THEY
USED TO USE DOWRIES FOR
UGLY WOMEN.
RED, WE'VE GOT TO
PICK SOMEONE TO SEND TO
THIS TV GAME SHOW THINGY.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, WHOSE HEAD
HAS THE MOST USELESS
INFORMATION IN IT?
BOY,
THAT'S A TOSS-UP.
THAT'S WHY I MADE UP
THIS PRACTICE SHEET.
IT'S KIND OF
A TEST TEST.
"HOW DEEP IS THE DEEPEST
PART OF THE OCEAN?"
MIKE?
UH, 12,000 MILES.
NO, I'M JUST NERVOUS.
YOU'RE HIGH.
RED, YOU WANNA
TRY ANOTHER ONE?
NO, I DON'T WANNA
TRY ANOTHER ONE.
OH, COME ON.
WRONG ANSWER.
NO, NO, NO.
"WHAT HAS FOUR LEGS --"
I'M GONNA ASK YOU ONE.
WHAT'S FIVE FOOT EIGHT
AND HATES TRIVIA GAMES?
AN IDIOT.
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT!
( laughing )
IT'S TIME TO PLAY THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S PRIZE
IS A POCKET WATCH,
FOR PEOPLE WHO FIND THAT
WEARING A WATCH ON
YOUR WRIST
IS JUST TOO
DARNED CONVENIENT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS TO
GET LOCAL FUNERAL DIRECTOR,
BRIAN JACOBS,
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, YEAH,
ALL RIGHT, ED.
OKAY, AND GO!
ALL RIGHT, BRIAN, YOU KNOW
A LOT ABOUT FUNERALS
AND SO ON.
WHAT DO YOU CALL IT WHEN
A PERSON NEVER DIES?
BAD FOR BUSINESS.
OKAY, NO, NO.
WHAT DO PETER PAN
AND DRACULA HAVE IN COMMON?
THEY SUCK.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OKAY, IF A GUY LIVES
FOREVER, HE WOULD BE...
VERY WRINKLY.
OKAY, OKAY, YOU KNOW
WHEN PEOPLE GET OLDER,
THEY START THINKING
ABOUT THIS A LOT.
VIAGRA?
ALMOST OUTTA TIME, RED!
OKAY, BRIAN, WHAT DO YOU CALL
SOMEONE WHO JUST KEEPS
COMING BACK
YEAR AFTER YEAR, FOREVER?
OH, UH, ALAN THICKE.
NO, NO, THAT'S NOT WHERE
I WAS GOING WITH THAT.
HE'S EVERYWHERE ON RERUNS
OF
GROWING PAINS.
THEY'VE IMMORTALIZED
HIM ON THAT SHOW.
THERE YOU GO!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, THROUGHOUT
HUMAN HISTORY,
SOME OF THE WORLD'S
GREATEST DISCOVERIES
WERE MADE IN THE SMALLEST
ROOM IN THE HOUSE.
ARCHIMEDES DISCOVERED
WATER DISPLACEMENT
WHILE SITTING IN THE TUB.
THAT'S WHERE NEWTON
FOUND OUT ABOUT GRAVITY.
AND IT'S ALSO WHERE
Da VINCI GOT THE IDEA
FOR THE LOOK ON
MONA LISA'S FACE.
IT ALL HAPPENED HERE
IN THE REST ROOM.
IT'S A SEA OF CALM
IN A TEMPESTUOUS WORLD.
THAT'S WHY ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES
IS PLEASED TO ANNOUNCE
THE LAUNCH OF
OUR VERY OWN BATHROOM
CLASSICS OF LITERATURE.
ORDER NOW AND
YOU'LL RECEIVE...
IT'S MY GIFT TO YOU.
I HOPE YOU ENJOY IT.
announcer:
VOID WHERE PROHIBITED;
PROHIBITED WHERE VOID.
HANDLING CHARGES,
P.S.T., G.S.T.,
STATE TAX AND
SHIPPING NOT INCLUDED.
ALLOW SIX TO EIGHT
WEEKS FOR DELIVERY.
CONSULT A PHYSICIAN
IF YOU ARE CURRENTLY ON
ANY BOREDOM MEDICATION.
CAN CAUSE HEADACHES
AND NAUSEA.
MAY LEAD TO ABHORRENCE
OF READING.
THAT'S THE BATHROOM CLASSICS
OF LITERATURE SERIES
FROM ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
AVAILABLE WHILE
SUPPLIES LAST.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, IT CAN REALLY
BE TOUGH ON A GUY
LOOKING THROUGH
A CAR MAGAZINE
WITH ALL THE FANCY NEW SPORTS
CARS AND CONCEPT CARS
AND THEN HAVE TO GO
BACK TO HIS OLD VAN.
BUT I HAVE A
SOLUTION FOR THAT.
IT'S ALL ABOUT HOW
YOUR VEHICLE LOOKS.
IT'S NOT HOW IT PERFORMS.
ALL THAT EXTRA HORSEPOWER AND
FANCY SUSPENSION OF THE
HIGH PRICED SPORTS CAR
ARE JUST WASTED
IN TODAY'S TRAFFIC.
SO INSTEAD OF SPENDING MONEY
YOU DON'T HAVE ON FEATURES
YOU WON'T USE,
WHY NOT JUST
REPAINT YOUR VAN
AND MAKE IT LOOK SPORTIER?
AND I'M NOT JUST TALKING
ABOUT A FRESH PAINT JOB.
OH, NO, I'M WAY PAST THAT.
YOU EVER SEEN THOSE ROOMS
WHERE THEY PAINT THE FAKE
WINDOWS ON THE WALLS?
IT'S CALLED trompe-l'oeil.
YEAH, THAT'S FRENCH.
IT MEANS "TRICK THE EYE."
WELL, WE'RE GONNA DO A
tromp-l'oeil 10-W-30.
WHAT YOU WANNA DO IS
PICK A CONCEPT CAR
OUTTA YOUR MAGAZINE.
THEN YOU WANNA DRAW THE
SHAPE OF THAT ON YOUR VAN.
I WOULD SAY GET SOMETHING
FROM FRANCE OR SWEDEN
OR SOMEWHERE FAR AWAY
SO THEY CAN'T SUE YOU.
NOW, IT DOESN'T MATTER IF
YOU DON'T GET BOTH SIDES
EXACTLY THE SAME.
NOBODY'S EVER GONNA SEE BOTH
SIDES OF YOUR VEHICLE AT
THE SAME TIME,
UNLESS THEY HAVE A REALLY
BAD ACCIDENT.
OKAY, NOW EVERYTHING
INSIDE THESE LINES,
THAT'S YOUR FANCY
NEW SPORTS CAR.
EVERYTHING OUTSIDE THE LINE,
YOU WANT THAT TO KIND OF
FADE INTO THE BACKGROUND.
SO WE GOTTA PAINT
THAT TO LOOK LIKE TREES
OR SKY OR WHATEVER.
AND WE'RE GONNA MAKE
IT KIND OF BLURRY
SO IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
GOING 100 MILES AN HOUR.
OKAY, ONCE I GOT MY BLURRY
BACKGROUND DONE,
NOW I GOTTA FILL IN THE SHAPE
OF THE SPORTS CAR ITSELF.
AND WITH THAT -- YOU COULD DO
THAT WITH PAINT, I GUESS,
OR PLASTER OR TAR.
I DECIDED TO GO WITH THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
IT'S EASY TO APPLY,
AND IT HELPS HOLD THE
VAN TOGETHER.
YOU CAN TAKE AN OLD
POTATO CHIP BAG, EH,
TURN 'EM INSIDE OUT,
IT LOOKS JUST LIKE CHROME,
AND IT'LL NEVER RUST.
AND THAT'S HOW YOU TURN
YOUR UGLY OLD VAN
INTO A BEAUTIFUL, SLEEK,
EUROPEAN SPORTS CAR.
[ HINGE CREAKS LOUDLY ]
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ ENGINE SPUTTERING ]
[ METAL CREAKING
AND EXHAUST SPUTTERING ]
WHEN YOU'RE MARRIED,
LIKE A LOT OF US ARE,
YOU NOTICE THAT
WIVES MAKE LISTS...
GROCERY LISTS;
CHRISTMAS CARD LISTS;
PEOPLE WHO OWE US A PARTY;
PEOPLE WE OWE A PARTY TO;
PEOPLE WHO WILL NEVER BE
INVITED TO DARKEN OUR
DOORWAY AGAIN --
OR AS SHE ALSO
REFERS TO THEM,
YOUR FRIENDS.
BUT THE SCARY LIST IS
THE ONE SHE HAS FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW THE ONE
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
THAT LIST OF ODD JOBS,
BIG AND SMALL,
FOR YOU TO DO
AROUND THE HOUSE.
NOW, IT'S CALLED A LIST,
BUT IT DOESN'T ACTUALLY
EXIST ON PAPER.
SHE'S WAY TOO
SMART FOR THAT.
SHE KEEPS THAT LIST
IN HER HEAD.
THAT WAY SHE CAN ADD TO IT
WITHOUT YOU NOTICING.
AND YOU, SIR,
WILL NEVER BE FINISHED.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S A GOOD THING.
SPEAKING ON BEHALF
OF ALL MEN,
WE'RE NOT AT OUR BEST WHEN
WE HAVE NOTHING TO DO.
YOUR WIFE KNOWS THAT,
AND THAT'S WHY SHE
MAKES THIS LIST.
SO LET'S BE HONEST,
WE'RE BETTER OFF
MARRIED AND BUSY
THAN SINGLE AND LISTLESS.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, DALTON'S
BEEN GOING ALL OVER TOWN
TRYING TO FIND SOMEBODY SMART
ENOUGH TO REPRESENT US FOR
THAT TV GAME PROGRAMME.
SO FAR, NO LUCK.
SEE, AROUND HERE
NONE OF US KNOW ANYTHING.
THAT'S WHY WE GET
ALONG SO WELL.
HEY, Mr GREEN, WE FOUND
OUR CONTESTANT!
WELL, ACTUALLY,
MIKE FOUND HIM.
IT WAS SO OBVIOUS.
WHO HAS MORE INFORMATION
THAN ANYBODY ELSE
IN THE WHOLE
POSSUM LAKE AREA?
I WOULD SAY THE RECEPTIONIST
AT THE PROCTOLOGY CLINIC.
[ LAUGHTER ]
DALTON!
NO. DALTON.
I WAS
SHOCKED, RED.
YOU SHOULD BE
SHOCKED, DALTON.
YOU SEE, DALTON KNOWS
ALL THIS INFORMATION
BECAUSE HE'S BEEN
RUNNING HIS STORE
ALL THESE YEARS.
PLUS, HE OFTEN GOES TO
THE LIBRARY AND READS
BORING BOOKS
BECAUSE HE WANTS
TO AVOID GOING HOME.
AND THEY'RE FREE!
THEY'RE FREE.
( chuckling )
SO YOU GO TO THE LIBRARY
UP IN PORT ASBESTOS?
NO, NO, THERE'S
A LIBRARY HERE
IN TOWN.
THERE'S A LIBRARY
HERE IN TOWN?
YEAH, RIGHT NEXT
TO THE FLORIST SHOP.
THERE'S A
FLORIST SHOP?
ANYWAY, DALTON'S GOING
TO GO ON THE TV
SHOW, RIGHT,
AND IF HE GETS A QUESTION
HE CAN'T ANSWER,
HE'S ALLOWED TO
PHONE A FRIEND.
THIS MUST BE A
FRIEND I HAVEN'T MET.
NO, NO, RED, THAT'S WHAT ALL
THESE BOOKS ARE FOR.
I AM GOING TO PHONE THE LODGE,
AND YOU GUYS WILL ALL BE HERE
WITH EVERY VOLUME
OF THE ENCYCLOPEDIA
SPREAD OUT IN FRONT OF YOU,
AND THEN YOU JUST LOOK UP
ANYTHING I NEED!
WE ARE GOING TO
WIN A LOT OF MONEY.
I GOTTA GO.
OH, SURE WE ARE.
YOU DIVVY UP
THE BOOKS, MIKE.
OKAY.
THERE YOU GO.
OH, LOOK AT THIS.
I GOT VOLUME 16,
"TIME TO WIN."
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
VOLUME SEVEN,
"GOING TO LOSE."
THIS IS THE TALKING ANIMALS
PORTION OF THE SHOW
WITH LOCAL ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICER, ED FRID.
SO, ED, WHAT HAVE
YOU BEEN UP TO?
WELL, LAST WEEK I WENT UP TO
THE BEHAVIORAL PSYCHOLOGY
DEPARTMENT
AT BEARDSLEY COLLEGE.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S WHERE THEY
TRAIN ALL THOSE RATS
TO FIND THEIR WAY
OUT OF THE MAZES.
YEAH, YEAH,
THEY GOT A GREAT CAMPUS.
BUT AFTER IT WAS OVER,
I COULDN'T FIND MY
WAY OUT OF THE BUILDING.
LUCKILY,
I SAW THIS RAT,
AND HE KNEW
WHERE HE WAS GOING.
I JUST FOLLOWED HIM.
OKAY, SO --
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
FOR US THIS WEEK?
TODAY I'M GOING TO
DEMONSTRATE ANIMAL
BEHAVIOR MODIFICATION.
BOY, WE COULD USE
THAT AT THE LODGE,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
WHAT HAVE YOU
GOT IN THAT THING?
OH, MY GOSH.
THAT'S A CHICKEN.
IT'S A CHICKEN.
I'M GONG TO HYPNOTIZE
THIS CHICKEN,
AND TEACH HER HOW TO PLAY
A SONG ON THE PIANO.
WOW!
WHAT SONG?
"IT'S MY POULTRY,
AND I'LL FRY IF I WANT TO"?
[ LAUGHTER ]
( continues laughing )
OH, ALL RIGHT.
NO.
OKAY.
OKAY, HERCULES.
SOON YOU'LL BE
COMPLETELY IN
MY POWER.
YOU'RE GETTING SLEEPY,
VERY, VERY SLEEPY.
WE'RE ALL GETTING A
LITTLE BIT SLEEPY
ABOUT THIS POINT, ED.
ED?
( clucking )
OH, NO.
ED, LET ME GET
YOU OUTTA HERE.
ED, COME ON!
( clucking )
ED! ED!
COME ON.
HERE WE GO.
LET ME GET YOU OUTTA HERE.
COME ON UPSTAIRS.
( clucking )
COME ON, ED.
COME ON.
( clucking frantically )
ED! ED!
SNAP OUT OF IT!
ALL RIGHT.
WHOA! WHOA!
WHERE AM I?
YOU OKAY, ED?
YEAH.
THAT WAS A LITTLE WEIRD.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
HI, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES
WITH A LESSON FOR YOU...
THERE ONCE WAS A
YOUNG MAN FROM TURKEY
WHOSE SEPTICS WERE
PLUGGED UP AND MURKY.
THEY BLAMED IT ON LEAD
FROM THE PIPES IN THE BED,
WHEN THE CULPRIT WAS
TOO MUCH BEEF JERKY.
HELLO, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
BOYS AND GIRLS.
AND BRIAN FROM GRADE 10,
IF YOU'RE WATCHING,
I'M FINE, OKAY?
YOU WERE OBVIOUSLY WRONG
ABOUT THOSE MUSHROOMS.
ANYWAY, TODAY'S EDUCATIONAL
ANIMATED FILM IS VERY SPECIAL.
IT'S ALL ABOUT PREJUDICE
AND BELIEVING IN YOURSELF,
WITH JUST A TOUCH OF VIOLENCE
THAT THE YOUNG PEOPLE TODAY
SEEM TO ENJOY SO MUCH.
SO WATCH, ENJOY AND LEARN.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT'S HIGH TIME YOU TWO
LEARNED TO DEFEND
YOURSELVES
AGAINST A
WILD SASQUATCH.
A WILD SASQUATCH?!
F-WOW!
F-WOW! IS RIGHT,
HAROLD.
BUT DON'T WORRY,
I'M HERE TO HELP.
FIRST OF ALL, DUE TO THE
LARGE FEET ON THESE CREATURES,
THEY TEND TO FAVOUR A
KICKBOXING STYLE OF ATTACK.
SO DEFEND YOURSELVES.
I WANNA SEE YOUR ARMS IN
FRONT OF YOUR FACE
AT ALL TIMES!
COME ON,
NOW, RED, ARMS UP.
I KNOW YOU DON'T WANT A
BIG SASQUATCH FOOT
IN THE FACE.
GORD, THERE'S NO SUCH
THING AS A SASQUATCH.
AND EVEN IF THERE WERE
SASQUATCHES,
THEY WOULDN'T
KICKBOX.
( roaring )
( screams )
FWAH-H-H-H!
( roaring )
( Harold screams )
HOW WAS THAT,
GORD, HUH?
DID I SEEM WILD
ENOUGH, HUH?
OH, YEAH.
YOU SEEMED
WILD, ALL RIGHT.
YOU JUST CAME IN
A LITTLE EARLY IS ALL.
I WASN'T QUITE
FINISHED THE LESSON.
OH, SORRY ABOUT
THAT, GORD.
OH, LOOK, CAN I TRY IT AGAIN?
HUH? HUH? HUH?
I'LL GET THE TIMING
RIGHT ON THIS NEXT ONE.
I P-P-PROMISE!
WELL, ALL RIGHT,
YOU BIG LUG.
GIVE IT ANOTHER SHOT.
JUST DON'T COME
OUT TOO EARLY.
NOPE. NOPE.
I CAN DO THIS.
GO ON, HIDE.
( chuckles ) DON'T
BE DISCOURAGED, YOU TWO.
A LITTLE MORE TRAINING,
AND YOU'LL DO FINE.
OKAY, ARMS UP IN
FRONT OF OUR FACE.
VERY GOOD.
NOW, STAY ON YOUR TOES.
( laughing stupidly )
OH, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
WELL, DON'T BEAT YOURSELF
UP ABOUT IT, THOUGH.
IT JUST GOES TO SHOW
YOU THAT YOU CAN'T TEACH
AN OLD SASQUATCH NEW TRICKS.
( laughing )
HEY!
( starts growling )
( laughing heartily )
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ]
YOU EVER NOTICE HOW THE WORST
RADIO STATIONS GIVE OFF THE
STRONGEST SIGNALS?
KINDA LIKE SKUNKS.
AND THEN THE STATION
THAT YOU LIKE
HAS A REAL WEAK SIGNAL.
TUNING THAT IN IS LIKE TRYING
TO GET THE RIGHT SHOWER
TEMPERATURE.
[ RADIO STATIC ]
( scoffing )
NOW, I SUPPOSE WE
COULD BLAME SOCIETY
FOR MAKING CRAPPY MUSIC.
OR YOU COULD BLAME YOUR
RADIO STATION
FOR NOT BROADCASTING
A STRONGER SIGNAL.
BUT I PREFER TO BLAME THE
CAR ANTENNA FACTORY
INSTALLATION HERE.
LOOK HOW PUNY THAT THING IS.
I THINK WE CAN DO
BETTER THAN THAT.
WITH EVERYBODY ON CABLE
AND THE HIGH FIBRE OPTICS,
THESE BABIES ARE
A DIME A DOZEN.
AND WAIT'LL YOU HEAR
THE RECEPTION.
[ RADIO STATIC ]
OH, NO, WAIT.
[ UNAPPEALING MUSIC PLAYING ]
YOU'RE STRAPPED INTO
COMPETITION WATER SKIS
AND SITTING ON THE DOCK,
STARING DOWN 75 FEET
OF SNARLED LINE
AT A 200 HORSEPOWER
WATER-SKI BOAT.
WHERE YOUR DERANGED
BROTHER-IN-LAW
IS SITTING AT THE WHEEL
GOOSING THE THROTTLE.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE WITHIN 100
MILES OF THAT DOCK,
BEHIND THAT BOAT,
WITH THAT LUNATIC DRIVING!
YOU'RE OUTTA SHAPE;
YOU'RE OUTTA EXCUSES --
YOU'RE OUTTA
YOUR MIND.
YEAH, BUT YOU'RE WAY
TOO PROUD TOO
CHICKEN OUT.
I'LL TELL
YOU WHAT, THOUGH,
IF YOU DON'T THINK OF
SOMETHING REAL FAST,
YOU, MY FRIEND,
ARE FISH FOOD.
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST
HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT ALL THIS STARTED
WITH ONE BEER.
BUT YOU KNOW
SOMETHING,
THE KIDS WERE SAYING YOU
JUST GOTTA GO FOR IT;
YOUR MOUTHY BROTHER-IN-LAW
WAS MAKING WISECRACKS
ABOUT BODY FAT
PERCENTAGES.
YOU JUST HAD TO
GO FOR IT
AND SHOW YOU HAD THE
MOVES OF A 20-YEAR-OLD.
AND NOW YOU'RE
GOING TO DIE.
YOU CAN'T BAIL WITHOUT
HUMILIATING YOURSELF.
THIS IS WHERE 25 YEARS OF
MARRIAGE IS GOING TO
SAVE YOUR BACON!
YEAH, YOU CALL
THE WIFE OVER;
YOU GIVE HER A KISS;
YOU LOOK HER STRAIGHT IN
THE EYE, AND YOU SAY,
"HONEY, I LOVE YOU."
THEN YOU ADD,
"I ONLY WISH I HAD ENOUGH LIFE
INSURANCE TO PROVIDE FOR YOU
AND THE CHILDREN."
THEN YOU LOOK REAL BRAVE,
LIKE YOU'RE REALLY GONNA
GO FOR IT.
IF SHE'S ANY KIND OF WOMAN --
AND YOU KNOW SHE IS,
SHE'LL HAVE YOU OUTTA
THOSE WATER SKIS
BEFORE YOUR
BATHING SUIT GETS WET,
FROM THE OUTSIDE
OR THE INSIDE.
YEAH, AND YOUR
BROTHER-IN-LAW'S NOT
GOING TO ARGUE WITH YOUR WIFE.
YEAH!
MARRIED TO HER SISTER.
ESPECIALLY IF HE'S
JUST REMEMBER NOT
TO LOOK RELIEVED,
AND YOUR SECRET IS SAFE!
FRIENDS ARE FOR.
THAT'S WHAT
NO NEED TO THANK US.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, I'M SHOCKED.
BUT THEN I'M
ALWAYS SURPRISED
WHEN THINGS GO WELL.
DALTON WENT DOWN
TO THE TV STATION.
WE WERE ALL WAITING HERE WITH
OUR ENCYCLOPEDIAS OPEN,
JUST IN CASE HE
NEEDED TO CALL FOR HELP.
YEP, WINSTON EVEN
FIRED UP HIS COMPUTER
AS AN EXTRA
SOURCE OF INFO.
BUT I THINK HE WAS JUST
SHOWING OFF THAT HE
HAD A COMPUTER.
BIG DEAL.
I GOT PLENTY OF COMPUTERS.
I JUST HAVEN'T CRACKED
THE PASSWORDS YET.
BUT THE TELEVISION
SHOW DIDN'T CALL.
THAT CAN ONLY
MEAN ONE THING...
DALTON MUST'VE WON A
MILLION DOLLARS!
OH, YEAH!
[ SOUND OF CAR DRIVING UP ]
MIKE, DID YOU CALL
FOR AN AMBULANCE?
NO, WHY?
WELL, ONE JUST PULLED UP,
AND DALTON'S GETTING
OUT OF IT.
IS HE ALL RIGHT?
I WOULD DOUBT THAT.
OKAY, THANKS, GUYS.
NO, NO.
( laughs )
NO, I'M OKAY.
ALL MY FRIENDS ARE HERE.
OKAY, BYE-BYE.
YOU BONEHEADED
IMBECILES!
I'D LIKE TO STRANGLE
YOU BOTH WITH MY
BARE HANDS!
IF I COULD
FIND 'EM!
IS ANYTHING WRONG,
DALTON?
OH, WRONG?
BECAUSE OF YOU TWO
I LOST A MILLION DOLLARS,
AND I WAS ALMOST CARRIED
AWAY TO THE ASYLUM.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, DALTON?
WE WERE ALL DOWN THERE.
WE HAD THE ENCYCLOPEDIAS
WIDE OPEN.
THERE WAS SO MUCH USELESS
INFORMATION IN THAT ROOM,
IT WAS LIKE A SESSION
OF PARLIAMENT.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
THEY TRIED TO PHONE,
BUT THERE WAS SOME PROBLEM,
AND EVENTUALLY TIME RAN OUT!
THAT'S WHEN I HAD
TO BE RESTRAINED.
I THINK MAYBE THEY
SHOULD'VE GIVEN YOU
A TRANQUILIZER.
I AM ON TRANQUILIZERS!
WHAT WAS THE QUESTION?
WHAT AFRICAN ANIMAL IS
KNOWN AS THE CUSTODIAN
OF THE JUNGLE?
OH, THAT'S AN EASY ONE.
THAT'S THE HYENA.
IT'S IN MY BOOK HERE.
IT'S A MEMBER OF
THE DOG FAMILY.
IT'S A CARNIVORE.
IT FEEDS ON WEAK
AND DECEASED ANIMALS.
AND IT LIVES IN
JANITORIAL AFRICA.
THAT'S - THAT'S EQUATORIAL.
BOYS, THAT WOULD HAVE
BEEN A LOT MORE
USEFUL TO ME
A COUPLE OF HOURS AGO.
HEY, GUYS, I'M OFF
THE INTERNET NOW,
SO YOU CAN USE THE PHONE.
( screaming )
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME, Mr GREEN.
OKAY, UM --
WELL, UM, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I THINK STUDYING AND
LEARNING ALL THIS TRIVIA STUFF
SO YOU'RE GOOD AT A GAME,
THAT'S NOT OUR STYLE
HERE AT THE LODGE.
WE PREFER TO GET OUR
KNOWLEDGE BY ACCIDENT.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND THE
WHOLE GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR
STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, EVERYBODY, SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, EVERYBODY.
SIT DOWN OVER THERE, PLEASE.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, I'VE GOT A
LITTLE TRIVIA QUESTION
FOR YOU.
WHAT AFRICAN ANIMAL IS KNOWN
AS THE CUSTODIAN OF
THE JUNGLE?
TOLD YOU IT WAS AN EASY ONE.