MY WIFE BERNICE WISHES I'D
GET DRESSED UP MORE OFTEN.
BUT WHEN IT COMES
TO WEARING A SUIT
I'M KINDA LIKE THE C.E.O.
"C" FOR CHRISTMAS,
"E" FOR EASTER,
"O" FOR OBITUARY.
MAYBE A LOT OF YOU
GUYS AREN'T LIKE ME.
MAYBE YOU GOT A JOB
OR A STRICT WIFE,
OR MAYBE YOU CARE
ABOUT YOUR APPEARANCE.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING
ABOUT THAT.
BUT WHAT I CAN DO
IS SHOW YOU A CHEAP WAY
TO DRY CLEAN YOUR CLOTHES
USING YOUR OWN FURNACE.
SEE, NOW, THIS HERE,
THIS IS THE HEAT CHAMBER,
WHERE ALL THE
AIR GOES THROUGH.
NOW, BEFORE YOU
TOSS THE SUIT IN THERE,
YOU WANNA REALLY SHOCK
THE AIR FRESHENER TO IT...
BECAUSE LET'S FACE IT,
PEOPLE ARE A LOT MORE
CONCERNED WITH HOW YOU SMELL
THAN HOW YOU LOOK.
THEN YOU WRAP THE WHOLE THING
AROUND THE AEROSOL CAN --
I'LL EXPLAIN WHAT
THAT'S FOR LATER.
OKAY, NOW YOU JUST STICK
THE PANEL BACK ON THERE.
THAT'LL TAKE CARE OF OUR AIR
MOVEMENT AND OUR DEODORISING,
BUT TO GET ANY
CLEANING DONE,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE INTRODUCE
SOME CHEMICALS INTO THE MIX,
YOU CAN GET THIS FROM
ANY HARDWARE STORE.
[ coughs ]
IN THE NO-SMOKING SECT
JUST SOAK YOUR
FILTER WITH THIS STUFF.
THEN WHEN THE
FURNACE FAN KICKS ON,
THE CLEANER WILL BE
EFFECTIVELY APPLIED
TO THE GARMENTS.
[ continues coughing ]
YOU KNOW, THIS STUFF'S
PRETTY TOXIC, SO...
[ slurring ]
WHEN YOU SOAK THE FILTER
MAKE SURE YOU DO IT
IN A WELL... VENTILATED...
BOY, HAD A BIT
OF A NAP THERE,
AND TALK ABOUT DREAMS!
I DREAMT I WAS RIDING A BIG
STRIPED ELEPHANT,
WEARING A
PURPLE SATIN MUMUU.
OKAY, NOW, TO GET
THE SUIT CLEAN,
WHAT YOU DO IS YOU TURN
THE FAN SWITCH TO THE
'ON' POSITION
WHICH WILL KIND OF
GET THE AIR MOVING AROUND
WITHOUT TURNING
THE FURNACE ON.
YOU LET THAT GO
FOR ABOUT 10 MINUTES,
AND THEN TO GET
THE SUIT BACK,
YOU TURN UP
THE THERMOSTAT.
THE FURNACE LIGHTS UP,
AND AS SOON AS
YOUR FURNACE GETS HOT,
THAT AEROSOL CAN IS GOING TO
FLATTEN THE WRINKLES,
FILL YOUR CLOTHES WITH A
LOVELY DRY CLEANING FRAGRANCE,
AND GIVE YOU
FREE DELIVERY.
OH, BOY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
EASY! EASY!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
ONE OF THOSE REALITY TV SHOWS
IS COMING HERE.
YOU BELIEVE THAT?
I FIGURED POSSUM LAKE WOULD
BE THE LAST PLACE ON EARTH
FOR REALITY TO SET IN.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT SHOW IT IS.
PROBABLY
"HOME BREW SURVIVOR."
OR MAYBE "WHO WANTS
TO MARRY STINKY PETERSON?"
ATCH FOR THE MAIL!
I'LL NEVER FAIL!
IF YOU DON'T
GET A LETTER
YOU'LL KNOW I'M IN JAIL
T-TOOTSIE, GOOD-BYE
T-TOOTSIE,
DON'T CRY!
YOU AIN'T SEEN
NOTHING YET.
NO ARGUMENT HERE.
SO YOU THINK
I HAVE A CHANCE?
DON'T EVER ASK ME
THINGS LIKE THAT.
HA HA HA.
WELL, I DO!
I'M AUDITIONING
FOR THAT REALITY SHOW.
OH, YEAH?
WHAT IS IT,
DORKS ON ICE?
NO, IT'S
"SINGING SENSATIONS."
AND THE WINNER GETS
A RECORDING CONTRACT
AND A CHEQUE
FOR $100,000.
HOLY COW, HAROLD!
YOU KNOW WHAT,
YOU SHOULD DO THIS.
I AM DOING IT.
SEE, THAT'S
GOOD ADVICE.
AND AS YOUR ADVISOR
I THINK I DESERVE
10% OF THE 100 GRAND.
OKAY.
HUNDRED DOLLARS, OKAY.
HAROLD, 10% OF
100 GRAND IS
NOT $100.
IT'S 1,000.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER WILL
RECEIVE THIS COUPON
FOR THE PORT ASBESTOS
LITTLE THEATRE PLAY
ABOUT TWO MIS-MATCHED
NOVA SCOTIA FISHERMEN
FORCED TO LIVE
IN THE SAME BOATHOUSE.
DON'T MISS...
"THE COD COUPLE ."
ALL RIGHT, COVER YOUR
EARS THERE, MIKE.
RED, YOU'VE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MIKE HAMAR TO
SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
UH, OKAY, MIKE,
THIS IS HOW YOU
GET STUFF.
SHOPLIFTING?
NO, NO.
OKAY, WHEN YOU GET SOMETHING
THAT YOU DIDN'T HAVE BEFORE,
THAT MEANS YOU...
SLEPT IN A CHEAP MOTEL.
NO, UH...
OKAY, WHEN YOUR DAD PASSES
HIS GENES ON TO YOU
YOU BLANK THEM.
STERILIZE THEM.
OKAY, NO, LET'S GO
A DIFFERENT WAY HERE.
THIS IS A PLACE
WHERE YOU SING.
UH, THE SHOWER.
NO, NO, ACTUALLY YOU PERFORM
WITH A WHOLE LOT OF PEOPLE.
OH! THE PRISON SHOWER.
NO, NO, NO, MIKE.
YOUR MOTHER SANG
IN ONE OF THESE.
A TOPLESS BAND?
THAT WAS A REAL TOUGH GIG FOR
THE ACCORDION PLAYER.
YEAH, UH, RED,
YOU'RE ALMOST OUTTA TIME.
YEAH, OKAY, MIKE,
WHEN RICH PEOPLE PAY A LOT
OF MONEY FOR SOMETHING,
YOU ALWAYS HEAR
THIS WORD...
OH, CAVIAR.
YOU KNOW THAT'S
JUST FISH EGGS?
GUESS YOU GOTTA
ACQUIRE A TASTE FOR IT.
THERE WE GO!
GRAB YOUR GLUE STICK
AND RUN WITH YOUR SCISSORS
DOWN TO HAROLD'S
HOBBY HOUSE!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
JOIN ME AS WE EXPLORE
THE EXCITING WORLD OF
EXTREME HOBBIES.
MY GUEST TODAY,
MR. GLEN BRACKSTON
FORMERLY OF
THE BRACKSTON MARINA.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WHY DON'T
YOU STAND UP, GLEN,
SO PEOPLE CAN
RECOGNIZE YOU?
OH, I THINK THEY CAN
RECOGNIZE ME BETTER
SITTING DOWN, HAROLD.
I'D PREFER IF
YOU STOOD UP.
REALLY?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
GLEN HAS A
FASCINATING HOBBY.
HE HAS AN EXTENSIVE
COLLECTION OF TEACUPS
AND COFFEE MUGS.
I'M TOLD THEY'RE FROM
THROUGHOUT THE COUNTRY,
AND SOME DATE BACK
TO THE 17th CENTURY.
MM-HMM!
WELL, THAT'S NOT
EXACTLY RIGHT, HAROLD.
THERE'S NO TEACUPS.
NO TEACUPS?
NO.
JUST COFFEE MUGS?
COFFEE MUGS ARE
EXCITING!
YEAH, IT'S A
LOT OF FUN.
ACTUALLY, IT DOESN'T
REQUIRE A LOT OF WORK,
WHICH IS THE BIG PLUS.
[ CHUCKLES ]
THOSE ARE PAPER
COFFEE CUPS.
YEAH, IT'S JUST
A SAMPLE.
THE COMPLETE COLLECTION
IS IN THE BACK SEAT
OF MY CAR.
YOU SAID SOMETHING ABOUT
THEM DATING BACK TO
THE 17th CENTURY.
NO, NO,
I MEANT MY CAR.
IT'S MY 17th
BUICK CENTURY.
YEAH, I LOVE THE
IT'S GOT THE RECLINING
SEATS THAT GO UP --
GLEN, GLEN GLEN!
WHAT WOULD EVER COMPEL YOU
TO START COLLECTING
PAPER COFFEE CUPS?
WELL, UH, I GUESS IT
WAS THE DRIVE THRU.
AFTER GOING THERE
FOR A FEW MONTHS,
THE WIFE GOT
ON MY BACK
ABOUT CLEANING OUT
THE BACK SEAT OF MY CAR.
SO I GET THIS BRAINSTORM.
I THOUGHT, I'LL TELL HER
IT'S A COLLECTION.
WELL, THE THING IS,
IT TURNED OUT
I ENJOYED IT
AFTER A WHILE.
WELL, ACTUALLY, I ENJOYED
IT A LOT MORE
THAN CLEANING OUT
THE BACK SEAT OF MY CAR.
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY,
COZ I THINK COLLECTING
PAPER CUPS
WOULD BECOME
KINDA LIMITING.
WELL, NO, THEY'RE NOT JUST
COFFEE CUPS, HAROLD.
NO, NO.
SEE?
THAT'S A DOUBLE DOUBLE.
AHH!
DECAF.
AH, THERE IT IS.
COFFEE?
LATTE.
LATTE!
YEAH,
FOOLS EVERYBODY.
YOU HEAR A LOT
OF TALK THESE DAYS
ABOUT FOSSIL FUELS AND HOW
THE DEPLETION OF THE
RAIN FOREST
IS MELTING THE ICEBERGS
AND DROWNING ALL THE WHALES.
SO NOW THEY'VE GOT A
WHOLE BUNCH OF ENGINEERS
TRYING TO MAKE CARS OUT OF
RECYCLED STYROFOAM CUPS
AND GASOLINE OUT
OF COW PATTIES.
BUT YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES WHEN
YOU CAN'T FIND THE ANSWER
LOOKING FORWARD,
YOU SHOULD LOOK BACK.
BACK IN TIME.
THIS CLOCK STOOD IN
THE POSSUM LAKE TOWN SQUARE
FOR 75 YEARS.
THEN LAST SUMMER THEY GOT
A GRANT TO SPRUCE UP DOWNTOWN,
SO THEY PUT UP SOME SPRUCE
AND TORE DOWN THE CLOCK.
NOW THEY GOT A BIG DIGITAL ONE
ON TOP OF CITY HALL.
PEOPLE DRIVING BY
THINK IT'S THE PRICE OF GAS.
PROBABLY BECAUSE IT
GOES UP EVERY MINUTE.
YOU KNOW, THIS CLOCK IS
KIND OF LIKE THE IDEAL
LODGE MEMBER...
STRONG, DEPENDABLE,
AND YOU ONLY HAVE
TO WIND IT UP ONCE A YEAR.
THEY SAY THE WHOLE WORLD IS
LOOKING FOR A CHEAP, REUSABLE,
ENVIRONMENTALLY FRIENDLY FUEL.
WELL, I GOT THE KEY.
GOT THE CLOCK MOUNTED AND
CONNECTED TO THE DRIVE TRAIN.
YOU KNOW A CLOCK IS REALLY
JUST A BUNCH OF GEARS.
SO I WENT TO THE HIGHEST GEAR
TO GET THE MAXIMUM HORSEPOWER.
THEN I RAN A L-O-ONG
BICYCLE CHAIN AROUND IT,
THROUGH THE SUN ROOF AND DOWN
THROUGH THE FLOOR OF THE CAR,
AND HOOKED IT AROUND
ANOTHER SPROCKET
I DUCT TAPED
TO MY DRIVE SHAFT.
YOU KNOW I DIDN'T EVEN NEED
TO CUT A HOLE IN THE
FLOOR BOARDS.
THAT'S THE BEAUTY OF
USING AN OLDER VEHICLE.
NOW, I NEEDED A PENDULUM
TO MAKE THE CLOCK WORK.
THE ORIGINAL ONE
WAS ABOUT 10 FEET LONG.
I DIDN'T HAVE
THAT KIND OF ROOM,
SO I JUST ADDED SOME
HORSESHOES TO A PICKAXE.
THAT SHOULD MAKE
THE CLOCK WORK FINE.
PEOPLE ALWAYS SAID I HAD
HORSESHOES UP MY SOMETHING.
THEY JUST HAD
THE LOCATION WRONG.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE
HOW OUR NEW ENGINE WORKS.
[ GRUNTING AND GROANING ]
OKAY, THANK GOODNESS I ONLY
HAVE TO DO THAT ONCE A YEAR.
BOY, I SOUND LIKE
DALTON'S WIFE.
ANYWAY, I SEE BY
THE BIG CLOCK ON MY ROOF
THAT IT'S TIME TO
TAKE THIS BABY FOR A SPIN.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME
I GOTTA GO SAVE
THE ANET.
[ BELL GONGING ]
I WENT TO A WEDDING
OVER THE WEEKEND,
AND I SAW SOME
BEAUTIFUL SIGHTS...
THE BRIDE, THE FLOWERS,
THE OPEN BAR.
BUT THERE WAS ONE SIGHT
THAT WAS LESS WELCOME.
THAT WAS WHEN DINNER ENDED
AND THE DJ STARTED
AND A BUNCH OF MIDDLE AGED
GUYS STARTED SHAKING
WHAT WAS LEFT OF THEIR
BOOTY ON THE DANCE FLOOR.
NO, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO.
NOW, JUST IN CASE YOU THINK
I'M BEING A WET BLANKET,
LET ME BE CLEARER.
IF YOU'RE THE FATHER
OF THE BRIDE,
WHEN YOU DANCE
WITH YOUR DAUGHTER,
THAT'S A MOMENT
TO REMEMBER;
LIKEWISE IF YOU'RE A GUEST
AND YOUR WIFE WANTS TO DANCE
WITH YOU TO 'MOON RIVER,'
GET OUT THERE AND DO THAT
LITTLE ROCKIN' TWO-STEP
THAT HASN'T LET YOU DOWN
SINCE THE SEVENTH GRADE.
BUT I'M TALKIN'
ABOUT THE FAST SONGS.
YOU'VE LET
YOUR BODY GO.
DON'T DO THE MASHED POTATO;
YOU ARE
THE MASHED POTATO.
YOU CAN'T DO
THE LOCOMOTION
IF YOUR ENGINE IS ONLY HALF
THE SIZE OF YOUR CABOOSE.
THOSE AREN'T
STROBE LIGHTS.
THAT'S YOU PASSIN' OUT.
NOW, I KNOW THERE'S ALWAYS
GONNA BE AT LEAST ONE GUY
WHO GETS A COUPLE
OF DRINKS IN HIM
AND IGNORES MY ADVICE.
THAT'S WHEN YOU NEED
TO DO THE RIGHT THING.
JUST GET A COUPLE OF
PARAMEDICS TO WALK OVER,
TAP HIM ON THE SHOULDER,
AND QUIETLY SAY MAYBE YOU
SHOULD JUST SIT THIS
ONE OUT, MR. GREEN.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, TODAY'S THE BIG DAY.
HAROLD'S GONE DOWN TO THE
COMMUNITY CENTRE
TO AUDITION FOR THAT
"SINGING SENSATIONS" TV SHOW,
ALONG WITH ALMOST
EVERYBODY IN TOWN.
MOOSE THOMPSON DIDN'T GO.
I BELIEVE HE HAS A DEAL
WITH ANOTHER NETWORK...
"ALL-STAR BATTLE OF THE
GIANT FREAKS OF NATURE."
BUT I GOTTA FIGURE
HAROLD DIDN'T DO SO WELL,
SO I SHOULD PROBABLY
BE NICE TO HIM.
I HATE THIS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YO, DAWG, 'AROLD'S
IN THE 'OUSE.
WHAT UP, G?
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHAT DID HE SAY?
AH, AHEM,
AH, HE'S SAYING, UM,
OH, HE WANTS TO KNOW
HOW YOU ARE.
WORRIED.
IT'S FOR REAL,
MR. GREEN.
HAROLD MADE IT INTO THE
SEMI-QUARTER SEMI-FINALS
OF "SINGING SENSATION."
HE'S GONNA BE ON TV!
SO WE REALLY GOTTA PITCH
IN FOR TOMORROW NIGHT,
FOR THE NEXT ROUND.
YEAH, UNCLE RED, COZ I NEED
ALL YOU GUYS TO PHONE IN, OKAY.
COZ YOU GOTTA PHONE IN
AND VOTE FOR ME.
THAT WAY I GET TO GO
ONTO THE NEXT ROUND
AND BEAT THAT 8-YEAR-OLD GIRL
FROM PORT ASBESTOS.
NO, I CAN'T DO IT,
NOT TOMORROW NIGHT,
BECAUSE I'M GOING DOWN TO THE
ARENA TO BUY TICKETS
FOR THE
MONSTER TRUCK RALLY.
SORRY.
I THINK MY SINGING CAREER IS A
LITTLE MORE IMPORTANT
THAN MONSTER TRUCKS.
OKAY, HAROLD,
I KNOW YOU'RE
EXCITED RIGHT NOW,
SO I'M GONNA
LET THAT GO.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
FORGET THE MONSTER TRUCKS.
I'LL DO THE
PHONE IN THING.
AH! THAT'S GOOD!
OH, THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
THAT'S GREAT.
COME ON MIKE.
THIS IS GREAT.
THIS IS PERFECT.
OH, BOY!
Red: COSTS 10 BUCKS
TO LAUNCH YOUR BOAT
AT THE POSSUM LAKE BOAT RAMP,
WHICH IS FINE,
BUT THE WORST THING IS
THEY ACTUALLY HAVE AN
ATTENDANT TO ACTUALLY
MAKE SURE YOU PAY.
SO AS A RESULT,
HE'S NOT ALL THAT BUSY
AS A RULE.
NOW, WE'RE THERE,
AND WE HAVE BOATS,
BUT WE'RE WAITING
FOR A CERTAIN TIME...
USUALLY AROUND NOW
WOULD BE LUNCHTIME.
AND THIS IS A MAN
WHO DOESN'T SKIP MEALS.
SO WE FIGURE AS SOON
AS HE CLEARS THE AREA,
WE GOT 30 MINUTES
TO GET OUR BOATS LAUNCHED.
THAT'S WHEN
THE FUN BEGINS.
NOW, I GOT THE V-8,
SO I'M THE FIRST ONE
DOWN THERE WITH THE
POSSUM VAN.
WALTER STUCK HIS BOAT ON TOP
OF HIS CAR POINTING DOWN
SO HE CAN HARDLY
SEE WHERE HE'S GOING.
AND I STARTED DOWN THERE,
BUT SOMETIMES
WHEN YOU'RE IN A HURRY,
YOU KNOW,
YOU GET A LITTLE --
WALTER'S A
BIT LOST THERE,
AND BILL JUST STUCK
THE CANOE ON TOP THERE.
SO I'M TRYIN' --
NO, NO, NO.
ONE MORE TIME.
NO, NO, BACK.
NO, CUT HER RIGHT.
CUT HER RIGHT.
NOT THAT -- NOT THAT --
AH!
THAT'S A LITTLE
FRUSTRATING.
AND, AGAIN, BILL
IS WORKING HIS WAY THROUGH.
SHE GETS TURNED SIDEWAYS
AND, UH --
WELL, YOU CAN
SEE WHAT'S COMIN' HERE.
SO NOW BILL PULLS UP
IN FRONT OF ME.
HE'S UPSET BECAUSE I'M
TAKIN' UP THE WHOLE RAMP,
AND HE'S SAYIN' HE WANTS
TO LAUNCH HIS CANOE.
TO WHICH I SAY,
WHAT CANOE?
AND YOU REALISE THAT HE'S
UP THE CREEK WITHOUT A CANOE,
ACTUALLY AT THIS POINT.
SO HE GOES BACK
TO GET HIS CANOE ON THERE.
MEANWHILE, WALTER'S HAVIN'
PROBLEMS, UH, WITH VISIBILITY,
SO HE FIGURES WHAT HE SHOULD
PROBABLY IS BACK UP
AND USE THE SIDE MIRROR.
HE'S GOT A
CLEAR VIEW THERE.
AND YOU KNOW, IN THEORY,
IT'S NOT A BAD PLAN.
BUT IN PRACTICE...
NOT SO GOOD.
SO NOW HE'S LOST HIS MIRROR,
SO HE PULLS AHEAD
TO PICK UP THE MIRROR,
NOT REALISING BILL IS DRIVING
AROUND IN THE SAME AREA.
AND NOW OF COURSE BILL HAS
DUCT TAPED THE CANOE
RIGHT ON THERE
AND HE THROWS THE ANCHOR
INSIDE UP AT THE BOW END.
AND HE'S OKAY.
HE'S GOOD TO GO.
SO HE TAKES OFF
WITH THAT UNIT.
AND MEANWHILE, WALTER IS
DRIVING ALL OVER
THE PLACE TOO,
AND SO AM I, TRYING TO
GET MY BOAT LAUNCHED.
BUT BILL DOESN'T REALISE
THERE'S A BIT OF A RAMP
ON THE SIDE OF THE ROAD,
AND THAT TENDS
TO FIRE THE ANCHOR OUT
AND SHE WINDS
AROUND A TREE,
WHICH PULLS THE
CANOE SIDEWAYS AND WELL...
THAT'S THE NAME
OF THAT TUNE.
MEANWHILE, I'M COMIN'
DOWN THE THING,
WALTER BANGS INTO ME,
BILL SLAMS INTO HIM,
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
EVERYTHING IS GOING
DOWN THE BOAT RAMP.
OKAY, THAT DIDN'T
WORK OUT PERFECTLY,
BUT I LIKE TO PUT A
POSITIVE SPIN ON THINGS.
SO I'M FIGURIN', YEAH,
IT COST US 10 BUCKS EACH,
BUT WE LAUNCHED
MORE THAN OUR BOATS...
WE LAUNCHED OUR VEHICLES.
[ APPLAUSE ]
KINDA LOOKS LIKE PBS,
DOESN'T IT?
UH, HAROLD'S DEBUT
WAS TONIGHT ON THE
BIG TV SINGING SHOW,
AND WE'VE BEEN TRYING
TO VOTE FOR HIM FOR
ABOUT AN HOUR,
BUT THE LINES
ARE ALWAYS BUSY.
THERE'S NO REDIAL BUTTOS
ON THESE PHONES THAT
DALTON GAVE US.
IN FACT, THERE'S NO
BUTTONS AT ALL!
OH, WAIT, WAIT.
I'M GETTIN' THROUGH.
UH, YES, I WANNA PLACE
A VOTE FOR, UH,
HAROLD GREEN.
WHAT?
OH, I'M SORRY.
NO, WAIT.
I'LL ORDER A DOUBLE CHEESE,
HOLD THE ANCHOVIES.
[ PHONE RINGS ]
UH, YES, A VOTE FOR
HAROLD GREEN, PLEASE.
IT'S ME,
YOU IDIOT.
DAD?!
HELLO?
OH, HELLO, YES.
HAROLD GREEN.
NO, NO, NO.
HE'S THE ONE
WITH THE TEETH.
WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN HE
WASN'T ON THE SHOW?
WASN'T HAROLD
ON THE SHOW?
I DIDN'T WATCH.
IT REMINDS ME OF WORK.
HAROLD!
HOW'D IT GO?
WHAT HAPPENED?
ALL THOSE PEOPLE,
WATCHING ME?
I GOT STAGE FRIGHT
AND DIDN'T GO ON.
BUT HAROLD YOU'RE
ON OUR SHOW ALL
THE TIME.
YEAH, BUT THIS TIME THERE WAS
GONNA BE WOMEN WATCHING.
THE PRESSURE WAS
JUST TOO MUCH.
PRESSURE WAS TOO MUCH.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
I THINK MAYBE WE
SHOULD STOP PHONING IN.
YEAH, BUT THEY GAVE ME
A PRIZE FOR PARTICIPATING.
I GOT FIVE TICKETS TO THE
MONSTER TRUCK RALLY.
WOW!
HEY, YEAH.
WHOA!
YOU GOT A PRIZE
FOR NOT SINGING?
I CAN SEE THE LOGIC.
WELL, COZ YOU ALL
PHONED IN FOR ME,
I WANNA GIVE YOU
EACH A TICKET.
HEY, THANKS,
HAROLD.
BOY, THESE SEATS
ARE PRETTY HIGH.
WELL, YOU CAN SEE
THE SHOW FROM THERE.
I CAN SEE MY
HOUSE FROM THERE.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
THANKS AGAIN,
HAROLD.
SO IF MY WIFE WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
GOT GREAT NEWS.
IT'S OKAY WITH ME IF YOU INVITE
YOUR PARENTS OVER FOR
THE EVENING
ON, UH, NOVEMBER 23.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD,
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
AND BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE
IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, HAROLD'S
HAD A PRETTY BIG DAY HERE.
HE REALISED HE WAS
IN A NO-WIN SITUATION,
AND HE HAD THE GOOD
SENSE TO GIVE UP.
HE MAY GET MARRIED YET.
I'D LIKE TO JUST HAVE A SMALL
ROUND OF APPLAUSE FOR HAROLD.
[ ONE PERSON CLAPS LIGHTLY ]
AND I BELIEVE, HAROLD,
YOU HAVE A FEW WORDS.
Harold: YES. YES.
UM, I WANNA THANK ALL MY FANS
FOR STICKING CLOSE TO ME,
BUT I'M AFRAID I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO ABANDON MY
SINGING CAREER.
[ STRONG APPLAUSE ]
[ CHANTING "HAROLD" ]