The Book of Genesis says that God created
heaven and Earth in seven days.
Well, every seven days we move heaven and
Earth to bring you the greatest show in the
history of the universe, you know?
But we're only mortals, so this is the
result, basically.
But, you know, considering the budget and
the talent, it's not bad when here he is the
most, not baddest guy of them all.
The star of the Red Green Show and my uncle.
Thanks so very much, ladies and gentlemen,
Mr.
Red Green.
Thank you, Harold. Thank you and welcome to
Possum Lodge.
Harold, I notice you have kind of a biblical
theme going there.
Yes, I do. And it's all leading up to some
nifty creations from my miracle box here.
That was a miracle, wasn't it?
Go ahead. I don't think so, Harold.
Miracles tend to be kind of good things.
I would put this in in the category of
pestilence and famine.
Well, we had a great week up at the launch.
We had the we had the Possum Lake Regatta
going here, which is a huge boat race is open
to all, all classes, all links and
everything.
We probably had about forty five sailboats,
I guess, on the lake from from possum lodges
all over North America vying for the coveted
Windy Possum Trophy.
I'll tell you, I haven't seen that much
canvas flapping in the breeze since they
serve chili at the toga party.
But you know, I'll tell you, we wanted a
game.
Moose Thompson and Stinky Peterson came in
first place and defended our unbeaten winning
streak of one.
Oh yeah, that was quite an accomplishment.
They won by taking the lodge water skiing
towboat that had like a four hundred
horsepower outboard on it.
Yeah. All right. Well, we just have a few
complaints.
But hey, a loophole is a loophole.
You may have to tighten up the rules for
next year.
And once you eliminate powerboats, you might
also want to consider taking out like
boarding parties and shooting flares in the
competition sales.
Well, what do you have left here?
Just a bunch of sailboats racing against
each other.
Uncle Red Yachting is not a contact sport.
Well, then we've improved it.
Anyway, the guy has really, really enjoyed
that regard, and we did well and everything
except whitewater rafting, finance, stalking
and sportsmanship.
But I'll tell you about that a little later
in the show.
That was a cue laser face.
Oh, sorry, I was drifting off, I'm back.
Well, I'm thinking I'm thinking, Harold, you
get any sixes, goldfish.
Bill William have any five.
No, no, no.
This game's getting too rich for me.
I think I'll go for a ride in the RV.
Anybody interested they might want to come
along over a little burn in the car and
Kirby, who's up for it, huh?
A lot of fun. Who's there?
Who's coming, hero bill?
Go ahead, Billy.
Come on. You want to go for a little run?
Don't read. I know you're always ready for
it.
Well, actually, it's a date. So what's the
date?
Oh, yeah. Well, that's today's the day I go
by myself.
I got I give her a little solo burn, do a
little lone wolf thing, you know, that kind
of thing. But you guys have a little fun
playing your little card game here.
Douglas, I'll go for a ride in the RV.
No, you can't come.
Anyway, I guess.
Would you like to play fish?
I don't gamble, which is more than I can say
for a helmet.
Here what?
I just saw the canoe.
Oh yeah.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
You turned a piece of large equipment into
scrap metal and you say, sorry,
I wanted to go whitewater rafting and we
don't have a raft, so I took
The canoe. Now we don't have a canoe.
What did you do? Go through a hydroelectric
plant?
You've got hydroelectric plant.
Stuff happens.
Yes, it does.
Stuff happens and then stuff gets replaced.
Now you weren't going to buy us a new canoe
and you are forbidden for three months to use
any large equipment and you have to have a
bath and a shave.
I don't like your tone.
You know, Douglas, lots of us damp boats and
stuff from time to time.
Oh yeah, yeah. Red.
This is not dented. It's shredded, it's
mangled.
I would have thought you'd been happy that I
was alive.
I am. It would take a lot longer to sue your
estate for damages.
No, I'm giving you twenty four hours to come
up with the money.
And picking apples, picking apples down at
Nash's farm, I climb up the highest branch, I
get a spartan and a broken arm,
An apple to apples to apples
For apples. Five.
I never knew he's going to get that many
apples and your mouse will still be alive.
Eating up, seeing apples.
Something from every tree.
The neighbor yells, Hey, those apples have
worms.
It's OK. So do we.
This week in Handyman Garner, I'm going to
show you how you could make do and just use
what you have. For example, I was I was
going through town the other day and I saw a
whole bunch of these blue boxes out in front
of people's houses filled up with tin cans
and they're just lying there, you know?
They just made my head spin.
And of course, I've seen that many tin cans
in my mind.
I got the kind of mine that just starts
rolling around with the ideas.
The first one being to just grab off the
boxes of cans and throw them into the van.
You know, nobody, nobody to stop me or
nothing.
And I got, I would say, maybe 50 or 60 of
the boxes and probably around 8000 cans, you
know? So I thought we can show you what you
can do with stuff like that.
Now, save the boxes for next week, we're
going to show you how to make a pontoon boat.
But this week we're going to show you what
you can do with the cans.
Ok, now I mean, there's the all the obvious
stuff, you know, ashtrays, drinking cups,
soap dishes, jewelry boxes, eyeglass frames
say a change purse or safety boots or even
portable urinals. But I'd like to
concentrate on some multicam projects you can
do using the handyman secret weapon duct
tape.
Ok, so we've got a bit of this off.
Stick it down. Sticky side up, sticky side
up.
Some important lesson in life.
Take two cans roughly of the same size.
You joining them together. Like so and just
roll it onto the onto the duct tape at the
going rate on the duct tape is fantastic.
You can glue anything with that little glue,
wouldn't the plastic or metal type glass or
doors to cars?
Let's repeat this process with a third can
of added on here.
And you know, I wouldn't be surprised if you
could glue putting the air with duct tape.
Wouldn't that be something big dollop of
butterscotch pudding just hanging in your
foyer? To see your mom come on in.
Ok, there we go.
You're right. It's a chair leg.
Ok, now we need a seat for our chairs.
Put down a strip of duct tape again.
The sticky side up that'll get you through
so much of your adult life that down there
like that. And then you take the cans, you
know, duct tape sticks well, two fingers do
and put the cans on the tape just a couple
inches apart.
Just slap my like that.
Now these are cans of approximately the same
size, but they're again.
Get creative. Once you've done that, you
just grab the end of the tape and you start
rolling her up. Oh, I bet every one of these
cans could the cow story.
I mean, the cans could talk.
Life's funny like that, isn't it?
I don't know if you'd want cans to be
talking.
You know what would can say about you.
Do you like if cans could actually talk?
You bring that up, bring that around and
there's a seat for your chair.
Mind you, you're going to want a small can
sit on that.
And there you have it.
Who says it's hard to make furniture?
That's not an attractive aluminum on chair.
Just picture yourself sitting out on that in
the sun.
And after you have a few drinks, you got
enough cans and make yourself a footstool.
No know something else you can make of tin
cans for the kids.
I'll tell you. You get the sound of the
youngster and you have them roller skating on
any kind of a concrete surface, and the
noise level gets to the point where you got
to talk to them with the sign language
there.
But on the other hand, you know, you always
know where your kids are.
I mean, if that's important to you and say
what we're talking about here is really
imagination, you know that that English
writer Samuel Johnson, the one time, said if
it wasn't for imagination, the man would be
just as happy in the arms of a chambermaid as
he as he wasn't a duchess.
He's dead now, but no, I'm just trying to
use my imagination, and I'm imagining that we
take these tin cans and make ourselves an
Easter off, huh?
So we take a count like this and we just cut
the Canada down.
All right, that's not going just quite as
well as I planned, so why don't we switch
over to the handy man's favorite power
tools?
And all right.
Ten snaps, huh?
Right through these.
So.
It's just a matter of using your imagination.
It's like Samuel Johnson said, the Lord
Chesterfield, if the women don't find it
handsome, they should at least find a handy.
He was horsing around with Lady Chesterfield
at the time.
Now reports have an interesting life on me.
Let's get rid of all.
Oh, excuse me a minute.
Everything you touch, you reckon?
I do not.
It is summer, the dog lies motionless on my
front porch.
This is strange because I don't have a dog,
nor do I have a front porch.
Obviously, one of us is not home.
I tell you this whole situation with helmet
in the crumpled canoe has got the whole lodge
buzzing, you know, because if Douglas pushes
this too far, it could set a real dangerous
precedent where people would actually be
held responsible for things they wrecked.
Well, I don't know. I think maybe people
should be responsible for their own
abilities, and these self-appointed experts
are dangerous.
I say more power than dogs.
For example, the producer and director of the
show would be held accountable for the look
and the pace. And of course, the audience
ratings what?
What I do the best with the talent available.
We can just replace you with some of the more
talented.
Ok. All right. You know what?
You know what? I think I think that people
like Douglas should be held accountable for
the lack of money in the large Treasury.
How about that? Yeah, yeah.
I thought you'd come around, Harold.
Yeah. Ok, here's what I think.
I think what you could do is we should
Sorry, Uncle Ray. There's no time for that.
Not if I'm in control the pace of the show
and everything got to go.
Glenn Land, hello.
Wow. Oh, no, that's not me, right?
It's me here. That's just a little decoy I
raked up.
Keep the looters away from the RV.
Yeah, it's kind of a scarecrow thing, you
know?
Yeah, yeah.
Looks just like me.
Don't it doesn't even move.
Perfect, man. Can you fix a canoe?
Well, see for your large brother and all
that.
Yeah, yeah. I'll have to charge you 10 bucks
for the estimate.
All right. Yeah. All right. Monday.
Look, see
Already.
Now what do you think?
Or is a canoe?
This is it right here.
It's been going over the falls again.
Yeah, yeah. Boy, he must know everything
there is to know about gravity.
Huh? Can you fix it, man?
Oh no, this is a write off read.
Yeah, you might be a fly in an art gallery
or something.
Might be interested, but
Oh, that's too bad.
Yeah. Well, that'll be 10 bucks read.
Yeah. Yeah. Say Glen.
You know, instead of any of the 10, you
think I could do something, you know, maybe
clean up the RV or something rather than
cash, you know?
Well, you know what? Yeah, actually, she
needs an oil change grid, so maybe you just
jump under there? Yeah, pull out the oil
plug.
Yeah, let it drain into the lake, though,
because it makes a hell of a mess right here.
Oh yeah. All right. And I'll cook it
tomorrow.
That's a good idea, right? Yeah.
Hey, right. Somebody just took off in your
van.
I guess you want one of my scarecrows?
No, don't tell. Just tell me when you need
the oil right, it's right behind you there.
Harold's Frisbee stuck up a tree, gave us the
subject for this week's Adventures with Bill.
Harry is all set to help us get the frisbee
down first.
First plan is not going to work Plan B
subsection four Climb a tree that has no
branches on it. Let's think this through
once in a while.
Can we bill? Now, when he when he made that
gesture, I thought he wanted me to do it and
I thought, no, he wants my.
Ok. All right. Yeah, that is what he meant.
All right, and then this doesn't Bill's not
like.
All right. He's going to just knock it down
with us.
Why don't we start with this?
Oh, wait, oh, it's he hit it and it went up
and actually went up and said it all now.
Oh man, it's way they were up there, 50 60
foot tree and way way.
Now what do we do, bill? That Bill never
gives up, unfortunately.
So he tied his rope around himself, and he's
going to throw the end of the rope through
the park and the tree, and then I'll pull, I
pull down on the rope.
But what happened was it hit the van and
then it was at last to not cord around the
trailer hitch, which we didn't notice.
So I started pulling down on the rope and
trying to pull Belle up the tree.
And what neither one of us realized was that
Harold had decided to take the van into town
by himself a new frisbee.
What he was doing across was pulling their
own.
Oh, oh, oh oh.
No arbitrary and came back down and the van
still going.
The news is we got the frisbee back.
Ok, with the plug, huh? Beautiful day.
Well, the largest kind of divided into into
two camps on this thing with the canoe, on
the one hand, there's people who think that
helmets shouldn't have to replace the canoe
or even repair it. They think that anybody
who can can turn on actually a metal boat
inside out, you know, that's something to be
admired, even with a with a little tinge of
fear. And then the other camp, you have the
pay as you play people, which is mainly
Douglas,
You know, actually, Uncle Fred Douglas is
convinced Moose Thompson to support him.
Wow. I wonder how he got moose on his side.
Maybe he removed a thorn from his paw, and
moose can sway a few votes.
That guy's got fish like tractors.
Oh, I changed my vote.
You know if I had one.
This is going to make the lads think twice.
I'll tell you. It might even make you think
once, Harold, how did how do you mean when it
happens? You'll know. Well, either either
Moose Thompson is just persuaded his first
lodge member, or that's the call of a
meeting.
No, that's the call of the meeting.
All right. Come on. Let's get down there and
see what's going on.
I wonder if any of the lodge members are
intimidated?
Oh, well, there's going to probably be some
nasty language and some violent threats and a
lot of crisis and conflict and all kinds of
horrible things going on down there.
So I really don't want to miss this.
All right. Guam.
No. Time now
For recognizers. Douglas Henry Jack.
Thank you, Ed. Well, everyone, I have some
excellent news I've discovered.
Thank you, Harold. I've discovered why our
Treasury is empty, why I think this is a list
of all the things that helmet has broken
over the years when I totaled what he
totaled. It came to twenty thousand dollars.
Are things
A dollars? Ten thousand things?
Well, maybe if I made a list of all this
stuff I fixed over the years, that had come
to twenty thousand two.
I think not helmet half the items on this
list you wrecked by fixing them.
Oh, I don't know. I don't know.
I mean, hell, it fixes a lot of things
around here like the pump.
He fixes the pump and we all know how
expensive plumbers are, right?
Tell me you're a menace.
Well, now I feel very strongly.
And more importantly, so does Moose Thompson
over there.
Thank you, Moose. But how much should
reimburse the lodge for damages?
I'm really surprised you're going along with
this moose.
We apply this rule to you.
You asked for seven beds, a hundred chairs
and a wall.
Well, actually not.
Is he in order to get moose support?
I made an immunity deal with him.
Well, hold it. Hold it, hold it.
Let's put some common sense into this.
All right. This is stupid.
I mean, this is this is a really stupid.
This is dumb. Look, I make a living out of
fixing things that you guys broke.
All right. So if you take that away, you
bankrupt the only marina on Possum Lake.
I mean, that's dumb. That's just stupid.
No, no. Wait a minute. We'll still need
repairs.
It's just now the members will pay instead
of the lodge.
Oh, so I might get paid.
Oh, I'm for it.
I'm for it.
No, no, no. Wait, now Glenn has a very good
point here.
Oh, no. Read just forget it.
What I said. Just move on, right?
That's OK. That's OK.
And we're glad you see it. If people have to
pay for stuff that they break, they'll
they'll start being careful and they'll
they'll start not using stuff, right?
And then there won't be any damage for you
to repair.
Oh, well, that's actually what I meant.
That sounds like what I meant. It was
stupid.
Just dumb, just stupid.
Now, wait a minute.
You don't fix anything anyways.
We've got a 14 foot lab streak that's been
in for repairs since nineteen fifty two.
It'll be ready Tuesday night, Wednesday
morning, early, maybe tomorrow.
Well, why don't we put this thing to a vote,
huh?
All those in favor of the members like
helmet hair being charged for whatever they
brake, say I, I.
All opposed, say nay.
Sorry, Douglas. Well, it was close.
Right? So if there's no other large
business, OK, Bill, I'm going to call on
helmet here to give us the evening's
entertainment.
All right. Oh, great.
Thank you, red. Thank you.
So I was white water rafting I always got.
I brought my mom there because we were going
over the falls that had come over to the
canoe bent up.
You know, listening to Douglas and Helmet
present their cases to forty six.
Normally slack-jawed, individuals who
listened in some cases comprehend them and
then cast their votes as their hearts and
their conscience dictated.
And I couldn't help but think that if we had
a TV and a good football game was on, none of
this would have happened better.
Like gas, they fill the space available
anyway.
Yeah, my wife is watching.
I'll be coming straight home after the
meeting and I'm I'm feeling kind of wide
awake. So why don't we hit the sack early?
So I'm so next time on behalf of Harold and
myself and the whole gang up here at Possum
Lodge? Keep your stick on the ice.
You know, I was like going like this with my
hands, and I kept on scooping little kids out
of the water. It's difficult, you know, to
move the boat through the water with your
hands open like that. We'll be tracking mud
on the carpet there anyway.