(Radio static and beeping)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S A MAN WHO KNOWS NO PEER,
AND YOU CAN TELL
BY HOW HE DOCKS HIS BOAT.
MY UNCLE, YOUR HOST, RED GREEN!
(Applause)
THANK YOU.
HEY, THERE, HAROLD.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WE'RE HAVING TROUBLE
WITH THE PHONE LINES.
(Ringing)
EXCUSE ME A MINUTE.
STOP USING THE PHONE.
EXCELLENT PHONE MANNERS.
IT STARTED WHEN
HAROLD HOOKED UP
HIS COMBINATION FAX/MODEM
AND WAFFLE TOASTER.
WELDED EVERYBODY'S
PHONE LINES TOGETHER
SO WE ALL GET EVERY CALL.
(Ringing)
THAT'S MY COMPUTER FRIENDS.
WRONG NUMBER.
(Applause and cheering)
THAT WAS CLEVER.
WHAT WILL WE DO NOW?
THE PHONE SYSTEM WON'T BE FIXED
BY THE PHONE COMPANY.
THEY KEEP CARPING
ABOUT UNPAID BILLS,
AS IF THAT'S GONNA MAKE
ANY DIFFERENCE.
WE'RE SWITCHING
TO A BETTER SYSTEM.
WE'RE GOING BACK TO C.B.
DOWNWIND DANGER --
COME IN, DOWNWIND DANGER.
DOWNWIND
DANGER?
STINKY PETERSON.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO
MAKE YOUR OWN PAY PHONE BOOTH,
BUZZ WILL BRING US A BARRAGE
OF OPINION WITHOUT ANY POINT,
I'LL TRY TO GET MIKE
TO FINALLY ACCEPT
RESPONSIBILITY,
AND GARTH HARBLE WILL TRY
AND BAG A FEW GEESE.
(Junior Singleton on radio)
IT'S NOT RAINING HERE, EITHER.
YOU'RE NOT THAT FAR AWAY.
I SEE YOU OUT THE WINDOW.
(Talking)
I'M NOT GONNA WAVE.
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES.
OVER AND OUT.
HOW'S THE COMMUNICATION
NETWORK WORKING OUT?
NOT BAD.
YOU ALWAYS GET GUYS
THAT ABUSE THE SYSTEM.
MOST MEN DON'T WANT
SOMEONE TO TALK TO.
THEY WANT SOMEONE
TO LISTEN TO THEM.
SINGLE GUYS ARE THE WORST.
THEY CAN'T GET IT AT HOME,
IS HOW THAT ONE GOES.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU SHOULD DO?
INSTEAD OF HAVING
THE PHONE LINES REPAIRED,
YOU SHOULD HAVE THEM UPGRADED.
GET CALL DISPLAY.
YOU COULD SEE THE NUMBER
OF THE PERSON
THAT YOU DON'T WANT TO TALK TO,
UNLESS THEY GOT
THAT DISPLAY BLOCK THING.
THEN YOU GOTTA GET INTERACTIVE
AND HAVE THEM FORWARDED
TO YOUR VOICE MAIL.
HAROLD, YOU HAVE ME CONFUSED
WITH A SUGGESTION BOX.
I'VE DIVIDED EVERY DAY
INTO HOURS,
AND EACH GUY GETS AN HOUR
TO DO ALL HIS COMMUNICATING.
I GOT 9:00 TO 10:00 P.M.
ON THURSDAY.
WHAT HOURS DO I GET?
AM I ON THERE?
YEAH, YOU HAVE 3:00
TO 4:00 A.M., TUESDAY MORNING.
DARN, IT'S THE SAME TIME SLOT
AS THIS SHOW.
(Red): BILL'S RADIO SHOW
IS GONNA FEATURE BOWLING.
STAY TUNED FOR THAT.
HE'S JUST PRACTISING RIGHT NOW.
IT'S 10-PIN,
ISN'T IT, BILL?
OH, NO, IT'S TWO-PIN.
THAT IS NOT THE PEACE SIGN.
OKEY-DOKE, THIS IS THE BIG ONE!
FOR THE GRAND PRIZE
OF FREE HERBICIDE AND PESTICIDE
FROM MOIRA'S HOUSE
OF SKIN CARE,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO MAKE MR. HAMAR SAY...
THIS WORD.
THIRTY SECONDS -- BEGIN.
ALL RIGHT, UH,
OBLIGATION.
PAROLE.
NO, NO, YOUR JOB.
(Sighing)
MANDATORY SUPERVISION.
NO, NO, WHEN SOMETHING
GOES WRONG, IT'S YOUR...
... REASON TO LEAVE TOWN
AND START A NEW LIFE?
UH, YOUR
BEHAVIOUR
IS YOUR..
DOWNFALL.
START A NEW APPROACH, HERE.
UM, YOUR WIFE
AND YOUR
CHILD ARE...
IN ALBERTA.
(Audience laughing)
I THINK.
NO, NO, NO.
ATLANTA?
NO, GEORGIA.
MIKE, LEGALLY, THEY ARE YOUR...
MONTHLY INSTALMENT.
ARE YOU CONCENTRATING
HERE, MIKE?
I'M GIVING IT ALL I'VE GOT,
MR. GREEN.
REALLY? HOLY SMOKE.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
SAY YOU'RE THE LEADER.
THEN YOU HAVE...
GUNS, GUARD DOGS...
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
UNCLE RED.
OK, MIKE, H-H-HOLD IT.
IF SOMETHING GOES WRONG
AND YOU'RE TO BLAME,
YOU HAVE...
CULPABILITY.
IF IT'S NOT THE FIRST TIME
IT HAPPENED, YOU HAVE...
CONVICTABILITY.
SO YOU WANT
TO AVOID...
RESPONSIBILITY!
(Ringing bell)
(Applause and cheering)
(Strums acoustic guitar)
OH, GET YOUR
RODS OUT, BOYS
AND LET YOUR SINKERS FLY
SET YOUR HOOKS AND LURES
BUT BE SURE
NOT TO CATCH THEM
IN ANY PART OF YOUR EYE
I KNOW WE'VE HAD OUR FUN
WITH CARDS AND JOKES
AND BEER
BUT IF I DON'T GO HOME
WITH AT LEAST ONE FISH
MY WIFE WON'T LET ME
COME BACK NEXT YEAR
THAT'S TRUE.
I'M SURE OUR C.B. RADIO THING
WILL WORK OUT ALL RIGHT,
BUT JUST IN CASE IT DOESN'T
AND WE MUST GO BACK
TO THE REGULAR PHONE SYSTEM,
I THOUGHT I'D SHOW YOU HOW YOU
CAN MAKE YOUR PHONE PROFITABLE.
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE
YOUR OWN PAY PHONE BOOTH.
START OFF WITH
THE ONE PAY PHONE BOOTH,
AND AS YOU'RE SUCCESSFUL,
MAYBE GET A CHAIN OF THEM,
EVENTUALLY HAVE CANDICE BERGEN
DO YOUR T.V. ADS.
THE MAIN THING YOU NEED
IS A COIN-OPERATED DOOR,
LIKE THIS ONE
ON THIS NEWSPAPER BOX.
YOU COULD USE THE DOOR OFF
A PAY TOILET OR A BANK VAULT,
BUT THIS IS EASIER
TO THROW INTO THE VAN
WHEN NOBODY'S LOOKING.
FIRST YOU GOTTA GET THE BOLTS
OFF THE BOTTOM, THERE.
THERE WE GO, AND SHE SHOULD
JUST POP RIGHT OFF,
I WOULD THINK.
(Grunting)
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES.
I HOPE THIS PROJECT'S WORTH
THE CASH INVESTMENT.
PICK A BUILDING THAT'S
THE RIGHT SIZE AND PERSONALITY
FOR A PHONE BOOTH.
THE BARN'S TOO BIG,
THE SHED ISN'T LOCKABLE.
THIS IS PERFECT.
ALL RIGHT, FIRST GET THE DOOR
OFF THE OUTHOUSE.
(Air horn blasting)
AMAZING HOW FAST THINGS RUST
AROUND AN OUTHOUSE.
I'M SURE THERE'S
A SCIENTIFIC THEORY,
BUT WE KNOW THE REAL REASON.
THE FIRST THING YOU GOTTA DO IS
TO ATTACH YOUR COIN-OPERATED
DOOR TO THE OUTHOUSE.
YOU COULD BOLT IT ON
OR WIRE 'ER ON,
BUT I PREFER TO USE SOMETHING
THAT WON'T RUST.
THE HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
I'VE GOT THE PHONE MOUNTED
ON THE WALL IN THERE.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS ADD
THE POSSUM LAKE PHONE BOOK
AND THE YELLOW PAGES.
ALL RIGHT, YELLOW PAGE.
ONCE THE PHONE SYSTEM
GETS GOING,
I'LL BE RAKING IN THE COIN.
THE BEAUTY OF USING AN OUTHOUSE
AS MY PHONE BOOTH IS
THERE'S A DUAL PURPOSE HERE.
YOU CAN ANSWER TWO CALLS
AT ONCE.
GOT AN EXTRA
BUSINESS LINE HERE.
AND EVEN THE NEWSPAPER
HAS MORE THAN ONE APPLICATION.
IF YOU GOT ONE
OF THEM TEENAGERS
WHO TIES UP THE PHONE
FOR HOURS,
HAVING THE PHONE
IN THE OUTHOUSE
WITH THE AROMA GOING
WILL NIP THAT IN THE BUD.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
(Creaking)
FOR GOSH SAKES.
HAROLD, YOU GOT A QUARTER?
HAROLD?
HAROLD!
COME ON, HAROLD.
EMERGENCY CALL.
YOU WON'T WANT TO MISS
RANGER GORD'S INFOMERCIAL.
WANT TO TALK ABOUT AN EVENING
WE'VE ALL GONE THROUGH.
HAD A QUIET DAY AT WORK.
YOU'VE HAD DINNER,
WATCHED SOME TELEVISION,
AND YOU CAN HARDLY
KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN.
YOU THINK ABOUT SLEEPING
ON THE COUCH,
WHICH IS USUALLY
YOUR WIFE'S SUGGESTION.
YOU FIGURE, "NO, I'VE GOT
ENOUGH ENERGY TO GO TO BED.
"I WON'T PUT ON
ALL MY PYJAMAS."
THERE'S ONLY ONE PROBLEM
WITH THIS PLAN.
IT'S ONLY 8:30.
(Audience laughing)
8:30, AND YOU CAN HARDLY
STAY AWAKE.
THAT IS PATHETIC.
IF YOU HAVE ANY HOPE
OF STAYING UP AFTER 9 O'CLOCK,
YOU'LL HAVE TO TAKE A NAP
IN THE AFTERNOON.
THIS CAN BE INCONVENIENT
UNLESS YOU WORK
FOR THE GOVERNMENT,
BUT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO FIND
A WAY TO DO IT.
IN THE OLD DAYS,
YOU'D STAY UP ALL NIGHT
AND GO STRAIGHT IN TO WORK.
YOU'D SPEND A WEEKEND PARTYING
AND YOU'D NEVER LIE DOWN --
AT LEAST, NOT FOR SLEEPING.
THE SLEEP YOU NEED NOW
IS TO MAKE UP FOR THE REST
YOU DIDN'T GET BACK THEN.
SO RELAX AND HAVE A NAP.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause)
OH, MAN, CAN'T TAKE
ANY MORE OF THAT.
"THE BUSTER HADFIELD HOUR".
SIXTY MINUTES OF ZITHER MUSIC.
YOU'D HAVE TO BE AN IDIOT
TO LISTEN TO THAT.
(Zither music playing)
WHAT? WHAT?
AFTER THE FIRST WEEK,
THE GUYS HAD PRETTY WELL SAID
EVERYTHING THEY COULD THINK OF.
A LOT KEPT TALKING ANYWAY.
OTHERS SWITCHED
TO DIFFERENT KINDS OF MUSIC.
SOME STARTED GETTING GUESTS
ON THEIR SHOWS.
I GOT GUESTS ON MY SHOWS.
I GOT KATHIE LEE GIFFORD
AND I GOT G. GORDON LIDDY.
THE TOPIC IS HOBBIES.
YOU GOT THEM FOR SURE?
NO, I LEFT AN E-MAIL MESSAGE
ON THE INTERNET.
I'M HOPING SOMEONE
RELAYS IT TO THEM.
I UNDERSTAND REGIS IS WIRED.
(Audience laughing)
ANYWAY, OUR PHONE SYSTEM
HAS TURNED INTO A RADIO STATION
WITH THE WORST PROGRAMMES
YOU EVER HEARD IN YOUR LIFE.
MOOSE THOMPSON'S SHOW IS
"WHAT I ATE TODAY".
"STINKY PETERSON,
UP CLOSE AND HAZARDOUS."
"THE OLD MAN SEDGWICK
INSPIRATIONAL HOUR."
I HEARD THAT ONE.
DOES HE SPEAK LATIN
OR DID HE HAVE HIS TEETH OUT?
I DON'T MIND COMPETITION,
BUT THESE GUYS ARE TAKING IT
SO SERIOUSLY.
THERE'S ONE WAY TO FIX IT.
YOU COULD HAVE THE PHONE
SYSTEMS REPAIRED
AND CANCEL ALL THE SHOWS.
NO, NOT ALL THE SHOWS, HAROLD.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HAVE
A SENSE OF THE RATINGS,
BUT I OWN THURSDAY NIGHT.
"RED'S E-Z LISTENING
HARMONICA HOUSE."
(Audience laughing)
HEY, BUZZ SHERWOOD
WITH SAFETY FIRST!
(Shouting)
... RINGING THE BELLS!
DON'T YOU WORRY, NO WAY!
THERE WILL BE
BLOOD EVERYWHERE!
SO, POINT IS, HOLD THE GUN,
SHOOT IT...
(Shouting)
OK!
HI, GORD.
OH, HI, RED.
I'D LOVE TO TALK,
BUT IT IS 50 CENTS.
WHAT THE HECK
YOU GOT GOING ON HERE?
WITH THE BUDGET CUTS
AT THE FORESTRY DEPARTMENT,
I'M HELPING THEM BRIDGE
THE FINANCIAL CRUNCH.
THEY HAVEN'T SENT ME
A PAYCHEQUE IN OVER A DECADE.
THAT'S A HUGE FUNDING GAP.
THAT WOULD BE
A COMMUNICATION GAP.
WHAT DO I GET FOR 50 CENTS,
ANYWAY?
WELL, GENERAL INFORMATION,
MOSTLY,
BUT ALSO FIRE DANGER REPORTS,
WEATHER REPORTS,
AND A BEAUTIFUL,
BREATH-TAKING VIEW
FROM HIGH ATOP
FIRE WATCH-TOWER 13.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL BITE.
YOU GOT 50 CENTS, HAROLD?
COME ON.
THERE WE GO.
GREAT.
AND 50 CENTS FOR HAROLD.
COME ON, HAROLD.
HAVEN'T GOT IT.
SORRY, HAROLD,
CAN'T USE THE STAIRS.
GO UP THE OUTSIDE.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
WOW!
YOU'RE MY FIRST CUSTOMER
TODAY, RED.
GORD, I'M
YOUR ONLY CUSTOMER EVER.
I COULD PROBABLY GET
QUITE A FEW TOURISTS.
PEOPLE LOVE TO CLIMB
HIGH TOWERS.
LOOK AT
THE WASHINGTON MONUMENT,
THE EIFFEL TOWER,
STATUE OF LIBERTY...
OR THE C.N. TOWER IN TORONTO.
THERE'S A TOWER IN TORONTO?
OH, YEAH.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
THEY'LL HAVE A BASEBALL TEAM.
WELL, THEY DID FOR A WHILE.
(Whistling)
OH, HAROLD, FINALLY!
WELCOME.
THANKS FOR DROPPING IN, HAROLD.
WHAT NOW, RANGER GORD?
WELL, FIRST, THE FIRE
SAFETY REPORT -- IT'S LOW.
NEXT, THE WEATHER REPORT --
IT'S FINE, GREAT.
SOUVENIR SHOP IS OPEN.
RANGER GORD DOLL...
OH, BOY, WHAT'S THAT?
THAT'S MY TOWER.
HOLY SMOKE.
NOTHING FOR ME, THANKS, GORD.
I'LL GIVE A SHORT TALK
ON THE HISTORY
OF FIRE WATCH-TOWER 13.
OH, MAN, NO, I'VE ALREADY HAD
MY 50 CENTS' WORTH.
THANK YOU, GORD.
OH, OK, GREAT.
(Coins rattling)
IT'S THE EASIEST MONEY
I
EVER MADE.
IT'S THE ONLY MONEY
I EVER MADE.
ATTENTION, HANDYMEN.
IF A PIECE OF METAL'S TOO LONG,
YOU CAN SHORTEN IT
WITH TIN SNIPS.
REMEMBER, ANY TOOL
CAN BE THE RIGHT TOOL.
MAN!
(Laughing)
WHAT IS IT WITH PEOPLE?
C.B. WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
A FUN WAY TO COMMUNICATE.
SOMEBODY FIGURES OUT
A WAY TO MAKE MONEY
AND EVERYBODY STARTS
TAKING IT TOO SERIOUSLY.
NO MATTER WHAT IT IS IN LIFE,
WHEN MONEY'S INVOLVED,
IT'S NOT FUN ANY MORE.
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY --
YOU'RE MARRIED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS
BUT MAKE SURE
I'M OUT OF THE BUILDING
BEFORE YOU PLUG IT IN.
IT'S A SIGNAL BOOSTER.
I'M MAKING IT OUT OF
MY OLD "CLOSE AND PLAY".
IT'S GONNA INCREASE THE REACH
OF "HAROLD'S HIP-HOP SOCK HOP".
THAT'S GONNA MAKE
MY SPONSOR HAPPY.
YOU GOT A SPONSOR?
WHAT? ACNE CREAM?
NO, NO, STODGY'S PICKLES --
THE OLD-FASHIONED-EXPERIENCE
PICKLE.
THE PICKLE
THAT KEEPS ON GIVING.
EVERYBODY'S TAKING IT
SO SERIOUSLY,
GETTING GUESTS,
GETTING SPONSORS.
THE GUESTS WANT BUS FARE
AND DOUGHNUTS.
THEN THEY NEED
BIGGER AUDIENCES.
THEY'RE STARTING
TO WELD LADDERS TOGETHER
SO THEY GOT A BIGGER ANTENNA.
THEY'RE PUTTING CLOTHESLINES
WITH STOVE WIRES ON THEM.
IT'S GETTING TO BE A REAL PAIN.
HAVE YOU SEEN
JIMMY GRISSLE'S SHOW?
IT'S CALLED "SHOCK RADIO",
AND IT'S SHOCKING, TOO.
IT'S WORSE THAN THE NAMES
KIDS CALL ME ON THE SCHOOL BUS.
YOU BEEN EATING
TOO MANY PICKLES.
NOT JUST ANY PICKLES --
STODGY'S PICKLES.
PICKLES GROWN IN THE SHADE
FOR A GREENER GREEN
AND A MORE NATURAL FLAVOUR.
NOW, THERE'S A SLOGAN.
STODGY'S PICKLES, FOR PEOPLE
WHO WANT A PICKLE
WHERE THE SUN DON'T SHINE.
HI, RANGER GORD HERE.
MAIL SERVICE HERE IS NOT GREAT.
IN THE 16 YEARS I'VE BEEN HERE,
I HAVEN'T RECEIVED
ONE PAYCHEQUE.
MOM, NONE OF YOUR LETTERS
GOT THROUGH.
RED HAS ALLOWED ME
TO USE THIS AIR TIME
TO SEND YOU A PERSONAL MESSAGE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
MOM, SINCE I LEFT,
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN ON MY MIND,
BUT I NEVER ASKED.
DID I LEAVE THE KETTLE ON?
(Red): AS I TRIED TO WARN YOU,
BILL HAD DECIDED TO DEDICATE
HIS RADIO PROGRAMME
TO... BOWLING.
NOT REALLY THE IDEAL GAME,
I WOULD THINK,
TO PLAY ON THE RADIO,
BUT THEN AGAIN, I'M NOT BILL,
AND I'M THANKFUL FOR THAT.
YEAH, HE'S BROADCASTING LIVE
FROM THE BACK
OF POSSUM LODGE...
AS LIVE AS HE GETS,
WHICH IS WAY TOO LIVE.
I MADE A FEW COMMENTS,
CHARACTER ASSASSINATION,
THAT TYPE OF THING.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
HE'S GONNA SET UP THE PINS.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
A BOWLING GAME.
I HAD HIS RADIO FOR HIM.
VARIOUS WEIGHTS OF THE BALLS.
THERE'S A VERY LIGHT ONE.
ANYWAY, YOU GOT
SOME FIVE-PIN BALLS
MIXED IN WITH THOSE, BILL.
THAT'S A 10-PIN BALL.
WHY DON'T YOU PUT THAT DOWN?
OH, BOY.
YOU WANT TO SIT DOWN--
YOU WANT TO STAY WELL BACK.
YOU THREW THAT STRAIGHT UP.
IT WILL BE BACK SOON.
OH, MY.
OUCH! OHHH!
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD.
WE BROKE HIS RADIO,
SO WE'RE MAKING PROGRESS.
I'LL GET THAT, BILL.
OH, BOY, OH, BOY!
SITTING OUT IN THE SUN,
THE BLACK BALLS ABSORB HEAT.
THE BALLS ALMOST CHANGE
THEIR FORM.
GOT KIND OF SPONGY ON US
AND...
OH MY GOSH.
BIG CLEAN-UP JOB?
OH, JUST WIPE THAT...
NEVER MIND.
ALL RIGHT, WE CREATED
SOME SHADE WITH A LAWN CHAIR.
BILL GRABS A 10-PIN BALL.
THE THING WITH BOWLING, SOME
PEOPLE FEEL THEY HAVE TO CHEAT.
WHAT ABOUT THE FOUL--
BILL, THE FOUL--
WE HAVEN'T GOT A FOUL LINE.
THAT'S CHEATING.
YOU GOTTA PUT SOMETHING--
GRAB THE PITCHFORK,
GRAB THE PITCHFORK.
NOW YOU JUST DON'T GO BY THAT.
BILL THOUGHT
THAT'S WAY TOO DANGEROUS.
OH!
HE THOUGHT HE WOULD MAYBE
TAKE THE DANGEROUS PART
OFF THE PITCHFORK.
THAT'S CALLED THE TINES,
SO HE WAS...
IF YOU HAD SOME LINE-DANCE
MUSIC GOING RIGHT NOW,
YOU'D SWEAR
YOU WERE WATCHING T.N.N.
HE'S TRYING TO GET
THE HANDLE OFF,
AND THERE SHE GOES.
OH, HERE COMES
THE HANDLE -- OW!
I CAN CARRY THE FLAG
IN THE PARADE NOW.
ALL RIGHT, SO THERE'S OUR LINE.
I DON'T KNOW --
I THINK 10-PIN IS JUST
TOO RIGOUROUS FOR ME.
THE PINS ARE TOO FAR AWAY.
BILL, LOTS OF JUICE.
LET 'ER GO!
OH! OH! OH!
HEAD DOWN THE RAVINE...
I GUESS-- UH-OH!
STINKY'S CAR!
MAN! MAN!
TOUGH TO EXPLAIN.
LET'S COUNT OUR SCORE.
BILL, YOU'VE GOT --
LET'S SEE -- TWO STRIKES.
I GOT A SPARE.
STAY TUNED
TO SEE HAROLD LISTENING
TO HIS SONY "DORK-MAN".
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL,
WITH ANOTHER FEATURE
ON ANIMALS IN YOUR LIFE.
COME ON IN, RED.
WHERE DID YOU GET THE HAND?
MIME SCHOOL?
I WAS PULLING RATS
OUT OF A BASEMENT SEWER TRAP.
MY WATCH BAND CAME OFF.
RATS REALLY LIKE SHINY THINGS.
I HAD TO GIVE ONE A BITE
TO GET IT BACK.
THAT SOUNDS AWFUL DANGEROUS.
NO, JUST ANOTHER SUPER DAY
ON THE JOB.
FOR YOU KIDS WHO MAY BE GOING
TO COLLEGE, HERE'S AN EXAMPLE
OF WHAT A FINE ARTS DEGREE
CAN DO FOR YOU.
GOT AN ANIMAL FEATURE?
HUH?
ANIMAL FEATURE?
OH, OH, OH, YES.
GEESE, CANADA GEESE.
SURE.
MAGNIFICENT BIRD,
BEAUTIFUL FLYER,
BUT BOY, THEY GOT
A LARGE INTESTINE
LIKE A SAUSAGE MACHINE.
I GOTTA GET A PACK OF THEM
OUT OF POSSUM PARK.
EVERYBODY'S COMPLAINING
ABOUT THE GEESE IN THE PARK.
ABOUT EATING THE GRASS
AND DROPPINGS AND WHATNOT?
MORE THAT THE MEAT IS SO TOUGH
AND REAL GREASY.
IT'S SOMETIMES HARD TO SWALLOW.
I'M GONNA FORGET I HEARD THAT.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
GIVE ME A HAND.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WITH THE GEESE?
I'M TAKING 'EM
TO MY BOSS'S HOUSE.
HE AND HIS WIFE
ARE ON VACATION.
HE ORDERED ME TO CUT HIS GRASS.
THAT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA.
THEY'RE FILTHY ANIMALS,
YOU KNOW.
OH, I KNOW, RED,
BUT SO ARE THE GEESE.
(Applause and cheering)
IT'S "MALE CALL"!
(Applause)
ALL RIGHT.
I GOT... I GOT THE LETTER
TODAY AND...
OH! OH! OH!
GOT SOME PICTURES, HAROLD.
YOU TAKE THE LETTER.
ALWAYS LOVE IT WHEN PEOPLE SEND
PICTURES OF THEIR CAMPING TRIPS
OR FISHING TRIPS
OR HANDYMAN PROJECTS.
IT MAKES US FEEL BETTER
ABOUT THE STUFF WE MESS UP.
WELL, ALL RIGHTY, APPARENTLY--
NO, NO, NO, LET ME GUESS.
NOT THE GREATEST PICTURES.
LOOKS LIKE A WILD ANIMAL.
COULD BE A SEA CREATURE
OF SOME KIND.
"DEAR RED, HERE ARE PICTURES
"OF MY WIFE GIVING BIRTH
TO OUR DAUGHTER."
OH MY GOSH!
I DON'T WANT TO SEE THAT!
WHAT?
OHHHHH!
TAKE A LOOK!
NO! NO!
THAT'S A... BIRTH IS BEAUTIFUL.
OHHH! OH! OH! OH! OH!
LOOK AT THAT!
OH! OH! OH! OH!
(Laughing)
WHOA!
BOY, OH BOY, LOOK AT THAT!
OHHH!
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL,
REMINDING YOU THAT THE BEST WAY
TO SPOT ANIMALS
IS BY STUDYING
THE TRACKS THEY LEAVE.
THE WORST WAY IS BY...
STUDYING THEIR... BITE MARKS.
(Static on radio)
WELL, THE POSSUM LODGE
RADIO STATION
IS OFFICIALLY OFF THE AIR
AS OF MIDNIGHT LAST NIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU LISTENING TO,
HAROLD?
NOTHING.
I KNOW -- POSSUM RADIO NETWORK
SHUT DOWN.
OH, OK.
HOW LONG WERE YOU GONNA LISTEN
TO DEAD AIR, HAROLD?
HOW LONG WERE YOU GONNA TALK?
(Audience laughing)
(Applause and cheering)
NOT EASY WHEN YOU GOT HIM
ON ONE SIDE
AND THE GOVERNMENT
ON THE OTHER.
THAT'S WHAT KILLED
THE RADIO STATION.
I BUILT A HUGE TRANSMITTER.
I DUCT-TAPED BAGS OF CHRISTMAS
TINSEL TO A DOUGLAS FIR.
WAS I GETTING A SIGNAL
OUT THERE.
I WAS GETTING CALLS
FROM TIBET, TIMBUCTU,
AND, UNFORTUNATELY, OTTAWA.
THE GOVERNMENT WANTED TO KNOW
IF I HAD
A BROADCASTER'S LICENCE.
I SAID I GOT
A LEARNER'S PERMIT.
WE SHOULD GET
A LICENCE.
WE COULD HAVE
OUR OWN STATION.
I DON'T WANT THE GOVERNMENT
IN MY LIFE.
I DON'T NEED ANYBODY ELSE
TELLING ME WHAT TO DO.
OK, FORGET THAT, THEN.
WE SHOULD GET
A TELEVISION
STATION.
I WANT TO HAVE FUN.
I DON'T CALL TELEVISION FUN.
YOU DON'T
CALL THIS FUN?
I DON'T CALL THIS TELEVISION.
(Possum squeal)
IT'S MEETING
TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
NOW THAT I'M NOT
IN THE RADIO BUSINESS --
I'M NO LONGER KING
OF THURSDAY NIGHT --
MAYBE I CAN GO BACK TO BEING
PRINCE OF SATURDAY MORNING.
FOR THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Whistling)
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): ALL RISE.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Harold): THERE YOU GO.
ANYONE DRIVING A 1986 CAR
OR NEWER,
RAISE BOTH HANDS LIKE THAT.