Sure we all have worries and
troubles and things that are wrong with the
world, but it's time to put trivial things
like meaning and relevance assign.
It's time you join us here at Possum Lodge
for a simpler time with simpler people,
especially Dwayne.
And now it's my pleasure to introduce the
star of the show and my uncle, which nobody
can do anything about. I'm very happy to say
that much.
It gives me a comfort. Here he is, the star
of the Red Green Show Mr.
Red Green.
Carol, thank you and welcome to Possum Lodge
for those of you who have never met Harold.
Save yourselves while there's still time.
Harold actually controls a lot of the
technical stuff on the show here.
That's through the the magic of digital
electronics, such as the following
Harold is responsible for the look of the
show.
I don't know who's responsible for the look
of Harold.
Maybe doofus are us.
I dress like you.
So we look alike. We look alike.
I better see an orthodontist
Gives us a lot. Look, it's cool.
Well, it leaves me cold, but not as cold as I
was last night.
I'll tell you. After dinner, Moose Thompson
got into one of those moods where he stands
in the middle of the floor and does things
with eggs.
And after they'd all broke.
Well, you know, the ball started rolling.
So on, we all ended up down at the dock
playing bobbing for surprises where everybody
drops their pants and tries to guess the
temperature of the lake.
I'll tell you, Buster Hatfield came that
close and a bunch of us went out on the large
party boat, which is a vessel we'd made
ourselves out of stuff as a garbage man
wouldn't take. It's kind of like a Chinese
junk without the word Chinese.
You guys are crazy to go out on that thing.
It's not seaworthy.
It's not even noteworthy.
Well, I think the problem was that where most
people fill their pontoons with air or or
styrofoam or tennis balls, our pontoons were
full of water, which apparently doesn't
float. It mixes.
I'm just saying, I figure you
Guys are very lucky that none of you drown
when that platoon of of death decided to
sink.
Yeah. Well, the non swimmers were OK because
they had the fear and the adrenaline which
allowed them to realize we were only in five
feet of water, whereas a swimmer just had
their heads down. They were just, you know,
stroking for shore, which is not that easy.
When your pants pockets are full of catfish
and your flannel button holes are snagging on
the bottom like no more floating parties,
huh?
It's a dark day for the brewery.
Anyway, we got a great show for you tonight,
so let's just get that started, Harold.
You know, we may be the only lodge in the
world that has a party submarine.
Oh, Glenn, how are things down at your
marina, your boat servicing boat, repairing
Marina, what fine?
I guess, I guess I didn't actually open
today.
I was up pricing the new RV.
Yep. I'm going to go into the 30 footer.
Yeah. Six extra feet.
Double air. Seven on wheels.
Glenn, do you remember working on our pontoon
boat this spring?
The lunch party. Oh, yes, sure.
You don't see two of those in a lifetime.
It's at the bottom of Possum Lake.
Oh, going to try to collect on the insurance
company, are we thinking, Doug?
No, no, we're going to collect from you.
Excuse me. Well, it's your fault.
You were supposed to fix the holes in the
pontoons.
Why do you think stinky Peterson brought it
To your marina?
Well, nobody told me that.
I thought it fell off the garbage scow.
I assume you remember writing you a check for
fifty dollars.
What was that about storage?
Sure, I should have charged him more.
The smell coming out of that bilge was bad
for my business.
We thought you had fixed the patches in the
pontoons, but as far as I'm concerned, you're
responsible and you're going to have to make
good on it.
What is he talking about?
Liability, Gleno?
No, you see this kind of thing all the time
when I was doing paralegal work for the DA's
office. Wow, is there anything you haven't
done doc now about Tell the truth.
Okay, fine. Fine, Douglas, suit yourself.
I was just trying to be of help here.
You know, I could prosecute this case on
real and applied liability with all the
tenants and caveats associated thereto,
which interrupted our party of the first part
hereafter referred to as the picnic.
But to yourself, your caveat?
Wow, boy. A lawyer and a doctor, you must
have been school a long time.
Thirty two years, you know,
I think waiting for a point would be a poor
investment of our time.
So why don't we try and reach an amicable
way to settle this?
I'm pretty amicable the way it's been
settled, Douglas man.
I think Douglas is trying to say that party
boat went down was your fault and we'd like
you to pay for it. I mean, I must have some
other idea.
Well, yeah, sure, actually. Firstly, not my
fault.
Secondly, you're all lucky to be alive.
And thirdly, I think we should start
thinking about a dry dock party boat a lot
less dangerous.
Blank what?
Oh, I don't know. How about a twenty four
foot RV, huh?
Pretty good, right down by the water.
Yeah, I was thinking of trading up anyway.
We can't afford an RV.
Oh, that's what I thought.
That's what I
Thought. But they financed me over thirty
five years.
All you guys
Have to do is pick up the last twenty seven
years of payments.
Well, high finance, a little over my
threshold of boredom or something you might
think about is raising the party vote up off
the bottom, you know, like like fishing for
Moby Dick?
Call me Ishmael.
I had similar sort of experience raising the
Titanic.
Perhaps you read the book? Yeah.
Well, we decided we'd try to photograph the
bottom by filling it with air.
Luckily, they had you along.
I like the RV concept.
I'm not going
To let it go at this, Glenn.
You'll be hearing from our lawyer.
Will you be at the marina this afternoon?
Glenn didn't mean you.
He's changing lawyers already.
That's a bad sign.
Late last night, there was a knock on my
door.
It was a bunch of aliens, many of whom I'd
never seen before.
They looked like us, but they didn't ask me
for our money.
And that's how I knew they were aliens.
This week, Matt Varner is going to show you
how to make a Webster for Up North, designed
by a guy down east.
And the first thing you need is a couple of
these vinyl plastic tablecloths.
And the second thing you need is one of
these electric glue guns.
I'll just plug this in if you don't, if you
don't have one of these glue guns, by golly,
they are a terrific investment.
They say, they say, OK, I'm real hot, sticky
glue, and you can use them to caulk around a
window if, say, if you never wanted to open
that window again.
Or you can do for decorating cakes, you
know, or you know, you can just take the glue
right out of there and it makes a dandy
little soldering iron.
It's also real if you've got if you got good
handwriting, you can use them the brand
cattle. Only downside is they take a little
while to heat up.
It's all right.
I guess it's ready. So now we just put a
glue stick in the end there and order up.
And we're ready to start gluing it just
comes real easy.
That's what's wrong.
Oh no, that's
That's a piece of char produced exclusively.
There they are. They are not always happy.
Well, here's one. Ok, so we stick to stick
the glue stick in there, and then you just
give it a little squeeze. And Oh, oh, oh,
all right.
Well, I'll clean that up later.
Ok. Next thing you want to do is you want to
spread the right one of the tablecloths out
on the floor and you want to lie down on it
and trace around yourself.
Spread your arms out. This is something that
may seem a little bit awkward, but it's not
that hard to do.
Ok.
You just start just crazed right around.
It should make a mark.
Oh, that's a glow stick.
There we go.
Scared me for a minute there, right around
yourself, and it's an unusual talent, but it
can come in handy if you ever get shot.
And, you know, leave her leave a little bit
extra room so that the raincoat doesn't fit
too tight. Sorry about the view, but right
up over your head.
And leave a space for your hands.
You're done.
And there's basically my shape when I could,
I could stand to lose a little weight there.
Anyway, now you cut that out and then you
put that on top of the other plastic sheet
and that becomes your form and then you've
got your raincoat on your way.
Ok, now you can just cut along the chalk
line using a pair of scissors or tin snips,
or if everybody's borrowed, all your stuff
never brought it back.
You may have to use some tree pruning
shears.
All right, we're through there, and I want
you done that.
You can start sewing the coat together with
the glue gun.
Just be sure that you leave the bottom open
where your legs are going to stick out and
leave the ends of the sleeves open or your
hands come through and you go right up around
the head, though. Another thing, too, is
just be careful.
You don't glue a coat to the floor or
yourself, to the coat
Or
The coat to say the table, or, more
importantly, that you don't glue any of your
really important body parts to the actual
glue gun.
I managed to find Bernie's sewing scissors,
which I'm using the cut a hole for the face.
But now you're over code.
You know, what I've done here is I've added
a couple of accessories to kind of enhance
the look and make the functionality, is that
much more?
I think the pieces of the inner tube I'm
using as epilepsy give it kind of a navel
look. I think we've used some cupboard
handles out of the kitchen, for sure.
A little bit. And then you've got the
sandwich bags here for pockets.
We're going to keep your car keys fresh, and
it's kind of a kind of a unisex design.
I mean, a man or a woman could wear this and
you'd have no idea what it was.
And then you got the pride factor, too of
knowing that that you made this yourself.
This is a one off to remember.
The women don't find you handsome.
They should at least find your handy.
I'm sweating like a pig in this thing.
So.
It is spring trout season.
You wade into the stream waist high, you
feel water, run down your legs.
There's a hole in your hip waders, you hope.
So anyway, Douglas is pretty upset about
Glenn's lack of interest in the party boat
shemozzle, and when Douglas gets mad, he's
kind of like a terrier, especially with that
short hair has a nose, funny ears.
Now, old man Sedgwick says he thinks we
should buy the RV, but Moose Thompson says,
No, no, no, you're going to have a party
vote.
It should be a vote of some kind.
What he wants to do is just rip the dock
right off the cribbing and lay it across 40
canoes. But then you really have to catch
moose before noon if you hope to get any
sense out of them.
I don't understand why you just can't have
the parties up at the lodge on terra firma as
it were. What's the big deal about a party
boat?
Oh, well, there's a historical significance
to to a floating celebration.
You know, it harkens back to the time of,
say, like Cleopatra or or Moses or or even
the crew of the Exxon Valdez.
Anyway, and Douglas is so mad at Glenn that
he's talking about taking our large boat
business elsewhere.
I also Glenn's got the only marine on the
lake where we're going to get our Bow Street
fair, the bakery.
Don't be surprised if you see Douglas opening
a new marina right here on Possum Lake.
Oh, that'll be great for the environment.
More leaky gas pumps.
Well, there's no fire hazard, Harold.
The gas goes right into the lake.
Oh, OK, then. Oh yeah, that's perfect.
I'll go ahead. Oh.
Is this where the party boat sank?
Not.
Yeah, see that that red, green and blue glow.
Oh yeah, yeah.
The Patio Lanterns are still lit down there.
Yeah. And you can see the outline of the
boat, too.
Yeah. And it looks like a blurry Christmas
tree.
This is great. Well, you know, small mouth
bass go crazy for bright colors.
Oh yeah. You guys ever use a rain bowl for
bait?
You mean you mean a rainbow trout?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Rainbow trout. Hey.
Doesn't matter anyway, I guess.
Drop anchor here, Harold and mines don't hit
none of those band instruments down there.
All right. Well, there you go again.
Oh, noise.
You know, it's it's not very far down there,
doc.
We could maybe raise her up. What do you
think?
Oh, dangerous rat. Very dangerous.
Yeah, yeah.
One of us would have to go diving down
there, and there's a good chance we'd get the
falls.
The fall. You mean the bands on, you
Know, no, no.
Your phones and what you get and you're
fresh one, they're far worse.
I never even heard of the full stock.
All that happened to me.
Oh yeah. Oh, I don't like to talk about it.
Oh, good.
That was a number of years back when I was
leading that, that expedition to raise that
Spanish galleon off of Bermuda.
I don't remember, but you telling me you went
treasure hunt.
Did you find the pirate treasure there?
Well, if I did read, you think I'd be hanging
around the lodge now?
Yeah, yeah. I don't get it in Bath.
Usually love to nest in barbecue.
What kind of I kind of treasure.
Where are you looking
For anything in particular?
Oh, pirates gold. Oh yeah.
Pieces of sixty four.
All that pieces of eight squared.
Yeah. The Spanish treasure ship Santa St
Nicholas went off course on Lake Erie and
sank.
I thought you said it was Bermuda.
Could I not say she went off course right
now?
Something a little special.
Sweet on eventually bill.
We're going to go sailing. They brought the
sailing bags down there and they get the
sails out and get it from a wide open
feather.
Is there anyone that's not a sail bag?
That's that's his pillow cap?
Here's a serious like primer sail bag and
starts taking the sail out there.
And you know it's folded a certain way.
So they're all kind of comes out because
suddenly sails are they can get pretty big on
you.
Yeah.
Well, you figure it, you know, and that's the
only power for the boat song.
You know, you're going to expect the sale to
be, you know, pretty decent, pretty decent
size. And probably be about a tear, I would
think.
Yeah, that'll be it. No, no, no, there's a
bit more.
It's a pretty big, it's a pretty big sail.
He's got there. Where are we going to get
much?
Well, you know, golly, there's a lot of
work, all the sailing, you know, when you get
these big sails, all kind of rigged and
everything.
And anyway, so now Bill is going to.
Step one is to close the hatch, you know, OK,
he's fine.
So now this is called, I think it's called a
halyard or something hook that on itself,
what he did is he hooked it right through
his suspender.
There's of course, none of us knew that, and
I was just I
Had my head down. I'm pulling up on it and
then I didn't, you know, it's not really my
fault. I don't think because he told me,
just pull.
And then I look up.
And of course, yes, although I can see no
problem.
So now he's trying to rig the rig, the sail,
and it was a windy day, you know, and I
thing, well, this is that that thing's
moving around, and I've heard of people
sometimes getting hit with that and what
have you.
But Bill seem to have the least.
I thought he had it now, and I, you know, I
always assumed Bill Bill knows what he's
doing. I I think I think that's kind of
foolish on my part.
So by now, I had gone to.
So this is fun for me because actually I,
you know, in all the years that I've done
most of our voting and what have you?
Even rowing the canoe and when when I had
to, I never had done any sailing.
So this is real fun for me.
And of course, my attention was drawn
completely to the sails, and I really wasn't
noticing that I had a bit of a tow away.
So anyway, Douglas has got dark and stinky,
all hyped up about opening this Marina Stinky
is going to pump gas and clean out the
bilgisayar, and that should eliminate all but
the most desperate customers.
I mean, nobody browses when stinky is behind
the counter, and Moose has offered to run the
dolphin show. But like I said, if it's
afternoon, you really have to take moose with
a grain of aspirin. Excuse me, but
Does it not matter that Douglas nor dock nor
stinky have any marina knowledge or business
acumen? Is that a consideration at all?
Well, it's not really a complex situation
here, Harold.
I mean, you just sell people stuff for more
than a cost you.
Yes, but we won't be
Able to get any service.
We don't get any now.
Well, OK. All right.
Well, what's the sense of having like
Two useless marinas?
At least you have a choice.
Oh, that's the sound in the meeting.
We've got to go uncle. Read time to go.
Well, this won't take long, you know, and it
doesn't.
It doesn't take men long to make a decision.
It's making the decision look smart.
That takes the time.
Oh, boy, oh boy.
Great, great.
All right.
How far is Douglas Henry, Jack?
Thank you, Brad. Well, everyone, I'm
delighted to report that stinky and I are
ready to open the Possum Lake Marina.
Now we bought a 40 foot floating dock and a
two inch monkey wrench.
Wow.
Well, as the as the owner of the only Marina
In the area, I got to say that this lake
won't support two marinas, so which doesn't
matter to me as long as you guys buy my RV
and then I can buy a new one and get out of
here. So if you'll support my proposition RV
and just vote yes, sign there.
Thanks, Michel.
Yes, Judy. Well, I vote yes.
We need a new dry dock party boat or, you
know, an RV is an excellent investment.
Fellas who as long as you don't drive it.
Well, luckily, we can't afford an RV because
I had the good sense to empty the Lodge
Treasury when we purchased the floating duck
dock.
Hey, hey guys.
Let's do it.
Don't forget I gave him a good deal on the
rent while we needed a ranch.
That's well, no. Now just wait a minute.
Just one second here.
You spent large money on that.
We're trying to get a new party boat, but
into the marina business, right?
Yeah. Right now, too late.
Now the die is cast.
That floating dock is ours
On paper, at least making Douglas say, I
know.
Hold on, hold on.
What about this, everybody?
We scrap the whole marina idea and just take
the floating dock back.
All right. Wait a minute, fellas.
Randa, I bought that dog from Mary's store.
Oh, no, no, it's changed, that's our policy.
Ok, OK, OK, why don't we keep the floating
dock and use that as our new party boat?
Well, if we can tie it up, the Moose
Thompson that way won't let all those in
favor of doing that. Say Hi.
Ok. Motion carried.
So there's no further
Large business
About a real treat for you tonight.
Glenn has managed to get a mint copy of a
great movie.
The guns in Ann Romney's
Election, there was a bit of a problem with
the guns are have thrown.
It was already out. But as a substitute, I
got some.
I got some slides, some new slides that I
just got back.
Well, I'm glad we'll be getting a new party
vote and things can get back to normal.
Well, normal for the lodge.
It's amazing what's important as you get
older, isn't it?
I guess it's important for large members to
be out on the water a fair bit.
Think of us as floaters.
That's what plumbers would call us anyway.
My wife is watching. I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting and I'll have a bite
of whatever you leave me on the kitchen
table and then I'll climb the stairs.
And if there is nothing on the table, I'll
run up the stairs.
So until next time, on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole gang up here in Possum
Lodge, keep your stick on the ice.
Mcgrath, but it's decided it was good for
cutting along a hill like I mentioned gravity
there, it's good.
That's a lot. It's very dense bushland
dense, dense with grit against the road
running the Department of Highways.
That's who this guy works for.
Here they only go back 30 feet from the edge
of the road.
Yeah, 30 feet.
That's right. Oh, there we go.
There is breakfast does not a fine look and
look at that there.
That's that's your grilled cheese sandwich,
I think.
Yeah. Grilled cheese sandwich with lots of
big.
Those big thick. The real potatoes.