YOU KNOW,
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE
I LIKE TO DO A LITTLE FEATURE
FOR PEOPLE WHO ARE MAYBE
A LITTLE LESS FORTUNATE
THAN THE REST OF US.
FOR EXAMPLE, PUMPKIN
CARVING IS A LOT OF FUN,
BUT WHAT IF YOU'RE
ONE OF THOSE GUYS
WHO'S NOT ALLOWED
TO HAVE SHARP OBJECTS?
WELL, HERE'S WHAT YOU DO...
FIRST I TAKE
THIS GLUE STICK.
THEN I JUST
DRAW A SCARY FACE
RIGHT ONTO THE PUMPKIN.
NO HARM THERE.
JUST KEEP THE GLUE
AWAY FROM YOUR FACE.
AND DON'T INHALE.
THERE WE GO.
OKAY, NOW YOU JUST
EMPTY A FEW SHOTGUN SHELLS
TO MAKE A HARMLESS
LITTLE PILE OF GUNPOWDER.
NOW ALL YOU DO IS ROLL OL'
PUMPKIN HEAD FACE DOWN
INTO THE GUNPOWDER.
AND YOU'LL FIND THAT IT ONLY
STICKS WHERE YOU PUT THE GLUE.
OKAY, NOW ALL'S YOU
HAVE TO DO IS THE CARVING.
YOU MAY NOT WANNA STAND
TOO CLOSE FOR THIS PART,
UNLESS YOU'RE REAL
TIRED OF YOUR FACIAL HAIR.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT. APPRECIATE THAT.
A LOT OF PEOPLE DROPPED
BY THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
I WAS KINDA HOPING THEY MIGHT
STAY OVER A NIGHT OR TWO,
BUT THEY WERE JUST
STOPPING TO ASK DIRECTIONS
TO THE NEW PROVINCIAL PARK
UP BY PORT ASBESTOS.
THEY'RE JAMMED
TO THE EYEBALLS;
WE GOT NOBODY!
BOY, IT'S FRUSTRATING
WHEN THE GOVERNMENT
USES YOUR OWN MONEY
TO COMPETE WITH YOU.
MAKES ME FEEL A LOT BETTER
ABOUT NOT PAYING MY TAXES,
I TELL YOU.
UNCLE RED,
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I GOT A QUESTION.
WHAT'S THE EXACT WORDING
ON YOUR BIRTH CERTIFICATE?
MALE -- WHAT IS
IT ON YOURS?
IS THIS HOW YOU
SPELL YOUR FULL NAME?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'VE NEVER WRITTEN IT.
WHAT IS THAT
ANYWAY, HAROLD?
THIS? OH, IT'S NOTHING.
IT'S NOTHING.
JUST A LITTLE
CRAZY IDEA I HAD.
DO YOU MIND
SIGNING THE BOTTOM?
THIS ISN'T LIKE
AN APPLICATION TO
TURN THE LODGE
INTO A CHESS CLUB
OR SOMETHING, IS IT?
HA! NO, NO, NO.
PROVINCIAL PARK.
YEAH, THE ONE IN PORT
ASBESTOS IS WORKING SO WELL
THE GOVERNMENT'S LOOKING TO
OPEN ONE IN OUR AREA, MAYBE.
WELL, WE'D BE PERFECT
AS A PROVINCIAL PARK.
I MEAN, WE'RE IN
A PROVINCE,
AND WE GOT
PLACES TO PARK.
THEY MAY WANT TO
MAKE A FEW CHANGES,
LIKE TEAR DOWN THE LODGE
AND RUN THE WATER THROUGH A
SEWAGE TREATMENT FACILITY.
BUT THAT'S
ABOUT ALL, I THINK.
TEAR DOWN
THE LODGE!
I'M NOT LETTING THEM
DO ANYTHING TO THE LODGE.
THEY'VE ALLOCATED
$15 MILLION FOR
THE PROJECT!
WELL, GO! GO! GO!
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER WILL
RECEIVE A COUPON
FOR A FREE WASH, WAX
BUFF, SHINE AND LUBE JOB
FROM THE POSSUM LAKE
FITNESS CLUB!
OKAY, MR. GREEN --
COVER YOUR EARS.
YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS TO GET
DALTON TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, OKAY,
MIKE.
AND... GO!
ALL RIGHT, DALTON,
THIS IS EASY.
IF YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT SOMEBODY IS SAYING,
YOU TELL THEM
TO SPEAK...
ENGLISH!
OKAY, OKAY, WHEN YOU'RE
PLAYING BASEBALL SOMEBODY
WILL YELL, YOU'RE...
OUT.
NO, I MEAN THIS IS
YOUR TURN AT BAT.
SO WHAT DO YOUR
TEAMMATES SAY?
OH, NO.
OKAY, OKAY.
DALTON, THE VERY FIRST THING
YOU DID THIS MORNING
WAS TO GET...
YELLED AT BY ANN MARIE.
YEAH, BUT AFTER
THAT YOU GOT...
THE HECK OUTTA THE HOUSE.
GO ANOTHER
WAY WITH IT.
WHAT'S THE OPPOSITE
OF BEING DOWN?
BEING SINGLE.
UH, YOU'RE ALMOST
OUTTA TIME, MR. GREEN.
OKAY, YOU HEAR
THAT, DALTON?
TIME'S ALMOST...
ALMOST...
GONE!
TIME'S ALMOST GONE!
HURRY UP!
THERE WE GO!
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THIS IS WHERE WE ADDRESS
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
audience:
I DON'T KNOW!
YES, YOU DO,
'CAUSE THAT'S THEM.
OKAY, UM, TODAY'S
LETTER GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS --"
LA LA LA.
"DEAR EXPERTS, NOW
THAT I'M OLDER,
"I'VE NOTICED THAT
CERTAIN PARTS OF MY BODY
"DON'T FUNCTION AS
WELL AS THEY USED TO."
AH, FOR GOD --
"MY WIFE SAYS THERE'S NO SHAME
IN SEEKING MEDICAL ASSISTANCE,
"BUT I WANT YOUR ADVICE.
"SHOULD I GET
A HEARING AID?
SIGNED, PHIL."
IT'S OKAY.
HE JUST WANTS TO
GET A HEARING AID.
DOES THAT HELP?
IT'S FOR HIS EARS!
WHAT?
ALL RIGHT, YEAH, SURE,
YOU CAN GET A HEARING AID,
IF YOU WANT TO.
BUT IF YOU'RE
A MIDDLE-AGED GUY,
YOU KNOW, LIKE HOW MUCH
ARE YOU REALLY MISSING?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, AT OUR AGE NOBODY
COMES UP AND SAYS STUFF LIKE,
WOW! NICE ABS.
OR, WHERE'D YOU LEARN
TO PLAY GUITAR LIKE THAT?
OR, UH, WHAT DO YOU
THINK ABOUT ANYTHING?
YEAH, I AGREE
WITH RED.
I RECOMMEND SOMETHING
CALLED SELECTIVE HEARING.
YOU ONLY HEAR WHAT
YOU WANNA HEAR.
OH, THAT'S A
GREAT THEORY.
THAT'S A
TERRIBLE THEORY!
THANKS, RED.
PHIL, GET A HEARING AID.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO COMMUNICATE
YOUR EMOTIONS AND THOUGHTS
TO YOUR LOVED ONES.
YOU GOTTA STAY
IN THE LOOP.
THAT'S WHAT THE
HANG MAN USED TO SAY.
OKAY, LOOK, I YOU'RE
JUST KIDDING AROUND,
BUT DO HOPE YOU'LL GET
HEARING AIDS IF THE
TIME COMES.
WELL, I THINK
IF MY HEARING GOES,
I MAY GET A HEARING AID.
BUT, HAROLD, IF YOU GO,
I WILL DEFINITELY GET ONE.
YOU KNOW, THERE HAVE BEEN
A LOT OF GREAT INVENTIONS
OVER THE LAST 100 YEARS...
THE SPLITTING OF THE ATOM,
POLIO VACCINE.
BUT THE GREATEST ONE HAS TO
BE THE DRIVE-THRU RESTAURANT.
MAN, IF I COULD'VE TOLD MY
GREAT-GRANDFATHER
THAT THE DAY WOULD COME
WHEN THEY COULD STUFF
A HOT MEAL IN A BAG AND
TOSS IT IN YOUR CAR WINDOW,
HE'D JUST SHAKE HIS HEAD.
BUT I'M THINKING IT'S MAYBE
TIME TO TAKE IT TO THE
NEXT LEVEL.
INSTEAD OF A
DRIVE-THRU RESTAURANT,
WHERE YOU HAVE
TO GO WHERE THE FOOD IS,
WHICH CAN BE HUMILIATING
IF YOU'RE, SAY, ON FOOT,
OR WORSE STILL,
RIDING A BICYCLE.
I SUGGEST A
DRIVE-TO RESTAURANT,
WHERE THE FOOD ACTUALLY
DRIVES TO WHERE YOU ARE.
AND I'M NOT JUST TALKING
ABOUT PLAIN OLD DELIVERY,
WHERE ALL YOU GET IS SOGGY
FRIES AND LUKEWARM ATTITUDE.
I MEAN AN ACTUAL
KITCHEN ON WHEELS.
IT'S A MILLION-DOLLAR IDEA
THAT YOU CAN MAKE
OUT OF A $40 CAR.
NOW, SINCE WE'RE
TALKING TAKEOUT,
WE GOTTA START BY
TAKING OUT A FEW THINGS...
LIKE THESE SEATS.
NOW, IF YOU END UP USING
A LUXURY VEHICLE WITH
HEATED CUSHIONS,
YOU MIGHT THINK
ABOUT KEEPING THEM.
THEY MAKE GREAT
BUN WARMERS.
OKAY, NOW THAT
THE SEATS ARE GONE,
THE ONLY OTHER THING
I HAVE TO LOSE IS THE ROOF,
IF YOU DON'T COUNT
MY CREDIBILITY --
AND I'M SURE YOU DON'T.
OKAY, JUST GOTTA GET
THIS OUTTA THE WIND HERE.
OKAY, NOT QUITE SURE
WHAT HAPPENED THERE.
MUST'VE BLACKED OUT.
THE ROOF IS MISSING.
[ SOUND LIKE BOMB WHISTLING ]
OH, THERE IT IS.
OKAY, NOW THE NEXT STEP IS
TO INSTALL OUR GRILL HERE.
IT ONLY MAKES SENSE TO BE
COOKING OUR BURGERS
ON A BARBEQUE,
BUT WE'RE GONNA ACTUALLY TIE
IT IN TO THE FUEL LINE
OF THE CAR.
I'M NOT GOING TO NEED
THIS PROPANE TANK.
[ EXPLOSION ]
LOOKED EMPTY.
OKAY, BARBEQUE'S GOING TO
TAKE CARE OF THE BURGERS
AND HOT DOGS,
BUT FOR THE FRENCH FRIES,
I NEED SOMETHING THAT
WILL HOLD LOT MORE GREASE.
AND I DON'T MEAN
HAROLD'S COMB.
HOW ABOUT THE TANK FROM
AN OLD OIL FURNACE, HUH?
AND THE BEAUTY
OF THESE BABIES IS
THE LONGER'S SHE'S BEEN THERE,
THE EASIER IT IS TO DETACH.
OKAY, NOW,
FOR YOUR FRENCH FRIES,
YOU REALLY WANNA HAVE
THOSE PRE-CUT BEFORE
YOU HIT THE ROAD.
YOU COULD SLICE
'EM BY HAND,
BUT FOR A JOB THIS BIG,
I PREFER SOMETHING A
LITTLE FASTER,
LIKE, SAY, A WOOD CHIPPER.
NOW WE'RE COOKIN', HUH?
I'VE CYCLED THE ENGINE OIL
THROUGH THE FRYER,
SO THE SAME OIL THAT
KEEP THE ENGINE COOL
KEEPS THE FRYER HOT.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING,
IF YOU WANT THOSE GOLDEN
FRIES EVERYBODY LOVES,
10-W-30.
I'VE EVEN GOT
THESE FRYER BASKETS,
WHICH YOU CAN GET
FROM ANY GROCERY STORE.
ATTENTION, SHOPPERS:
YOUR FRIES ARE READY.
MEANWHILE, UP FRONT,
OUR BURGERS ARE PIPING HOT,
PERFECTLY BROILED, ALL READY
FOR OUR PREP STATION.
AND WHILE YOU'RE AT IT,
WHY NOT FILL THE CAR
RADIATOR WITH HOT COFFEE
AND THE HOOK IT UP TO A TAP
MOUNTED RIGHT HERE ON THE
DASHBOARD, HUH?
OH, YEAH.
OKAY, I MAY HAVE JUST ANSWERED
MY OWN QUESTION THERE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW, IF YOU'LL
EXCUSE ME,
I'VE GOT A
HUNGRY TOWN TO FEED.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, MOST MEN
ARE LITTLE VAGUE
ABOUT WHEN EXACTLY
MIDDLE AGE BEGINS.
IT'S GOT NOTHING TO DO
WITH YOUR CHRONOLOGICAL AGE.
DOESN'T MATTER IF
YOUR HAIR HAS GONE GREY,
GONE WHITE OR
GONE AWOL.
YOU HAVE OFFICIALLY
ARRIVED AT MID-LIFE
WHEN THE MOST IMPORTANT
ASPECT OF ANY ACTIVITY
IS COMFORT.
EXCITEMENT, ADVENTURE,
EVEN FINANCES ALL TAKE
A BACK SEAT TO COMFORT.
YOU DON'T CARE
ABOUT PHYSICAL FITNESS.
YOU WANT HEATING AND
AIR CONDITIONING.
YOU WANT PADDING,
ON YOUR FURNITURE,
ON YOUR PAYCHEQUE,
ON YOUR OWN BUTT.
EVEN YOUR LOVE LIFE
IS AFFECTED.
FORGET PASSION.
YOU'RE READY TO BE IN A
COMFORTABLE RELATIONSHIP,
YOU KNOW, WHERE NOBODY
YELLS AT ANYBODY,
WHERE NOTHING CHANGES,
AND NINE TIMES OUTTA TEN,
YOU FALL ASLEEP
BEFORE YOUR WIFE DOES.
YOUR WILD OATS HAVE
TURNED INTO WILD OAT BRAN.
AND AS MID-LIFE PROGRESSES,
YOU MAY EVENTUALLY
GET TO THE POINT
WHERE YOU'RE EVEN
COMFORTABLE WITH YOURSELF.
NOW, SOME PEOPLE
CALL THAT GIVING UP.
I CALL IT TRUE SUCCESS.
IF YOU CAN STAND IN FRONT OF
A MIRROR, A WIFE OR A BANKER
AND SAY, HEY, THIS IS
AS GOOD AS I GET,
THAT'S GOTTA BE
A COMFORTING THOUGHT --
FOR YOU,
NOT FOR THEM.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
announcer:
CHINESE KUNG PAO
CHICKEN WITH PEANUTS,
MEXICAN CHILI CRUST QUICHE,
WITH CHORIZO SAUSAGE,
INDIAN BENGALI
RED CURRY,
MOROCCAN NOODLES WITH CUMIN,
VIETNAMESE
PEPPER CASSEROLE,
TURKISH EGGPLANT GOULASH
WITH CURDED GOAT CHEESE,
ARGENTINEAN MARINATED
AARDVARK AND MORE...
IF THIS IS WHAT
YOU'RE EATING,
WE NEED TO TAKE A MEETING.
WELL, WE HEARD BACK
FROM THE GOVERNMENT
ON OUR PROVINCIAL PARK
APPLICATION.
THEY'RE GONNA SEND AN
INSPECTOR IN THREE DAYS
TO HAVE A LOOK
AT THE PLACE.
ACTUALLY, THE WHOLE TOWN IS
PRETTY DARNED SUPPORTIVE.
AS SOON AS THEY FOUND OUT
WE MAY TEAR THE LODGE DOWN,
BOY, THEY'RE ALL FOR IT.
HEY, RED, YOU WANTED
TO SEE US?
I NEED YOU TO OUT
THERE AND CLEAN UP
THE PROPERTY
AROUND THE LODGE BEFORE
THE INSPECTOR GETS HERE.
OKAY, WE'LL JUST THROW ALL
THE JUNK IN THE LAKE THEN.
NO, DON'T THROW
ALL OF IT IN,
'CAUSE IF THE LAKE
GETS UP TOO HIGH,
THE BOATS'LL SINK.
OKAY.
UH, WHAT IS THESE
INSPECTORS GONNA LOOK AT?
I MEAN, WILL THEY
BE INSPECTING OUR PERSONS?
I DON'T KNOW.
LET'S GO. LET'S GO.
OKAY, WELL, WHAT
ABOUT THOSE HOLES
THAT LOOK LIKE SOMETHING HAS
JUST BEEN BURIED RECENTLY?
I'M JUST ASKING.
IT'S NOT A SCAVENGER
HUNT, MIKE, OKAY!
THEY'RE GOING TO
LOOK AT THE BUILDINGS,
THE PROPERTY
AND THE LAKE.
COME ON, MIKE.
COME ON.
OKAY, WELL,
WILL THEY BE --
WILL THEY BE CHECKING
THE VEHICLES?
IF YOU GOT SOMETHING
IN YOUR VEHICLE,
MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST
STASH IT SOMEWHERE
FOR A WHILE.
OH, YEAH,
I DID.
I PUT IT IN THE
BACK OF YOUR VAN.
UNCLE RED, WE'VE GOT
A BIT OF A WRINKLE.
THE GUY FROM THE GOVERNMENT
SAYS THEY ONLY APPROVE
PLACES WHERE FAMILIES GO,
AND THIS IS A
BIT OF A MEN'S LODGE.
OKAY, HERE'S
WHAT WE DO...
OKAY, THE TOWN
IS BEHIND US, OKAY.
OKAY, SO YOU TELL ALL
THE WOMEN AND THE
CHILDREN
TO BE HERE ON
INSPECTION DAY.
YOU'RE OKAY WITH THAT?
YEAH, TELL 'EM NOT
TO TOUCH ANYTHING.
THEY WON'T WANNA
TOUCH ANYTHING.
DON'T WORRY.
Red (voice over):
DALTON AND THE GUYS ARE
PUTTING ON A CHARITY CAR WASH
AND MY CAR, WELL,
WASN'T REALLY FILTHY.
IT HAD A LITTLE
DUST ON HER,
AND I THOUGHT, MIGHT AS WELL
SUPPORT A LOCAL CHARITY.
THEY NEVER SET
THE PRICE ON THESE.
WHATEVER YOU GIVE 'EM,
THEY'RE USUALLY THANKFUL.
I FIGURED A LOONY
WOULD PROBABLY --
BE GRATEFUL FOR THAT.
THEN DALTON CALLS
EVERYBODY OFF,
SAYING THE LOONY DIDN'T
QUALIFY FOR THE FULL
TREATMENT,
AND THAT'S
APPARENTLY ALL I GOT.
SO I FIGURED I BETTER
TAKE HER UP A NOTCH OR TWO.
THIS'D BE MY
ANNUAL GIVING HERE.
THAT'S A CANADIAN 20;
ABOUT AN AMERICAN
ONE OR TWO, I BELIEVE.
SO AWAY THEY GO,
AND WALTER'S SOAPING HER UP,
AND WINSTON'S
GOT THE VACUUM CLEANER.
AND YEAH, THERE'S
SOME STUFF IN THERE.
GONNA FILL THAT
BABY UP PRETTY FAST.
I DON'T REALLY CLEAN THE
CAR OUT AS OFTEN AS I SHOULD.
OH, THERE -- NEED A
LITTLE MORE WATER PRESSURE,
SO DALTON'S SAYING
TO ME WOULD I --
I'D NEVER ACTUALLY SEEN
THE TYPE OF VALVE
THEY WERE USING.
ANYWAY, I JUST
PULLED HER BACK,
AND THERE'S A LOT
OF PRESSURE IN THERE.
AND, UH -- THEN OF COURSE,
THE HANDLE COME RIGHT OFF.
NOW THE HOSE IS --
NOW THE HOSE CAN DANCE AND
STARTS BANGING ON THE CAR.
AND WINSTON THINKS
SOMEBODY'S KNOCKIN' FOR HIM.
SO ANYWAY, HE'S GETTIN'
THE INSIDE OF HER,
AND THE VACUUM CLEANER'S
REALLY TAKIN' A --
GETTIN' A LITTLE
BIT BIGGER THERE.
TAKING ON A
FAIR BIT OF STUFF.
AND WALTER'S GOT HER --
NOW IT'S TIME TO RINSE,
SO DALTON AIMS THE --
SOMETHING WENT WRONG
WITH THE NOZZLE,
SO HE'S SHOOTING AT KIND
OF A 90-DEGREE TO THE RIGHT,
KIND OF LIKE
THE ALLIANCE PARTY.
AND SO WALTER GETS THE
IDEA IF HE STANDS HERE
AND DALTON AIMS AT HIM,
IT'LL GO SIDEWAYS,
AND IT'LL RINSE
OFF THE CAR.
AND DALTON'S
HESITANT TO DO IT,
BUT YOU KNOW
WALTER'S INSISTING.
HE FINALLY UNDERSTANDS.
BUT APPARENTLY IT HAD --
WHATEVER IT WAS HAD
CLEARED ITSELF OUT...
SO LATER THAT DAY,
WINSTON PRETTY
MUCH HAD HER FULL,
BUT BY NOW THE
VACUUM CLEANER --
WE'RE REALLY
STRAINING THE LIMITS
OF THAT PARTICULAR UNIT.
SHE'S GETTING TO
BE A REAL GOOD SIZE.
AND I FIGURED
I'D HAD ENOUGH.
SO I THOUGHT I'D JUST RINSE
OFF THE CAR ON MY OWN.
AND WHILE I WAS
RINSING OFF THE CAR,
THERE'S ALWAYS TIME
FOR A LITTLE BIT OF FUN.
[ RED CHUCKLES ]
OH, I LOVE HOSES, YEAH.
SO I GOT THE SOAP
OFF OF THERE.
I SAID THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
THAT'S 20 BUCKS WORTH,
AND I'M A HAPPY MAN.
JUST GONNA GET
WINSTON OUTTA THERE.
WINSTON, JUST CLEAR OUT.
OUT YOU GO.
AWAY YOU GO.
OH, BOY, THAT BABY'S --
I DIDN'T REALISE
THE DOOR SLAM WOULD --
OKAY, DIDN'T GAIN
THAT MUCH, DID I?
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
[ BRAKES SCREECHING ]
MAN, COFFEE ALL OVER ME!
AND YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE OF THE
COFFEE CUP HOLDER.
IT CAN'T ADAPT TO
THE IRREGULARITIES OF
MY DRIVING PATTERN,
SO EVERY TIME I SWERVE,
I'M HANGING TEN
IN A WAVE OF CAFFEINE.
NOW, I SUPPOSE I COULD WAIT
UNTIL THE AUTOMOTIVE
ENGINEERS COME UP
WITH A SOLUTION.
BUT YOU CAN PROBABLY
TELL BY LOOKING AT ME
THAT I DON'T HAVE THAT
KIND OF PATIENCE OR TIME.
SO INSTEAD,
ALLOW ME TO PRESENT
THE RED GREEN, DYNAMIC,
GIMBLE MOUNTED,
SPILL-PROOF
COFFEE CUP HOLDER.
IT'S A SIMPLE DESIGN REALLY.
I JUST ATTACHED A BICYCLE
PEDAL TO THE STEERING WHEEL.
THAT MAKES A
FLEXIBLE MOUNT.
THE CUP HOLDER ITSELF IS A
ROLL OF THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON.
AND THEN THE
COUNTERWEIGHT FOR THE UNIT
IS THIS SMALL TROPHY
I WON AT A YARD SALE
FOR BEING THE FIRST ONE
TO OFFER THEM A QUARTER.
NOW NO MATTER WHICH
WAY I TURN THE WHEEL,
THE CUP STAYS LEVEL.
IS THAT BRILLIANT OR WHAT?
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES I THINK
I'M JUST WASTING MY TIME HERE.
WELL, I'M WASTING
SOMEBODY'S TIME.
CALL THE DOCTOR,
IF YOU'RE NOT FEELING WELL.
CALL THE PLASTIC SURGEON,
IF YOUR FACE JUST FELL.
CALL QUASIMODO WHEN
YOU WANNA RING YOUR BELL.
BUT CALL ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE,
IF THERE'S A HORRIBLE,
MIND-NUMBING SMELL.
WELL, OUR HOPES OF TURNING
POSSUM LODGE INTO A
PROVINCIAL PARK
HAD A BIT OF A SETBACK.
THE INSPECTOR SHOWS UP TODAY,
TWO DAYS EARLY.
ALL THE WOMEN ARE AT WORK,
AND ALL THE KIDS
ARE IN SCHOOL.
SO ALL'S WE GOT IS MEN HERE,
THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
LUCKILY, WE'VE GOT
THE IMAGINATION
TO COME UP WITH
AN EMERGENCY PLAN.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
SO HOW'D THAT GO?
OH, FINE.
WELL, WHAT
DID HE SAY?
NOT MUCH.
HE ASKED
HAROLD OUT.
YEAH! TONIGHT FOR
DINNER AND A MOVIE.
YOU WEREN'T LEADING HIM ON,
I HOPE, HAROLD.
YOU WANT THE
CONTRACT, DON'T YOU?
WHAT AM I GONNA DO,
UNCLE RED?
WHAT IF HE GETS
FRESH WITH ME?
OKAY, YOU GUYS
WAIT RIGHT HERE.
I GOT AN IDEA.
YOU'RE NOT UPSET THAT
HE ASKED ME OUT, ARE YOU?
NO!
NOT AT ALL.
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
THANK YOU.
HE IS KINDA CUTE
IN A RUGGED WAY.
YOU KNOW,
HE'S NOT MY TYPE.
REALLY?
YEAH, I AM GUESSING
HAIRY BACK.
OH! OH!
OKAY, HAROLD, I GOT
IT ALL FIGURED OUT.
YOU ARE STILL GONNA
GO ON THE DATE,
BUT YOU'RE GONNA
TAKE YOUR SON.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
[ HORN HONKING ]
THERE HE IS, YOU GUYS,
SO AWAY YOU GO.
HAVE A GOOD
TIME, OKAY.
CAN I PLAY VIDEO GAMES
AT THE RESTAURANT?
WELL, WE'LL SEE.
DON'T SLOUCH.
DON'T SLOUCH!
I'M NOT.
[ ARGUING ]
I HATE YOU!
GET IN THE CAR!
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME, RED.
YEAH, YOU GO
AHEAD... DALTON.
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
AND I REALLY HOPE YOU'RE NOT,
I GOT A BIT OF
A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
HAROLD IS FINALLY
GOING OUT ON A DATE.
THAT'S GOT TO BE
GOOD NEWS, RIGHT?
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLDINE
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
COMING TO ORDER.
COME ON, SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, EVERYBODY.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
TAKE YOUR SEATS, PLEASE.
TAKE A SEAT.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
Red: WELL, DID WE GET
THE PROVINCIAL PARK?
Harold: NO!
AND I'M THROUGH WITH MEN.
DID YOU GET
HIS NUMBER?
I GOT HIS WALLET.