OH, DON'T WORRY.
I'M JUST FAKING THIS.
PULLIN' THE CHUTE,
I THINK THEY CALL IT.
I JUST WANTED TO SHOW YOU
WHAT A GREAT TOOL THESE
ADJUSTABLE CANES ARE
FOR ANY OF YOU TRAVELLING
HANDYMEN OUT THERE.
FOR STARTERS, WHEN THE
ATTENDANT AT THE GATE SAYS,
"NOW BOARDING ALL
FIRST CLASS PASSENGERS
"AND THOSE
NEEDING ASSISTANCE,"
THAT MEANS YOU.
FIRST CLASS TREATMENT
ON A THIRD CLASS TICKET.
AND ONCE YOU GET
INSIDE THE PLANE,
THIS BABY REALLY
KICKS INTO HIGH GEAR.
USE IT TO STUFF
YOUR BAGS UNDER THE SEAT;
OR TURN YOUR LIGHT ON;
OR TURN THE OTHER
GUY'S LIGHT OFF;
OR FLIP HER AROUND AND BRING
THE REFRESHMENT CART A
LITTLE BIT CLOSER.
OKAY, HERE'S THE
BEST PART...
ONCE YOU GET YOUR
SEAT THE WAY YOU LIKE IT,
JUST ADJUT THE CANE SO IT
JAMS UP AGAINST THE NEXT
GUY'S HEADREST.
THAT WAY, WHEN HE'S
INCLINED TO RECLINE,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO DECLINE.
SO IF ANY OF YOU HAVE GOT ANY
AIR TRAVEL COMING UP,
I SUGGEST YOU TAKE
ALONG ONE OF THESE BABIES.
IN FACT, YOU CAN TAKE MINE.
APPARENTLY, I'M NOT ALLOWED TO
GO ON AIRPLANES FOR A WHILE.
[cheers and applause]
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
WELL, IT'S A BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
YOU KNOW PART OF HAROLD'S JOB
IS TO PUT ON THESE
SPECIAL EVENTS
TO ATTRACT TOURISTS
INTO THE AREA HERE.
BOY, HE'S COME UP
WITH A DANDY THIS TIME...
HE'S HIRED LOCAL DAREDEVIL,
PSYCHO ERNIE,
TO JUMP OVER THE LODGE
ON A MOTORCYCLE.
IF HE MAKES IT,
HE BREAKS A RECORD;
AND IF HE DOESN'T,
HE BREAKS 'SOMETHING.'
EITHER WAY, IT'S A
HUGE CROWD PLEASER.
UNCLE RED!
[cheers and applause]
PROBLEM?
WE HAVE A
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
YES! PSYCHO ERNIE
BACKED OUT.
I WAS JUST TALKING
TO HIM YESTERDAY.
HE WAS ALL
EXCITED ABOUT IT.
EVEN MORE SO WHEN HE
FOUND OUT WE'RE THE
SAME BLOOD TYPE
AND I'VE GOT
TWO KIDNEYS.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU
TWO WERE TALKING ABOUT,
BUT WHEN YOU FINISHED
TALKING, HE FOUND GOD.
ALL I SAID WAS: "AFTER THE
JUMP I'LL SEE YOU ON
THE OTHER SIDE."
I MEANT THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE LODGE.
YEAH, WELL, NOW THAT
HE'S FOUND OUT ABOUT HELL,
HE'S VERY CONCERNED
ABOUT DYING.
WELL, MAYBE YOU CAN
REASON WITH HIM.
HA! YOU REASON WITH A
GUY NAMED PSYCHO.
WELL, HAROLD, I GUESS
WE'LL HAVE TO CANCEL.
NO!
NO, WE CAN'T.
WE'RE EXPECTING PEOPLE
FROM ALL OVER THE
TRI-COUNTY AREA.
AND I SOLD A LOT OF TICKETS
TO THE SENIOR COMMUNITY.
I'M NOT ABOUT TO TELL
THOSE DEAR, SWEET
OLD GRANDPARENTS
THEY'RE NOT GONNA SEE
ANY BLOOD ON SUNDAY.
WELL, THEN WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TO FIND A REPLACEMENT.
BUT WHO DO WE KNOW THAT
WOULD BE STUPID ENOUGH
TO TRY TO JUMP
OVER THE LODGE?
[laughter and applause]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
TODAY'S PRIZE IS
THIS GRAB BAG
OF PREVIOUSLY
ENJOYED FOOTWEAR
GATHERED FROM THE
ROADS IN OUR AREA.
WHO KNOWS? THERE MIGHT
BE A MATCHING PAIR
IN HERE.
UH, MR. GREEN,
YOU GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET WINSTON --
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
COVER YOUR EARS.
-- TO SAY THIS WORD...
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
AND GO!
OKAY, WINSTON,
THIS IS AN EVENT.
YOU HAVE MUSIC AND
FAT PEOPLE SINGING.
LAST YEAR'S
CHRISTMAS PARTY?
NO, NO.
THERE'S A PHRASE...
PHANTOM OF THE...
UNDERPANTS.
OKAY, THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
ITALIAN PEOPLE ENJOY.
SAUSAGE.
NO, THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT'S REALLY LOUD.
YOU'RE SURE IT'S
NOT SAUSAGE?
ALMOST OUTTA TIME,
MR. GREEN.
WHAT DOES THE NAME
PAVAROTTI MEAN TO YOU?
I BELIEVE IT'S A
TYPE OF CHEESE.
NOW, WINSTON,
YOU KNOW THIS ONE.
WHY ARE YOU ANSWERING
THE WRONG ANSWERS EVERY TIME?
ARE YOU DOING
THAT ON PURPOSE?
RED, IT'S JUST A GAME.
DON'T TURN IT INTO
A SOAP OPERA.
OKAY, TODAY ON
TALKING ANIMALS,
LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER ED FRID
IS GONNA TELL US A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT THE SNAPPING TURTLE.
COME ON UP
HERE, ED.
COME ON, NOW, ED.
I MEAN, THE TURTLE
IS JUST LYING THERE.
WELL, SURE, HE'S MOVING
PRETTY SLOWLY NOW,
BUT HE COULD STRIKE
AT ANY TIME.
SOUNDS LIKE AN
AUTO WORKER.
[laughter and applause]
HEY, I'M NOT
JOKING HERE, RED.
HE COULD SIT
THERE FOR HOURS,
JUST LAYING IN WAIT.
AND THEN WHEN YOU'RE NOT
LOOKING... AMBUSH!
OKAY. OKAY.
AR! AR! AR!
YOU KNOW, ED, THIS THING
LOOKS PRETTY HARMLESS TO ME.
[shushing]
YOU WANNA GET
HIM MAD?
HE'S GOT EARS,
YOU KNOW?
HE DOESN'T HAVE EARS.
WELL, NO,
BUT THEY
CAN READ LIPS.
WHAT DO YOU FEED A
SNAPPING TURTLE,
ANYWAY, ED?
WELL, ALMOST ANYTHING
YOU FIND IN THE WATER.
I STOCKED THIS TANK WITH
CRAYFISH, SNAILS,
FISH STUFF.
I DON'T SEE
ANYTHING IN HERE.
WHY DON'T YOU BRING ONE
OF THOSE OUT TO SHOW TO US?
WELL, I CAN THINK OF
A FEW REASONS WHY NOT.
OKAY, FINE, THEN
BRING THE TURTLE OUT.
THAT'LL BE FINE.
OKAY, I'LL GET
YOU A SNAIL.
BUT THAT'S IT, OKAY?
JUST DON'T STARTLE
HIM OR NOTHING.
JUST GET THE --
GOT A FEW IN HERE.
WHAT?
OH! OH!
( sigh of relief.)
YOU GO.
OH, THERE
[applause]
THAT WASN'T SO
BAD, EH, ED?
DIDN'T YOU
HAVE A WATCH ON?
OH, MY WATCH!
[chomp!]
[screaming]
ED! ED! ED!
ED! ED!
TAKE HIM DOWN
TO THE LAKE.
HE'LL SWIM AWAY!
PUT HIM IN THE LAKE!
DON'T WORRY.
HE'S JUST TAKING
HIM DOWN TO THE LAKE.
HE'LL PUT HIM IN THERE,
AND HE'LL SWIM AWAY.
[splash]
THERE.
HE'S GONNA BE FINE.
[chomp! ]
[ ED screaming]
UH, IT WASN'T FINE.
[screaming]
YOU KNOW, GARDENING IS
A LOT OF WORK.
I KNOW BECAUSE I OFTEN ZAP
BY THE GARDENING CHANNEL
BETWEEN GAMES.
BUT YOU KNOW THE THING I
DON'T LIKE ABOUT GARDENING?
WELL, THERE ARE SO MANY,
BUT THE MAIN ONE
IS THAT YOU'RE TOTALLY AT
THE WHIM OF THE WEATHER.
WELL, NO MORE.
I CAN DRIVE THIS PORTABLE
GARDEN TO GET THE
WEATHER I WANT.
I CAN DRIVE IT
INTO THE SUN
OR SNEAK IT
UNDER MY NEIGHBOUR'S
SPRINKLER FOR WATERING.
HECK, IF THERE'S A
RISK OF FROST,
I CAN PARK MY WHOLE
GARDEN IN THE GARAGE.
NOW, I KNOW SOME PEOPLE
GROW STUFF FOR SALADS
AND CASSEROLES,
BUT THEY EAT VEGETABLES.
I GOT A WAY
BETTER IDEA.
TAKE A BUCKET OF WATER.
THROW A LITTLE SUGAR IN --
ACTUALLY,
A LOT OF SUGAR.
THEN YOU ADD
SOME BREWER'S YEAST.
OKAY, MIX THAT STUFF
REAL GOOD IN THERE.
THEN WHAT YOU WANNA DO IS POUR
THAT INTO YOUR GAS TANK.
THAT'S GONNA BECOME THE
BASE OF YOUR ALTERNATE FUEL.
NOW ALL WE DO IS ADD SOME CORN
FROM OUR PORTABLE GARDEN HERE.
SO FIRST OF ALL,
GET RID OF YOUR GAS CAP.
REPLACE THAT WITH A BATTERY
POWERED GARBURATOR,
AND YOU'RE IN BUSINESS.
OKAY, JUST LET THAT FERMENT
IN THERE FOR A WHILE,
AS YOU DO WITH ALL THE TRULY
GOOD THINGS IN LIFE.
AND THEN YOU'RE
GOOD TO GO.
I'LL TELL YOU,
THAT'S THE CHEAPEST
FUEL YOU'LL EVER FIND.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[engine won`t turn over]
IT MIGHT BE A
LITTLE HARD TO START,
AND ACTUALLY, WHEN IT
DOES GET GOING,
IT SMELLS LIKE
A GIANT TORTILLA.
[engine starts]
MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
SIT IN THE UNIT TOO LONG.
YOU COULD GET ROOT ROT.
[applause]
I WANNA TALK TO
YOU MIDDLE-AGED GUYS
WHO THINK IT'S
TOO LATE FOR YOU...
TOO LATE FOR
A NEW CAREER;
TOO LATE FOR SUCCESS;
TOO LATE TO APOLOGIZE FOR
WHAT YOU DID IN THE HOT TUB.
AND NOW YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT
QUITTIN' YOUR JOB
AND OPENING A BRAND NEW
FAST FOOD RESTAURANT.
ALL YOUR FRIENDS
SAY YOU'RE CRAZY...
YOU'RE GONNA JUST SAY
GOOD-BYE TO YOUR PENSION,
AND YOU'RE GONNA LOSE
ALL YOUR SENIORITY,
PLUS THE GOOD IDEAS ONLY
COME FROM YOUNG PEOPLE.
ARE THEY RIGHT?
PROBABLY.
BUT YOU NEED TO KNOW
THAT RAY KROC WAS 65
BEFORE HE STARTED
McDONALD'S.
AND COLONEL SANDERS
WAS INTO HIS 70s
BEFORE KENTUCKY FRIED CHICKEN
STARTED SHOWING A PROFIT.
THE MORAL:
FAST FOOD IS GOOD FOR YOU.
AND I FIGURE THOSE GUYS ARE
A LOT OLDER THAN YOU
ARE RIGHT NOW.
SO I SAY GO FOR IT.
PEOPLE HAVE PROVEN
THAT THEY LOVE SALT AND FAT,
AND YOU LOOK LIKE
A WINNER TO ME!
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE DON'T REALISE
HOW SCIENTIFIC MOTORCYCLE
JUMPING IS.
YOU'VE GOTTA TAKE
INTO ACCOUNT
THE BALANCE OF THE BIKE,
THE APPROACH ANGLE,
AND THE THICKNESS
OF THE RIDER'S HEAD.
BUT I THINK WE'RE GOOD
TO GO, RIGHT, MIKE?
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
NOW, MIKE, YOU'VE GOT
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
HAROLD AND I HAVE
GOT IT ALL FIGURED OUT,
DON'T YOU, HAROLD?
WELL, HERE'S HOW
I SEE IT.
MIKE, YOU AND THE MOTORCYCLE
HAVE A COMBINED WEIGHT
OF 317 POUNDS.
NOW, WITH OUR LIMITED
GIVEN APPROACH,
THE MOTORCYCLE WILL REACH A
MAXIMUM SPEED OF 42.7
KILOMETRES PER HOUR.
ALLOW ME TO SHOW YOU
WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
WATCH THIS, MIKE.
YOU'LL FEEL A LOT
BETTER ABOUT THIS.
MIKE, LET'S ASSUME THIS IS
YOU ON THE MOTORCYCLE.
AND YOUR GOAL IS TO
LEAP OVER THE LODGE.
THERE'S THE
LODGE THERE.
WE'LL TAKE THIS BACK TO
47.2 KILOMETRES PER HOUR,
AND HERE'S WHAT
WILL HAPPEN...
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
SEE, THAT'S WHY
I WAS LOOKING AT
THE MOTORCYCLE BOOK.
WE CAN SOUP UP THE
ENGINE AND GIVE IT
A LOT MORE POWER.
WHEN I GET DONE WITH IT
WHAT WILL HAPPEN IS
WE'RE GONNA GET
HER UP TO 85 mph.
THAT'S LIKE A ZILLION OVER
THOSE KILOMETRE THINGS HE
WAS TALKING ABOUT.
SO THIS IS MORE
HOW SHE'S GONNA GO...
SEE LIKE THAT.
OH! OH!
OKAY, TOO MUCH.
WE'LL BACK UP.
IT'S GONNA BE FINE,
RIGHT, HAROLD?
IT WENT RIGHT
ACROSS LIKE THAT.
COME ON BACK HERE.
COME ON.
TAKE THE BIKE,
OKAY?
TAKE HER DOWN TO THE GARAGE.
WE'LL WORK ON IT TOGETHER.
WE'LL GET HER
WORKING FINE.
COME ON.
JUST GET HER --
AWAY YOU GO.
WE'RE GONNA BE GOOD.
WE GOT HER GOOD.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA
BE GREAT.
OKAY -- NO!
HEY, THAT'S SMART.
MAKE THE BIKE LIGHTER.
I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THIS!
OH, MIKE, COME ON.
NOTHING TO WORRY
ABOUT AT ALL.
COME ON,
HELP ME OUT.
IS THERE ANYTHING
I CAN DO TO MAKE
YOU FEEL BETTER?
YOU COULD TRY
THE JUMP FIRST!
Red: DALTON AND I WERE GONNA
HAVE A GAME OF BADMINTON
OUT BEHIND THE LODGE.
WALTER WAS THERE,
MORE AS A SPECTATOR.
HE HAD THE LOUNGE THERE,
AND HE WAS GONNA LIE BACK.
COULDN'T GET COMFORTABLE.
NEEDED SOME TYPE
OF A PILLOW;
DECIDED TO USE
HIS OWN SHOES.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW COMFY THEY WERE,
BUT THEY SURE PUT
HIM TO SLEEP.
AND I HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH BADMINTON.
I SEEM TO ALWAYS HIT THE BIRD
JUST A LITTLE TOO HARD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
LOOK AT THAT!
THE SHOES CAME
BACK AND -- OH!
THIS WAS AN ODD THING,
BECAUSE WALTER WAS HURTING,
YET EVERYTHING SEEMED
EXACTLY THE WAY IT WAS
BEFORE ANYTHING
HAPPENED TO HIM.
LIFE'S LIKE THAT
WHEN YOU GET OLDER.
SO I TRIED TO
TONE IT DOWN A BIT,
BUT I SEE THAT BIRD,
AND, BAM! I JUST GOTTA --
AND IT WENT RIGHT
UP INTO THE --
OKAY, OKAY, NOW, IT'S THE
ONLY BIRD WE'VE GOT,
AND IT'S UP IN THE TREE.
WELL, THAT'S WHERE A BIRD
BELONGS IF YOU THINK
ABOUT IT.
I'M SAYING, DON'T WORRY.
JUST RELAX.
I'LL GET THE RACKET.
DOWN SHE'LL COME.
AND... UH-OH!
ALL RIGHT, GIVE ME YOURS.
WELL, FINE. OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW BETTER.
YOU GO AHEAD,
MR. SMARTY PANTS.
SO DALTON SHOWS US
HOW EASY THIS REALLY IS.
JUST THAT SIMPLE, REALLY.
SO THEN I COME BACK.
I'VE GOT WALTER'S LOUNGE.
DON'T WORRY.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA
COME DOWN HERE.
WHAT COULD
POSSIBLY GO WRONG?
STAND BACK, GUYS.
ALL GONNA COME DOWN NOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
OKAY, WE'VE GOT
TWO CHOICES...
EITHER PLAY BADMINTON
UP IN THE TREE,
OR GET SOMEBODY TO GO UP
THERE AND BRING IT DOWN.
SO WALTER'S THE
LIGHTEST ONE,
SO WE HAVE A LITTLE --
JUST STOP.
GRAB MY ARMS!
STOP FOOLING AROUND.
ALL RIGHT.
UP YOU GO, WALTER.
AWAY YOU GO.
UP YOU GO.
WATCH WHERE YOU STEP.
WATCH -- LOOK OUT.
OH, MY GOSH.
OH, BOY!
WOW!
OW! OW! OOH!
SO WALTER GETS UP THERE,
STARTS SHINNYING OUT
TO THE END OF THE BRANCH
AND AND ALL HE'S
GOTTA DO IS GRAB THE --
GRAB THE RACKETS AND --
OH, THERE'S ONE RACKET.
AND IT STICKS
RIGHT INTO THE GROUND.
AND THEN HE --
OH! THERE GOES THE LOUNGE.
WOW!
OKAY, WE'RE GETTING THERE.
THERE GOES THE
OTHER RACKET.
THEY'RE ALL SET UP.
JUST GOTTA GET
THE BIRD NOW.
REACH OUT -- OH!
EASY, EASY, EASY!
OH! OH!
WELL, WALTER,
YOU DIDN'T GET THE BIRD.
OH, HERE IT COMES.
AND... THERE WE GO.
HI, EVERYBODY.
RANGER GORD HERE.
YOU KNOW, PREJUDICE
IS A TERRIBLE THING.
I DON'T THINK IT'S
RIGHT FOR PEOPLE TO MAKE
JUDGMENTS ON OTHER PEOPLE,
ESPECIALLY WHEN THEY
DON'T KNOW THOSE PEOPLE.
NOW, I GET VERY
UPSET WHEN SOMEBODY
WHO DOESN'T EVEN KNOW ME
CALLS ME AN IDIOT.
IF SOMEONE I KNOW
CALLS ME AN IDIOT,
THAT DOESN'T BOTHER
ME AT ALL.
WHY?
BECAUSE THEY'RE
ALL MORONS, THAT'S WHY.
WHICH REMINDS ME,
TODAY'S ANIMATED
EDUCATIONAL FEATURE
IS ALL ABOUT LUMBERJACKS.
SO SIT BACK,
ENJOY IT.
I HOPE YOU LEARN
SOMETHING FROM IT.
BUT REMEMBER,
DON'T CALL ME AN IDIOT,
UNLESS YOU KNOW ME FIRST.
HERE WE GO.
[quirky upbeat music]
TODAY, I'M GOING TO TEACH
EVERYONE ON THE PLANET
ABOUT BEING A
LUMBERJACK,
BECAUSE NOT EVERYBODY
IS LUCKY ENOUGH
TO BE AN ACCOUNTANT OR A
FREELANCE PROCTOLOGIST.
OH, WELL,
LOOKY HERE.
HERE'S THE LATE
RED GREEN.
I SEE IT TIRED YOU OUT
DRAGGING YOUR AXE ALL
THE WAY OUT HERE, HUH?
YOU SEE, HAROLD,
WE HAVE HERE A TREE
THAT IS DEAD AND DANGEROUS
TO EVERYONE WHO PASSES BY.
NOW, LET ME SHOW YOU WHAT
A REAL LUMBERJACK DOES
TO A TREE LIKE THIS.
HAND ME THE AXE,
PLEASE, RED.
NO, IT'S OKAY, GORD.
I'LL GET
THIS BABY DOWN.
YOU KNOW, A REAL LUMBERJACK
WOULD SEE THIS ISN'T A
TREE AT ALL.
IT'S A STEEL POLE!
[hearty laugh]
YOU KNOW, YOU COULD'VE
MENTIONED THAT, GORD.
NO! EXPERIENCE IS THE BEST
TEACHER, HAROLD.
COME ON.
CLIMBING TREES IS A BIG PART
OF BEING A LUMBERJACK.
HEY, LET'S HAVE A LITTLE RACE,
SHALL WE, HAROLD?
OKAY, READY,
ON YOUR MARK --
YOU SEE,
HAROLD,
IT'S NOT JUST MY SUPERIOR
KNOWLEDGE AND ATHLETICISM.
EQUIPMENT IS A
BIG PART OF IT.
YOU SEE, I HAVE THESE SPECIAL
CLEATS ON MY BOOTS
THAT DIG RIGHT
INTO THE TREE TRUNK.
DO YOU HAVE
THOSE, HAROLD?
UH, NO.
[Harold screaming]
[Harold and Red screaming]
THE LESSON HERE,
BOYS AND GIRLS,
IS NEVER UNDERESTIMATE
JOB SKILLS.
YOU KNOW, JUST BECAUSE
YOU'RE A LUMBERJACK,
OR EVEN A FOREST RANGER,
FOR THAT MATTER,
THAT DOESN'T NECESSARILY MEAN
YOU'RE A HOPELESS LOSER
WITH NO CHANCE OF
EVER MEETING WOMEN.
WELL, IT DOES IN
SOME CASES.
[hearty laugh]
THAT'S LUMBERJACK
HUMOUR, ISN'T IT?
[hearty laugh]
[quirky upbeat music]
[applause]
I GOT SOME GREAT
NEWS FOR YOU.
CORDLESS TELEPHONES ARE NOT
JUST FOR THE SUPER
RICH ANYMORE.
OH, NO.
NOW YOU CAN HAVE THAT SAME
FREEDOM AND LUXURY
NO MATTER WHAT LEVEL
OF POVERTY OR SQUALOR
YOU'RE WALLOWING IN.
ALL YOU NEED IS JUST
A NORMAL TELEPHONE,
A COUPLE OF THESE
CONSTRUCTION SAFETY CONES
AND OF COURSE, A RAT.
OKAY, NOW, YOU TAKE
THE HANDSET OFF THE PHONE
AND MOUNT THAT ON THE WALL.
AND THEN YOU ATTACH THE
OTHER SAFETY CONE TO
THE LISTENING END.
OKAY, NOW YOU PUT A LITTLE
TEETER-TOTTER OVER
THE PHONE HERE.
AND THIS IS WHERE YOU
PUT YOUR CHEESE ON HERE,
AND THEN YOU HAVE THE RAT YOU
TAKE OUT OF YOUR POCKET,
AND YOU PUT HIM ON THERE.
WHEN HE EATS THE CHEESE
AND THE WEIGHT PUTS
THE PLUNGER DOWN,
AND YOU'RE READY
TO RECEIVE CALLS.
NOW, I'VE ARRANGED
FOR WINSTON TO CALL
AND GIVE US A LITTLE
DEMONSTRATION.
WATCH WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN THE PHONE RINGS.
[ring]
HELLO!
WINSTON: Hey, Red, how's
this comin' through?
LOUD AND CLEAR.
Great.
Well, gotta go.
Septic emergency.
YEAH, OKAY, WINSTON.
[disconnnects dial tone]
[applause]
WELL, IT'S ALL
SYSTEMS GO.
MIKE'LL BE JUMPING OVER
THE LODGE ANY MINUTE NOW.
THE SENIORS HAVE BEEN A
BIT OF A PROBLEM IN
THE CROWD THERE.
THEY COMPLAINED THEY WERE
SO CLOSE THEY WERE
GONNA GET KILLED.
WHEN WE
MOVED THEM BACK,
THEY COMPLAINED THEY
WERE TOO FAR FROM
THE BATHROOMS.
BUT ALL IN ALL,
IT'S PRETTY EXCITING,
ISN'T IT, HAROLD?
I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THIS.
WELL, NOW
DON'T YOU START.
THIS IS YOUR EVENT!
OH, NO!
IT'S NOT MY EVENT!
MY EVENT WAS PSYCHO ERNIE
LEAPING OVER THE LODGE --
A PROFESSIONAL CYCLE JUMPER,
WITH NO SECOND THOUGHTS.
ERNIE DOESN'T
HAVE FIRST THOUGHTS.
EXACTLY.
BUT THIS IS MIKE,
OUR FRIEND,
A LODGE MEMBER.
WHAT IS THE WORST
THAT COULD HAPPEN?
MIKE SCREAMING TO HIS DEATH
IN AN EXPLODING BALL OF FIRE.
YOU ARE SO NEGATIVE,
YOU KNOW THAT?
WELL, I WANTED
TO CANCEL THIS.
I SHOULD'A CANCELED THIS!
YOU TALKED ME
OUT OF IT.
HAROLD, EVERYTHING'S
GONNA BE FINE.
MIKE IS READY.
WE OVERHAULED
THE MOTORCYCLE.
THE ENGINE'S GOT
PLENTY OF POWER.
I GIVE YOU MY
WORD AS A MECHANIC
THAT EVERYTHING IS
GOING TO BE GREAT.
[motorcycle motor revving]
I'M CANCELING!
YOU'RE TOO LATE.
HE'S ALREADY ON HIS WAY!
LOOK!
OH! OH!
LOOK AT HIM GO!
WHAT DID YOU DO
TO THAT MOTORCYCLE?
WELL, WE BURROWED
OUT THE CYLINDERS,
PUT IN OVERSIZED
PISTONS, RACING CAM.
I FIGURE WE QUADRUPLED THE
HORSEPOWER ON THAT BABY.
IT'S LIKE A ROCKET!
DID YOU PUT A BIGGER
GAS TANK ON IT?
WHY WOULD WE DO
THAT, HAROLD?
WELL, WHEN YOU INCREASE
THE DISPLACEMENT,
YOU INCREASE THE
FUEL CONSUMPTION.
MIKE COULD RUN
OUT OF GAS.
[engine sputtering]
I THINK.
YOU SHOULD CANCEL.
MIKE!
MIKE, ARE YOU OKAY?
Mike: I'M FINE.
I'M ON THE ROOF!
HAROLD, HAROLD,
GET THE LADDER.
IT'S OKAY, MIKE.
WE'LL GET YOU DOWN.
OKAY, YOU KNOW,
THERE'S A LESSON TO YOU
YOUNGSTERS WATCHING
OUT THERE...
DON'T EVER JUMP A BUILDING
WITH A MOTORIZED VEHICLE,
UNLESS YOU HAVE A
REALLY HUGE GAS TANK.
[possum squealing]
OH, MEETING TIME!
MEETING TIME!
MEETING TIME, EVERYBODY!
UNCLE RED!
UNCLE RED.
IT'S MEETING TIME.
SHOULDN'T YOU
BE HOLDING THE
LADDER FOR MIKE?
YES.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
WE MADE A LITTLE
MISTAKE TODAY.
HAROLD AND I THOUGHT THAT MIKE
COULD BE AN ENTERTAINER,
BUT YOU KNOW, HE DIDN'T
GO OVER ALL THAT WELL.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND THE
WHOLE GANG AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
COME IN, GUYS.
COME IN.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, NOW THAT WE
KNOW WHAT WE DID WRONG,
WOULD ANYBODY HERE
LIKE TO VOLUNTEER
TO JUMP THE LODGE NEXT YEAR?
DALTON, YOU WANNA
JUMP THE LODGE?
OH, I'M SORRY.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
'JUNK' THE LODGE.