THE TERM COURAGE HAS
CREATED A LOT OF
CONFUSION
AMONG MEN OVER
THE YEARS.
TO A RATIONAL PERSON,
COURAGE MEANS PROCEEDING
WITH SOMETHING
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE FULLY
AWARE OF PERSONAL RISK.
THIS SHOULD NOT
BE CONFUSED WITH
PROCEEDING WITH SOMETHING
OUT OF A LACK
OF INFORMATION,
INTELLIGENCE OR HUMILITY.
THAT'S THE KIND
OF COURAGE WE SEE
WITH A LOT OF MEN.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT MAKES
US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
RED GREEN:
ON TODAY'S SHOW,
BUZZ SHERWOOD SAYS
HELLO IN HIS OWN
SPECIAL WAY,
I'M GOING TO
TURN A BICYCLE
INTO AN ELECTRIC
GENERATING STATION,
TROUBLE ON THE COUCH,
I'LL EXPLAIN THAT
LATER,
AND I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU THE IN-DEPTH DANGERS
OF SMOKING
ON THE JOB.
AND NOW HERE IS THE
MAN OF THE HALF HOUR,
THE HOST OF THE SHOW AND
THE UNCLE TO BEAT,
MR. RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IF YOUR TV PICTURE
GOES KIND OF NUTS
AT HOME THERE,
PLEASE DON'T ADJUST
YOUR SET.
BECAUSE IT'S JUST
THE HIGH TECH TRICKERY
OF THE PRODUCER/
DIRECTOR/NEPHEW,
HAROLD.
NO, I WAS REFERRING
TO ANOTHER MINOR
INCONVENIENCE.
THE ELECTRIC SYSTEM
IS ALL OUT OF WHACK
HERE UP AT POSSUM LAKE.
YEAH, IT'S MOOSE THOMPSON'S
HOMEMADE FENCE, ISN'T IT?
HIS ELECTRIC HOMEMADE
FENCE, ISN'T IT?
YEAH.
YEAH, WELL, HE DIDN'T
INSULATE IT VERY
WELL, HAROLD.
HE DIDN'T INSULATE
IT AT ALL.
IT'S JUST A BUNCH
OF BARE WIRES RUNNING
FROM BRANCH TO BRANCH.
EVERY TIME THERE'S
THE SLIGHTEST BREEZE
A TREE EXPLODES.
YEAH, APPARENTLY IT'S
AFFECTING THE WHOLE
POWER SYSTEM, TOO.
EVERY TIME MOOSE'S DOG
LEAVES HIS MARK
ON A TREE,
IT BLOWS OUT A
CIRCUIT BREAKER
IN OTTAWA.
SO THEY'VE TOLD US
EITHER WE DISCONNECT
THAT ELECTRIC FENCE
OR THEY'RE GOING
TO CUT OFF OUR
ELECTRIC POWER
AND WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO BUILD OUR
OWN GENERATING STATION.
WOW.
DOESN'T LEAVE
YOU MUCH CHOICE.
IT CERTAINLY DOESN'T.
SO WE START WORKING ON
THE GENERATING STATION
TOMORROW, I FIGURE.
WHAT?
OH, YEAH.
I HATE BEING
PUSHED AROUND BY THOSE
PUBLIC UTILITIES, HAROLD.
NOW ALL'S WE GOT
TO DECIDE IS
WHETHER WE'RE GOING
TO BE OIL-FIRED, COAL-
FIRED OR BUILD A DAM.
WELL, I FIGURE YOU'LL
BE ALL FIRED AND NO
ONE WILL GIVE A DAM.
WINSTON ROTHCHILD
HERE OF ROTHCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES
REMINDING YOU, NO REASON
TO BLUSH IF YOUR TOILET
WON'T FLUSH,
CALL 1-800-555-SUCK.
OH HE WAS A REAL BIG DOG,
HIS NAME WAS KONG
HE MUST HAVE
WEIGHED 300 POUNDS
ONE EYE WAS BLUE AND
THE OTHER WAS GONE
AND HE TENDED TO DO
THINGS IN MOUNDS
THERE WASN'T A JOB
THAT DOG COULDN'T DO
IF YOU GAVE HIM THE
PLANS HE'D BUILD IT
UNTIL HE DARTED ACROSS
THE ROAD ONE NIGHT
RAN OVER A SUZUKI
SIDEKICK AND KILLED IT
[ HAROLD MAKING
ENGINE SOUNDS ]
WELL, YOU ARE IN THE
SOUP NOW, MY SON.
GOOSE IS COOKED,
FOX IS IN THE
HEN HOUSE.
YOU WENT TO YOUR
WIFE'S COMPANY PARTY,
YOU SAT IN THE CORNER
RUDE AND ACTING BORED
THE WHOLE EVENING.
YOU FIGURED ROOM
FULL OF JERKS,
WHO COULD BLAME YOU?
WELL, YOUR WIFE,
THAT'S WHO.
YOU CAN'T SLOP
THIS ONE OFF
WITH MUST HAVE BEEN
SOMETHING I ATE.
NO, YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO EAT SOME CROW
AND SURPRISE THE WIFE.
WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO
IS INVITE OVER
TO YOUR HOUSE
THE MOST OBNOXIOUS
COUPLE YOU MET AT
THE COMPANY PARTY.
BITE THE BULLET,
RESTITUTION,
CALM THE WATERS.
WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU
A COUPLE OF POINTERS
TO HELP EASE THE PAIN.
DO IT WHEN IT'S NICE
OUT SO YOU WON'T BE
STUCK IN THE HOUSE.
YEAH, MAYBE PLAY
HORSESHOES,
THAT WAY YOU'RE GOING
TO BE 30 FEET AWAY
FROM THEM
AND DON'T EVEN HAVE
TO TALK TO THEM.
YOU MIGHT EVEN BE
ABLE TO BEAT THEM.
OR NAIL THEM
WITH A HORSESHOE.
ACCIDENTALLY.
YEAH.
HAVE A BARBECUE.
THAT WAY YOU CAN COOK
THEIR MEAT BLACKER
THAN A MOLE'S ARMPIT.
OR INVITE THEM WHEN
THE BUGS ARE BITING
SO THEY MIGHT REACT AND
SWELL UP AND HAVE TO
RUSH HOME EARLY.
WORST CASE SCENARIO,
YOU'RE LOOKING AT
TWO HOURS
AND THEY'RE OUT
OF THERE,
YOUR WIFE IS TALKING
TO YOU AGAIN
AND YOUR LIFE IS BACK
THE WAY YOU WANT IT.
UNTIL THE NEXT
COMPANY PARTY.
WELL, WITH EVERYBODY
TRYING TO THINK OF WAYS
TO GENERATE
ELECTRICITY THIS WEEK,
I THOUGHT WE'D GET
HANDYMAN CORNER
INTO THE ACT
WITH THIS OLD
BICYCLE HERE.
NOW THESE THINGS HAD
A LITTLE UNIT ON THE BACK,
A LITTLE GENERATOR,
THAT WORKED BY THE
ROTATION OF THE TIRE, HERE.
AND THE POWER WOULD
GO UP THE WIRE AND
AROUND THE CROSSBAR,
YOU GOT TO BE CAREFUL
OF THAT, AND IT WOULD GO
UP INTO THE
HEADLIGHT HERE.
THE ONLY PROBLEM WITH
THESE THINGS IS THAT
THEY REQUIRED
A FAIR AMOUNT OF SPEED.
YOU GOT TO BE GOING AT
A PRETTY GOOD CLIP
IN ORDER TO GET SOME
LIGHT COMING OUT
OF THIS THING.
SO YOU WOULD BE
RIDING ALONG AT NIGHT
AND YOU THINK YOU SEE
SOMETHING UP AHEAD,
IT COULD BE A BRICK WALL
OR A TRAIN WRECK
OR WHATEVER,
YOU ACTUALLY HAVE TO
SPEED UP TO SEE IT.
BY THE TIME YOU DO,
YOU'RE GOING TOO
FAST TO STOP.
SO I THINK THE SAFEST
THING TO DO WITH
THESE UNITS
IS TO TAKE THEM RIGHT
OFF THE ROAD AND
TURN THEM
INTO A STATIONARY POWER
GENERATOR/EXERCYCLE.
NOW TO DO THAT YOU'RE
GOING TO NEED A WHACK
OF WIRE LIKE THIS
AND A REAL
STURDY SAWHORSE.
OKAY, NOW I GOT THE
BIKE GENERATOR HOOKED UP
TO THE WIRE THAT I SHOWED YOU.
THE ELECTRICITY WILL
GO AROUND, AROUND THERE,
AND I GOT IT
HOOKED UP TO THIS
NORMAL LIGHTBULB.
AND I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW WE CAN USE
THE BIKE
TO GENERATE HOUSEHOLD
ELECTRICITY.
I ALSO GOT HER UP
ON THE SAWHORSE THERE
SO THE BIKE WON'T
GO ANYWHERE.
AND THE IDEA IS YOU
JUST KEEP PEDALING
'TILL IT'S BEDTIME
AND THEN YOUR LIGHTS
WILL GO OUT.
ACTUALLY, MINE MAY GO
OUT LONG BEFORE THAT.
IT'S NOT VERY BRIGHT.
HMMM.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TRY A PLAN THAT
DOESN'T INVOLVE
CARDIAC CARE.
A LOT OF PEOPLE DON'T
KNOW THIS BUT EVERY
ELECTRIC MOTOR
CAN BE USED AS
A GENERATOR.
ALL'S YOU DO IS WIRE
IT UP BACKWARDS
AND THEN PUT A
MAGNETIC FIELD IN THERE
AND TURN THE ARMATURE.
IN LAYMEN'S TERMS THAT
MEANS THE OLD GUY
RIDES THE BIKE
AND THE
LIGHT GOES ON.
WELL, THEN, GLAD THAT
WASN'T THE STOVE.
ALL RIGHT, THE PROBLEM
WE HAVE NOW IS THAT WE
GOT SO MUCH POWER
WE HAVE TO REGULATE IT
AND TO DO THAT
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED SOME
VEHICLE BATTERIES.
NOW IF YOU HAVE A PROBLEM
GETTING A HOLD OF
VEHICLE BATTERIES,
JUST GO OVER TO A
MALL PARKING LOT WITH A
CROWBAR AND 9/16 WRENCH.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW USING THE
MOTOR AS A GENERATOR,
I HAVE JUST PUMPED UP
A HUGE WAD OF ELECTRICITY
THAT I'M STORING IN
ALL THESE BATTERIES
THAT I HAVE MOUNTED
ON THE HANDYMAN'S
COLLAPSIBLE VERTICAL
SHELVING UNIT.
AND NOW WHEN I WANT
TO USE ANY ELECTRICITY
LIKE TO TURN THIS
LIGHT ON,
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
FLICK THIS SWITCH.
IT'S THAT EASY.
SO REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
LET'S GIVE IT A TRY.
WELL, THERE'S A
LESSON FOR YOU.
A GENERATOR CAN ALSO
TURN BACK INTO A MOTOR,
AND A BICYCLE CAN TURN
INTO AN ELECTRIC
MOTORCYCLE,
AND AN ELECTRIC
MOTORCYCLE CAN TURN
INTO AN OUTHOUSE.
HEY, BUSTER,
DON'T GET UP.
RED GREEN:
STAY TUNED.
BILL GOES RIDING ON
ONE OF THOSE WAVE
RIDER THINGS
AND HAROLD PROVES
THAT NOT EVERYBODY
SHOULD BE OUT
IN THE WOODS.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
MIDDLE AGE GUYS OUT THERE.
NOW, I KNOW THIS MAY
BE A LITTLE HARD TO TAKE,
BUT I GOT TO SAY
IT ANYWAY,
WHEN YOU GET TO BE
AS OLD AS WE ARE,
AND I KNOW IT'S HOT
OUTSIDE, BUT YOU GOT
TO STOP GOING TOPLESS.
PLEASE FOR GOD SAKES
WEAR A T-SHIRT AT
ALL TIMES.
YEAH, I KNOW, 20 YEARS
AGO I DIDN'T LOOK SO
BAD EITHER
IN NOTHING BUT SHORTS
AND A PAIR OF
RUNNING SHOES,
BUT EVEN I'M GIVING MY
NEIGHBOURS A BREAK NOW.
I MEAN, WE USED TO
LOOK LIKE HARD
WASHBOARDS,
NOW WE LOOK
LIKE SEA COWS.
SOME OF US HAVE BREASTS
AND IT'S SCARING
THE KIDS
AND CONFUSING
THE BABIES.
AND THAT'S A LOT OF
HAIR TO LOOK AT.
STRANGE CLUMPS ON
THE BACK AND ON
THE SIDE,
COMING OUT THE NOSE
AND THE EARS AND
NONE ON THE HEAD.
IT'S LIKE YOUR SKIN
GOT TOO TIRED TO HOLD
YOUR HAIR UP THAT HIGH.
SO WEAR A SHIRT, OKAY,
BECAUSE WHEN A SHIRT
FLAPS AND WRINKLES
IN THE BREEZE,
IT DOESN'T
LOOK TOO BAD.
WHEN SKIN DOES THAT,
THAT IS NOT PRETTY.
REMEMBER, I'M
PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, THE POSSUM LODGE
POWER PLANT IS ALL SET
TO GO ON LINE,
WE'RE GOING TO BE
TOTALLY SELF-RELIANT --
WELL, IN TERMS OF
ELECTRICITY.
OUR WIVES STILL HAVE TO
DRESS US IN THE MORNING,
YOU KNOW.
YOU GUYS BUILT A
POWER DAM THAT
QUICKLY, HUH?
NO, NO, WE GAVE UP
ON THAT ONE, HAROLD.
BEAVERS CAN MAKE DAMS.
WE HAD A REAL
PROBLEM WITH IT.
DID YOU USE BIG
ENOUGH TREES,
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE
BEAVERS USE PRETTY
BIG TREES?
OH YEAH.
YEAH, WE
USED HUGE TREES.
IN FACT OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK EVEN CHEWED
A COUPLE DOWN, YOU KNOW,
UNTIL HIS DENTURES
WEDGED INTO A BIRCH
BARK THERE.
I TELL YOU, THERE IS
NOTHING SO ODD LOOKING
AS A TREE WITH A
BIG TOOTHY GRIN.
ALL RIGHT, I
STAND CORRECTED.
AND YOU KNOW THEN
WE THOUGHT OF USING
THE SOLAR-POWERED LIGHTS
LIKE BUSTER
HADFIELD HAS.
OH, YOU MEAN THE
HOLES IN HIS ROOF?
YEAH.
BUT JUNIOR SINGLETON
HAD A GREAT IDEA.
HE'S GOT SOME CARS
AROUND THE BACK OF
HIS HOUSE,
WE WENT AROUND THERE,
TOOK OUT THE
ALTERNATORS,
OKAY, 'CAUSE EVERY
ALTERNATOR GIVES
YOU 12 VOLTS,
SO YOU GET 10
OF THEM IN A ROW,
THERE'S YOUR 120.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
USE TO POWER THE
ALTERNATORS?
WELL, ELECTRIC
MOTORS.
WE TOOK THE STARTING
MOTORS OUT OF THE
SAME CARS,
SO YOU PUT THE
STARTING MOTOR
TO THE ALTERNATOR,
THAT'S HOW
THAT WORKS.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
USE TO POWER THE
POWER MOTORS?
THE ALTERNATORS,
HAROLD.
YEAH, I KNOW, OKAY.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
BUT WHAT ARE YOU --
OKAY.
NO.
NEVER MIND.
OKAY.
YEAH.
JUST LET ME KNOW
IF IT WORKS.
WELL, WHY SHOULDN'T
IT WORK?
[ POWER HUM ]
OKAY.
SOUNDS LIKE THE WHOLE
SYSTEM IS ALL SET
TO COME ON LINE
HERE, HAROLD.
HERE WE GO.
[ EXPLOSION ]
EVERYTHING YOU'RE
WATCHING IS
FOR SALE.
AUNT BERNICE SHOWED
ME A PICTURE OF YOU
WHEN YOU WERE A TEENAGER.
YOU WERE WITH YOUR
FIRST STUDEBAKER.
YOU WERE MUCH
THINNER THEN.
WELL, THAT'S AN OPTICAL
ILLUSION, HAROLD.
CARS WERE A LOT
BIGGER IN THOSE DAYS.
NO.
YOU WERE MAJORLY THIN.
YOU WERE LIKE NORMAL SIZE.
ACTUALLY, I NOTICED A LOT
OF THE GUYS UP HERE
AT THE LODGE
ARE ON THAT
BEEFY, HEFTY, YOU
KNOW, CORPULENT SIZE.
THAT'S A METABOLISM
THING, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW, AS YOU GET
OLDER YOU DON'T NEED
AS MUCH FOOD
TO MAINTAIN THE
SAME BODY WEIGHT.
WELL, THAT'S GOING
NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN TO ME.
I'M GOING TO
STAY IN SHAPE.
THAT SHAPE THERE?
YES.
WELL, I GUESS YOU
GET A BIT OF EXERCISE
RUNNING AWAY FROM GIRLS
AND BULLIES AND DOGS.
DOGS.
A LOT OF DOGS.
WITH ANY LUCK THAT
WILL MAINTAIN RIGHT
THROUGH YOUR ADULT LIFE.
BUT HAROLD I THINK
BY THE TIME YOU'RE
MY AGE,
YOU WILL BE GOING
AROUND 400 POUNDS
AND LYING IN A
HAMMOCK SOMEWHERE
WITH YOUR ARM WRAPPED
AROUND AN OXYGEN TANK.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO BE
ME BECAUSE I'M GOING
TO WATCH MY WEIGHT,
I'M GOING TO EAT RIGHT
AND I'M GOING TO
STAY IN SHAPE.
WELL, YOU BETTER
START NOW, HAROLD.
AH, COME ON, PLEASE,
I JUST WANT TO
TAKE FIVE.
ALL RIGHT.
IF YOU WANT TO GROW
UP LOOKING LIKE ME.
I'LL TAKE IT.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
WIND'S IS COMING
UP HAROLD.
JUST BURN THE
WHOLE THING?
YEAH.
WITH A BUNCH OF
US ON THE BRINK
OF GENERATING OUR OWN
ELECTRICITY UP HERE,
I THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE A GOOD TIME
TO TALK ABOUT THE
OPPORTUNITIES OF
THE NORTH.
AND WHAT BETTER GUY TO
TALK TO THAN WINSTON
ROTHCHILD
OF ROTHCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING
SERVICES.
WHERE OUR MOTTO IS
NO JOB TOO HUMBLE,
NO CUSTOMER
TOO STUCK UP.
THAT'S A DANDY.
NOW, WINSTON, I THINK
MAYBE A LOT OF OUR
URBAN VIEWERS
ARE THINKING ABOUT
MOVING UP HERE AND
STARTING OVER.
OH YEAH, YOU KNOW,
THAT REMINDS ME A
LOT OF MY DAD, EH?
HE WAS FOREVER, YOU
KNOW, STARTING OVER
AND MOVING UP.
YOU KNOW, FOR INSTANCE,
I GOT 12 STEP-BROTHERS,
NINE STEP-MOMS AND
THREE STEP-FRIENDS.
YEAH, HIS MOTTO ALWAYS
WAS THE GRASS IS
ALWAYS GREENER
ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE DOOR.
OH, I JUST
ABOUT FORGOT, DO
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED?
I HAVEN'T TOLD
YOU THIS YET,
HAVE I?
NO.
WELL SOME PIN HEAD
STOLE THE ALTERNATOR
AND STARTER OUT
OF THE HONEY WAGON.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
PEOPLE ARE SCUM,
YOU KNOW.
OH, THEY ARE.
YEAH, THEY ARE.
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE IS,
THE PEOPLE FROM THE CITY
THEY THINK WE'RE
TECHNOLOGICALLY BEHIND
THE TIMES UP HERE.
OH, THAT'S YOUR
INFORMATION SUPER
HIGHWAY THERE.
I GOT A COMPUTER
FOR MY OPERATION.
OH YEAH?
WHICH OPERATION,
THE GALL BLADDER
OR THE YOU KNOW?
NO, NO. NO.
MY SEWAGE BUSINESS.
OH, YEAH.
COME ON AND SEE IT.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW SOMETHING,
RED, I GOT MY ENTIRE
LIFE ON ONE OF THESE.
IT'S WHAT THEY
CALL A FLABBY
DISK, EH?
LET ME SHOW YOU HOW
IT WORKS 'CAUSE IT'S
REALLY EXCITING.
OKAY.
YOU PLUG IT IN.
AND THEN YOU PUSH A
COUPLE OF BUTTONS
ON THE MACHINE.
AND YOU SEE THAT?
YEAH.
THAT'S ALL
THE PEOPLE WHOSE
TANKS I'VE SUCKED.
WOW.
RIGHT?
AND THEN YOU PUSH A
COUPLE MORE BUTTONS,
YOU SEE THAT?
THAT'S ALL THE PEOPLE
WHOSE TANKS NEED
SUCKING.
YEAH, I CAN SEE THAT.
YEAH.
AND THEN YOU CAN
GET INTO YOUR
BOOKKEEPING.
SEE THERE'S
ACCOUNTS DECEIVABLE.
AND SO ON.
WOW.
SO IT'S REALLY
STREAMLINED THE
OPERATION, EH?
IT'S MADE IT
MORE HANDS ON.
IS THAT A GOOD IDEA IN
THIS LINE OF WORK
DO YOU THINK?
OH, YEAH.
ABSOLUTELY.
SO LISTEN, IF YOU'RE
THINKING OF COMING OUT HERE,
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT,
'CAUSE YOU CAN USE THE
SAME TOOLS YOU WOULD
IN A REAL URBAN
CENTRE, EH?
WHEN I THINK OF
HOW MY LIFE WOULD BE
WITHOUT THE COMPUTER
AND THE MODEM
AND THE CELL PHONE
AND THE FAX,
WELL, GEEZ, I WOULD
JUST BE ANOTHER GUY
WITH AN ODD
SMELLING TRUCK.
RED GREEN:
WELL, BILL'S
GOT A NEW TOY TODAY
ON ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
THIS IS ONE OF THESE
WAVE RIDER THINGS.
AND THIS THING HERE
IS CALLED A KILL SWITCH.
WHAT THIS DOES,
IT CLIPS IN HERE
AND THEN THE UNIT
WOULD ACTUALLY
START FOR YOU.
AND ONCE YOU GOT
IT RUNNING, SAY YOU
FALL OFF OR SOMETHING,
THEN THIS THINGS
SPRINGS OUT AND
IT STOPS.
BILL IS REAL PROUD
OF THAT KILL SWITCH UNIT
AND THE SPRINGINESS
OF IT AND SO ON.
MAYBE A LITTLE LESS
PROUD OF IT NOW
THAN HE WAS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
NO PROBLEM?
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
GO OUT THERE WITH --
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH MY GOSH.
THAT'S THE IGNITION
WIRES, BILL.
WHAT ARE YOU -- OH,
HE'S GOING TO --
THIS IS CLEVER.
THAT'S HOW THAT WORKS.
AND RIGHT NEAR THE
WATER, THAT'S REAL SMART.
WHAT DID YOU EXPECT
WOULD HAPPEN, BILL?
ALLRIGHT, I GOT
TO GO SAVE HIM.
LUCKILY, I KEEP THE BOAT
RUNNING AT ALL TIMES.
NAIL HER!
BEAUTIFUL, RUNS LIKE
IT WAS BRAND NEW.
AND OUT I GO, HANG ON,
BILL, I'M COMING.
I'M THINKING IF I CAN
GET THE BOAT HOOK THERE
AND HOOK IT DOWN
IN BETWEEN THE WIRES,
PULL THE WIRES APART AND
THAT WILL KILL THE MOTOR
AND JUST -- HOLD STILL
BILL, HOLD STILL.
I GOTCHA.
OH MY GOSH.
SORRY BILL.
THEN I GOT THE WIRES
AND HOOKED THEM THERE --
YEAH, THERE WE GO.
THERE WE GO.
AND THEN I HOOKED IT
AND THAT HOOKED
ON THERE.
BUT OF COURSE IT
STOPPED NOW
SO IT PULLS ME RIGHT
OUT OF MY SEAT OVER
THE BACK.
OH MY GOSH.
THE WATER IS SO COLD.
NOW THE BOAT IS GOING
FULL THROTTLE,
NO DRIVER.
INTERESTING.
HELP, BILL, HELP.
BILL HAD TAKEN THE
AMBULANCE COURSE
WHERE THEY TEACH YOU HOW
TO SAVE SOMEBODY'S HAT.
THANK YOU, BILL.
YOU KNOW THERE'S A
TIME FOR HUMOUR
AND THERE'S A
TIME FOR BILL.
THE TIME FOR BILL IS
NOT GOING TO BE
DURING MY LIFE.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
NOW, THE BOAT IS
HEADING RIGHT
TOWARDS US.
BILL, BILL!
WE GOTTA GO,
GOTTA GO, GOTTA GO!
RED GREEN: STAY TUNED
FOR DOUGIE AND DALTON
IN A DISCUSSION YOU
WON'T WANT TO MISS
AND BUZZ SHERWOOD SHOWS
YOU WHY HE CAME IN LAST
ON THE DEBATING TEAM.
WELL, THE POSSUM LODGE
POWER PLANT IS REALLY
GOING ON LINE THIS TIME.
YOU GUYS FIXED
ALL THOSE ALTERNATORS
AND ELECTRIC MOTORS?
OH, HAROLD, THAT
IDEA COULDN'T WORK.
ANY IDIOT KNOWS THAT.
NO, NO, NO, WE
DECIDED TO SWITCH
OVER TO NUCLEAR POWER.
I'M SORRY?
YEAH.
GOOD OLD-FASHIONED,
CLEAN, SAFE,
NUCLEAR POWER.
GOT OURSELVES A
CAN-DO REACTOR, HAROLD.
A CANDU REACTOR, YOU MEAN
A REAL CANADIAN
DEUTERIUM HEAVY WATER
FISSION REACTOR?
NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS JUST A REACTOR
BUILT BY A BUNCH
OF CAN-DO GUYS.
JUNIOR SINGLETON GOT ALL
THE PLANS OUT OF A BOOK
HIS SON HAD
CALLED THE HOW AND
WHY BIG BOOK OF
ELECTRICITY.
THE ONLY TOUGH PART
WAS FINDING THE
RADIOACTIVE FUEL,
SO WHAT WE DID WAS WE
SCRAPED ALL THE RADIUM
OFF OF THOSE GLOW IN
THE DARK WATCHES.
I'LL TELL YOU, HAROLD,
WHERE ELSE BUT AT
POSSUM LODGE
COULD YOU DO SOMETHING
THIS GREAT, HUH?
CHERNOBYL
SPRINGS TO MIND.
HERE WE ARE WITH OUR
RESIDENT BUSH PILOT,
BUZZ SHERWOOD.
HOW YOU DO
DOING TODAY BUZZ?
HEY, RED!
HAROLD!
BUZZ, I WAS HOPING
TODAY YOU COULD
TEACH US
HOW TO LAND A
PLANE ON THE WATER.
NO CAN DO,
RED, NOT TODAY.
TODAY I'M GOING
TO LEAD THE PEOPLE
AND WE ARE GOING TO
PROTEST THE NUCLEAR
POWER PLANT.
WELL, I THINK YOU
SHOULD WAIT UNTIL
THERE'S SOMETHING WORTH
PROTESTING, DON'T YOU?
HEY, HEY, YOU CAN'T
DENY ME MY FREEDOM
OF SPEECH HERE, MAN.
YOU KNOW PROTESTING
NUCLEAR POWER PLANTS
IS WHAT FORMED
THIS COUNTRY.
BUZZ, YOU GOT TO STOP
READING HISTORY BOOKS
WRITTEN BY JOAN BIAZ.
OH, COME ON MAN, RED,
IT WILL BE GREAT TO
GET OUT THERE
AND MARCH AGAIN AND
CHANT AND PROTEST
AND YOU START THINKING
I'M MAKING A DIFFERENCE,
AND ALL ALONG,
YOU KNOW, YOU START
THINKING WELL, NO,
IT'S A TOTAL WASTE OF
TIME AND I'M USELESS.
BUT I MIGHT MEET SOME
LIKE-MINDED WOMEN.
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO
WAIT 'TILL AFTER
THE ARRESTS,
THAT'S WHEN THEY'RE
MORE RECEPTIVE.
NOBODY AROUND
HERE WANTS TO GET
ARRESTED, ALL RIGHT?
OH THEY'VE JUST
FORGOTTEN HOW MUCH
FUN IT CAN BE, RED.
THAT'S WHY I'VE STARTED
MY CIVIL DISOBEDIENCE
REFRESHER COURSE.
I CALL IT RIOT 101.
LOOK AT THIS.
THE FIRST THING YOU
GOT TO DO IS YOUR
SIGNS, RIGHT?
HERE YOU TAKE
THAT ONE.
NOW I HAVE ADAPTED THIS
OF COURSE TO OUR CURRENT
POLITICAL SITUATION,
BUT I'VE HEARD
THEY STILL WORK.
YOU KNOW, RED, IF YOU
FEEL IT IN YOUR HEART,
YOU GOT TO LIVE
IT IN YOUR LIFE,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, I THINK MAKING
THEM OUT OF COMBUSTIBLE
MATERIALS IS A GOOD PLAN.
AND DO YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE TELEVISION
LOVES A GOOD FIRE.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
TELEVISION LIKES?
YOU GOT TO TALK
IN THOSE SOUND
BITES, RIGHT?
SO IT GOES LIKE
THIS, YOU GO:
IT'S A DISASTER
WAITING TO HAPPEN.
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
OR: WOULD YOU RAISE YOUR
CHILDREN NEXT TO THAT?
I LIKE THAT ONE.
OR THERE'S THIS ONE:
YOU SHUT UP.
NO YOU SHUT UP!
SHUT UP!
YOU'RE A LIAR!
NO YOU SHUT UP!
IT'S THE 90S, NOBODY
CARES ABOUT ANYTHING
ANYMORE.
THAT'S WHAT I'M GOING
TO DO, I'M GOING TO
PROTEST APATHY.
I'M GOING TO RID
THE WORLD OF APATHY.
AND WHEN ARE YOU
GOING TO DO THAT?
WHAT'S IT TO YOU?
THAT'S TRUE.
JOINING MY UNCLE RED
ON THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW
THIS WEEK IS MR. DOUGIE
FRANKLIN AND MR.
DALTON HUMPHREY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
HAROLD, HAROLD,
READ THIS ONE,
READ THIS ONE.
NO, I GOT A LETTER
WAY MORE BETTER,
WAY MORE BETTER.
DEAR EXPERTS:
SHOULD GAY PEOPLE BE
ALLOWED TO SERVE IN
THE MILITARY?
OH.
HAROLD, I WANTED YOU
TO READ THIS ONE.
THIS GUY HERE HE WANTS TO
KNOW WHAT'S THE BEST
KIND OF SANDWICH,
PEANUT BUTTER AND BANANA
OR CORNED BEEF AND
CHEESE SPREAD.
NO, NO, YOU SEE BECAUSE
THIS IS RATINGS WEEK,
UNCLE RED,
WE GOT TO BE
CONTROVERSIAL,
WE GOT TO HIT THOSE
HOT TOPICS, YOU KNOW,
THE BIZ.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL ANSWER IT.
DOUGIE?
DALTON?
WELL, TO BE HONEST, RED,
I SORT OF PREPARED
A LITTLE BIT
TO GO WITH THAT
PEANUT BUTTER AND
BANANA BUSINESS.
I WAS PUSHING
THE CORNED BEEF
AND CHEESE SPREAD.
I DON'T REALLY HAVE
MUCH OF AN OPINION
ON GAYS IN
THE MILITARY.
YOU DO NOW.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO BACK TO
THE ANCIENT GREEKS
WHO HAD A LOT
OF GAY SOLDIERS
AND THEY WERE A
PRETTY IMPRESSIVE
MILITARY MACHINE.
YOU KNOW THEY
WOULD RUN A MARATHON,
THEY'D HAVE PLENTY
OF STRENGTH LEFT TO
FIGHT A BIG BATTLE
BECAUSE THEY ATE A
LOT OF RED MEAT AND
DAIRY PRODUCTS
LIKE CORNED BEEF
AND PROCESSED CHEESE.
WAIT A SECOND.
YOUR NORMAL PEOPLE,
I BELIEVE,
MUCH PREFER THE DELICIOUS
COMBINATION OF PEANUT
BUTTER AND BANANA.
I BELIEVE YOUR PERVERTS ARE
INTO YOUR CORNED BEEF
AND CHEESE BUSINESS,
WHICH TO ME IS JUST
TOTALLY UNNATURAL.
CORNED BEEF AND CHEESE
SPREAD IS JUST AS NORMAL
AS PEANUT BUTTER AND BANANA.
IT'S A MATTER OF
PERSONAL CHOICE.
WELL, ALL I'M SAYING IS
SHOULD YOUR CORN BEEF
AND CHEESE TYPES
BE ALLOWED TO MINGLE
WITH, YOU KNOW,
YOUR PEANUT BUTTER
AND BANANA PEOPLE?
MY ANSWER TO THAT
QUESTION IS, NO, SIR,
THEY SHOULD NOT BECAUSE
IT WILL LOWER MORALE
AND IT'S JUST A MATTER
OF TIME BEFORE SOMEBODY
IS GOING TO GET THEIR
CRUSTS CUT OFF.
THERE ARE PLENTY OF
GAYS ALREADY IN
THE MILITARY
AND IT'S JUST AS NATURAL
AS RYE BREAD WITH A
PICKLE ON THE SIDE.
FINE.
ALL I'M SAYING IS
HOLD THE PICKLE.
ALL RIGHT.
HAROLD, THIS HAS
GONE COMPLETELY
OUT OF CONTROL.
WELL, IT'S AT A
STALEMATE, UNCLE RED,
YOU HAVE TO BREAK THE TIE.
ALL RIGHT.
ACTUALLY, I'M KIND OF
HUNGRY WITH ALL THIS.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
I'LL GIVE YOU
AN OPINION
RIGHT AFTER I
MAKE MYSELF A
SANDWICH.
WHAT KIND?
HAM.
STRAIGHT HAM.
ARE YOU OKAY?
DON'T EVER STAND NEAR
A NUCLEAR REACTOR
OR IN FACT ANY TALL
METAL DEVICE DURING
A SEVERE THUNDERSTORM.
YOU GOT HIT
BY LIGHTNING?
OH, MAN.
THE NUCLEAR REACTOR
GOT NUKED, HAROLD.
WE'RE BACK TO BUYING
OUR POWER FROM THE
UTILITIES AGAIN.
WHAT ABOUT THAT ELECTRIC
FENCE ALL AROUND MOOSE
THOMPSON'S HOUSE
TO KEEP THE
TRESPASSERS OUT?
OH, GOOD NEWS THERE.
IT SHORTED OUT AGAIN,
BURNT MOOSE'S HOUSE
TO THE GROUND.
SO ALL'S WELL
THAT ENDS WELL.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
YEAH.
YOU GO AHEAD,
HAROLD.
I'M GOING TO
GET CLEANED UP.
I'LL BE DOWN SOON.
AND IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M KIND OF IN THE
MOOD TO GET GROUNDED
IF YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH
FOR WATCHING.
AND UNTIL NEXT TIME ON
BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
HAROLD:
OKAY, ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
RED: SIT DOWN, GUYS.