It's time to head north up to the unspoiled
wetlands and unpolluted air of places like
this where people don't seem to want to go.
But we're up here on your behalf.
Beam me back an action packed, fun filled
show for you to appreciate, even though the
ratings suggest otherwise.
And here's the probable cause for all that
the star of the Red Green Show and a close
personal uncle of mine.
Ladies and gentlemen, Mr.
Red
Green, Oh, thank you and
Welcome to Possum Lodge.
I don't want to take all the credit for the
show.
Harold's got to share the blame for at least
his part.
I guess you're talking about my state of the
art visual effects, what
I think make a little break from content I
always say.
Actually had a little problem up at the
Lodge this week.
You know, we like to we like to think of
this as virgin territory.
Nothing personal, Harold. But, you know,
sometimes civilization kind of encroaches
here and messes things up, and we got to do
some cleanup.
Like, for example, it might have to replant
some trees that we've driven over or replace
the topsoil in the den.
Or sometimes on a Saturday, we'll just
shovel the empties off the beach.
Remember that time we had the Big Oil spill?
Yeah. Well, that's why we make stinky
Peterson.
Wear a bathing cap now, right?
Yeah, we have had some environmental
problems in the past.
We used to get a lot of gas leaks up here,
and then we realized that the propane tanks
are left hand thread.
After that, we could actually tighten the
coupling rather than just wrap it in the duct
tape. Once we started doing that, the
campfires got a lot more controllable and
managed to bring the forest fire level down
down a peg or two.
And then pretty soon the geese and the loon
started coming back and nesting on the lake
again, and we could go out hunting.
So what's the big emergency this week, Uncle
Ray?
Well, we're getting a lot of build up of foam
on Possum Lake,
A little bit of foam. It's of no consequence.
Yeah, OK, I agree.
But this is this is real thick foam here and
you can't see the lake.
You can't see the dock, you can't see the
canoes.
I was out there this morning and a motorboat
and boys ever tough whipping around when you
can't see the dock or other boats or rafts
or the shore or barbecues or people
sunbathing on the beach.
I thought I heard screaming, Yeah, well,
anyway, we either have a pollution problem
here or Possum Lake is rabid anyway, but I'm
going to show there, Harold.
Oh, yeah, right? How you guys doing inside?
How can you justify being in a lodge in such
a beautiful day?
Oh, it's a glorious day for a game of golf.
There's no snow. There's no lightning.
I'd be up for another 18 if anybody's
interested, huh?
Aren't you supposed to be working today,
Bob?
I'm working, Eddie, but I'm I'm in here on
ministry business.
Yeah, any idea what this is?
Well, it's too clean to be a cookie.
Exactly. I was on the 12th hole and I
ducked, hooked a three wood and a lake.
Of course, it was on purpose, but it is a
joke.
You are. You got it. So naturally, I didn't
count the stroke, but when I reached in and I
fished this out, I looked at it very closely
and I noticed how clean this ball really is
when I went to the end of Possum Lake and I
saw that it was covered in foam.
Oh yeah, well, that's probably just, you
know, the white caps from the waves.
You know, sometimes it gets like that, you
know, the white cap and they eat like that.
That could happen. No, this stuff is six
feet deep pink and smells like old fat, ugly
foam from some form of low grade detergent
or something like that.
You wouldn't know anything about that, would
you?
Eddie, what kind of cheap shot is that, Bob?
Are you saying my food makes toxic suds?
Or are you going to make a joke about me
washing my hair in the lake?
That's a good joke.
You were thinking, of course.
You know, some people might laugh at that,
you know, because humor is such a subjective
thing, isn't it? You know, wait, I'm going
to go read about the subjective humor element
of it all. Awesome.
Eddie Fife.
I find that sticky froth on Possum Lake is
coming from your kitchen.
Well, I'm just going to have to inspect it
on behalf of the department.
No, that's my job.
You know, Bob, there's been something I've
wanted to tell you for a long time.
You're a crappy golfer.
That's it. I'm going to appoint you to the
ministry.
And if I don't get you under on the suds
thing, I'm going to get you on your meatloaf.
There's nothing wrong with my meatloaf.
Oh, come on now, Eddie. Don't say things you
don't mean
To off time right now.
I reply you right now.
Why does he do that to me?
He knows I hate confrontation.
I'm an artist. I wear my heart on my sleeve.
How are you enjoying the cookies?
No, I have an eating disorder.
This could cure it. I want to get that bill.
That would be Noel.
You don't ask for a passport.
You like just anybody in here.
Well, I heard somebody having trouble opening
an unlocked door.
That's pretty sure to you.
That matters. Not Mr.
Poor security is what you've got here.
No, I'm sorry. I had to come down on you
like that.
But that's my responsibility.
Which reminds me I've got a report.
I just completed an exhaustive surveillance
of the lake and surrounds, and I'm happy to
report everything is called normal.
Well, what about the six feet of foam down
south?
And I miss that.
It's a call for a redo. Starship entry one
16 Area of surveillance incomplete.
Reconnoiter ASAP.
Don't you worry, red, I'll find it.
I did think of the source.
I'll be sure to wash your hands before it's.
Now, water, you want to take some cookies
with you.
Oh, yeah, thanks. I wouldn't want to go out
there on the arm.
About the lodge, where the men like to play,
there's new guys and wedges at all times a
day, booby trapped cow flap, short sheeting,
beds that don't play out run
The bullets measure professional.
As we've done gone the handymen
Corner, we're going to show you how to turn a
negative into a positive and I don't just
mean hiring him as a producer director.
I'm talking about the frustrations of what
happens when your lawnmower meets your garden
hose. We've all experienced this.
Some of us, more than others, you know?
I've never been involved with any high level
management meetings, but if I'd have been
there when they were designing the garden
hose and realizing it was going to lie on the
lawn, then it was going to be a lawn mower
going by.
I'm not sure I would have picked Green, you
know, as the ideal color.
I'm just a consumer in that carries its own
responsibilities, but rather than just throw
all these little slats into the lake or what
have you, I'm going to show you today how you
can create some interesting alternatives of
using these things.
I wasn't the first one, for example, is a
little bit obvious, but this would be your
high volume, long range drinking straw for
those unfortunate times when you're at a
party or what have you. And for whatever
reason, you just can't pick up your beverage
or you can't afford another one, but he's
got one, that kind of thing.
You know something else? Sound travels and
straight lines.
People don't know that it won't go around
corners, so you can't hear what they're
saying about you and headed down the hall.
You have an ear trumpet like this with a
flexible hose on it.
Like this? You stand there.
You put this into your ear and you put the
other end.
Well, sound travels underwater.
Real good, too. So that's another that's
another bonus you ever notice when you pick
up a paint can and the handle can just rip
right through your skin and just take the
bone right off the air if you're not
careful.
You take a little piece of your hose and you
split it up lengthwise.
You put that through the handle and look at
just goes on there.
No problem. And you pick it up and.
Well, of course, the first thing that you
can do with your with your hose couplings is
you can actually recreate the whole hose
just by putting the pieces together, except
it'll be about three feet shorter because
you've got to cut up one of the pieces for
washers. And another thing to do, which I
think is darn attractive, is your own
personal bike lock.
You know, you would probably want to have a
bike worth locking, for starters, to wrap
this around here, and you would taking that
up real good use a vise grips or a wrench or,
you know, a pipe wrench, whatever you have
on there, because nobody can steal your bike
that way, I must, I must. They have pliers
and criminals just don't don't think I had
like that. I think the best application of
this is what I'm wearing right here.
You see this, you catching this, you're
getting this on camera and these are
suspenders. They go down through my belt
loops and up and over with the cufflinks
attached and everything. And the beauty of
these is in the winter, you can fill them on
some sort of a hearty soup, you know, to
keep you warm.
I would suggest a cream of mushroom or
possibly even a beef, barley or soup deserve.
You just want to fly by the seat of your
pants.
And I think these are dandy.
And you know, I'm even thinking of patenting
these.
I'm going to call them pantyhose anyway
until the next time.
Remember, if the women don't find you
handsome, they should at least find your
handy, friendly pair.
Typekit. It is a winter animals lie in a
deep sleep hidden away from air and light in
a place called the Senate.
And so, anyway, Bob's been accusing Eddie of
polluting the lake with his cooking and that
he doesn't take criticism well, even with
all the practice he's had.
I'm sorry,
Excuse me, but nor asked me to tell you to
drop by his place.
Ok, so I told you so there.
What does he want, Harold Power?
I think you mean now?
I'm sorry. I have. I have no idea.
Well, that would have been my guess.
Funny when people choose to be defensive
about, isn't it?
I mean, Eddie with his cooking and mouse
with his weight and Bob with his golfing.
And you, Harold, you with your complexion
and your teeth and your eyesight and the way
you walk and the way you talk and your hair
and your school marks.
Ok, thank you very much.
Thank you. I was wondering, you know, did Bob
ever find out what those pink bubbles were?
I mean, you know, he works for the Ministry
of the Environment.
I think pink bubbles were pretty much fall
into
The government jurisdiction, wouldn't it?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, it does.
Actually, what he did was he sent Bill out
in a canoe right into the phone, and Bill
just disappeared, never seen from since.
So then Bob teed up some balls and started
just driving golf balls into the fall.
I think he was testing the texture or the
cohesiveness or something.
He hasn't learned anything, but he has
located Bill's head twice.
Well, that's important, too. Ok, well, we
should get on with the show actually now.
Yeah, yeah. Ok, I'll just go see what Noel's
got on his mind.
Shouldn't take long.
Now, I'm this close to a discovery of
breakthrough on the frothy foam case.
You mean the suds on the leash?
You have almost no muscle tone at all.
J Lo, I don't know where you find the energy
to pull your pants up.
Well, the suspenders help
I give it. Want my God, grant?
Yeah.
Congratulations. And I kick your tires.
Now I can bench press two hundred and fifty
pounds three sets of 12.
Boom, boom, boom.
That's something you do for work. Or is that
like a party piece?
Something I do for life?
Well, I'm tough, right?
Physically, mentally.
Kind of like Chuck Norris,
A guy I love connection.
I pity you read one of these days you're
going to wake up dead and you won't know what
hit you. That's why I got to solve this
sudsy.
Like Kate said, I am this close to
discovering the purpose of purpose.
Tick tock. Ok.
I observe some suspicious activity.
Yeah, some around the large Cedar Prefab
Cottage down on the far end of possum like
that is a beautiful Scottish center hall
plan.
Three oversized bedrooms and that living
room.
You can play handball in it anyway.
On the evening, prior to the mysterious
appearance of that diaphanous detergent
residue that crap on the lake, I was engaged
in some security surveillance on the main
road. Yeah, I was in the ditch.
Oh yeah, I observed a truck approaching,
said Cottage at one 15, three twenty seven
and then later on. Yeah, I can't really be
exact on that time because three twenty seven
a truck ran over my watch.
Oh yeah, I can tell you that the vehicle had
studded tires.
Yeah, oh yeah. Sure.
Yeah, with that tire tread, I can run a
trace on those.
Yeah, yeah, well, it's a lot.
With the appearance of the fall.
The very next day, I think we can come to
the conclusion that those people are
responsible for releasing illegal and toxic
chemicals into the lake or they're running
some sort of carpet cleaning business.
I'm not sure we're still at the theory
stage.
Yeah. All right.
Well, I'll tell you what. Oh, why don't you
go up there and check that out?
Because that way you won't be here talking
to me, and you won't be able to get an
imprint of their front grille, maybe on your
forehead.
I need back. Yeah, I'm going to head up there
now.
Ok. Listen, read don't you
Jog or something? Well, maybe after lunch,
I'll see you
In bed for. Yeah.
Oh, right. Yeah, I probably wouldn't tell
anybody about this.
Oh, don't worry.
This is hockey night in Canada.
Bill and I went down to Bob's Marina, took a
bucket full of pucks and built out of skates
on there. They're kind of weak ankles, which
actually extend right up to the top of his
tooth, and we're going to do a little bit of
hockey practice and bills.
It looks like Bill spent most of his career
on the bench or under the bench.
It is basically a goaltender, so he is going
to get in that there and literally in that.
And he's all right, well, he's got all the
patty, he's got the stick and he's got their
gloves, and now I've never seen anybody put
on padding before, but this didn't strike me
at the end of balance on his skates, and I
thought, why don't we put him on the ice and
just kind of nail into them, you know?
But you know, when you're trying to think of
a system that'll work, it's tough to do with
Bill. But eventually he got everything on
there and I went out around the blue line and
had all the pucks and sort of sort of spread
them out, put them in line.
And the idea is I'm going to start firing
shots at them.
I can really whip that people.
They save. And then he got himself regrouped,
and I just said, Now I'm going to mix up the
shots to slap her and a wrist shot and an
overhand slider and, you know, kind of
sideways submarine curve shot.
And by golly, I started getting lucky their
catch in the top corner and putting a few
into the five hole or.
It's four point eight metric.
Oh, sorry, sorry, Bill.
So Bill said, hold everything he says he
wants to try a different approach and he
really he felt the padding was what was
holding them back.
So this very strange starts taking all the
padding off, just throwing her down on the
ice there. And I didn't know how far he was
going to go with this, you know, going down
to the bare skiff on the ice or whatever.
But now we just got rid of all the padding
and figured he'd be more mobile.
And of course, now I'm motivated to really
rip the puck in there is just that's fun.
That's fun for me. That's fun.
I call that fun. Call me crazy.
And I rip around, Darren.
Here we go. Nice.
Save Floyd. He's right.
He's going, Oh yes, I don't think that was
going in anyway to me.
Oh, that feels great.
Look at this. Look at this and you got it.
It was really good. Look, you got a really
relative, beautiful work.
Build beautiful. And.
Well, I don't know, I think this Possum Lake
foam thing was just part of a natural cycle
freezing, thawing, rising, falling, coming
over with pink foam.
I remember one time we had thousands of
splinters of wood, naga hide and plastic out
there that turned out to be nothing.
You mean, when the old marina blew up?
That wasn't nothing.
Well, no, I meant nothing that had any
environmental side effects to it.
And nobody cares what you blow up as long as
it doesn't release any chemicals being dumped
a lot worse into Possum Lake over the years,
including each other.
I mean, people could see the bottom.
They wouldn't be concerned about a little
bit of pink foam on the top will tell you
that it's 100 years of garbage down there,
plus four stoves combination washer dryer.
It doesn't old boats, nine car batteries
plus the cars they come out of, and a full
set of patio furniture, including mosquito
coils.
Oh all right. You have an amazing memory for
stuff like that.
Well, it's been a memorable summer, Harold.
That's the call of the meeting.
Come on, let's go.
Bob and Noel have some answers for it.
Well, that'd be worth. Anyway, this is this
should go pretty quickly.
We don't spend a lot of time on
environmental issues, which you probably
already guessed.
Why did you get a cherry tree with the
pencil when you get a chair, right?
Ok, all right.
Get up, get up.
Oh, I'm no longer on this earth kind of guy.
Yeah, yeah, he wants
Me to tell you that he's got a tray of
cookies here.
If anybody's hungry.
Not just now. Thank you very much.
Now the floor recognizes Bob Stuyvesant
Leg around while I ran a battery of tests on
the lake water and I think I've been able to
pinpoint the source of the pink foam.
My goodness, look at that. Well, look, it
was only six over par on that one, wolf.
All right. Oh yeah, right?
Well, the foam, the foams.
Two hundred and sixty parts per million of
pine scrub.
It's a common dish detergent.
Well, I guess that lets me off the hook.
I don't use liquid detergent.
Well, it's not liquid.
It's a fine powder.
It's used for dishwashers.
Looks a lot like flour.
And what are you insinuating that that I'm
using that I'm using detergent instead of
flour? Is that it? Oh, give me a this bill.
I mean, come on, Andy.
It's obvious you're using the detergent in
your baking from one of the cake pans were so
easy to clean. Well, I'll tell you whose
fault it is.
It's Murray's fault in those those damn boat
food containers.
I mean, who thought the labeling would be
right on it, for heaven's sake?
All right. Well, don't worry, the Department
of Natural Resources is on the job.
I've ordered a water bomber to drop a load
of acid on the lake.
It should neutralize the pH and melt the
foam down.
All right. That's really good.
Thank you. Hey, know, pull the weight, aren't
you?
Oh yeah. Sorry, right?
I got it. I got some great news, everybody.
I called the producers of 60 Minutes see if
they wanted to investigate that mystery
cottage at the far end of the lake.
You know, the A-frame with the wind, Chad?
Well, they weren't too keen on that idea,
but they got real excited about that pink
foam, and they're coming up here to do a big
story on pink blossom pond.
And treated like some sort of miracle or
something.
Hey, wait, we're going to have tourists by
the millions.
We're all going to be rich. How do you get
it back on one thing, though?
Yeah, I might have led them to believe that.
Well, the pink foam cures sick people in
Baltimore.
And you're going to have to stay out of
sight on this one anyway.
They bought it. And we're all going to be
rich.
I'd like to see it
Now, which probably, but.
It's going to be later. Thank you very much,
Bob.
Excellent work as usual.
And how about we reward Bob by having him
entertain us this evening?
Here's what you can do whatever you want
done.
Thank you.
Well, I just want to talk to you about golf,
and I'll just go change.
Wow, there you go.
You learn something every day, don't you?
Granted, it's usually the same thing that
you learned the day before and the day before
that. But if repetition wasn't a good thing,
who'd get married?
Speaking of which my wife is watching, I'll
be coming straight home after the meeting.
And if the bedroom light is on, I'll take
that to mean that are environmentally
friendly. So until next time, on behalf of
myself and Harold and the whole gang up here
at Possum Lodge, keep your stick on the ice.
Well, then there's her three Iron
Paul boy, she's a.
Oh yeah. What a character.
A quick, sassy, always lively, though, and
then you're fired.
This is the dark web Bookabag, the moody,
unpredictable.
Sometimes you're there for you and sometimes
you just post.
I can tell you something knowing you'll find
a five iron that stands by you.
Take good care of it. Well, wow, you got
your drivers know your woods, and when you
play, they'll sit back. Oh, oh oh.