THERE’S NOTHING SCARIER THAN
WHEN YOUR DOCTOR
DELIVERS THE BAD NEWS...
THAT YOU GOTTA
EAT MORE VEGETABLES
AND CUT DOWN
ON YOUR DRINKING.
TALK ABOUT A DOUBLE WHAMMY.
WELL, HERE'S A TRICK THAT
WILL MAKE EVERYBODY HAPPY...
DRINK YOUR VEGETABLES.
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT GETTING
ONE OF THOSE FANCY JUICERS.
I SAY USE YOUR
GARBAGE DISPOSAL.
IT'S SELF-CLEANING,
DOESN'T TAKE UP ANY
COUNTER SPACE,
AND IT WON'T COST YOU
AN ARM AND A LEG,
UNLESS YOU GET YOUR SUSPENDERS
CAUGHT IN THE BLADES.
NOW, I PUT A Y-CONNECTOR ON
THE OUTPUT SIDE OF THE UNIT.
AND IN THIS POSITION,
IT'S JUST A REGULAR
GARBAGE DISPOSAL.
THE GOO JUST GOES
DOWN THE DRAIN.
BUT FOR JUICER MODE,
I SWING HER OVER
TO THE DISPENSER,
AND YOU PUT A
GLASS UNDERNEATH HER.
I WOULD RECOMMEND
YOU USE A BEER STEIN.
PRESENTATION IS EVERYTHING.
AND I JUST THROW IN
A HANDFUL OF VEGETABLES,
AND IT'S JUST WHAT
THE DOCTOR ORDERED.
LET'S TOSS THIS SALAD.
FULL OF VITAMINS...
AND MINERALS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANKS VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
YEAH.
BIG KERFUFFLE UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
HAROLD LOST HIS WALLET.
EVERYBODY'S LOOKIN' ALL
OVER THE PLACE FOR IT,
BECAUSE HE'S THE ONE GUY WHO
ACTUALLY HAS MONEY IN IT.
TURNS OUT I HAD IT
IN MY POCKET.
I FORGOT I'D
BORROWED IT FROM HIM
TO USE A CREDIT CARD
TO JIMMY OPEN A PAY TOILET.
AND THEN I GOT THE WALLET OUT,
AND I SAW A LIBRARY CARD
IN THERE,
AND I THOUGHT, BOY,
THIS CAN'T BE MY WALLET.
UNCLE RED, THEY SAID
YOU FOUND MY WALLET.
YEAH, THERE IT IS,
HAROLD.
OH! THANK GOODNESS.
THANK GOODNESS.
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
YEAH, THANK YOU.
SO WHERE WAS IT,
ON THE FLOOR,
UP IN THE RAFTERS OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT
I BET, HUH?
DID YOU JUST
KISS ME, HAROLD?
MY WAY OF SAYING
THANK YOU.
WELL, A WEDGIE IS MY WAY OF
SAYING YOUR WELCOME.
HEY!
DON'T EVER DO THAT.
I WON'T.
BUT THE GOOD NEWS IS THAT
WHILE WE WERE LOOKING
FOR HIS WALLET
WE FOUND A WHOLE BUNCH OF
OTHER STUFF THAT WE
THOUGHT WE'D LOST.
WE GOT LOOSE
CHANGE AND TOOLS,
A MOTORCYCLE.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S
BROTHER.
MR. GREEN! MR. GREEN!
LOOK WHAT WE FOUND.
YEAH, IT'S THE ORIGINAL
LODGE CHARTER.
FROM THE VERY FIRST
DAYS OF THE LODGE.
YEAH, WE FOUND IT
IN A CAN OF RAT POISON.
[ ALL COUGHING ]
OKAY, RED, THERE'S GOOD NEWS
AND THERE'S BAD NEWS.
NOW, THE GOOD
NEWS IS, UH --
OKAY, THE BAD NEWS IS
THE CHARTER SAYS
THAT THE LODGE LEADER
CAN ONLY SERVE FOR...
I-V YEARS,
WHATEVER THAT IS.
I-V MUST MEAN I NEED
TO BE HOOKED UP
WITH A DRIP.
WELL, I AM.
HA! HA! HA!
IV IS THE ROMAN NUMERAL
FOR THE NUMBER FOUR.
THAT MEANS WE HAVE
TO HAVE AN ELECTION
EVERY FOUR
ROMAN YEARS.
YOU'VE BEEN
HOLDING OFFICE
ILLEGALLY, RED!
WE HAVE TO HAVE AN
ELECTION FOR A
NEW LEADER.
WELL, FINE,
THEN HAVE AN ELECTION,
IF YOU CAN FIND ANYBODY
TO RUN AGAINST ME.
I WILL.
OKAY, ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS PAY FIVE DOLLARS TO GET
YOUR NAME ON ON THE BALLOT,
AND YOU'RE
A CANDIDATE.
I'M OUT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FOR A PERSONALIZED GIFT
FROM ZELDA'S BODY
WAXING PARLOUR,
"WHERE WE REMOVE YOUR HAIR
AND THEN REMOLD THE WAX
"INTO A ROMANTIC CANDLE
WITH A THOUSAND WICKS."
OKAY, COVER YOUR EARS,
WINSTON.
UH, MR. GREEN,
YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET WINSTON
TO SAY THIS WORD....
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
MIKE.
AND... GO!
UH, OKAY, WINSTON,
YOU SAY THIS BEFORE DINNER.
PASS THE KETCHUP.
NO, NO, THIS IS
MORE OF A PRAYER.
HOPE WE'RE NOT
HAVING ASPARAGUS.
NO, NO.
OKAY, SAY YOU WANNA
GET INTO HEAVEN,
BUT YOU COMMITTED
A LOT OF SINS,
YOU APPEAL TO GOD'S...
SENSE OF HUMOUR.
NO, NO, WINSTON,
THIS IS WHAT SAVES PEOPLE.
AMAZING...
LUCK.
NO, OKAY, GONNA GO
ANOTHER WAY WITH IT.
LET'S YOU MEET SOMEBODY
WHO'S ELEGANT AND CHARMING.
YOU WOULD SAY
THEY'RE FULL OF...
IT.
OKAY. OKAY. OKAY.
YOU KNOW, THERE WAS
THIS GREAT ACTRESS,
SHE MADE A BUNCH OF MOVIES.
IN FACT, HER NAME
DESCRIBED HER BEST FEATURE.
OH, CHESTY MORGAN!
UH, WE'RE ALMOST
OUTTA TIME, MR. GREEN.
YEAH, YEAH.
WINSTON, EVERY YEAR,
AT THE ANNUAL LODGE DINNER,
YOU STAND UP AND SAY,
"HOLY..."
I-I CAN'T SAY THAT
ON TV, RED.
I'LL DISGRACE MYSELF.
THERE WE GO!
WE HAVE A LODGE MEMBER
WHO HAS A NEW SHOW
ON THE PORT ASBESTOS
TV STATION
AND IT FEATURES ONE OF HIS
FAVOURITE ACTIVITIES...
SNOWMOBILING.
I SHOULD GET A WATCH.
BUT HE'LL BE
HERE IN A MINUTE.
UH, HIS NAME
IS BLAIR COBDEN,
AND IT'S JUST SO NICE
TO SEE A YOUNG PERSON
WITH SOME GET UP AND GO.
[ SNOWMOBILE ]
[ CRASH! ]
Red: OKAY, HOW'S
IT GOIN', BLAIR?
GOOD.
I PICKED UP
YOUR MAIL.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
JUST, UH, HAVE
A SEAT.
BOY, IT'S GOT TO
BE GREAT TO HAVE A
SNOWMOBILING SHOW,
EH, BLAIR?
YOU CAN SHOOT IT
IN THE WINTER
AND THEN SPEND
ALL SUMMER TO HEAL.
ACTUALLY, RED, THEY ACTUALLY
MAKE ME SHOOT THE SHOW
IN THE HOT WEATHER.
THE STATION ONLY
HAS THE ONE CAMERA.
THEY USE IT IN THE WINTER
TO SHOOT PEEWEE HOCKEY.
OH, OKAY, WELL, WHAT
I THOUGHT WE'D DO
IS RUN A FEW CLIPS
FROM YOUR SHOW,
AND THEN YOU AND I CAN
TALK ABOUT WHAT
WE'RE SEEIN'.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
I WOULD DO,
BUT, HEY,
THIS IS YOUR SHOW.
UH, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, OKAY.
Blair: SO THIS IS ME
TAKIN' OUT THE SLED.
I HAD ONE OF THOSE GARAGE DOOR
REMOTE THINGYS INSTALLED.
FOR SECURITY, BECAUSE I DIDN'T
WANT ANYBODY STEALING
THE SLED BACK.
BUT FOR SOME
UNKNOWN REASON
THE THING STARTED TO MESS WITH
MY NEIGHBOUR'S FANCY SUV.
I'M WONDERING MAYBE
IF YOU PICKED UP HIS
REMOTE BY MISTAKE.
NO, I HAD THE
RIGHT CONTROLLER.
I JUST -- I GOT THIS
METAL PLATE IN MY HEAD,
AND I THINK IT MESSES
WITH ELECTRONIC SIGNALS.
WHEN THERE'S A FULL MOON,
I GET HBO.
Red: OH, THERE SHE GOES.
OKAY. OKAY.
SHE'S OPENING UP NOW.
ALL RIGHT, SO THERE'S
THE UNIT THERE.
OKAY, NOW -- WOW!
UH, OKAY, IS IT SAFE TO
DRIVE A SNOWMOBILE ON
THE ROAD LIKE THAT?
YEAH, I THINK SO,
BUT IT'S PRETTY LOUD.
I GOTTA KEEP HER UNDER
80 KLIKS OR I CAN'T
HEAR THE RADIO.
Blair: OH, THIS IS
MY BUDDY GARY.
HE'S HITCHHIKING BECAUSE HE
TRASHED HIS GIRLFRIEND'S CAR.
YOU DIDN'T EXACTLY STOP
FOR HIM, THOUGH.
THE SLED STALLS
WHEN I STOP,
SO GARY HAD TO FIND A WAY
TO JUMP ON AT HIGH SPEED.
ANYWAY, WHAT I WANTED
TO SHOW THE VIEWERS, RED,
IS THAT HAVING A SNOWMOBILE
IS JUST AS GOOD AS
HAVING A CAR.
Red: OH, YEAH, I SEE THAT.
I SEE THAT.
Blair: YOU CAN MAKE
ANYTHING WORK,
AS LONG AS YOU PUT
YOUR MIND TO IT.
YOU KNOW, A SNOWMOBILE
IS AN AWESOME MACHINE.
I DON'T EVEN MISS
DRIVING A CAR.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
HOW DID YOU LOSE
YOUR LICENSE AGAIN?
PUT IT THIS WAY,
IF YOU EVER HIT A MOOSE
WHILE DRIVING A FORKLIFT,
YOU JUST KEEP DRIVING --
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, WE ALL
HAVE PREOWNED VEHICLES
OF UNSPECIFIED VALUE,
STRATEGICALLY PLACED
THROUGHOUT OUR
REAL ESTATE HOLDINGS.
THE QUESTION IS, CAN YOU DO
ANYTHING WITH CRAP?
OBVIOUSLY THE
ANSWER IS YES.
WE'RE IN OUR 14th SEASON.
FOR EXAMPLE, WHY NOT TAKE
EVERYTHING THAT STILL
WORKS FROM THE CAR
AND USE IT TO UPGRADE
THIS OLD FISHING BOAT?
WITH A LITTLE WORK
AND WAY TOO MUCH IMAGINATION
WE CAN TURN THIS
UNIT INTO SOMETHING
THAT REALLY KICKS BASS.
TO GET THE ENGINE
OUT OF THIS BABY,
YOU WANNA SOAK THE MOTOR
MOUNTS WITH PENETRATING OIL.
LOOSEN 'EM UP A LITTLE BIT.
THEY'RE RUSTED ON
THERE PRETTY SOLID.
THIS STUFF WOULD MAKE
A GREAT LAXATIVE.
OKAY, I GOT THE ENGINE AND
TRANSMISSION MOUNTED UP
FRONT HERE.
IT'S FRONT WHEEL DRIVE,
SO THAT MADE IT EASIER.
BUT I'M GOING TO NEED
SOMETHING TO USE AS A RUDDER.
POSSUM LAKE'S PRETTY SMALL,
SO YOU NEED TO
BE ABLE TO STEER.
YOU KNOW, I'M THINKING ONE OF
THESE DOORS WOULD MAKE
A DANDY RUDDER.
THAT ONE.
OKAY, GOT THE STEERING
ALL HOOKED UP
SO THAT MY DOOR RUDDER
IS PULLED SIDE TO SIDE.
WHEN I TURN THE --
OH, SHE'S LOCKED.
GOTTA TURN THE KEY ON.
[ warning signal beeping ]
WHAT THE HECK?
OH, THE DOOR'S OPEN.
I MADE SOME
OTHER CHANGES TOO.
I TUNED THE CAR RADIO
TO THE WEATHER STATION,
AND I DISCONNECTED
THE SPEEDO
AND HOOKED THE MECHANISM
UP TO THE SUN VISOR.
THAT MAKES IT
INTO A FISH SCALE.
I ALSO LEFT THE
REARVIEW MIRROR ON THERE
SO YOU CAN SEE
THE ONE THAT GOT AWAY.
AND YOU KNOW, THE ARMREST AND
HEADREST MAKE DANDY
BOAT FENDERS.
BUT SHE'S STILL
A LITTLE FRONT HEAVY,
WHICH IS OKAY FOR A
LOT OF THINGS IN LIFE,
BUT A BOAT ISN'T
ONE OF 'EM.
THERE WE GO.
OKAY, NOT ONLY HAVE I SOLVED
THE FRONT HEAVY PROBLEM,
I'VE INSTALLED A 360°
SWIVEL FISHING CHAIR,
SOMETHING EVERY
BASS FISHERMAN WANTS.
AND THAT'S
AN OVERSIZED TIRE,
IN CASE YOU HAVE A FAT BASS.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
AND NOW IF
YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I'VE GOT BIGGER FISH TO FRY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THERE WAS A
MOVIE THAT CAME OUT
BACK AROUND THE TIME
BERNICE AND I GOT MARRIED.
IT HAD A LINE IN IT
THAT SAID,
"LOVE MEANS NEVER
HAVING TO SAY YOU'RE SORRY."
IT WAS A LOVE STORY.
I DON'T REMEMBER THE TITLE.
ANYWAY, AS THE
YEARS WENT BY,
WE LEARNED THAT LOVE NOT
ONLY MEANS HAVING TO
SAY YOU'RE SORRY,
BUT MOST TIMES YOU
ACTUALLY HAVE TO MEAN IT.
THESE DAYS, SORRY IS A PART
OF OUR DAILY VOCABULARY,
ALONG WITH "OW," "OOPS,"
AND "HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?"
MY WIFE AND I
ARE SORRY A LOT.
FOR INSTANCE, I'M SORRY
I SNORED LAST NIGHT.
AND BERNICE IS SORRY SHE TRIED
TO SMOTHER ME WITH A PILLOW.
LIKEWISE, BERNICE IS SORRY
SHE BOUGHT ME THAT SWEATER
WITH THE ELVES ON IT.
AND I'M SORRY I USED IT
TO MOP UP THE PAINT SPILL.
SEE, SORRY WORKS.
IT'S THE BEST
TOOL WE HAVE.
AT LEAST UNTIL THEY
BUILD A TIME MACHINE
SO WE CAN GO BACK AND
NOT DO THE STUPID THINGS
WE'RE APOLOGIZING FOR.
THAT MOVIE WAS WRONG.
LOVE IS NOT
NEVER HAVING TO
SAY YOU'RE SORRY.
IF YOU SPEND YOUR LIFE WITH
ONE WOMAN AND NEVER APOLOGIZE,
YOU'RE IN FOR A
ROUGH RIDE, BELIEVE ME.
I KNOW YOU DIDN'T
WANNA HEAR THAT.
SORRY.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ UPBEAT JAZZ ]
CHEERS
HERE'S TO
YOU AND ME
BABY, CAN'T YOU SEE
WE CAN WIN THE DAY
SHOW THE WAY
WE'VE GOT THE
WORLD BEFORE US
WE'RE GONNA BE RICH
NOT POOR US
DON'T BE A BRONTOSAURUS
GO TO IT,
WE CAN DO IT
[ MUSIC ]
THIS IS GOING TO
BE BROADCAST NATIONALLY,
SO DON'T BE
NERVOUS, OKAY.
[ SHUDDERING ]
WELCOME TO "DECISION DEBATE"
WITH YOUR HOST HAROLD GREEN.
[ voice cracking ]
I'M HAROLD.
EACH CANDIDATE HAS
30 SEXIST -- SECONDS --
SECONDS --
30 SECONDS TO DISCUSS
WHAT THEY'RE GOING TO BE
DISCUSSING --
WE'LL START WITH
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD.
THANK YOU, UH, HAROLD.
FRIENDS, YOU KNOW ME.
YOU KNOW THAT I'M THERE
WHEN YOU HAVE A PROBLEM.
LIKE WHEN YOUR SEPTICS
EXPLODE AND YOU CAN'T BREATHE
AND YOUR EYES ARE
WATERING SO BAD
THAT IS SHRINKS YOUR TIE.
BUT I GO IN THERE
AND I CLEAN UP THE PROBLEM
AND I TAKE IT
AWAY WITH ME...
AND DUMP IT IN THE LAKE.
SO YOU HAVE A CHANCE
TO SHOW YOUR APPRECIATION.
NOW, ACCORDING
TO THE POLLS,
I'M IN THE DEEP
STUFF RIGHT NOW.
SO I'M COUNTING ON EACH
AND EVERY ONE OF YOU
TO SUCK IT UP AND CAST A VOTE
FOR WINSTON ROTHSCHILD.
WE ALL KNOW POLITICS STINKS.
SO WHY NOT SEND A GUY
WHO'S USED TO IT?
[ APPLAUSE ]
THAT'S 30 SECONDS.
THANK YOU.
NOW MR. MIKE HAMAR.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
A VOTE FOR MIKE HAMAR
IS A VOTE FOR HONESTY.
AND CHANGE.
AND ME.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU,
RIP TAYLOR.
OKAY --
ACTUALLY, UNCLE RED,
MIKE STILL HAS 15 SECONDS.
Mike: HUH?!
YEAH.
AND, UH --
OH, ALSO, UM --
OH, I ALMOST FORGOT,
IF ELECTED, I PROMISE --
AND THAT'S 30!
OKAY, GOOD.
YOU WANNA BE FAIR HERE.
OKAY, UNCLE RED.
WELL, I DON'T HAVE
MUCH TO SAY.
I'VE BEEN DOIN'
THE JOB FOR 20 YEARS.
IF YOU'RE OKAY WITH THAT,
TOSS ME A VOTE.
AND IF YOU'RE NOT,
GET SOMEBODY ELSE,
AND I'LL GET OVER IT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
UNCLE RED,
YOU PROMISED NOTHING.
AND I'M JUST
THE MAN TO DO IT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Red: WALTER WAS HAVING TROUBLE,
COULDN'T GET HIS CAR GOING,
SO BOTH OF US OPENED THE HOOD
AND PRETENDED WE KNEW WHAT
WE WERE DOING.
WE'RE JUST TOUCHING
STUFF, BASICALLY.
[ HONKING ]
OKAY, THAT'S THE HORN.
I FIGURED MAYBE IF I HOOK UP
SOME JUMPER CABLES,
SOMETHING SHOULD HAPPEN.
I WAS RIGHT.
SO NOW WALTER'S FLASHING THE
WORK LIGHT IN MY FACE
AND I WANNA GET HIM UNDER THE
CAR AS QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
MAYBE IT'S SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE TRANSMISSION LINKAGE.
JUST GET AWAY, GET ON
THE OTHER SIDE OF THINGS.
HE NEEDS A LITTLE
HELP GETTING UNDER.
HE CAN'T GET FAR
ENOUGH UNDER THE CAR.
SO I MAY HAVE
OVERREACTED HERE.
BUT YOU KNOW,
YOU STOP HIM
AND WHEEL HIM BACK IN.
IT'S OKAY, I HAVE
A LICENSE FOR THIS.
AND THEN WE
BRING HIM THROUGH.
HE'S COMPLAINING
A LITTLE BIT.
LET'S JUST PUSH HIM
BACK UNDER ENOUGH TO --
THERE, NOW YOU CAN
GET TO WORK.
OKAY, LATER THAT DAY...
I WAS HELPING
AS MUCH AS I COULD.
I DECIDED MAYBE I'D GO
AND GET MYSELF A COFFEE,
BUT BEING THOUGHTFUL,
I ASKED WALTER
IF HE'D LIKE A COFFEE TOO.
AND HE SAID YES, HE WOULD.
HE'D HAVE A DOUBLE LATTE
MOCHA FRAPPUCCINO,
WITH, WHAT WAS IT,
TWO ARTIFICIAL SWEETENERS
AND JUST A DASH
OF COCOA POWDER,
JUST A SLICE OF MY LIFE
I'LL NEVER GET BACK.
SO I JUMP IN
THE POSSUM VAN.
I'M TRYING TO DO
THE GOOD THING.
I DIDN'T REALISE THAT THE CORD
FROM THE WORK LIGHT --
BUT TO ME, WALTER
COULD'VE JUST LET GO,
BUT OH NO.
AND YOU KNOW,
I TOLD HIM BEFORE,
IF YOU CAN'T SEE THE MIRRORS,
I CAN'T SEE YOU.
NOW, OF COURSE, I DIDN'T EVEN
REALISE THAT, UH --
YOU KNOW, IF I'D HAVE KNOWN
WALTER WAS WITH ME,
I WOULDN'T HAVE
GOTTEN THEM TO GO.
AND MY HAND IS STILL
TWITCHIN' FROM THE --
AND WALTER'S MAD AT ME,
THROWS THE COFFEE,
AND THAT STARTS THE CAR!
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
SEE, I TOLD HIM NOT
TO GET THE DECAF.
OH, AND ONE MORE
FOR MIKE.
YES!
AND UNCLE RED.
AND FINALLY...
WINSTON.
SO TALLY
THE VOTES NOW.
OKAY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I GOT SO MANY VOTES.
NOBODY CAN.
WELL, IT'S A TIE,
A THREE-WAY TIE.
IT CAN'T BE A TIE.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
DID YOU VOTE?
YEAH.
OH, I DIDN'T VOTE!
I DIDN'T VOTE.
I STILL GOT TWO MINUTES BEFORE
THE POLLING STATIONS CLOSE.
I GOTTA HURRY.
WHEW!
Red: WHAT IS IT?
WHO'D YOU VOTE FOR?
AH! UNCLE RED!
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, AS OFFICIAL SCRUTINEER,
I DECLARE RED OUR
NEW LODGE LEADER.
Red: ALL RIGHT,
I ACCEPT THAT.
THE PEOPLE HAVE SPOKEN.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
AND SO HAS THE POSSUM.
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
SORRY, GUYS.
[ chuckling ]
SO, UH, HAROLD,
UH, HOW COME YOU
VOTED FOR ME?
NO. NO. NO. NO.
AWAY YOU GO.
GO ON.
GET OUTTA HERE.
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I WON THE ELECTION,
AND I'M HOPING TO MAKE OUR BED
INTO MY PARTY PLATFORM.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY, SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, ONCE AGAIN,
YOU'VE ELECTED ME
AS LODGE LEADER.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT
I DON'T FEEL ANY BETTER
ABOUT IT THAN YOU DO.