You know what this is?
It's called
a skeet thrower.
It's for hunters who only
like birds that fly in
a straight line.
This would have been real
handy when I had my
paper route.
But that's just my
creative side coming out,
Bernice hates that.
But hey, I've got an even
better use for this thing,
every man's dream,
an automatic
beverage dispenser.
See when I'm out
on the lake fishing,
the drinks'll get
warm in the sun
but if keep the cooler
cool in the shade
I've got to bring
the boat back in
every time I need a drink.
So in an eight-hour day,
that's only going to leave
about 12 minutes for fishing
but this rig keeps them cold
and then when I feel
a thirst coming on,
I just pull on
the trigger line
and the unit will deliver
the drinks right to me.
When Mohammed can't come
to the Mountain Dew,
the Mountain Dew has
to come to Mohammed.
See, I cut a hole in
the bottom of the cooler
and lay the
cans on their side
so they'll roll
out one at a time
and then I've got
this bungee cord
to reset the mechanism
after each toss.
And my trigger line
serves a dual purpose,
I ran it through an eyelet
on the front of the thrower
so as I move
around the lake,
the unit stays
aimed right at me.
You're probably as
impressed with me as I am.
Man, I'm getting thirsty,
oh... waiter...
Perfect.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
All right.
Thank you very much.
Appreciate it.
Big, big week up at
the lodge this week.
You know they have those
companies that put on seminars
for people who like to spend
all their time figuring out
how come they never
get anything done?
Well, apparently
they're sending
a bunch of them up
here to Possum Lodge.
I mean, I always think
that self-help companies
are a waste of money
but it's fine if they're
going to waste it here.
Oh, Uncle Red,
this is so exciting!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Boy oh Boy!
Aren't you excited?
This is so exciting!
These are very successful
people that are coming up
here, you know.
Yeah, these are
movers and shakers.
Oh yeah?
Yeah.
Movers and shakers,
losers and fakers,
Harold.
Who cares as long as
the cheque clears?
Boy, these are the top
CEO's in the country.
I'll finally have
someone to talk to.
Well that'll be good
for all of us, Harold.
Hey, you know, if
these are high rollers
maybe I should get in
a couple of kegs and
a bunch of cigars
and set a room full
of poker tables.
Oh, no, no, no, they're
here to explore nature.
Well, those things
are my nature, Harold.
You know, I'm just thinking
that maybe I should spend
a fair whack of time
with these guys.
I mean, these guys
are winners, Harold.
Around here, that's an
endangered species.
That's very true.
Red?
Yeah?
They're here.
The CEO's, the
movers and shakers?
Yeah, I guess.
Okay, well, go tell them
I'm going to crack
open the bar
and we'll go down and
have a skinny dip, okay?
Maybe you better
tell them.
[ LAUGHTER ]
They're women!
Woo-hoo!
This is excellent!
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
Today's winner receives
this coupon for a free visit
to Crazy Lu's Super-Competitive
Discount Save-a-torium.
Where the motto is,
if you can find a cheaper
price anywhere else,
we'll go over there and buy
it before you get a chance to
and then we'll sell it
to you for our price.
Okay, cover
your ears, Winston.
Mr. Green, you have 30 seconds
to get Winston Rothschild
to say this word...
Yeah, all right.
All right, Mike.
And GO!
Okay, Winston, what do you
think of when I say first?
Rothschild's Sewage and
Septic Sucking Services.
Okay, okay, okay,
try this: Number two.
Rothschild's Sewage and
Septic Sucking Services.
Okay, no, okay, okay.
What do you call the place
between first and third?
Pitcher's mound?
No, okay.
Remember Dalton was
having a few problems
when he first
married Anne-Marie
and he came to you and said
he was having certain
kinds of thoughts?
Suicidal.
Okay, no.
If you got to
a lodge meeting
and somebody puts
a motion on the floor,
what's the next step?
I clean it up.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, no.
Your cousin is
your first cousin
but what's his son called?
Oh, Uncle Helen.
We're almost out
of time, Mr. Green.
Yeah, okay,
let's go another way.
There are 60 of these
in every minute.
Septic overflows.
That's why I'm so busy.
I'm thinking about
getting a second truck.
There we go!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
You're the man!
Welcome to
Talking to Animals.
A special treat today is
local animal control officer
Ed Frid is bringing us
another interesting animal,
the cardboard box.
Completely wrong
as always, Red.
No, I was
just being funny.
Wrong again.
Okay, okay.
This box contains a very
rare jumping frog from
the Amazon jungle.
These frogs are
excellent jumpers.
You're a pretty good
jumper yourself, Ed.
I think he's
just hungry.
I didn't want to
overfeed him
because there's holes
in the bottom of the box
and I just had
my truck cleaned.
Don't ever transport
a wild turkey
in the front seat
of your vehicle...
especially around Thanksgiving.
No, I can see that.
So what does a
jumping frog eat?
Oh, flies.
Yeah, yeah, I always
keep a few on me.
Oh, now you got something
to feed them to.
Rather than desperately
trying to be funny,
why don't you hold
the box for me.
Oh, yeah,
all right, sure.
All right,
careful, careful.
They love flies.
To this frog, each fly
is like a filet mignon.
Oh yeah, I never
had a filet mignon
but I love frog legs.
Wow!
Watch out! Easy, easy.
Put him down, put him down!
Okay, he's settling down.
Okay, he'll be okay
for a few moments.
Okay, boy, he's got some
strong let muscles that guy.
Oh yeah.
Then when they see a live
fly they go really nuts!
That's why I
only use dead ones.
[ BUZZING ]
Oh, they're not all dead.
I'll distract the frog,
you shoo the fly away.
Mr. Frog! Hello!
Look over here!
Oh!
Ooo, ooh!
Got him,
got him, got him!
Okay, hold him,
don't let go.
I don't think
he's in there, Ed.
Well, where is he?
What?
[ FROG CROAKING ]
Shh, shh, shh.
I think he's
in your pants!
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, oh!
Well, he said
they love flies.
When you're young
you can't sit still
because there's a great
big world out there
just waiting for you.
When you get older
you can't sit still either
but that's
just the hemorrhoids.
The point is, men don't like
to sit still for too long.
Like when you're
driving in the car
and all of a sudden
you get a charley-horse
and your leg flies up,
knocks your coffee over
spills into the
ignition wires,
you've got
yourself a car fire.
I wish I had a nickel for
every time that's happened.
So when you're on a
trip wouldn't it be great
to be able to stand up
once in a while?
The answer is yes.
Real men do lots
of things standing up.
What we need to do
is maximize the leg room
and then convert some of
that leg room into head room.
That's not going to do it.
I took the back seat out
and moved the driver's seat
away from the steering wheel.
The downside is, you now
have less room for passengers.
The upside is, you now
That gives us enough floor
space for standing up
but we'll move
the seat forward
so that we can start from
the sitting position
and then just
slide her back
when the sciatica
starts acting up.
Okay, we have a couple
of choices here.
You could put blocks
on the pedals
like your dad did
with your tricycle
or you could hire
an ex-basketball player
as your chauffeur.
I'm going to go with Plan A.
Now we need to
check the headroom.
You want the roof to be
at least six inches
above your head
especially if you
have potholes.
I'm going to need another
two-and-a-half feet
of headroom,
but here again, I only
need the extra height
when I'm standing up.
So what I need is some type
of retractable hydraulic lift.
Where am I going to find
something like that?
Oh wait...
Now I'll just
cut the roof off
and mount it on
those trunk lifts.
With a brain this big,
you need extra headroom.
Great, cordless saw.
Maybe I should have done
this with a convertible
but we're good to go.
I've got my roof mounted
on my trunk-raising mechanism
so now, when I get
tired of sitting,
I just slap her
into cruise control,
slide the seat back and press
the trunk release button,
which is my way of
raising the roof.
Then I just stand up until
the feeling comes back
into my legs.
Now, I was going to wear
sunglasses to keep the
bugs out of my eyes
but I put them in the trunk
and it doesn't
open anymore.
Other than that, we're
ready for a test drive.
So remember, if the women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
I'm looking forward
to a long trip
but there was a time
I wouldn't stand for it.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I need to talk to you
guys about a milestone
a lot of us have reached.
You know, milestones
are like kidney stones.
You just got to close your
eyes, bite your lip
and let them pass.
I'm guessing that by now
you're getting a little
long in the tooth
and chances are,
it's not even your tooth.
At this time in our
lives, like it or not,
we have to start
looking dapper.
We have to wear nice clothes
and we have to keep
them clean and pressed.
You no longer look good
in a baggy sweatshirt.
That's because you are
a baggy sweatshirt.
Those folds and
flaps are you.
So now your clothes have
got to always be neat
and completely
wrinkle-free.
Beauticians say that your
full-length fully-clothed
appearance
should never contain
more than 150 wrinkles.
Your forehead covers that.
So get a hat to
cover your forehead.
The sad truth is that
old guys have to dress
better than young guys.
Just accept it.
I suggest you wear a
shirt and tie at breakfast,
a three-piece suit when
you're washing the car
and a tuxedo when
you go to church.
Look at the bright side,
every day you're getting
a little closer to
your own funeral.
It'll save
the kids a bundle
if you're already
dressed for it.
Remember, I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
[ APPLAUSE ]
If you need to get
your septic bed moved,
call me soon.
If you need to get your
septic bed to stop moving,
call me now.
Yeah but I don't know why
they can't just leave
things the way they are.
Well, around here,
the way things are
doesn't mean that's
the way they should be.
Boy, everybody
tries to change me.
Take that as a hint.
So we've got these women
senior managers up here
and it's
driving me crazy.
I mean, I spend all day
restocking the fridge
with bottled water
and then going around to
make sure all the toilet
seats are down.
I think there's
a connection.
Well, they're very friendly
and they're polite.
You know, they've made
a huge difference to
the whole lodge.
They cleaned up all the car
parts off the front porch.
I didn't know we had
a view of the lake.
But they're not
supposed to be here
to wreck my world, Harold.
I mean, this is a retreat.
Yes, it is and
you should retreat.
No, I just need to
re-group, that's all.
I'm going to get a chance
to do that this afternoon
'cause Dalton
has rented a bus.
He's going to take
the ladies on a tour
of the area.
Oh, that'll
be very nice.
I think it'll
work all right.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Can I help you?
I think it's Dalton!
Yes, it is.
I cleaned out my car
and I found my comb.
Boy, these woman are
changing you, aren't they?
Yes, they are.
You know and
I kind of like it.
I enjoy having them around.
It makes me feel
almost bubbly.
You don't seem
yourself at all.
Yes, I know.
Yes, Anne-Marie
noticed that too.
She gave me kind of a
funny look at breakfast
this morning
so I'm going to save
my energy all day
just in case.
Well, see you
boys later.
Where are you taking
the ladies, Mr. Humphrey?
To my store.
I've got a free
gift and a corsage
for anyone who
spends over $200.
You know, some
of the ladies say
I look a little bit
like Jack Nicholson.
Boy, they're really
getting to you,
aren't they?
Red, they make me want
to be a better salesman.
RED: Bill had decided to
spend a day out on the lake
in a little home-made
boat that he made.
He tied her up not
only to the dock
but apparently
to his own leg.
Away you go, all right.
And a little picnic
area we have
down near the edge
of the water there.
Bill was taking all of it.
Bill doesn't like to
make a lot of trips
so he likes to try to
take everything at once.
I mean that's the plan.
It doesn't all make it
to the destination.
Bill hasn't grasped the
concept of gravity just yet.
So by the time he gets
down to the dock
there's not too much left
but at least he can go
fishing, you know.
So he jumps into the boat
and he's going to get
ready to paddle off
and he notices the oars --
the oars are gone, Bill.
No oars.
Doesn't quite know
what happened there
but don't
worry about it.
Just go get a paddle.
Go on get a paddle,
all right.
Away you go.
You know, sometimes you can
be looking for something
and you can't see it and it
jumps straight up
and bites you.
Okay, there's your paddle.
Now he goes back.
Now at least you can get
going, get your day
of fishing in.
And he sits down.
Now he's got no seat
in the boat.
So he's starting to think,
what the heck is going
on around here?
Things are like,
disappearing like crazy.
Well, you got a lawn chair,
go get a lawn chair.
You got to adapt in life.
You've got to go with the flow.
Oh, oh, oh...
All right, that'll be fine.
You can sit on that.
You've got your paddle.
You should be fine.
So he jumps in the boat and...
Now we've got no
floor in the boat
so now he goes back,
gets the cooler
and now when he comes
down to the dock,
he sees that the sides
and the transom are
missing from the boat
and he's so struck with that
that he doesn't notice the
whole dock is also missing.
Something very, very
strange is going on.
So he's just got to --
Bill -- Bill just sit down,
take a deep breath
and re-group.
I'm not sure that's
a complete chair, Bill.
Boy oh boy,
this is starting to
feel a bit like the
Twilight Zone for Bill
and he takes the cooler up
and that's not a
complete table either
and now he's starting
to really panic.
Like something
weird is going on.
There's the barrel,
what happened there?
and the picket fence is gone
and this is just very odd.
So he decides just to go
home and just maybe
have a little sleep
and maybe this was all
a dream of some kind.
And he gets there and he sees
that his mailbox is okay
but there's no post
and this is very odd.
And then he pulls up
in front of the house,
and the house is okay
but the dog house
doesn't look quite right.
I don't think it's a
complete dog house.
You know, this was just
a complete misunderstanding
as it turns out.
In the old days, now,
I know they used to call
this vandalism
but since about '97, I
believe it's called recycling.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Could someone please
explain to me
why a bag of snacks
has to be welded shut?
During the playoffs a
man could starve to death.
Luckily, I have
an easy solution.
Remember in science class,
there was a thing
called a bell jar?
Me neither.
But apparently they
would put a ringing bell
inside a glass jar
and then suck all the
air out of the space,
kind of what Harold does
during a conversation.
Once the air was out of
there, you had a vacuum,
you couldn't hear
the bell anymore.
No such luck with Harold.
But I figure we can use
that same technology
to open our bag of snacks,
because inside here
we've got air pressure,
and as soon as it
goes into a vacuum,
something's gotta give.
You don't need a
bell jar either,
just something air tight
and I don't mean an alibi,
I'm thinking diving helmet.
And you set the whole unit
down on a rubber car floormat,
smooth side up so
you get a good seal.
Okay, then you hook up a
heavy-duty industrial
vacuum cleaner to
the breather pipe
and that snack bag
will burst open
like the seam on Moose
Thompson's Sunday pants.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Well, you know,
having those women
CEO's up here
hasn't been too bad.
It's given us a break
from each other, anyhow.
They're nice, they're
bright and they smell good.
I am so proud
of you, Uncle Red.
That always
scares me, Harold.
Hey, I spend 95%
of my time with men
so this is a new
experience for me.
Yeah, but things seemed
to go a little better
once you started
talking to them.
Yeah, I suppose.
You know, when you
don't talk to men,
they appreciate that.
Yeah but see, then you don't
know what they're thinking
you know and they can't help
you with your problems.
I know, it's great.
Well, I'm still
very proud of you.
You know, the way
you interacted
with those women
head honchos like that
'cause I know, you're not
comfortable around people
who have, like, an
education or teeth or --
Don't ruin it, Harold.
Well, the point is, men
and women, pretty much,
we're all the same.
Well, that's certainly
true in your case.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Oh, meeting time.
Yeah, you go ahead,
Harold.
Tell the ladies
I'll be right down.
Oh, they'll
be so excited.
So if my wife is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting
and I've been thinking, hey,
I'm the CEO of the lodge,
you're the CEO of our home,
what say we have
a high-level meeting,
maybe consider a merger.
[ LAUGHTER ]
To the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of
myself and Harold
and the whole gang up here
at Possum Lodge...
keep your stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Okay everybody,
c'mon hurry up and sit down.
Sit down please.
Please would you sit down.
Thank you.
C'mon you guys, sit down.
Sit down.
All rise, please.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
Sit down.
All right-y, bow your heads
for the woman's prayer.
I am woman,
hear me roar,
I'm in charge,
get over it.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]