AT MY AGE, A GOOD LONG SHAG
MEANS ONLY ONE THING...
CARPETING.
AND I'LL TELL YOU, IT'S THE
UGLIEST ROLL IN THE STORE.
THEY THOUGHT THEY'D
NEVER UNLOAD IT.
SO I GOT IT AT
A GREAT PRICE.
THEY'RE SO HAPPY
TO GET RID OF IT,
THEY EVEN LENT ME THIS
FORKLIFT TO TAKE IT HOME.
THEY MUST THINK I'M NUTS.
BUT THEY'RE WRONG.
I'M NOT CRAZY,
I'M LAZY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE THAT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
WE'RE ALL GETTING READY FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE BARBEQUE GAMES.
THAT'S WHERE ALL THE MEMBERS
BRING IN THEIR GAME,
AND WE BARBEQUE IT.
NOW, I WAS SUPPOSED TO
GET THE BARBEQUE SAUCE,
BUT YOU KNOW THE STUFF THAT
YOU BUY, IT'S WATERED DOWN,
IT'S OVERPRICED,
PLUS I FORGOT TO GET IT.
SO INSTEAD, I WENT DOWN
IN THE BASEMENT
AND MIXED UP MY OWN.
I CALL IT
RED'S HOT SAUCE.
PRETTY SPICY,
I'LL TELL YOU.
MY SLOGAN IS:
WHO SAYS MEN NEVER CRY?
IT WAS EITHER THAT
OR WIND AT MY BACK.
HEY, RED, HAROLD'S LOOKING
FOR THE BARBEQUE SAUCE.
HE WANTS THAT
MILD HONEY MESQUITE.
NO, NO, NO.
WE'RE GOING ANOTHER
WAY THIS YEAR, DALTON.
RED'S HOT SAUCE.
OH, REALLY!
WHAT'S IN IT?
UH, MAINLY KETCHUP,
BUT THERE'S SOME
OTHER STUFF.
I GOT MUSTARD
AND JALEPEÑOS
AND CAYENNE
AND WASABI
OH, HO HO!
AND HORSERADISH
IN HERE.
I GOT SOME ALLSPICE,
I GOT A SECRET
INGREDIENT
AND ONE REALLY
MOIST PRUNE.
WOW!
GEEZ,
IT LOOKS GREAT.
WHAT'S THE
SECRET INGREDIENT?
EVEN I DON'T KNOW,
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU!
YOU KNOW, THERE WAS
THIS CAN OF BLUE
GOOEY STUFF
AT THE BACK OF THE PANTRY,
SO I, YOU KNOW --
MIND IF I
HAVE A TASTE?
NO! NO! NOT THAT WAY.
WHOA. WHOA. WHOA.
HERE, PUT A LITTLE
ON A TOOTHPICK
AND TRY THAT.
OH! HA HA!
HEH. HEH. HEH.
HMM.
YEAH? YEAH?
YOU KNOW, THAT PRUNE
GIVES IT A NICE --
AH, YEAH. YEAH!
YEAH.
OH, BOY.
WHOA!
WHOO!
[ SIGH ]
THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD!
I'M TELLIN' YOU.
YEAH.
EXCUSE ME!
YOU GUYS --
[ APPLAUSE AND CHEERS ]
WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
HAVE YOU GOT A
PROBLEM OR SOMETHING,
BECAUSE MY LOINS
ARE OVERHEATING.
I'M HERE FOR
THE BARBEQUE SAUCE.
WHAT'S THIS?
THAT'S
BARBEQUE SAUCE.
THAT'S BARBEQUE SAUCE?
VERY MUCH SO.
OKAY.
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
MILD HONEY MESQUITE.
NO, NO, IT'S SOMETHING
A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
VERY MUCH SO.
HAROLD, YOU'RE THE ONE
ALWAYS COMPLAINING THAT
I NEVER TRY ANYTHING NEW.
HM, OKAY.
WHAT?
NUTHIN'.
NO, NOTHING.
IT'S GOOD.
GO.
GOOD. GOOD.
[ SHRIEKING! ]
[ SHRIEKING ]
[ HEARTY LAUGH ]
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY, MR. DALTON HUMPHREY
WILL BE PLAYING FOR THIS
GORGEOUS NECKLACE
FROM DIAMOND JOE'S
DISCOUNT JEWELLER
AND HOG FAT RENDERING PLANT.
"AT DIAMOND JOE'S,
WE PUT PEARLS BEFORE SWINE."
OKAY, COVER YOUR
EARS HERE, DALTON.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON TO SAY
THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
OKAY, AND... GO!
OKAY, DALTON,
WHEN TWO PEOPLE DO BATTLE
AND NEITHER ONE
COMES OUT AHEAD,
THAT'S CALLED A...
MARRIAGE.
NO. NO. I'M SAYING --
THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT'S A DEAD HEAT.
IT'S A...
HONEYMOON.
NO. OKAY.
OKAY, NO.
OKAY, PRETEND ANNE MARIE
COMES HOME IN A BAD MOOD.
PRETEND! HA!
NO, OKAY, BUT YOU
WANNA MAKE HER FEEL GOOD,
SO YOU TURN ON THE
TAP IN THE BATHTUB
AND YOU...
DROWN MYSELF?
OKAY. OKAY. OKAY.
THIS IS ANOTHER WORD FOR
TAKING MONEY OUT OF
YOUR BANK ACCOUNT.
HEH. HEH.
TAKING MONEY
OUT
OF MY BANK ACCOUNT!
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
RED, YOU'RE ALMOST
OUTTA TIME.
YEAH. YEAH.
OKAY, DALTON, THIS IS A
FOUR-LETTER WORD, OKAY,
BUT IT'S PART
OF ANOTHER WORD.
IT'S SOMETHING YOU
PULL OUT IN THE BEDROOM.
YEAH.
OH, MY GOD!
I CAN'T SAY THAT!
I GOTTA WITHDRAW.
THERE WE GO.
GRAB YOUR CANS
AND LABEL MAKERS
COZ IT'S TIME FOR
HAROLD'S HOBBY HOUSE!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
MY FIRST GUEST TODAY --
MY FIRST GUEST TODAY,
HE'S A HOBBYIST,
AND HE'S ALSO THE OWNER
OF THE LOCAL -- THE CRAFTS
SUPPLY STORE HERE IN TOWN.
IT'S THE
HOT DOG HOBBY SHOP.
YEAH -- YEAH,
HE'S LIVING HIS DREAM.
PLEASE WELCOME
MY FIRST GUEST,
MR. FRANK KOEPKE!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WELCOME, FRANK.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
SOME OF YOUR
VIEWERS MAY KNOW ME
AS THAT FELLA WHO MAKES
HANDY HOUSEHOLD ITEMS
USING ONLY HOT DOGS.
WOW!
NOW, WHY HOT DOGS?
I-IT'S CHEAPER
THAN LUMBER.
REALLY?
COZ YOU SEE,
I WOULD THINK THAT
A 4X8 SHEET OF WIENER
WOULD ACTUALLY COST
MORE THAN PLYWOOD.
NO!
NO?
NOT IF YOU BUY IN BULK
AND VERY CLOSE TO
THE EXPIRY DATE.
THEN YOU CAN MAKE
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
IT'S A
DOG FOOD DISH
MADE ENTIRELY
OUT OF HOT DOGS.
PERFECT FOR
WIENER DOGS.
I LOVE WIENER DOGS.
WELL, I LOVE
THE NAME.
WIENER DOGS.
JUST, UM, FRANK, UM,
WOULDN'T THE DOG
JUST EAT THE DISH?
NO.
I DON'T THINK SO, NO.
I DO.
I THINK THE DOG WOULD
JUST EAT THE DISH.
UH, WOULD ALL
HOT DOG EXPERTS PLEASE
RAISE THEIR HANDS?
AHA!
I THINK A DOG KNOWS
ENOUGH NOT TO EAT
ITS SERVING DISH.
DOGS!
DOGS BARK AT THEIR
OWN REFLECTIONS.
THEY LICK PLACES I
CAN'T EVEN SAY ON TV.
IT'S TRUE. IT'S TRUE.
I'M PRETTY SURE
I KNOW DOGS WELL ENOUGH
THAT A DOG WOULD
EAT THAT DISH
AND THEN HE'D
LICK THE FLOOR
AND THEN WASH IT ALL DOWN
WITH A BIG GULP OF
TOILET BOWL WATER.
WHAT ELSE DO YOU
HAVE FOR US, FRANK?
WELL, NOTHING SAYS
ROMANCE LIKE CANDLES.
AND YOU JUST
CAN'T GO WRONG
WITH THESE ALL BEEF
CANDLE STICKS.
AND THE BEST PART IS
THEY'RE SCENTED.
IS THAT HICKORY?
YES, IT IS.
I THOUGHT SO.
IT ALSO COMES IN
BARBEQUE, GARLIC, CAJUN
WHICH ISN'T A FLAVOUR,
BUT IT REALLY
IMPRESSES THE LADIES.
OH, ALSO HAVE SOMETHING
VERY SPECIAL HERE.
TADA!
GUESS WHO THAT IS.
SIGOURNEY WIENER?
NO.
MR. STUPID HOT DOG HEAD?
I DON'T KNOW!
YOU KNOW WHAT,
IT'S ACTUALLY MY FAULT,
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T
QUITE FINISHED IT YET.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
IT'S HIS FAULT.
CAN'T BLAME ME.
WHEN I SAY
IT WAS MY FAULT,
I WAS JUST BEING POLITE.
OH.
HA! THAT'S ME!
WE HAVE A WIENER.
THAT'S GOOD.
THE TEENAGE YEARS
ARE PAINFUL, DIFFICULT
AND AWKWARD.
AND NOT JUST
FOR THE PARENTS,
ESPECIALLY IF THE TEENS GET
INTERESTED IN HOBBIES
LIKE KNOCKING OVER
LIQUOR STORES
OR BEATING UP THE ELDERLY.
AND THE MOST
DANGEROUS STUFF IN LIFE
HAPPENS LATE AT NIGHT,
WHICH YOU PROVED
DURING THEIR CONCEPTION.
SO THE BEST WAY TO PREVENT
BAD THINGS FROM HAPPENING
IS TO GET YOUR KIDS TO
COME HOME AT A DECENT HOUR.
TO DO THAT YOU NEED
SOMETHING TO ATTRACT THEM.
YOU KNOW, OTHER THAN THE
$5,000 WORTH OF VIDEO GAMES
AND COMPUTER EQUIPMENT
YOU BOUGHT 'EM.
YOU NEED A LURE,
A TEEN TRAP.
SEE, WHEN A
TEENAGER GETS HOME,
FIRST PLACE HE
GOES IS THE FRIDGE.
A FRIDGE DOOR
HAS MAGICAL POWERS
THAT DRAWS IN
ALL TEENAGERS.
MAYBE IT'S FROM THE MAGNETS
ON THERE, I DUNNO.
BUT THE SAME KID WHO CAN'T
FOCUS ON THE BLACKBOARD
FOR 30 SECONDS
WILL SPEND AN HOUR,
BENT OVER,
STARING INTO THIS BABY.
SO TAKE THAT POWER
AND USE IT...
ON THE FRONT
OF YOUR HOUSE.
NOW WHEN YOUR KID
IS OUT A NIGHT, DANCING
OR THROWING ROCKS
AT TRAFFIC OR WHATEVER,
HE'LL REMEMBER
THIS FRIDGE DOOR,
AND HE'LL WANNA COME RUNNIN'
HOME TO SEE WHAT'S INSIDE.
AND HERE'S
AN ADDED BONUS...
HE'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO SNEAK INTO THE HOUSE.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY
THAT IN A MAN'S LIFE
HE'LL OWN AT LEAST 10 CARS.
WELL, MAYBE NOT "OWN",
BUT AT LEAST MAKE PAYMENTS ON.
GUYS GET DIFFERENT
TYPES OF VEHICLES,
DEPENDING ON THEIR AGE
AND SITUATION.
AT FIRST IT'S
SOMETHING SLEEK AND SPORTY
THAT SAYS,
I'M SINGLE AND FAST,
AND THERE'S NO ROOM FOR A BABY
CARRIAGE IN THIS UNIT.
BUT AFTER A FEW MILES AND A
BUNCH OF SERVICE CENTRES,
THINGS HAVE CHANGED.
HE'S NOT A
SPORTS CAR ANYMORE.
WHAT WAS ONCE
SLEEK AND SPORTY,
IS NOW MEEK AND FORTY.
HE'S A MINIVAN.
BUT HE DOESN'T
CALL IT A MINIVAN.
HE CALLS IT
A "MAGIC WAGON".
OH, SURE, A RUSTED OUT
DUMPSTER ON WHEELS
IS A MAGIC WAGON.
AND DANDRUFF
IS FAIRY DUST.
THE CAR YOU DRIVE IS A
MIRROR OF YOUR OWN VITALITY.
AND HAVE YOU LOOKED
IN THAT MIRROR LATELY?
"OBJECTS MAY APPEAR
OLDER THAN THEY ARE."
NOT PRETTY, IS IT?
BIG AND SLOW,
AIRBAGS EVERYWHERE
AND A HUGE TRUNK.
BUT HERE'S THE GOOD NEWS.
AT THIS POINT,
YOU DON'T NEED SPEED.
YOU DON'T HAVE
VERY FAR TO GO,
AND YOU SURE DON'T
NEED TO GET THERE EARLY.
JUST RELAX, TAKE
YOUR FOOT OFF THE GAS,
AND DO WHAT YOU SPENT
YOUR WHOLE LIFE PERFECTING,
COAST.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU THINK
FEAR FACTOR'S GROSS,
I EAT WITH THESE HANDS!
WELL, THE BARBEQUE
GAMES WERE SO SUCCESSFUL,
WE'RE TAKING RED'S HOT SAUCE
TO A WHOLE NEW LEVEL.
WE'RE GOIN' COMMERCIAL.
BUT IT'S NOT ENOUGH
TO HAVE A PRODUCT.
YOU ALSO HAVE TO HAVE
THE MARKETING.
I MEAN, WHERE WOULD
PAUL NEWMAN SALAD DRESSING BE
WITHOUT PAUL NEWMAN?
OR MICHELIN TIRES WITHOUT
THE BIG, HAIRLESS, FRENCH,
ALBINO, MARSHMALLOW GUY?
OR JANET JACKSON
WITHOUT THE SUPERBOWL?
SO OUR MARKETING GIMMICK
IS OUR PACKAGING.
IT'S A WATER PISTOL, HUH?
NOW YOU CAN SPICE
UP YOUR STEAK,
WITHOUT EVEN GETTING
OUT OF YOUR LAWN CHAIR.
YOU CAN SHOOT
YOUR GAME TWICE.
AND I GOT A
NEW NAME FOR IT...
RED'S SATURDAY
NIGHT SPECIAL SAUCE.
IF YOU'RE GOIN'
TO A PARTY,
MAKE SURE
YOU'RE PACKIN' HEAT.
UNCLE RED! UNCLE RED!
WHAT IS THE SECRET
INGREDIENT IN THAT SAUCE?
I DUNNO, HAROLD.
SEE, THAT'S THE
BEAUTY OF IT.
NOBODY KNOWS.
I WENT UP TO THE UNIVERSITY
AND TOOK THIS UP TO THE LAB,
AND THEY'VE
ANALYZED IT, RIGHT.
OH, NO, HAROLD,
WAIT A SEC.
THE TIME HAS COME.
IT'S JET FUEL.
WOW!
YOU CANNOT
SELL THAT SAUCE!
PEOPLE DON'T LIKE
BLOWING UP.
OKAY, FIRST OF ALL,
THAT'S A GENERALIZATION.
AND SECONDLY, WE'RE NOT
GONNA SELL IT AS
BARBEQUE SAUCE.
WE'RE GONNA SELL IT
AS GASOLINE ADDITIVE.
WE'RE GONNA MAKE
A KILLING, HAROLD.
EXACTLY!
Red: WE ALL AGREED TO MEET
OUT BEHIND THE LODGE
AND FIX THE PICKET FENCE.
ARE GOING TO HELP OUT.  ANR
AND I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE BALE OF STRAW --
GUYS, WE'RE DOIN'
THE PICKET FENCE.
NO, NO, YOU AGREED --
WHAT'S THE STRAW --
WHAT'S THE BALE OF STRAW FOR?
OKAY, THEY'RE GONNA
DO SOME KIND OF ARCHERY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN', BILL?
WHAT IS THAT?
HE'S GOT A --
WOW!
HE'S GOT A CROSSBOW
IN HIS PANTS.
OKAY.
WELL, I'LL JUST WORK
ON THE FENCE MYSELF.
IT'S REALLY NOT
THAT MUCH OF A SURPRISE
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
HE'S GOT ANOTHER
CROSSBOW IN HIS PANTS!
HOLY COW.
SO THEY GET ALL SET UP.
TO ME, IT'S A
MATURITY THING.
I'D JUST AS SOON
DO IT MYSELF,
WITHOUT A COUPLE OF GOOFBALLS
LIKE THIS WORKING WITH ME.
OKAY, YEAH, YOU GOT
THE ARROWS AND EVERYTHING.
SEE HOW I BECAME LEADER?
SO I'M WORKIN' AWAY, TRYIN'
TO CLEAN UP THE ENVIRONMENT
TO MAKE THIS A BETTER
WORLD FOR ALL OF US,
MEANWHILE,
THEY'RE GOOFIN' AROUND
DOIN' A KIND OF
A CHARLIE'S ANGELS THING.
NOW, THE PROBLEM
WITH THE CROSSBOWS IS
THEY'RE A
LITTLE BIT TRICKY,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU HAVE
NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE DOIN'.
SO BILL STICKS
AN ARROW IN THERE,
AND OF COURSE,
IT DOESN'T SHOOT.
NOW, YOU KIDS AT HOME,
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT DOIN'
WHAT WALTER'S ABOUT TO DO.
THIS IS NOT HOW YOU CHECK --
NO, THIS IS NOT --
THIS IS NOT A GOOD IDEA.
NO, WALTER. NO.
NO, NO, NO.
WELL, AS IT TURNS OUT,
THE SAFETY WAS ON.
I SEE WHY.
THERE WE GO.
WE'RE FINE, OKAY.
NOW THEY'RE ALL
SET TO GO,
AND, UH -- OOPS.
OH, ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
SAVES MONEY ON
A BABYSITTER.
OKAY, NOW, JUST GET
THAT OUT OF THERE, WALTER.
JUST YANK IT OUT.
THERE WE GO.
OKAY, NOW, THE THING
WITH THE BALE OF STRAW --
I'M NOT SURE IT'LL STOP.
THESE CROSSBOWS
HAVE A --
STRAIGHT THROUGH AND...
NAILS MY HAMMER.
OF COURSE, THESE
GUYS ARE OBLIVIOUS,
AND THEY JUST KEEP FIRING.
AND THE NEXT
THING YOU KNOW
MY PAINTBRUSH IS JAMMED
WITH AN ARROW THROUGH IT.
AND NOW THEY START
COMING THICK AND FAST.
THEY GET THE
MAILBOX THERE
THEY'RE STARTING
TO HIT THE PICKET FENCE
WITH THE ARROWS
COMING THROUGH,
AND THE NEXT THING I LOSE
MY BOUQUET OF FLOWERS HERE.
SO I'M THINKING
I BETTER GET IN THE VAN,
GET SOME SAFETY.
THEY DON'T EVEN REALISE
THESE THINGS ARE GOING RIGHT
THROUGH THE BALE OF STRAW.
SO I'M IN THE VAN --
OH, BOY!
OKAY, BUT DO YOU THINK METAL
WOULD STOP ONE OF THESE --
NOT SO.
APPARENTLY NOT SO.
SO NOW I'M THINKING,
I SHOULD PROBABLY --
OH, THERE GOES A TIRE.
I SHOULD BE FIGHTING
FIRE WITH FIRE AT THIS POINT.
SO I'LL USE MY WHEEL DISKS,
GET BACK THERE.
I DECIDE TO MAKE
MY OWN CROSSBOW,
USING THE
OLD PICKET FENCE.
AND THERE'S ONE ARROW
COMIN' THEIR WAY.
AND HERE COMES
ANOTHER ONE.
AND THEN...
OH!
WOW, NOW, THIS IS FUN.
HEY, THAT'S
A TOUCHDOWN.
IF YOU HAVE TO CUT YOUR GRASS
MORE THAN THREE TIMES A WEEK,
CALL ROTHSCHILD'S.
IF YOUR LAWN MOWER
DISAPPEARS INTO A SINKHOLE,
TRY OUR EMERGENCY NUMBER.
BOY, I TELL YOU, THIS GASOLINE
ADDITIVE IS A REAL WINNER.
GUYS CARE A LOT MORE
ABOUT THEIR CARS
THAN THEY DO ABOUT
THEIR BARBEQUES.
WE CHANGED THE PACKAGING;
WE GOT A NEW NAME.
I'M CALLIN' IT
RED'S GAS ATTACK.
I'M ACTUALLY GONNA PLAY MYSELF
IN THE TV COMMERCIAL.
DALTON'S JUST ON HIS
WAY OVER HERE RIGHT NOW
TO FIGURE OUT HOW
WE CAN DO IT FOR FREE.
BUT I TELL YOU,
MAN OH MAN,
EVERYBODY'S CAR
IS RUNNIN' GREAT.
THEY'RE GETTIN'
FANTASTIC GAS MILEAGE.
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS THE EXHAUST
SMELLS LIKE A SIRLOIN STEAK.
YOU KNOW, LIKE A DOG'LL CHASE
YOU FOR LIKE 90 MILES.
WHEN I WAS SITTING
THERE IDLING,
FAT GUYS STARTED
CIRCLING MY VEHICLE.
[ EXPLOSION ]
EXCUSE ME A MINUTE.
OH, BOY.
AHEM.
RED, I NEED
TO TALK TO YOU.
WHAT EXPLOSION?
I DIDN'T HEAR
ANYTHING.
THAT WAS MY CAR.
THAT WAS MY CAR WITH YOUR
GASOLINE TREATMENT IN IT.
THAT WAS THE LOUDEST
BACKFIRE I'VE EVER HEARD.
OH, SURE,
IT WAS EXCITING,
AND IT SMELLED
A BIT LIKE RIBS,
BUT IT BLEW MY ENGINE!
BOY, THAT
IS UNFORTUNATE.
YEAH! YEAH! YEAH!
NOW, WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
WELL, UH, HOW ABOUT
A LIFETIME SUPPLY
OF THE --
NO! NO!
UH, WELL,
OKAY, I'LL REPLACE
YOUR CAR.
WHAT WAS IT
ANYWAY?
WELL, IT WAS AN
'82 RELIANT
WITH LESS THAN
500,000 MILES ON IT.
OKAY,
I CAN GET ONE,
BUT YOU'LL HAVE TO
WAIT TILL GARBAGE DAY.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME!
YEAH. YEAH.
LIGHTEN UP,
DALTON, OKAY.
THE PLAN BACKFIRED
AND SO DID YOUR CAR.
BUT YOU DIDN'T
GET HURT.
NOBODY WAS
FOLLOWING YOU,
WERE THEY?
I DON'T THINK SO.
I DUNNO.
WELL, SEE, SO THERE'S
NO PROBLEM.
AWAY YOU GO.
GO ON.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
UNCLE RED --
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR TAILGATING,
HAROLD.
IT'S MEETING TIME.
I WAS AN INNOCENT VICTIM IN A
BARBEQUE SAUCE EXPLOSION!
YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
YOU'RE NOT THE FIRST
VIRGIN TO BE BURNED
AT THE 'STEAK'.
AWAY YOU GO.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I AM OUT OF
THE BARBEQUE BUSINESS,
AND HOPING MAYBE YOU AND I CAN
COOK SOMETHING UP LATER
NOW THAT I'M
OFF THE SAUCE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, EVERYONE,
HAVE A SEAT.
COME ON, SIT DOWN NOW.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, IT'S ALL OVER WITH
THE BARBEQUE SAUCE
AND THE FUEL ADDITIVE,
BECAUSE APPARENTLY
THE STUFF BLOWS UP.
SO I WOULD SUGGEST YOU GET THAT
OUT OF YOUR GAS TANK IMMEDIATELY
UNLESS YOUR CAR IS A RENTAL.