Red Green:
YOU KNOW, THERE'S
BEEN A LOT OF TALK ABOUT
MEN HATING TO
ASK FOR DIRECTIONS.
THAT'S NOT
REALLY THE POINT.
THE REAL PROBLEM IS
MEN LOVE TO DRIVE.
AND IF YOU HAVE
TO ASK FOR DIRECTIONS,
THAT MEANS YOU DON'T
KNOW WHERE YOU'RE GOING,
AND THAT MEANS THE PASSENGER
SEAT IS IN YOUR NEAR FUTURE.
SO WHEN YOU'RE OUT WITH YOUR
WIFE AND YOU LOSE THE ARGUMENT
AS YOU KNOW YOU MUST,
AND YOU END UP ASKING
A GUY FOR DIRECTIONS,
HERE'S WHAT TO DO TO STOP YOUR
INTEGRITY FROM SHRINKING --
BECAUSE SIZE MATTERS.
MAKE A LITTLE SIGN,
HIDE IT UNDER YOUR SLEEVE,
ATTACH A COUPLE OF
SINKERS TO THE EDGE
SO IT'LL UNROLL WITHOUT
YOUR WIFE SEEING IT.
AND YOU WANT TO
PICK A MARRIED GUY,
BECAUSE HE'LL UNDERSTAND.
OKAY, SO PULL OVER,
TELL HIM WHERE YOU'RE HEADED,
AND AS SOON AS YOU ASK HIM
IF YOU'RE GOING IN THE
RIGHT DIRECTION,
SECRETLY RELEASE THE SIGN.
[cheers and applause]
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
WELL, IT'S A BIG, BIG WEEK AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
WE'VE GOT A HORSESHOE
TOURNAMENT GOING ON.
MIND YOU, I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO FIND MY HORSESHOES.
I FIGURE THEY'LL TURN UP
SOONER OR LATER.
MIKE CAN YOU COME UP
HERE A MINUTE, PLEASE?
UM, I DIDN'T
STEAL IT, MR. GREEN.
WHAT?
DIDN'T STEAL WHAT?
YOU'LL HAVE TO BE
MORE SPECIFIC.
WELL, I CAN'T SEEM
TO FIND MY HORSESHOES.
ARE THEY IN THERE?
[clunking sound]
PROBABLY NOT.
I KNOW THE SOUND
OF MY OWN HORSESHOES.
CAN I HAVE
THEM BACK, PLEASE?
OH! HA-HA!
YOU SHOULDA TOLD ME
YOU PUT 'EM IN THERE.
OH, RIGHT, YEAH.
THANK YOU, MIKE.
WHERE'D YOU
GET THAT PEN?
OH, I'VE ALWAYS
HAD THIS PEN.
THAT'S MY
PEN, MIKE.
OH, REALLY?
HAS IT GOT YOUR NAME ON IT?
YEAH.
OH.
YOU KNOW, MIKE, THIS
STICKY FINGERS STUFF
IS GETTIN'
OUTTA HAND.
I'M SORRY, MR. GREEN.
I JUST CAN'T HELP MYSELF.
ALL MY LIFE I'VE BEEN TAKING
STUFF THAT WASN'T MINE.
IT'S JUST BEEN GETTING
WORSE AND WORSE.
BUT DON'T SEND ME BACK
TO PRISON, PLEASE!
PLEASE DON'T SEND ME BACK
TO PRISON, MR. GREEN.
I CAN'T DO IT
ANYMORE, I TELL YOU!
I JUST CAN'T DO IT!
MIKE, MIKE, MIKE.
I'M NOT GONNA SEND
YOU BACK TO PRISON.
GREAT.
BUT YOU NEED TO
DO SOMETHING, MIKE.
WHY DON'T YOU GO DOWN AND
SEE YOUR PAROLE OFFICER
AND OFFER TO HELP
HIM OUT, EH?
I THINK YOU'D HAVE A
WHOLE DIFFERENT ATTITUDE
IF YOU WERE LOOKING
AT LAW ENFORCEMENT
FROM THE OTHER SIDE.
THAT'S A GREAT
IDEA, MR. GREEN.
I'M GONNA GO RIGHT
DOWN THERE AND DO THAT.
CAN I CATCH A
RIDE WITH YOU?
SURE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'D BE GLAD TO
DO THAT.
AH, GEEZ,
THANKS, MR. GREEN.
HERE'S THE KEYS
TO YOUR VAN.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
TODAY'S WINNER WILL RECEIVE
THREE BOXING LESSONS
FROM TUCKER'S
MANUFACTURING,
THE MAKERS OF THE FINEST
CARDBOARD BOXES.
OKAY, UH, COVER
YOUR EARS, THERE, ED.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER ED FRID
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
AND GO!
OKAY, ED, THIS IS SOMETHING
ALMOST ALL ANIMALS HAVE.
SHARP TEETH.
OKAY, NO, NO.
THIS IS WHAT ANIMALS USE
TO FIND THEIR WAY BACK TO
SOMEWHERE THEY'VE BEEN BEFORE.
OH! TRAIL OF BLOOD.
NO, NO, NO.
OKAY, OKAY.
THIS IS SOMETHING ANIMALS
HAVE THAT HUMANS DON'T.
UH, ANTLERS?
OKAY, ED, WHY DO
SALMON SWIM UPSTREAM?
PANIC.
YEAH, DID YOU EVER
SEE THEIR EYES?
ED, ED, ED,
THEY'RE NOT AFRAID.
THEY SWIM UP TO
THEIR SPAWNING GROUNDS,
THEY LAY EGGS AND DIE.
NOW, WHAT CHARACTERISTIC
MAKES THEM DO THAT?
STUPIDITY, I GUESS.
UH, RED, YOU GUYS ARE
RUNNIN' SHORT OF TIME.
OKAY, ED, YOU'RE AN
ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN YOU AND THE ANIMALS?
I CAN OUTRUN THEM.
YEAH, BUT THAT'S JUST MY
SURVIVAL INSTINCT.
THERE WE GO!
[cheers and applause]
IF YOU'RE SITTIN' ON
THE DOCK OF THE BAY,
WATCHING THE TIDE ROLL AWAY,
AND YOU DON'T LIVE
ANYWHERE NEAR WATER,
CALL ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
SEE, IT'S PEOPLE LIKE THAT
THAT HAVE RUINED IT FOR
EVERYBODY.
MY WIFE BERNICE SEES THEM
WITH THE SLIM WAISTLINE
AND THEIR LOW PULSE RATE,
SHE TAKES A LOOK AT ME
AND STARTS GETTING
ALL KINDS OF IDEAS.
SEE TO ME, YOU SHOULD KEEP
YOUR PULSE RATE HIGH, NOT LOW,
BECAUSE EVENTUALLY
IT GOES TO ZERO,
AND YOU WANT TO KEEP IT AS FAR
AWAY FROM THAT AS YOU CAN.
SO BERNICE GETS ME ONE OF
THESE TREADMILL MACHINES.
TELLS ME SHE WANTS ME
TO DO THREE MILES A DAY.
AT THE SPEED I WALK,
THAT'S A 24-HOUR COMMITMENT.
YOU NEVER GET ANYWHERE.
THE SCENERY
DOESN'T CHANGE.
IT'S USELESS AND BORING.
AND THOSE ARE TWO WORDS THAT
I HEAR ENOUGH OF IN MY LIFE.
SO I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
SEE THIS IS
THE KEY RIGHT HERE.
THIS MACHINE RUNS
ON 12 VOLTS DC,
JUST LIKE A CAR.
THAT MEANS YOU DON'T HAVE TO
PLUG IT INTO A HOUSE CURRENT.
YOU CAN ACTUALLY RUN THIS ON
A COUPLE OF CAR BATTERIES.
NOW, YOU MAY BE A LITTLE BIT
CONFUSED AT THIS POINT.
YOU MIGHT EVEN BE SITTING
THERE WITH YOUR MOUTH
WIDE OPEN,
BEER AND CHIPS ARE
GOING EVERYWHERE.
SO LET ME EXPLAIN
THE MYSTERY TO YOU.
SEE, WHEN THEY BUILD
THESE MACHINES,
THEY GO TO A LOT OF EFFORT
TO MAKE SURE THIS BELT
NEVER TOUCHES THE GROUND.
WELL, THAT'S WHERE THEY
MAKE THE BIG MISTAKE.
OKAY, I'VE GOT MY
CAR BATTERIES WIRED IN.
I'VE GOT MY BELT SITTING
FLAT ON THE GROUND.
ALL I GOTTA DO IS PUT MY
FEET ON THE SIDE RAILS HERE,
AND I'M READY TO
START EXERCISING.
AH, AH, AH.
WAIT A MINUTE.
LET'S PLAY IT
SAFE FOR A CHANGE.
REALLY SAFE.
OKAY, HERE'S THE
BEAUTY OF A DC MOTOR...
TO MAKE THE BELT
GO THE OTHER WAY,
ALL I HAD TO DO WAS SWITCH
THE BATTERY TERMINALS.
DON'T YOU WISH
PEOPLE WERE DC?
ALL RIGHT, IT'S TIME
FOR MY THREE-MILE WALK,
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
DO ANY OF YOU HAVE ANY UGLY
PICTURES OF YOURSELF
SITTING AROUND?
NO?
DIDN'T THINK SO.
SEE, WHEN MOST PEOPLE FIND
AN UNFLATTERING PICTURE
OF THEMSELVES,
THEY RIP IT UP AND BURN IT,
THEN GO BURY IT
IN THE BACKYARD.
I THINK THAT'S A BAD IDEA.
I KNOW SOME PEOPLE TAKE A
FAT PICTURE OF THEMSELVES
AND THEY'LL PUT
IT ON THE FRIDGE
AS A DETERRENT TO KEEP
THEM FROM SNACKING.
THAT DOESN'T REALLY WORK.
IT ENDS UP AS KIND OF A
TERRITORIAL THING...
"THIS FRIDGE AND ITS CONTENTS
ARE THE PROPERTY OF MOOSE."
I TELL YOU WHAT I SUGGEST.
GET THE UGLIEST, FATTEST,
MOST DISGUSTING
PICTURE OF YOURSELF
EVER TAKEN,
AND PUT IT IN A NICE
FRAME AND HANG IT
BESIDE A
FULL-LENGTH MIRROR.
MAKE SURE IT'S SUCH
A HORRIBLE PICTURE
THERE'S ALMOST NO CHANCE
YOU'RE EVER GONNA LOOK
THAT BAD AGAIN.
THIS MEANS WHEN YOU STAND
IN FRONT OF THE MIRROR,
YOU'RE GONNA SEE THAT
YOU LOOK WAY BETTER NOW
THAN YOU DID BACK WHEN
THAT PICTURE WAS TAKEN.
THEN YOU START THINKING
THAT AS YOU GET OLDER,
YOU START LOOKING BETTER.
AND THAT'LL MAKE
YOU LOOK BETTER STILL.
AND IF THE DAY EVER COMES WHEN
YOU ACTUALLY LOOK WORSE
THAN YOU DO IN THE PICTURE,
WELL, HEY, TIME TO
GET OUT THE CAMERA.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
WELL, THIS IS THE EXPERTS'
PORTION OF THE SHOW,
WHERE WE FEATURE.
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW.
AND TODAY'S LETTER
READS AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS: OUR DAUGHTER'S
ABOUT TO MARRY A MORON."
OH, GEEZ.
"IS THERE ANYTHING
WE CAN DO TO STOP HER?
"IF NOT, HOW DO WE
CARRY ON WITH OUR LIVES
"ONCE WE HAVE AN
IDIOT IN THE FAMILY?"
OKAY, WELL, NOW,
AS A FATHER,
IT'S YOUR RESPONSIBILITY
TO POINT OUT THAT
THIS GUY REALLY
IS STUPID,
SO WHAT YOU WANNA
DO IS INVITE HIM OVER
FOR THE "TRIVIAL
PURSUIT" GAME.
ONLY INSTEAD OF
A GAME PIECE,
YOU MAKE HIM USE YOUR
DAUGHTER'S ENGAGEMENT RING.
EVERY TIME HE
GETS ONE WRONG,
YOU PRY A DIAMOND
OUTTA THERE.
THAT IS SO WRONG!
A MARRIAGE IS BASED ON
MUTUAL RESPECT, NOT IQ.
IF YOU HAVE MUTUAL RESPECT,
YOU DON'T NEED ANYTHING ELSE.
HOW MANY YEARS
YOU BEEN MARRIED, HAROLD?
OKAY, I HAVEN'T FOUND
THE RIGHT PERSON YET,
BUT AT LEAST I KNOW
WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR.
YES, UNFORTUNATELY,
SO DO THEY.
EXCEPT FOR THIS
GUY'S DAUGHTER,
WHO THINKS SHE'S LOOKING
FOR A MORON, I GUESS.
YEAH, WELL,
I'M IN THE SAME BOAT.
YEAH, MY DAUGHTER'S FIANCé
IS SURE NO BRAINIAC.
IT'S SO DISAPPOINTING
WHEN YOUR DAUGHTER
STARTS GOING OUT
WITH A TOTAL IDIOT.
WELL, BE CAREFUL,
NOW, MR. DALTON.
THEY SAY GIRLS ARE
ATTRACTED TO MEN
WHO REMIND THEM
OF THEIR FATHER.
AH, HAROLD,
COME ON, NOW.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
THE FACT THAT THIS GUY NOTICES
THE BOYFRIEND IS STUPID
MEANS THAT HE'S
PRETTY SMART.
'CAUSE STUPID PEOPLE DON'T
THINK ANYTHING IS STUPID.
WHEREAS YOU THINK
EVERYTHING IS STUPID.
OH, HAROLD, DON'T
BE ST -- STEREOTYPING.
DON'T BE
STEREOTYPING ME.
WELL, MY ADVICE TO THIS VIEWER
IS TALK TO ANOTHER COUPLE
WHOSE DAUGHTER
MARRIED AN IDIOT.
BUT THERE WON'T
BE ANYBODY LIKE THAT
UNTIL YOU GET ENGAGED.
I WAS THINKING MORE OF
AUNT BERNICE'S PARENTS.
[Dalton laughing]
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
Red: YOU'RE HOME, DALTON.
YOU CAN GET OUT NOW.
Dalton: I CAN'T GET
THE PAINT OFF.
YES!
TRY THE VARSOL?
YES, RED!
GASOLINE?
WELL, THERE'S A
BELT SANDER BACK THERE,
BUT NOWHERE TO
PLUG IT IN.
I CAN THINK OF
A PLACE!
NOW, DON'T GET YOURSELF ALL
WRANGED UP HERE, DALTON.
ANN MARIE PROBABLY
WON'T EVEN NOTICE.
WON'T EVEN NOTICE?!
LOOK AT ME.
I LOOK LIKE
BOZO THE CLOWN.
WELL, THAT'S NOT
A HUGE STRETCH FOR HER.
I CAN'T GO IN THERE.
ANN MARIE DOES NOT LET
ME GO TO PAINT BALL.
IF SHE SEES THE PAINT
ALL OVER MY FACE,
SHE'LL KNOW I DISOBEYED
A DIRECT ORDER.
ANN MARIE A LITTLE ON THE
MILITANT SIDE, IS SHE?
WE ARE MESSING WITH
THE WRONG MARINE.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU SHOULD'VE BEEN WEARING
ONE OF THOSE
PROTECTIVE MASKS.
YOU KNOW, I WAS,
BUT IT GOT KNOCKED OFF
IN THE FIRST SHOT.
WELL, YOU COULDN'T HAVE
HAD IT ON PROPERLY.
YOU SEE,
THE PROBLEM WAS,
YOU SHOT ME FROM
FOUR FEET AWAY.
OKAY, I PANICKED,
ALL RIGHT?
I SAW THE ENEMY;
I DID WHAT I HAD TO DO.
I WAS ON YOUR
TEAM, RED!
WELL, WHO COULD TELL
WITH THAT MASK ON?
ALL RIGHT,
I GOT AN IDEA.
I'VE GOT A GALLON
OF PAINT HERE.
TAKE THE LID OFF THERE.
HOLD ONTO THAT, ALL RIGHT?
NOW, YOU TAKE THIS
INTO THE HOUSE,
AND YOU TELL ANN MARIE
YOU WERE GONNA PAINT
THE FRONT HALL,
BUT YOU SLIPPED AND
YOUR FACE WENT RIGHT
INTO THE CAN.
OH, OH,
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
YOU CAN TELL YOU'RE A
MARRIED MAN, HUH?
YEAH.
OH, HEY, NO, NO.
THIS COLOUR WON'T MATCH.
OH, NO PROBLEM.
[applause]
WELL, WE SURE GOT A DIFFERENT
MIKE IN TOWN, I TELL YOU.
HIS PAROLE OFFICER
GAVE HIM A JOB
AS ASSISTANT BYLAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICER.
AND THE CRIME RATE
HAS JUST DROPPED.
THAT'S BECAUSE MIKE IS
TOO BUSY TO STEAL STUFF.
RED! RED!
MIKE IS
OUT OF CONTROL!
YOU GIVE A GUY
A GOOFY UNIFORM,
AND HE SURE THINKS
HE IS SOMETHING.
[laughter]
YOU KNOW, HE NAILED ME
TWICE TODAY FOR PARKING
VIOLATIONS?
I DIDN'T HAVE MY CAR.
I WAS JUST SITTING
ON THE CURB.
THAT'S NOT PARKING.
THAT WOULD BE EITHER
LOITERING OR LITTERING.
OH, RED,
HE'S GONE FANATICAL.
HE JUST SNEAKS UP FROM
BEHIND AND NAILS YOU.
HE'S LIKE A WEDGIE.
COME ON.
JUST GO EASY ON HIM
FOR CRYING OUT --
HE'S TRYING TO
BECOME A BETTER PERSON.
WELL,
IT'S NOT WORKING.
I LIKED HIM MORE WHEN
I COULDN'T TRUST HIM.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT,
WE'VE GOTTA GIVE HIM A CHANCE.
HE'S GOT A BAD
SELF-IMAGE.
HE SEES HIMSELF AS A LOW-LIFE,
TWO-BIT CRIMINAL.
HE IS A LOW-LIFE,
TWO-BIT CRIMINAL!
WELL, I KNOW, BUT WE'RE
GIVING HIM AN OPPORTUNITY
TO BE SOMETHING BETTER.
WHAT? A PAIN-IN-THE-BUTT
BYLAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICER?
OKAY, OKAY,
MAYBE AT FIRST.
BUT ONCE HE SETTLES INTO
THE JOB AND COOLS OFF
A LITTLE BIT,
THEN WE'LL HAVE A
GUY ON THE INSIDE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL,
I'M TELLING YOU.
ONCE HE TRIES ALL THESE
POWERS AND EVERYTHING,
THEN SUDDENLY HE'LL
REMEMBER WHO HIS
FRIENDS ARE,
AND WE'LL BE ABLE TO
DO WHATEVER WE WANT...
WE CAN SPEED; WE CAN PARK
WHEREVER WE FEEL LIKE.
GO THROUGH
RED LIGHTS!
WALK AROUND TOPLESS!
[laughter]
Red: HAD A SPECIAL PROJECT.
INSTEAD OF
BUILDING SOMETHING
WE WERE GONNA TEAR
DOWN THE SHED.
AND WALTER DROVE
OVER IN HIS CAR.
I JUST FIGURED GET A SLEDGE
HAMMER AND JUST START
WAILING AWAY.
SOMETHING WAS BOUND TO
GIVE SOONER OR LATER,
HOPEFULLY NOT MY OWN BACK.
BUT WALTER CAME
AND SAID, NO, NO.
HE WANTED TO STOP ME.
HE HAD A BETTER IDEA.
HE'S FIGURIN' WE
COULD USE OUR POLE THERE.
AND IF WE HOISTED UP, SAY,
A -- ONE OF THE OIL DRUMS,
THEY HAVE A LOT OF WEIGHT,
WE COULD MAKE OUR
OWN WRECKING BALL.
ALWAYS WANTED TO
HAVE A WRECKING BALL.
I LIKE THE IDEA OF THAT,
SO WE TIED HER UP
TO THE LINE
AND WE FILLED HER
WITH ALL THE --
BOY, WE'RE SO LUCKY
HAVING ALL THOSE CAR
BATTERIES AROUND.
LUCKILY, NONE OF
THEM WERE TOO JUICED UP,
AND NEITHER WERE
WE AT THIS POINT
SO WE COULD GET MOST OF
THEM INTO THE BARREL.
SO WE HOISTED
HER UP ON THE POLE.
IT WAS A METAL POLE,
SO A LOT OF STRENGTH.
AND JUST WIND HER UP THERE.
AND SHE'S READY TO GO.
THEN WE JUST TAKE HER BACK,
SWING HER BACK.
THIS IS GONNA BE GREAT.
YOU KNOW, UNFORTUNATELY,
WE HIT THE POLE.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY. OKAY.
OKAY, SO, UH,
SO NOW WHAT?
WELL, WALTER'S
GOT ANOTHER IDEA.
HE SAYS WE'LL JUST LOAD HER
UP WITH THE BATTERIES AGAIN.
AND INSTEAD OF STICKING
THE POLE BACK IN THE GROUND.
WHAT WE'LL DO IS
MOUNT THE WHOLE POLE
SOMEWHERE ELSE, LIKE, SAY,
THE POSSUM VAN.
NOW, HE SAID TO ME,
'JUST DRIVE HER UP CLOSER
'TO THE SHED,
AND WATCH ME.
'I'LL TELL YOU
WHEN TO STOP.'
BUT HE WASN'T LOOKIN',
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN --
I SLAMMED ON THE BRAKES,
SO IT SWINGS BACK TOWARDS ME.
THANK YOU
VERY MUCH, WALTER.
WHAT'S YOUR NEXT IDEA?
SO THEN HE GETS ME
TO PARK HER SIDEWAYS,
PUT THE BATTERIES ALL IN,
AND AWAY WE GO AGAIN.
BUT HE FIGURES MAYBE WE
CAN JUST HOIST HER UP
BY GETTING ON
A LADDER OR WHATEVER,
AND GET ENOUGH
HEIGHT ON HER
THAT WE CAN SWING HER UP.
WE'RE STILL GONNA TRY TO MAKE
THIS WRECKING BALL WORK.
I THOUGHT THIS WAS
A LITTLE TOO HIGH,
BUT HE SEEMED TO
FEEL GOOD ABOUT IT.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THE
ONE THING WE FORGOT TO DO
WAS TO CHECK THE
KNOT ON THE ROPE.
AND, UH --
SO WALTER TIED A LITTLE
TOUGHER KNOT THIS TIME.
AND NOW WE'RE READY TO GO,
AND HE WANTS TO
DO HER AGAIN,
SO BACK UP THE
LADDER HE GOES.
UNFORTUNATELY, WHEN YOU
TIE A BIGGER KNOT,
IT USES MORE ROPE.
SO WHAT HAPPENED HERE
WAS THAT SHE WAS JUST
A LITTLE TOO SHORT
TO ACTUALLY HIT THE SHED,
SO SHE, UH, SWUNG UP
IN THE PENDULUM STYLE,
SO FAMOUS FOR NEWTON.
AND IT CAME UP.
THEN IT JUST CAME
RIGHT BACK.
NOW IT'S NAILING WALTER,
SO I GOTTA MOVE
HIM AWAY FROM THE SHED.
SO I GET HIM INTO THE --
AND HE KINDA WENT
INTO THE TREES THERE.
I THINK HE'S ALL RIGHT.
NO, HE'S GOOD.
HE'S GOOD.
HE'S GOOD -- OH!
AND, UH -- OH!
NO, NO, HE'S FINE.
[applause]
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING.
SO WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
FOR US TODAY, WINSTON?
WELL, RED,
I WAS HOPING
YOU COULD FIX
MY MAILBOX.
BOY, WHAT
HAPPENED THERE?
MY NEIGHBOUR
HAD A SLIGHT
"ALTERCATION" WITH IT.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I CAN'T FIX THAT.
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST TRADE
MAILBOXES WITH THE GUY?
WELL, SEE, THAT'S
NOT REALLY AN OPTION.
WELL, WHAT
HAPPENED HERE?
WELL, HE CLAIMS THAT I
HIT HIS MAILBOX WITH
MY SEWAGE TRUCK.
AND THAT'S WHEN HE CAME AND
DANCED ALL OVER MY MAILBOX
WITH HIS PERSUADER.
OKAY, BUT THIS
DIDN'T HAPPEN?
NO, I WASN'T EVEN
IN TOWN!
I WAS IN PORT ASBESTOS
FROM THE 12th TO THE 17th
AT THE PRUNE FESTIVAL.
YEAH, RED, THOSE FOLKS WERE
GOING DAY AND NIGHT.
BOY, IT'S NOT LIKE YOU
TO BACK DOWN FROM
AN ARGUMENT.
WHAT CONVINCED YOU?
THE GUY'S
6'7", RED.
WELL, THAT
DOESN'T MATTER.
RIGHT IS RIGHT.
IF WE CAN PROVE
THAT THIS HAPPENED
WHILE YOU WERE AT
THE PRUNE FESTIVAL,
YOU'RE A FREE MAN.
WELL, HOW ARE
YOU GONNA DO THAT?
WELL, THERE'S A
LETTER IN THERE.
IF THE LETTER IS
POSTMARKED AFTER THE 12th,
YOU'RE IN THE CLEAR.
YOU'RE A GENIUS!
OH, NO, WINSTON.
JUST BECAUSE SOMEONE
IS SMARTER THAN YOU
DOESN'T MEAN
THEY'RE A GENIUS.
THERE WE GO.
LOOK AT THE THAT, THE 15th.
I'M IN THE CLEAR!
HEY, DID YOU KNOW THIS GUY
WORKED FOR THE GOVERNMENT?
YEAH. YEAH.
HE'S AN INCOME
TAX AUDITOR.
REALLY?
YOU KNOW, WINSTON,
MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST BUY
YOURSELF A NEW MAILBOX.
MAYBE I SHOULD BUY
HIM A NEW MAILBOX.
LET'S BOTH BUY HIM
A NEW MAILBOX!
[applause]
YOU KNOW HOW EVERYBODY LIKES
THOSE FANCY NEW TVs,
THEY'RE ABOUT AN INCH THICK
AND THEY HANG ON THE WALL?
THOSE THINGS COST $25,000,
WHICH SEEMS HIGH TO ME
BY ABOUT $24,900.
STILL, THERE IS NOTHING MORE
EMBARRASSING IN LIFE
THAN HAVING AN OLD-FASHIONED
TELEVISION SET.
SO HERE'S A CHEAP EASY WAY TO
CONVERT YOUR OLD FLOOR MODEL
INTO A STATE-OF-THE-ART
WALL HANGING JOB.
FIRST THING YOU WANNA DO IS
HANG A MIRROR ON YOUR WALL
ABOUT THE SAME SIZE AS
THE TELEVISION SCREEN.
THEN YOU JUST CUT
A HOLE IN THE FLOOR,
AND DROP YOUR TV
SET DOWN IN THERE
WITH THE SCREEN FACING UP.
AND THEN YOU PUT A HINGE TRAP
DOOR OVER TOP LIKE THIS ONE.
AND ON THE INSIDE
OF THE TRAP DOOR,
YOU MOUNT ANOTHER MIRROR.
NOW, WHEN YOUR
AMISH FRIENDS DROP OVER
FOR AN APPLE OR WHATEVER,
YOU CAN JUST CLOSE
THE TRAP DOOR.
BUT ON THE OTHER HAND,
WHEN YOU'RE READY
TO WATCH SOME HI-TECH,
CUTTING EDGE STUFF LIKE
WRESTLING OR TRACTOR PULLS,
YOU JUST TURN
ON THE TV SET.
AND THEN YOU JUST
LINE UP THE MIRRORS.
You know, there's
an expression...
"The apple doesn't fall
too far from the tree."
Okay, in human
terms that means,
"like father, like son."
WELL, I THINK WE
GOT THE PROBLEM
WITH MIKE'S POLICE
JOB ALL SORTED OUT.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES HE'S
A LITTLE TOO THOROUGH.
SAME WAY WHEN HE
WAS A CROOK.
YOU KNOW, IF HE HAD
A PIECE OF CHAIN,
HE'D STEAL TWO CARS
AND TOW ONE OF THEM.
[laughter]
MR. GREEN, I JUST WANTED
TO SAY, THANKS AGAIN.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS THE
FIRST JOB I'VE REALLY
BEEN GOOD AT?
YOU KNOW, MIKE,
YOU CAN ACTUALLY
BE TOO GOOD AT A JOB?
I FEEL I'M REALLY MAKING A
DIFFERENCE OUT THERE.
YOU KNOW, I'M MAKING
THE STREETS SAFE FOR
ORDINARY CITIZENS.
AND I'M RIDDING THE WORLD
OF HARDENED CRIMINALS.
[laughter and applause]
Dalton: THIS IS ALL
YOUR FAULT, RED.
YEAH: "WE'LL HAVE A
GUY ON THE INSIDE."
ALL RIGHT, STOP IT.
NOW IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TWO GUYS
ON THE INSIDE.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE, MIKE?
THESE ARE YOUR
FRIENDS.
THESE AREN'T
CRIMINALS.
JAY WALKING IS
A SERIOUS OFFENCE!
YOU CAN'T ARREST
THEM FOR THAT.
WELL, BOY,
MR. GREEN,
FIRST YOU SAY ONE THING,
AND THEN YOU SAY ANOTHER
TOTALLY OPPOSITE THING.
IT'S JUST LIKE
WHEN BOTH MY DADS
EXPLAINED THE
FACTS OF LIFE.
WELL, OKAY, LOOK,
I MADE A MISTAKE WHEN
I TOLD YOU TO BECOME A COP,
BUT WE GOTTA PUT THINGS
BACK THE WAY THEY WERE,
WHERE EVERYBODY KNEW
WHERE THEY STOOD...
US ON ONE SIDE
OF THE ONE-WAY GLASS,
AND YOU IN
THE LINE-UP.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
OKAY, BOYS, ONE OF THESE
KEYS WILL OPEN YOUR LOCKS.
WHAT'S THE OTHER ONE?
IT'S A KEY TO
YOUR STORE.
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME.
COME ON, BOYS.
YOU BETTER MOVE ALONG NOW.
COME ON!
MOVE ALONG!
GET THE LEAD OUT.
COME ON!
COME ON.
MOVE ON!
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I THINK IT
WAS ABRAHAM LINCOLN
WHO SAID THE
LAW'S AN ASS.
I GUESS HE KNEW MIKE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND THE
WHOLE GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheers and applause]
SIT DOWN.
MEETING'S COMING TO ORDER.
Mike: SIT DOWN!
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
I'M VERY PLEASED TO ANNOUNCE
THAT MIKE HERE
HAS RESIGNED AS
ASSISTANT BYLAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICER.
HE'S GOING BACK
TO JUST NORMAL NOW,
SO I SUGGEST YOU
ALL CHANGE YOUR LOCKS.