But.
And now it's time for a show that answers the
philosophical question if a tree falls in the
forest and lands on a guy's head and you
know, a bunch of bees come out of the
branches and right into his pants, as does
make a sound?
Well, the answer is yes.
Believe me, I know.
And anyway, here's a man who has a bunch of
sounds of his own.
The star of the Red Green show a man I like
to call uncle even when he doesn't have me in
the headlock. Here he is, Mr.
Red Green.
Thank you, and welcome to Possum Lodge, I'm
Bret Green, head of head of this possum
lodge, which is Chapter 11, and you've
already met my nephew, Harold, who's been
second on the head by his share of trees
falling in the forest.
Harold is actually the producer and director
of the show.
Whatever that means,
It happens to mean that when I push these
buttons, this happens
Anyway. Lots of stuff going on up the lodge
this week.
We're getting a brand new four man raft, so
we're probably going to be a lot of arguing
about which four guys are going to get to
win that first.
And besides, the other thing was going on
was, you know, the bunch of us like just kind
of work on our own cars.
So we thought we'd build one of them
mechanics, bits like they have at the gas
station. So we thought we just wouldn't dig
it.
And we all got a bunch of shovels and picks
and hockey sticks and they went out there.
And actually the way it worked was a moose.
Thompson and Helmet Winter Garden were the
only ones that were digging the trench, and
the rest of us just kind of stood there
leaning on our tools, so it looked like a
real professional government job.
They got her. They got her dug pretty fast
because the ground was real soft.
Although hacking through the waterline took
some time.
They got her all done there and it was long
enough that we could get six cars on that.
We just would straddle the ditch right up
there.
Just one two three. Bang, Bang, Bang, Bang,
Bang.
And then we all crawled under our own
vehicles and and started working on them.
Unfortunately, like I said, the ground was a
little soft and one side started to cave in
and all the cars started rolling over and
they all ended up right up.
Yeah, yeah. What happened to the guys working
under the cars?
Well, the herd went so slowly we see that the
guy could actually open the driver's door and
climb up over the seat and go right out the
passenger door.
So we ended up with six cars lying there
upside down.
Why you don't see that every day?
No, no, not. Not since Moose got fired from
that job.
Valet parking.
This is cool. It's like that town in Texas,
where they got those six Cadillacs buried in
the ground and only their tail stick out.
It's really avant garde and trade cool.
Oh yeah. And it's a major tourist
attraction.
I guess they must have done their their
mechanics pit in the same kind of sandy soil
that we got. Yeah, I guess so.
Well, let's get the show rolling, Harold.
Hopefully not into the ground.
All righty, then.
Oh, is that right here?
Yeah. How about inside a large tire
Sitting on the couch they're doing?
That's a raft.
That's your idea of a four man red.
Yeah. Murray's own brand, that's not a raft.
That's a piece of homemade crap.
That's a kindergarten science project.
Duct tape is a nice touch.
Well, you enjoy it.
Let's go, Dwayne Murray.
Hold it, Dwayne. I'm not paying for this.
Well, you already have remember, I want a
refund with interest.
Oh, that's good. Douglas, I like that.
But we have a policy about returning items.
Oh, what's that?
We don't. This is not a raft.
A raft has a bow and the stern.
Well, this one has lots of side.
Can you call this a four man raft?
Oh, maybe it's out of a four by four.
How do you put them on a run?
Well, it hangs in the middle there.
I'm real impressed. Marie Chromatograph takes
lots of guts.
Marie, if you value your reproductive
abilities, you won't get this out of here.
And very quickly, give me back my money.
Your money, huh?
It's the largest money, Douglas.
Let's go, Dwayne. Ok, Murray, hold it,
Murray.
Get it, Douglas. Let's go, Duane.
Ok, hold it. Ignore him.
Blake Murray.
No. Why move Freddie to look at lovely to
hold?
But if you break it, consider it sold.
That's our creed, you know?
You can learn a lot at parties, as we did
last night.
We learned that fat people aren't always
jolly and you should never dare someone to
throw bullets in the fire.
We learned that alcohol and power tools
don't mix, and we learned that the fire
department doesn't always arrive soon enough
to make any tangible difference.
This week on Handymen Corner, we're going to
show you some things you can do with all of
those oil drums that you have lying around
your house like everybody does.
We're not too bad here up the lodge because
we can use them for flotation, for the dock
or maybe make a couple of ashtrays out of
them, you know, but maybe something you want
to be more stylish because you're actually
concerned with what other people think.
So I suggest you do something like this.
You take a cold chisel and persuader of some
kind and you just drive a hole and then the
little drum. What you have, there is just an
ideal piggy bank for the youngsters.
That's enough. Know what you can do there
too is just, well, the hunk of chain on here
and just hanging over the hotel, his neck
and he can go out in Halloween, collect for
UNICEF. And once he gets filled up course,
you drop her on her side and you can use it
to roll on. Or you can just knock the lid
off the thing and there's your college
education paid for.
If that's the way you carry it, spend your
money and that one thing I can do is I'll be
getting old chisel or a screwdriver and pry
the lid off.
Or you could you could use whatever you got
in your pockets.
You know your your car keys or bottle opener
or business card, and it just comes off as
easy as pie to. Ok,
once you've done that, you can use the lid
as a serving tray and you can cover it all
with crackers and then you fill your oil
drum with Pat, or if you're on a budget, just
use peanut butter with anchovies in it.
Just take a cracker
Scoop into the Oh boy,
So that looks great, doesn't it?
Ok, maybe we should rinse the oil out of
there first.
You're having a party in, you got three
thousand guests are so coming.
I'm telling you an oil drum for the party is
going to just serve everybody.
You're going to run out of crackers way
before you run out of paté.
And the beauty of it is with this system
that when the party is over, just pop the lid
back on there and run a bead of silicone
caulking around the outside.
And that'll keep indefinitely without
refrigeration.
We've had this particular party since, uh.
I was in the forties, I think. And if you're
dealing with a cutting torch, you know, you
can really go to town on these units.
You know, you cut up the oil drums into all
kinds of different things.
Love seat or patio furniture or some kind of
a decorative awning.
There's all kinds of things. Another idea is
a bird feeding station, you know, one of
these. You're talking about a 50 gallon bird
feeding station.
You only have to fill that sucker once a
year.
Ok, so you got yourself a dandy bird feeder
and you know, this is a joke.
You can fill that thing up with oat bran.
The birds will eat that and they'll wish
they'd gone south, but you're going to have
the best lawn on the street.
And here's something else you can do an oil
drum.
You can build yourself a doorbell that you
can hear from any room in the house.
What you do is you just get a pretty heavy
little persuader such as this and you hang it
from one ear rafters or the doorknob, your
bedroom or whatever, and you have that
hanging down and you line it up with an oil
drum and then you put the hammer over the
door. And then when anyone arrives the
swings in, then you can really hear.
I'll show you how it works. This is going to
be the sound you're going to hear when your
guests arrive. Ok, I got to
watch for the type of not use on that, OK,
for the next thing, now you're going to need
a picnic table. Now you can buy a picnic
table or you can build your own or if you
have a decent chain cutter, you can get one
free from a conservation area.
And I don't think they're going to need is a
couple of these steel rods.
These are what they call reinforcing rods
they use for the construction crews.
But you know you can horse them right out of
the concrete if you get there before it sets.
That's how I learned all my Italian swear
words.
And the next thing you're going to need is
what we call a whole saw.
And they use that you're going to punch some
holes in each end of the oil drums and also
into the picnic table. I'd like to
have is an industrial strength T wagon.
You're right, Harold. You know, it does look
like Fred Flintstone Scar.
Anyway, we put our patch up here and now
we're all set to go serve our
guests. So remember, until next time the
women don't find you handsome, they should at
least find your handy yabba dabba doo.
Well, I guess you hear that you can leave it
there.
You know, if they're doing get away.
This spring, I pluck the petals from a
flower.
She loves me, she loves me, not she loves
me.
He loves me, not. I pluck another flower.
He loves me. She loves me.
Not. I pluck another flower.
She loves me. Not another flower and another
until there is one flower left.
She loves me. She loves me.
Not she loves me.
Oh, good. She loves me.
The gardener, on the other hand, hates my
guts.
Well, the situation with the large number of
cars is still up in the air, or, I should
say, down in the ground.
And then the four man raft has caused some
unpleasant feelings too.
Actually, I should say there are some
unpleasant smell.
I mean, that rubbery odor for it's like it's
like old gym socks, you know, anytime we get
that smell as Thanksgiving, when Eddie makes
one of his pumpkin pies,
You know, it's it's been going.
For about 20 minutes now, I think scaring
me.
Why hasn't Douglas just, you know, write it
off, what's 60 bucks
On my van with 60 bucks, Harold?
Yeah, you were able to write off that loss.
Why can't Douglass do the same?
Well, Harold, you know, it's tough for a man
to admit that he's made a mistake.
You know, the whole point of being a man is
just a it's just a tough these things
through. See them through, you know, I mean,
take a stand show some leadership and others
will follow. Well, that way you have six
cars upside down instead of just one.
Basically, yes, but but that way you end up
looking equally stupid with everybody else,
you see. And that's OK.
It's it's a male pride thing, you know,
something that you'll understand when you're
older and male.
Oh, yeah.
This is not a boat ride.
I've worked with Marina all my life.
I've seen skiffs catches everything, you
know, kayaks.
This is not a boat,
So it doesn't have a lot of trade in value
then.
Well, if you brought me something in, there
was more boat like red, you know, like an old
apple crate or an old bathtub or something.
No, I'm glad you like that.
Well, I'll give you a buck for it.
I just made twelve hundred
Twelve hundred one dollars.
Oh yeah. I can't see this particular item
being worth twelve hundred bucks anywhere,
right? Unless there's a thousand dollar bill
in that tackle box or something?
No. It boggles my mind when I look at the
size of this tire.
So imagine the RV that this would fit this
time here, and it has to be a hundred feet
long and 30 feet wide.
Yeah. Well, Douglas was one.
Maybe you could just kind of trade us even
for a wooden pump.
Oh yeah, right? You know, I don't be that
big, but you could have a spiral staircase in
there.
Yeah. Well, I got to tell you, I got some bad
News, man. I mean, it was just so high off
the ground that you could have a basement,
you know, an actual basement.
Well, thanks for your time glam.
I got I got to get back to work.
All right, right?
I imagine trying to back up on our view that
big.
I mean, imagine trying to back up something
a hundred feet long into a parking spot at
the mall. I mean, even those big, huge side
mirrors.
You know what?
What am I thinking? Something that big would
have to come with that standard on it.
It would have everything standard equipment
on that thing.
There'd be no options.
That would be a dream boat.
Sorry. That's just that pie in the sky
stuff, honey.
Well, call nine one one.
It's a time for adventures of Bill, Vail
said.
We can do some archery. So I brought a bowl
on a couple of arrows, but it's not the way
he had in mind. Even just check those out of
there.
This, I thought, was a little presumptuous.
Hey. That was a fitting response, I felt.
What do you want to do was he wanted to go
into the woods and make our own bows and
arrows just from whatever we could find in
the woods.
So it's amazing how fast you can find stuff
when you're filming.
And I came out with what I thought was a
good stick, and bill was going to make that
into some type of a bowl.
I mean, I don't ask because Bill's.
He knows what he's doing. I'm just kind of,
you know, poking my way along.
I'm using logic and common sense.
He's using a lot of book reading and in his
stuff, anyway, I got my vote done and he got
his done a little different, I guess is more
of a repeater.
I guess that's out there.
I did question it, though. Now we want to go
find some little sticks to use for the shafts
and arrows. So I saw something lying there I
thought would be adequate.
But Bill, you know, he's a bit of a
perfectionist.
He wants just that.
To me, that tree seemed it seemed dead, but
I guess he just wanted it out of it.
I think you want just to get that out of the
way, Martin.
Well, but then bills the bills, really?
The Woodsman. But he did find something
there.
Yeah, it could have just got that.
And then. Oh, I see a little plowing.
And now he's back in.
Thank you, Bill. Now we're going to carve
out the shaft shafts again here with the
arrow shaft, you picked one that I thought
was a little, well, I lost my temper anyway.
We tied stones onto the shafts of the
arrows, so that would be the one.
I'd be the arrowhead. And Bill's was pretty
generous.
And then we snip off the string I got that's
a little leaves we use for the feathers and.
It was kind of fun, you know, it was getting
a bit interesting, Bill put a target up on
the tree and start to feel like day camp,
you know, and there's mine and and there's
been there's bills.
So I loaded mine up and I gave her a try.
How's that, Robin Hood?
And now Bill's going to probably split that
arrow with his could happen, I guess.
Not too likely.
So you look at this.
Now you see Bill is a be prepared kind of
thing whips that out and to find out how we
got enough to make bows and arrows for the
whole watch.
Well, that four man raft has really come in
handy for getting the cars out of the ditch.
What we do is we we slide the deflated tube
in underneath the cars and then we start
pumping it up and it presses up against the
roof of the car.
And when she gets up to 60 70 pounds, the
carts pop straight out of the inland lands
right on its wheels. But of course, Murray
and Douglas are still at each other's
throats. Douglas hired a skywriter to fly
over the store and say, Do not shop at.
Murray's will not ever need exposing a guy
with letters five hundred feet high.
Yeah, but unfortunately, the pilot bought the
smoke canister at Murray's store, so you know
it misfired. And what he ended up writing
was doughnut shop at Murray's Murray and
Wainer, making a fortune selling doughnuts.
And of course, Douglas won't admit he made a
mistake.
Oh yeah, well, that male pride thing, right?
Yeah. See, you're lucky you don't suffer
from that like male ego thing.
No, no, not really.
No. James, it's too bad more men can't be
like you.
You know having nothing to be proud of.
Get that inner tube thing going again.
No, that's the choir of the wild foursome.
The meeting is about to come to order.
Come on, let's get down there and find out
what's going on.
Yeah, OK, Harold.
Well, so far today we've had a cartoon up
turn into an auto graveyard and we've had a
four man rafting into a whoopee cushion.
Let's see what the lodge meeting turns into,
right?
I think we to start right away.
I would sit down first before he gets here
high.
Here we go. All right.
I'm no longer in quarantine to know
The floor, recognizes Douglas Hendricks.
That man has no scruples.
Well, that's probably from that hunting
accident.
I mean, he has no ethics read.
He sold us a four man raft that turned out
to be a donut with gas.
Are you going to come down and look at it
first?
But all you cared about was the price.
See that.
See that that's the last thing you worry
about when you buy something.
For me, the price
I am for all the Possum Lodge members to
boycott Murray's store until I get a full
refund for the raft and the skywriter, he
can afford it out of doughnuts.
Well, that is just fine.
All I ever get from you is why is that so
expensive?
Or We can't afford that?
Or why does all your stock have all these
burn marks on them?
Well, you are not getting a refund, and I do
not care if you ever walk into my store
again. Your business isn't worth keeping you
a when I'd rather be a crook than a
skinflint. I admire people who make definite
career choices.
I put this to a vote.
But this is a special problem, and it
requires a special solution.
A dual. It'll get the fire extinguisher.
You two guys are going to need seconds,
right, you're like seconds, you'll be very
second man.
Gabby Douglas a second.
Oh man.
Douglas. Be brave.
Be brave.
All right, guys. Superposition.
Come on. Come on. Go back to Mike Elliott
about it.
The fire
Extinguishers. Now here's how it works.
You take three paces.
You turn your fire.
You got it. Really?
Go, Hey, what?
Call them off for a while now.
Harold, get them into their seats.
All right now I call on their chickens
To work out some kind of a compromise.
Well, they're going to cough up their fifty
dollar refund.
I think I can find another rat for 40 bucks.
So does that sound?
Well, we can only give you fifty dollars
because the other 10 was the cost on that
item. Hmm.
Well, I'll tell you what, I'll give you ten
bucks for the old inner tube and I'll throw
that in. And then then we're there, right?
Done. Done. All right.
Great. What we're proposing is put that
down, bill.
What we're proposing is that Gary Starr is
going to give us 50 bucks back on the roof.
I'm going to throw in a sob.
We're going to get another 40 from the lodge
getting.
We can buy a new four man raft flap.
All in favor. We're all in favor, say I.
Motion carried. Just no other large business,
right?
I'm going to call on Glenn here to give us
an evening's entertainment.
Ok, thanks, Fred.
That you don't like this.
Well, it's nice to see Murray and Duane get
what's coming to them.
None of their customers ever have.
And Douglas has learned that you get what
you pay for.
It's like my Uncle Clydesdale used to say,
if you buy the best, you'll never regret it.
But if you steal the best, you'll never
regret it and still have money for a nice
dinner. And that's a philosophy he
maintained throughout his prison term.
Anyway, yeah, my wife is watching.
I'll be coming straight home after the
meeting and I'm bringing the inner tube so we
can pop your mother out of the bathtub.
So until next time, on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole gang up here at Possum
Lodge. Keep your stick on the ice.
And that's the history of the overpass.
Yeah, the first one, okay.
Oh, all right. Let's see the focus.
So gelding, farm or horses?
Yeah, it was made Horse Race gelding.
Yeah. The Pretty. At work or in the Arab.