IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE MAN WITH THE PLAN
HE THOUGHT OF IN THE CAN...
IF YOU'RE A FAN
OF THE MAN IN THE VAN...
PUT YOUR HANDS TOGETHER FOR
RED GREEN... EGGS AND HAM!
HOW YOU DOIN'?
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
(Applause and cheering)
HERE'S THE FREAK WITH THE BEAK
AND THE CHUBBY CHEEK -- HAROLD!
(Applause)
ALL RIGHT, COOL IT --
PUT A SOCK IN IT.
I DID, AND EVERYBODY LAUGHED.
(Laughing)
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW, OK?
WE HAD A GOVERNMENT BUILDING
INSPECTOR COME INTO TOWN
AND PULL A SURPRISE
SAFETY INSPECTION
ON THE COMMUNITY CENTRE
THIS MORNING.
HE FILLED OUT A REPORT,
SAYS IF WE DON'T FIX IT,
HE'S GONNA HAVE IT CONDEMNED.
HE CAN'T DO THAT!
WHERE WILL THEY HOLD
THE TEEN DANCES?
YOU DON'T GO
TO DANCES.
I WILL... WHEN
I'M BETTER-LOOKING
AND I LEARN KARATE.
SO WE GOTTA
SAVE
THE COMMUNITY CENTRE --
WHAT'S WRONG WITH IT?
JUST THREE THINGS --
THE ROOF, THE WALLS, THE FLOOR.
OH!
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MAIN MESSAGE BEING,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
I GOT THE SCOOP -- THE BUILDING
INSPECTOR WAS CALLED IN
TO THE COMMUNITY CENTRE
BY A WEDDING PARTY.
THEY HAD A WEDDING THERE
LAST WEEK.
ONE OF THE STEEL "I" BEAMS
SWUNG LOOSE FROM THE CEILING,
DROPPED DOWN
ONTO THE WEDDING CAKE...
CRACKED THE ICING AND CRUSHED
THE BRIDE AND GROOM.
I'LL TELL YOU,
PEOPLE ARE SUCH WHINERS.
IT'S THE BRIDE
AND GROOM
ON THE CAKE.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
YEAH.
MAN!
OK, ANYWAY, IF THE COMMUNITY
CENTRE GETS CONDEMNED,
PEOPLE WILL HAVE QUILTING BEES
AND CRAFT SHOWS AT THE LODGE.
WE CAN'T HAVE THAT!
YOU KNOW WHAT I DID?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
I SUGGESTED WE HAVE
A FUND-RAISER,
TO RAISE FUNDS TO REPAIR
THE COMMUNITY CENTRE.
IT'S THE CENTRE
OF OUR COMMUNITY.
ABSOLUTELY,
YEAH.
THE HEART AND SOUL
OF POSSUM LAKE,
AND REFLECTS OUR COMMUNITY...
ESPECIALLY NOW THAT
IT'S OLD, CRACKED, AND SMELLY.
THAT'S IT, HAROLD.
UNFORTUNATELY, THE TOWNSPEOPLE
DIDN'T TAKE THAT WELL
TO HAROLD'S SUGGESTION.
I TOOK A REAL HAY-MAKER
RIGHT TO THE STOMACH.
MOOSE'S GRANDMOTHER
CAN BE MEAN!
SHE'S GOT THE...
I GAVE AS GOOD AS I GOT...
IN TERMS OF SCREAMING.
DON'T WORRY -- THE MEN OF
POSSUM LODGE WILL TAKE OVER.
WE'RE GONNA RAISE MONEY
TO REBUILD THE CENTRE.
REMEMBER LAST YEAR
WHERE WE SOLD CHOCOLATE BARS?
CHOCOLATE BARS?
YEAH.
THOSE WERE BRICKS
OF OLD CHEESE.
CHOCOLATE BARS.
OLD CHEESE.
WHAT WAS THE CRUNCHY MIDDLE?
VERY OLD CHEESE.
(Audience laughing)
(Red): SOMETHING SPECIAL
ON THE "ADVENTURES
WITH BILL" SEGMENT.
BILL AND I HAD
THE CANOES OUT AND...
HOW DOES HE DO THAT?
HOW DOES HE MANAGE...
BILL HAD GONE TO THE
CHOCOLATE-BAR DRIVE-THROUGH.
OHHH!
YEAH, OH, THAT'S A SHAME.
OH, BY GOLLY, HUH?
YOU OK? ALL RIGHT.
IT'S THE KIND OF FUN
THAT YOU CAN HAVE OUTDOORS.
THE BEAUTY OF BEING OUTDOORS IS
THAT YOU'RE NOT INSIDE AS MUCH
AND YOU CAN BE OUT THERE,
AND THERE'S ROOM FOR YOU,
BECAUSE GUYS LIKE US ONLY NEED
THAT LITTLE EXTRA SPACE...
A PLACE TO DUMP
OUR CHOCOLATE BAR WRAPPERS...
AND THE MOTOR.
IT WILL BE EASIER TO PORTAGE.
BILL AND I, EVERY YEAR, WE HAVE
OUR LITTLE PORTAGING RACE.
WE PUT THE CANOES ON
AND AWAY WE GO.
I DIDN'T THINK
IT WAS FAIR... OHHH!
OHHHH! OHHHH! OHHHH!
BILL DROPPED THE CANOE
ON ME -- JUST A WAY
OF HANDICAPPING ME A LITTLE.
IT'S NOT FAIR,
JUST TO BEAT HIM,
SO LET'S HELP HIM OUT.
WE WANT A FAIR RACE,
RIGHT, BILL?
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
YOU CAN USUALLY
PICK UP THE CANOE.
WHAT'S THE TROUBLE?
OH, MY GOSH,
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT--
OH, ALL RIGHT, OK.
THIS MAKES IT HARDER
TO BEND THE KNEES.
WE'LL BE BACK LATER WITH OUR...
... BIG RACE,
SO HANG IN FOR THAT.
OHHHHH
YIPPEE-YO, YAAA,
YAHOOEY, YALADY
YIPPEE-YI-YI-YI-YI-YI-YI
YES, THIS IS THE SONG
OF THE LONESOME COWBOY
WHEN HE LANDS THE WRONG WAY
ON HIS SADDLE
AIEE-AIEE-AIEE!
YIIII!
THIS IS FOR THE BIG ONE!
FOR A GRAND PRIZE
OF NINE COILS OF KOLBASA
AND A 12-POUND BREATH MINT,
UNCLE RED,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. DOUGIE FRANKLIN
TO SAY THIS WORD.
"ROMANTIC."
WAHAHH!
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT,
DOUGIE.
SENSUAL, PASSIONATE, POETIC...
1963 CORVETTE STINGRAY.
NO, NO, WHEN A MAN BUYS A WOMAN
FLOWERS AND CANDY,
THAT'S VERY...
... OBVIOUS.
NO, YOU BRING A WOMAN
BACK TO YOUR PLACE.
THAT'S...
... A MIRACLE.
(Audience laughing)
OK, YOU DIM
THE LIGHTS DOWN LOW
TO MAKE IT
MORE...
... DIFFICULT
FOR THE NEIGHBOURS
TO SEE WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
I REALLY GOTTA GET ME
SOME DRAPES, RED.
IT'S HIDEOUS BACK THERE.
UH, I KNOW.
A WOMAN FALLS FOR A MAN
WHO IS...
... UH, ABLE TO DRIVE
A MONSTER TRUCK?
NO? THAT'S
NOT IT?
I KNOW, I KNOW.
WHEN A GUY IS VERY SENSITIVE,
LAVISHES GIFTS,
AND IS VERY CONSIDERATE AND
VERY FEELING, HE'S OBVIOUSLY...
... GAY.
(Audience laughing)
WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
A '63 STINGRAY.
OH, ROMANTIC!
(Laughing and applause)
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
WE'LL SOLVE A MEMORY PROBLEM
WE'VE ALL FACED...
IT'S SUNDAY AFTERNOON,
YOU'RE LYING THERE RELAXING.
RELATIVES PULL IN
TO YOUR DRIVEWAY.
YOU REALIZE IT'S THANKSGIVING
AND IT'S YOUR TURN
TO HOST THE DINNER,
AND YOU'RE NOT DRESSED.
SO TWO QUESTIONS
POP INTO YOUR MIND.
FIRST, HOW CAN YOU COOK A
25-POUND TURKEY IN 13 MINUTES?
AND, SECONDLY,
WHERE ARE YOUR PANTS?
I'M GONNA ANSWER
THE FIRST QUESTION.
YOU MIGHT BE THINKING
MICROWAVE OVEN.
THEY COOK FAST,
THEY DON'T HEAT UP THE KITCHEN,
AND THEY DING
WHEN THEY'RE DONE.
PROBLEM IS,
THEY'RE TOO DARNED SMALL.
CAN'T GET THE TURKEY IN THERE.
YOU COULD CUT THEM UP
INTO PIECES
AND JAM EVERYTHING IN.
YOU COULD PUT THE MICROWAVE UP
ON ITS BACK
AND JUMP ON THE TURKEY.
YOU COULD RIP THE DOOR OFF
AND COOK 'ER,
BUT THAT REDUCES THE QUALITY
OF YOUR DINNER CONVERSATIONS.
SO I SAY JUST FORGET
ABOUT THE MICROWAVE.
(Crashing)
GO WITH A MACROWAVE OVEN.
I LIKE THE SOUND OF THAT.
YOU WANT TO GET
A BUNCH OF THESE ANIMAL CAGES.
YOU'RE GONNA BE COOKING
IN THESE
SO MAKE SURE THEY'RE EMPTY...
UNLESS YOU GOT
A REALLY WEIRD UNCLE.
BUT THE MAIN INGREDIENT IS YOUR
ENERGY-GATHERING HEAT-A-TRON,
ALSO KNOWN AS A SATELLITE DISH.
YOU CAN PICK THESE UP ANYWHERE,
ESPECIALLY IN OPEN FIELDS
ON MOONLESS NIGHTS.
YOU WANT TO MOUNT
YOUR SATELLITE DISH
ON SOMETHING SOLID AND LOW,
LIKE A WATER HEATER
OR MOOSE THOMPSON'S
BEAN-BAG CHAIR.
I GOT 'ER ONTO AN OIL DRUM.
NO MATTER WHAT TIME IT IS, PART
OF THIS IS ALWAYS FACING SOUTH.
LOOKS GOOD, LOOKS GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, THE NEXT PROBLEM IS,
GOTTA FIND A WAY
TO RAISE MY OVEN CHAMBERS
SO THEY'RE IN THE PRIMARY
COOKING ZONE
OF MY SATELLITE DISH.
OH! ALL RIGHT.
THIS SWING SET SHOULD WORK
ABSOLUTELY GREAT.
NOT ONLY WILL THIS HOLD
THE TURKEY UP HIGH,
IT ALLOWS ME TO SWING IT OUT
OF THE HARMFUL RAYS
SO I DON'T ADD MY OWN
RUMP ROAST TO THE MENU.
ALL I GOTTA DO
IS REMOVE THE SEATS.
RUST IS A REAL TIME-SAVER.
NOW ALL WE GOTTA DO
IS STICK FOOD INTO THE CAGES
AND LET MR. SUN DO HIS THING.
I THINK WHAT I'VE FORGOTTEN
IS THAT, AROUND THANKSGIVING,
THE SUN IS NOT AS HOT
AS IT NEEDS TO BE FOR THIS.
MAYBE WE NEED TO SWITCH TO
A DIFFERENT SOURCE OF ENERGY.
MAYBE TAKE APART
THIS MICROWAVE OVEN
AND GET THE MICROWAVE TUBE
OR GENERATOR
OR WHATEVER IT IS
THAT MAKES MICROWAVES.
MIGHT EVEN BE A LITTLE
WAVE-POOL IN THERE.
WE'LL FIND OUT
WHEN WE TAKE 'ER APART.
ALL RIGHT, WE GOT
SQUARE-HEAD BOLTS.
LOOKS LIKE THE RED SIZE.
I GOT THE GREEN...
I GOT THE BLACK -- NO RED.
OH, WELL.
WE GOT OUR MICROWAVE GENERATOR
WIRED TO THE SATELLITE DISH,
WHICH BECOMES AN AMPLIFIER --
GONNA BOOST THE MICROWAVE
OUTPUT OF 1,500 WATTS
UP INTO THE AREA OF
5 TRILLION MEGAHERTZ
OF NEUTRON FUSION ENERGY.
THAT SHOULD BE ENOUGH TO COOK
THOSE HARD-TO-GET-AT PLACES.
IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
LET'S GET COOKIN'.
(Coughing)
AHHH...
HOLY MACKEREL.
THERE'S A FAIR AMOUNT
OF SHRINKAGE WITH THESE.
I THINK I SHOULD HAVE STARTED
WITH A LARGER TURKEY.
HAROLD!
JUST KIDDING...
... UNLESS YOU WANT TO.
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
SOMETHING I HEARD IN TOWN.
OLD LADY BENKMAN SAID
YOU CAN'T CONTROL
THE UGLY THINGS
PEOPLE SAY ABOUT YOU
AFTER YOU'RE DEAD.
I THINK THAT'S TRUE.
I CAN'T CONTROL THE THINGS
PEOPLE SAY ABOUT ME
WHILE I'M LIVING.
I DON'T ANTICIPATE
GETTING BETTER AT IT
AFTER I'M SIX FEET UNDER.
SO YOU CAN'T STOP PEOPLE
FROM SAYING BAD STUFF ABOUT YOU
AFTER YOU'RE DEAD.
IS THAT REAL IMPORTANT?
UNLESS YOU HAVE
EXCEPTIONAL HEARING,
YOU MAY NOT NOTICE.
TO PLAY IT SAFE, YOU COULD GET
BURIED WITH EARPLUGS IN.
YOU CAN'T CONTROL WHAT THEY SAY
BUT YOU CAN CONTROL
WHETHER OR NOT IT'S TRUE.
ACTIONS SPEAK LOUDER THAN WORDS
SO MAKE SURE YOUR ACTIONS
ARE LOUDER THAN THEIR WORDS.
IF THEY SAY THAT
YOU WERE A DRUNKEN WOMANIZER,
WHEREAS YOU LED A SOBER LIFE
AND WERE A DECENT FAMILY MAN,
THEY'RE GONNA HAVE A HARD TIME
GETTING ANYBODY TO LISTEN...
WHEREAS IF IT WAS THE BOOZE
AND BABES THAT KILLED YOU,
WELL, YOU GOT A PROBLEM.
BUT BY THEN, YOU'LL PROBABLY BE
IN A HOT SPOT
AND NOT THAT CONCERNED
WITH PUBLIC RELATIONS.
SO DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause)
THE COMMUNITY CENTRE
FUND-RAISING COMMITTEE
HAD ITS FIRST MEETING --
DIDN'T GO REAL WELL.
IN HINDSIGHT, THE OPEN BAR
WAS A MISTAKE.
DID YOU EVER MAKE ANY MOTIONS
FOR FUND-RAISING?
BUSTER HADFIELD SUGGESTED
WE HAVE A WALK-A-THON.
THAT'S EXCELLENT! THAT'S GREAT!
A WALK-A-THON'S
A GREAT WAY TO MAKE MONEY!
WE FOUND OUT
THERE'S WALKING INVOLVED
SO WE PUT THAT ASIDE.
MOOSE THOMPSON
HAD A GREAT IDEA.
BELCH-A-THON?
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF WHEN I SAY
"THRILLS, CHILLS, AND SPILLS"?
ANDREA THOMPSON POURING
A CHERRY SLURPEE DOWN MY PANTS
AT THE SADIE HAWKINS DANCE.
(Audience laughing)
PEOPLE MIGHT PAY MONEY
TO SEE THAT, BUT...
I'M TALKING ABOUT A FUN FAIR...
THE POSSUM LODGE FUN FAIR --
NOT LIKE ANY OTHER FUN FAIR.
THERE WILL BE NO FUN
AND NO FAIR.
(Laughing)
ALL RIGHT, WELCOME TO
"AUTO BIOGRAPHY",
WHERE MEMBERS OF POSSUM LODGE
TALK ABOUT CARS
THAT MEANT SOMETHING TO THEM.
HAP, WHAT WAS
YOUR FAVOURITE CAR?
OH, MY...
I'D HAVE TO SAY
MY '62 ASTON-MARTIN D.B.S.
GOLD FINISH...
BEAUTIFUL MACHINE.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE THE CAR
JAMES BOND DROVE
BEFORE HE WAS ROGER MOORE
OR TIMOTHY DALTON
OR PIERCE BROSNAN
OR THAT OLD GUY.
IT WAS THE CAR, HAROLD.
I OWNED THE CAR
THAT WAS IN THOSE MOVIES.
YOU BOUGHT THAT
FROM THE PRODUCERS?
NO, THEY BOUGHT IT FROM ME.
THEY NEEDED AN ASTON-MARTIN
AND THEY KNEW
MINE HAD MACHINE-GUNS
AND BULLET-PROOF SHIELDS...
(Audience laughing)
... AND REVOLVING LICENCE
PLATES, AN EJECTION SEAT,
AND THAT THING THAT CAME OUT
OF THE WHEEL -- WAH-WAH-WAH!
AND THAT WAS IT --
END OF STORY.
THIS WHOLE STORY'S
KIND OF WAH-WAH-WAH.
(Laughing)
YOU'RE TELLING ME
YOU USED ALL THOSE GADGETS?
NO!
GOD! YOU KIDDING?
NO, I NEVER USED
THE REVOLVING LICENCE PLATES,
BUT THOSE MACHINE-GUNS
CAME IN HANDY MORE THAN ONCE.
WITHOUT THE BULLET-PROOF
SHIELD, I WOULDN'T BE HERE NOW.
NO, WHEN YOU HAVE THOSE THINGS,
YOU USE 'EM.
I COULD GO FOR AN EJECTION SEAT
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
OR A CYANIDE CAPSULE.
THIS WAS A BUSINESS CAR, HAP?
OH, YEAH! YEAH, KIND OF.
COME ON, YOU KNEW I WAS IN
HER MAJESTY'S SECRET SERVICE.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
DOUBLE-OH-NOTHING,
LICENCE TO BULL.
OHHHH... OH, BEAUTIFUL CAR,
THOUGH, RED.
YEAH.
HAD A BUILT-IN BAR
AND A SPY CAMERA...
SATELLITE LOCATOR...
EVEN A LIE-DETECTOR.
MUST HAVE DRAINED THE BATTERY
EVERY TIME
YOU OPENED YOUR MOUTH!
HERE WE ARE, ALL SET
FOR OUR BIG PORTAGE RACE.
OK, GENTLEMEN...
START YOUR ANGINA.
OK, WE'RE OFF AND
I GOT A BIT OF A LEAD.
ONE THING SURPRISES ME.
WE NEVER GET A TURN-OUT,
SPECTATOR-WISE, FOR THIS,
FOR SOME REASON.
I THINK THERE'S A LOT TO WATCH.
I'M NOT SURE HOW SAFE YOU'D BE,
WITHIN, SAY, A CANOE'S-LENGTH
OF THE ACTUAL RACE ITSELF.
IF YOU HUNG BACK
WITH A TELEPHOTO, YOU COULD GET
INTERESTING SHOTS.
I'M WELL OUT AHEAD.
BILL HAS A DIFFERENT APPROACH.
HE REALLY BENDS OVER.
HE'S GOT
THE LOWER-BACK PROBLEM.
THAT SHOULD HELP THAT.
HANG ON, HANG ON,
BUT HE'S GOT THE RIGHT IDEA.
LOOK OUT, BILL --
TREE, BILL! TREE, BILL!
OHHHHH! DON'T BE HAMMERING
ON THAT TREE -- LOOK OUT!
LOOK OUT, HERE COMES THE CANOE!
THAT HAS GOTTA HURT.
I'M JUST MAKING MY WAY ALONG,
DOING JUST FINE.
BILL, YOU'RE GOING
THE WRONG WAY.
NO, YOU SHOULD BE--
WHERE IS HE?
OH, THERE HE IS.
EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, SEEMS FINE.
AND... LOOKS LIKE I WON.
ALL I GOTTA DO
IS GET THE WHOLE THING IN--
BUT I LOOKED BACK.
HERE HE COMES.
GONNA BE A CLOSE RACE.
HANG ON, BILL, HANG ON!
BETTER GET MY CANOE--
WHAT'S GOING ON? BILL!
LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT!
UH-OH! UH-OH!
OHHH... AHHHH!
HOLY MACKEREL.
HE WON!
I'D RATHER LOSE.
HERE'S A WALKING STICK
MADE BY OUR PAL MICHAEL --
THANKS, MIKE.
THE FUN FAIR'S GONNA RAISE
SO MUCH CASH,
WE CAN BUILD
A NEW COMMUNITY CENTRE.
I'M LOOKING AFTER
THE FIREWORKS.
MOOSE THOMPSON'S GOT
THE DART-THROW GOING.
GOT HIMSELF A '64 DART.
(Audience laughing)
STRAPS PEOPLE INTO IT
AND JUST CHUCKS 'ER.
HOW'S THE RING-TOSS COMIN'?
EXCELLENT -- WATCH THIS,
WATCH THIS.
OH, BOY.
NO PROBLEM --
JUST WATCH.
THAT'S HARD! WE'LL MAKE
A TON OF MONEY!
OH, RIGHT, HAROLD.
THE BIG MONEY-MAKER'S GONNA BE
BUSTER'S FLIGHT SIMULATOR.
A FLIGHT SIMULATOR?! AWWWWWW!
THEY'RE EXCELLENT!
THEY'RE SO WAY COOL!
THEY'RE LIKE VIRTUAL REALITY,
3-D TO THE MAX, THEN YOU BARF.
(Laughing)
IS IT STATE-OF-THE-ART?
IS IT CUTTING-EDGE?
YOU COULD CUT YOURSELF REAL BAD
ON ONE EDGE.
IT'S A CHERRY-PICKER.
HE FOUND IT JUST SITTING
IN THE TELEPHONE PARKING LOT,
AND HE JUST BLINDFOLDS PEOPLE,
WHIPS 'EM AROUND.
HAROLD, WE GOT THE DUNK-TANK,
WHERE YOU THROW BASEBLLS AND
THE GUY DROPS INTO THE TANK.
I LOVE THOSE! I LOVE THOSE!
WHO'S SUPPLYING THAT?
UH, ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE.
OH, EXCELLENT,
EXCELLENT.
WHOOOOO!
WHO'S THE SUCKER
WHO'S GONNA FALL
IN THAT TANK ALL DAY LONG?
(Audience laughing)
WHO? TELL ME!
I'M GONNA FIND OUT!
I KNOW THE PERSON, DON'T I?
I DO.
HAWWW....
IT'S THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE EXAMINE
THOSE THREE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
(Audience):
"I DON'T KNOW!"
EITHER DO THEY.
JOINING MY UNCLE RED
IS HIS BEST FRIEND--
OH, INSTEAD,
IT'S MR. DALTON HUMPHREY!
(Applause and cheering)
THE VIEWER ASKS, "DEAR EXPERTS,
WHENEVER WE HAVE FRIENDS OVER
"AND PLAY WORD GAMES,
LIKE SCRABBLE, THE MEN LOSE.
"THEN WE GET TO HEAR
HOW GOOD THEY ARE
"AT THE GAME
'BUT I'VE GOT AN EXCUSE'.
"WHY ARE MEN BAD
AT WORD GAMES?"
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET THIS
CLEARED UP.
THIS IS A MYTH.
IT'S COMPLETELY FALSE.
MEN ARE NOT, UH...
OK, BAD... AT WORD GAMES.
"BAD", AS IN LIMITED,
DEFICIENT, INADEQUATE, INEPT?
NO, I MEAN "OBNOXIOUS"
AS IN "HAROLD".
(Laughing)
YOU KNOW,
MY WIFE, ANNE-MARIE,
AND I PLAY WORD GAMES
AS PART OF
OUR NORMAL CONVERSATION.
SHE'LL STRING WORDS TOGETHER
AND I'LL TRY AND GUESS
WHAT SHE'S TALKIN' ABOUT.
NOW, OK,
I USUALLY GUESS WRONG,
BUT THAT'S BECAUSE I LOST
INTEREST AND STOPPED LISTENING.
IT IS NOT BECAUSE
I'M NOT GOOD AT IT.
SEE, THERE'S NO INCENTIVE
TO WIN ON THAT.
IF YOU DO UNDERSTAND,
YOU HAVE TO GET UP
AND DO SOMETHING.
SEE, DALTON AND I,
WE UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER.
WELL, MEN UNDERSTAND MEN.
WHEN MEN AND WOMEN HAVE WORDS,
THAT'S WHERE
THE TROUBLE STARTS.
SEE, WOMEN USE WORDS... UM...
THEY, UH...
WOMEN...
TO, UH...
COMMUNICATE, INFORM, DISCLOSE?
WELL... CLOSE.
YEAH, OK.
BUT... BUT...
BUT NOW, WITH MEN,
WHAT THEY, UH... THEY, UH...
UH...
MEN... USE WORDS
TO AVOID SAYING
SOMETHING.
HERE WE GO -- THAT'S IT.
THAT'S IT, THAT'S IT.
THERE WE GO -- YEAH.
(Laughing and applause)
AND, YOU SEE,
IF MEN HAVE SOMETHING
REAL IMPORTANT TO SAY,
THEY'LL SHAKE HANDS...
OR HITCH UP THEIR PANTS
OR POINT AT SOMETHING.
YEAH, SURE, THAT'S IT.
THAT'S ALMOST ELOQUENT
IN ITS SIMPLICITY.
(Audience laughing)
SORRY, HAROLD, YOU LOST ME.
NEVER MIND,
IT'S OK.
MEN ARE NOT BAD AT WORD GAMES.
IT'S JUST THAT WE... WE...
WHAT WE... WE, UH...
WE USE THE BODY LANGUAGE.
WELL!
YOU CERTAINLY HAVE
A WELL-ROUNDED VOCABULARY
TO WORK WITH.
(Laughing and applause)
(Audience laughing)
(Coughing)
(Clearing throat)
WELL, UH...
THAT WAS, UH...
THAT WAS QUITE A FUN FAIR.
FLIGHT SIMULATOR WAS GOOD,
RING-TOSS WAS GOOD.
WHAT IDIOT WAS IN CHARGE
OF THE FIREWORKS?
YOU SHOULDN'T GO AROUND
CALLING PEOPLE IDIOTS.
I KNEW IT WAS YOU! I KNEW!
FUN FAIRS ALWAYS END
WITH FIREWORKS.
EVERYBODY AGREED TO THAT.
BUT IT WASN'T RAINING THEN.
WE DIDN'T KNOW
WE'D MOVE THE FUN FAIR INDOORS.
(Laughing)
OTHER THAN THE FIRE,
I THINK IT WENT PRETTY WELL.
HE BURNED THE COMMUNITY CENTRE
DOWN -- IT'S GONE!
(Laughing)
THE FUN FAIR RAISED
ENOUGH MONEY
TO COVER THE DEDUCTIBLE
ON THE INSURANCE.
NOW WE GET A BRAND-NEW
COMMUNITY CENTRE.
I DON'T SEE A DOWN-SIDE.
OK, HOW ABOUT
THE INSURANCE COMPANY
CANCELLING
YOUR POLICY?
NOW WE DON'T HAVE TO
PAY PREMIUMS.
OK, HOW
ABOUT THIS?
I REFUSE TO HELP
WITH YOUR PROJECTS.
MAN, I'M ON A ROLL!
(Possum squeal)
OH, MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD --
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
I'M GONNA GET THE ASHES
OUT OF MY NOSTRILS.
I THOUGHT THAT SPARKLER
WOULD NEVER GO OUT.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
IF YOU SEE SMOKE
COMING FROM MY PANTS,
REMEMBER, WHERE THERE'S SMOKE,
THERE'S FIRE.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): ALL RISE FOR
THE BEGINNING OF THE MEETING!
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN.
STINKY PETERSON ASKED ME
TO ANNOUNCE THAT
YOU CANNOT JUMP-START
A '78 GREMLIN FROM A STOVE.
ANYBODY WHO THINKS YOU CAN
IS WELCOME TO DROP BY HIS PLACE
AND PUT OUT A KITCHEN FIRE.