[quirky upbeat music]
[chain saw buzzing]
[gunshots, glass shatters]
>> AND NOW FOR THE PROGRAM THAT
DARES TO BREAK ALL THE RULES
BUT APPEARS TO BE DIFFERENT,
BECAUSE IT DOESN'T HAVE THE
BUDGET THAT OTHER SHOWS DO.
AND I THINK THAT'S PARTICULARLY
UNFAIR IF YOU ASK.
WELL, ANYWAY, THE POINT IS,
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW.
AND NOW IT'S TIME FOR THE MAN
WITH A HALF HOUR IN YOUR HOME,
MY UNCLE AND EVERYONE'S FAVORITE
WOODSMAN, RED GREEN.
[applause]
GO FOR IT, UNCLE RED.
DON'T BLOW IT, OKAY?
>> OH, THANK YOU, HAROLD.
WELL, THANK YOU.
AND WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
WE'VE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
THIS WEEK.
WE GOT--WHAT DOES THAT SAY?
TRUCKLOADS OF FUN, BOATLOADS
OF GUESTS, AND ARMLOADS OF LOVE
FOR YOU?
THAT SOUNDS TERRIBLE, HAROLD.
>> NO, IT SOUNDED GREAT.
THAT ARMLOADS THING SOUNDED
FANTASTIC, VERY NATURAL,
VERY TV.
>> HAROLD HERE IS PRODUCER AND
DIRECTOR OF THE SHOW.
AND HE'S ALSO MY NEPHEW.
>> THANK YOU FOR THAT GENEROUS
APPLAUSE.
>> I DIDN'T HEAR ANY APPLAUSE.
>> I WAS SHAMING THEM.
>> YOU SHAME EVERYONE, HAROLD.
HAROLD'S KIND OF HOOKED INTO
THE MODERN TECHNOLOGY HERE.
YOU COULD EVEN SAY HE'S WIRED.
I DO.
BUT, YOU KNOW, HE'S NOT JUST
PRODUCER AND DIRECTOR JUST
BECAUSE HE'S MY NEPHEW.
>> NO, IT'S BECAUSE
I CAN DO THIS.
[keys clacking]
[chuckles]
THAT'S WHY I'M PRODUCER AND
DIRECTOR.
>> NO, THAT'S NOT IT, HAROLD.
IT'S BECAUSE YOUR FATHER PUT UP
51% OF THE MONEY TO DO THE SHOW
HERE.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU OFFERED ME THE JOB LONG
BEFORE DAD BAILED YOU OUT OF
THAT TELEFILM DISASTER.
>> YEAH, BUT AT THAT POINT, YOUR
JOB DESCRIPTION WAS KEY GRIP.
>> IS HE THE GUY THAT, LIKE,
WORKS WITH THE LIGHTS AND THE
CABLES?
>> NOT IN THIS CASE, HAROLD.
THIS IS THE GUY THAT GRIPS THE
KEYS TO MY TRUCK WHILE I'M ON
CAMERA AND KEEPS GRIPPING THEM
TILL I WANT TO GO HOME.
>> OH, YEAH, I GOT THEM.
I GOT THEM.
IT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
I'M OKAY THERE, UNCLE RED.
I FIGURED MAYBE WE'D JUST GO
RIGHT INTO THE NEXT SEGMENT,
IF THAT'S OKAY WITH YOU.
>> WHAT ABOUT MY STORY?
>> OH, WHAT ABOUT IT?
>> WELL, I WAS GONNA TELL THE
PEOPLE AT THE LAUNCH HERE ABOUT
HOW WE GOT A NEW OUTHOUSE.
>> OH, THAT'S AN INTERESTING
SEGUE.
>> THAT WASN'T A SEGUE, HAROLD.
>> THEY NEVER ARE.
[slow guitar and spoons music plays]
>> HE WAS SHORT AND MANGY
AND MISSING ONE EAR
HE ATE MOSTLY SQUIRRELS
AND HE DRANK MOSTLY BEER
HE LOOKED LIKE A RODENT
HE SMELLED LIKE A BOG
BUT HE WASN'T EITHER
HE WAS MY HUNTING DOG
MY HUNTING DOG
WAS A WONDERFUL FRIEND
BUT WITH A SLIP OF MY SAFETY
HE COME TO AN END
HE WAS THE BEST COMPANION
THAT I EVER HAD
MY GOOD OLD DOG, UH...
CAN'T REMEMBER
HIS NAME RIGHT NOW.
WAS IT KING?
>> IT WAS REX.
>> NO, IT WASN'T REX.
>> DAVE?
>> NO, IT WAS MISTER SOMETHING.
MISTER--OR WAS IT MISSUS?
MISS?
>> NO, IT WAS MISTER.
>> WAS IT MISTER?
>> IT WAS A MISTER.
BELIEVE ME, IT WAS A MISTER.
>> OH, YEAH.
YOU REMEMBER THAT?
>> YEAH.
WHOO, THERE WAS A WEEKEND.
>> THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU HOW TO
FIX A LAWNMOWER.
WHEN YOU DO FIX A LAWNMOWER,
THERE IS A CERTAIN ORDER THAT
YOU CHECK THINGS IN.
NOW, THIS PARTICULAR MACHINE
HAS A SEIZED ENGINE.
SO THE FIRST THING YOU CHECK
IS THE PRICE OF A NEW ONE.
AND THEN YOU CHECK THE I.Q.
OF THE LAST PERSON THAT USED IT.
AND YOU'LL FIND ONLY ONE OF
THOSE IS HIGH.
THE NEXT THING YOU CHECK IS
THE SPARK PLUG.
DISCONNECT THE PLUG.
AND TAKE OUT THE SPARK PLUG.
ADJUST THE GAP.
AND REINSTALL IT.
AND WHILE YOU GOT THE GAS CAN
OPEN ANYWAY, YOU MIGHT AS WELL
CHECK TO SEE IF THERE'S ANY
EXCESS GAS IN THERE.
I GUESS NOT.
THE NEXT THING YOU MIGHT WANT
TO TAKE A LOOK AT IS THE BLADE
ITSELF.
WHAT YOU'RE CHECKING FOR HERE
IS NICKS AND BUMPS.
NO, THERE'S NOT NEARLY ENOUGH
OF THOSE.
THAT'S ABOUT IT.
I GUESS THE LAST STEP WHEN
YOU'RE CHECKING A LAWNMOWER
WITH A SEIZED ENGINE IS TO KILL
YOUR NEPHEW HAROLD.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME, REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
HAROLD, CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A MINUTE?
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE
OF THE SHOW AND THE STORY OF
THE OUTHOUSE.
>> BUT NOT HOPEFULLY AT THE
SAME TIME.
>> YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN WORKING
REALLY HARD ON THE SHOW.
AND YOU PROBABLY NOTICED THAT,
YOU KNOW, WITH THE DIRECTING
AND THE CUTTING-AWAYS AND THINGS
LIKE THAT.
SO I THOUGHT--EMMY.
WE'RE GONNA GET ONE FOR SURE.
>> YOU MEAN AN AWARD?
>> AN AWARD FOR THE MOST
OUTSTANDING PRODUCTION IN
THE WOODS.
IS THAT A CATEGORY?
THAT'S MY PROBLEM.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> I DON'T THINK THERE'D BE TOO
MANY IN THE CATEGORY.
WHAT ABOUT BEST FOREIGN FEATURE
FILM LENGTH 30-MINUTE
DOCU-QUASI-COMEDY AND, UH,
SPORTS SHOW?
>> WELL, THERE'S A LOT IN THAT
CATEGORY.
I THINK L.A. LAW
IS IN THAT CATEGORY.
>> IS IT?
>> YEAH.
IT'S A TOUGH COMPETITION.
THEY GOT MORE PEOPLE THAN US.
WE COULD BE BEST MUSICAL COMEDY
VARIETY SERIES IN A WOODED AREA.
>> THAT HAS A RING TO IT.
>> YEAH.
THERE'S NOT A LOT IN THAT.
NOW THAT YOGI BEAR'S BEEN
CANCELED, WE'RE PRETTY MUCH
A SHOO-IN.
>> YOGI BEAR'S BEEN CANCELED?
>> HEARTBREAKER, ISN'T IT?
>> "IT IS WINTER.
OUTSIDE, THE SNOW IS PILED DEEP.
THE NORTH WIND BLOWS ALL NIGHT.
BUT HERE, INSIDE, YOU'RE
SNUGGLED WARM, YOUR FACE BATHED
IN ORANGE LIGHT FROM THE
CIGARETTE LIGHTER AS YOU WAIT
FOR THE TOW TRUCK."
SO ANYWAYS, I WAS TRYING TO TELL
YOU A STORY ABOUT HOW THE LODGE
GOT A NEW OUTHOUSE.
AND, WELL, IT STARTS WITH
A MISSING STICK OF DYNAMITE
AND OLD MAN SEDGEWICK NEEDING
A CANDLE FOR ONE OF HIS
LATE-NIGHT VISITS TO THE WOODS.
>> UNCLE RED, I DON'T REALLY
THINK THIS IS A GOOD STORY TO
BE TELLING.
I MEAN, IT WAS ALREADY ALL OVER
THE LOCAL NEWS AND IN
THE PAPERS.
"TNT TURNS TOILET TRIP
TO TERROR."
>> WELL, BUT THEY DIDN'T GET
ALL OF IT, HAROLD.
THEY DIDN'T GIVE IT THE FULL
COVERAGE.
>> YEAH, WELL, IT WASN'T EXACTLY
THE KIND OF STORY THAT LENT
ITSELF TO PICTURES.
I MEAN, AN OLD MAN STANDING
THERE IN A SINGED NIGHTGOWN,
JUST STANDING THERE, SMOLDERING
AWAY GOING, "DOROTHY, WAS THAT
YOU?" NOT EVEN MOVING.
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
TV NEEDS ACTION, UNCLE RED.
LIKE THIS.
>> YOU'RE RUINING THE STORY,
HAROLD.
>> WE BOTH ARE.
>> [sniffs]
BOY, THE AIR SURE SMELLS GOOD
TODAY, HAP.
IS THAT THE NEW LID ON THE BAIT
BUCKET DOING THAT?
>> YEAH, I HAVEN'T SMELLED AIR
THIS FRESH SINCE I WORKED ON
THE RAILROAD.
>> YOU WORKED ON THE RAILROAD?
>> ALL THE LIVELONG DAY.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
>> YEAH, I GONE WEST, YOU KNOW,
JUST TO GET THE LAY OF THE LAND.
DID A LITTLE RAILROAD WORK.
WE WERE TRYING TO FIND A NEW
ROUTE THROUGH THE ROCKIES.
>> JEEZ, HAP, I ALWAYS HEARD
THAT WORKING ON THE RAILROAD
WAS PRETTY TOUGH STUFF.
>> OH, YEAH.
YEAH, IT WAS TOO HARD FOR MOST
OF THE MEN.
YOU DIDN'T BOTHER HAVING AN
EXPENSIVE BREAKFAST, OR YOU'D
THROW IT UP AND TRY TO GET
YOUR MONEY BACK.
I'LL TELL YOU THE WORST OF IT,
THOUGH.
>> THE LAY OF THE LAND,
I'LL BET.
>> THE LAY OF THE LAND.
SEE, THE MASSIVE POWER OF THE
ROCKIES WAS SO STRONG THAT IT
MAGNETIZES THE RAILS, MAKES THEM
ALL MOVE NORTH.
YOU KNOW?
WE WERE HALFWAY TO ALASKA
BEFORE WE NOTICED.
>> MAGNETIC RAILS, HAP?
MUST'VE BEEN HARD ON YOUR WATCH.
>> PULL THE LOOSE CHANGE
RIGHT OUT OF THE BOTTOMS OF
YOUR POCKETS.
ONE FELLA LOST ALL THE FILLINGS
OUT OF HIS TEETH.
>> WHAT WERE YOU THEN, HAP,
A GANDY DANCER?
>> A WHAT?
>> A GANDY DANCER, HAP.
MY COUSIN'S A GANDY DANCER
FOR C.P.
ARE YOU TELLING ME YOU WORKED
FOR THE RAILROAD, AND YOU DON'T
KNOW WHAT A GANDY DANCER IS?
>> SURE, I KNOW.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT
IT; THAT'S ALL.
CAN'T YOU TELL THAT?
DID YOU COME HERE TO FISH
OR TALK?
>> OH, SORRY, HAP.
JUST TRYING TO GET THE LAY OF
THE LAND.
[slow guitar and spoons music plays]
WHEN MY LIFE IS OVER
AND I'VE FIRED MY LAST ROUND
TAKE ALL MY LURES
AND PASS THEM AROUND
HAVE YOURSELF A COLD BEER
FOR THE GOOD TIMES WE HAD
THEN DROP ME INTO THE WATER
SUPPLY TANK
RIGHT NEXT TO DAD
>> OH, UNCLE RED, GREAT.
IT'S LETTER-READING TIME.
THIS IS FANTASTIC.
I'M ALL SET WHEN YOU ARE, C.B.
[chuckles]
ALL RIGHT, YOU GIVE ME A SIGNAL,
AND THEN I'LL KNOW
YOU'RE READY TOO, OKAY?
LIKE, WE COULD USE, LIKE,
A SECRET WORD OR PHRASE OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
THAT WOULD BE COOL, EH?
>> JUST READ THE LETTER, HAROLD.
>> OH, VERBAL CUE.
EXCELLENT CHOICE OF TECHNIQUE.
THAT'S FANTASTIC.
OKAY, LETTER NUMBER ONE GOES
AS FOLLOWS.
"DEAR RED, CAN YOU DO ANYTHING
ABOUT MY LAWN?"
>> WELL, IS THERE ANY MORE
INFORMATION THAN THAT, HAROLD?
>> OH, YEAH, OKAY.
ALL RIGHTY.
"CAN YOU DO ANYTHING
ABOUT MY LAWN?
NAME WITHHELD."
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S DIFFICULT TO
BE SPECIFIC IN THIS CASE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, GENERALLY, LAWN
PROBLEMS RANGE ANYTHING FROM
WEED SPRAY TO SHOOTING YOUR
NEIGHBOR'S DOG.
>> OH, YOU MEAN "SHOOING" THE
NEIGHBOR'S DOG, RIGHT?
>> WELL, YOU CAN GIVE THAT A TRY
FIRST, I GUESS.
FOR ME, PERSONALLY, NOW, I HAVE
AN ATTITUDE OF SURVIVAL OF
THE FITTEST.
IF THE WEEDS WIN, HEY,
THEY DESERVE IT.
>> OH, BUT NOBODY LIKES A LAWN
FULL OF DANDELIONS, UNCLE RED.
OR IS THAT JUST ME?
>> I HAVE NO PROBLEM WITH
DANDELIONS.
YOU CAN MAKE WINE FROM
DANDELIONS, HAROLD.
YOU CAN'T MAKE WINE FROM SOD.
MIND YOU, YOU CAN MAKE A SOD
FROM WINE.
LOOK AT OLD MAN SEDGEWICK.
>> [chuckles]
JEEZ, YOU NEVER THOUGHT LIKE
THAT BEFORE.
YOU ALWAYS HAD A NICE LAWN,
I THOUGHT.
>> YEAH, BUT THAT WAS BEFORE
SOMEBODY SEIZED UP MY LAWNMOWER
AND DIDN'T EVEN TELL ME.
>> OH, YEAH.
WELL, MAYBE, MAYBE, UNCLE RED,
LIKE, THE OIL FILLER CAP
IS IMPOSSIBLE TO FIND ON THAT
MODEL.
YOU EVER THINK OF THAT?
MAYBE THAT'S WHY, HUH?
>> WELL, HAROLD, THERE IS NO
OIL FILLER CAP.
YOU MIX THE OIL RIGHT IN WITH
THE GAS ON THAT ONE.
>> REALLY?
OH, WELL, WHOEVER DID IT,
I'M SURE I'M SORRY.
>> TODAY ON ADVENTURES WITH
BILL, BILL HAS A WHOLE TABLE
FULL OF KNIVES THERE.
HE'S GONNA DO SOMETHING REAL
SPECIAL TONIGHT.
HE'S--OH!
OH...
I GOT TO GET THOSE BRAKES
LOOKED AT ON THE VAN THERE.
I DON'T LIKE STOPPING ALL THAT
MUCH, ANYWAY.
I LIKE GOING.
I'M MORE OF A GOER THAN
A STOPPER.
ANYWAY, AS I SAY,
BILL HAD THE KNIVES.
AND WE GOT THE TABLE ALL SET UP.
AND WE GOT THE KNIVES KIND OF
JAMMED INTO HER THERE.
THAT'S THE WAY HE LIKES TO
KEEP THEM.
HE GOES THROUGH A LOT OF TABLES.
AND YOU DON'T WANT TO HAVE
DINNER ON THAT TABLE AFTERWARDS.
YOUR SOUP KEEPS GETTING LOST
DOWN TO YOUR LEGS, WHICH CAN
HAPPEN.
BUT HE'S GOT QUITE A COLLECTION
OF KNIVES.
AND WHAT--WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
OH, OKAY.
BOY, OH, BOY.
HE'S A DANGEROUS MAN, THAT BILL.
AND HE'S GOT THESE LEATHER
STROPS HERE.
HE'S SHARPENING--NOW--WHAT?
SOMETHING'S VERY, VERY BIZARRE
ABOUT THAT STROP.
ANYWAY, LIKE I SAY, BILL HAS
HIS OWN TECHNIQUES.
AND I DON'T QUESTION THEM,
'CAUSE ONCE I STARTED, I'D BE
THERE FOREVER.
NOW HE'S GONNA PUT
THE TARGET UP.
THIS WOULD BE A KNIFE HE SAW
ADVERTISED ON TV MAYBE.
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT HE'S GOT HER UP THERE.
AND HE BACKS OFF EXACTLY
EIGHT STEPS.
FIVE--OH.
WELL, I GUESS WE'LL MAKE IT
FIVE.
YEAH, FIVE.
FIVE STEPS.
AND HE'S ALL SET.
HE GETS HIS FIRST KNIFE.
AND WATCH THE WAY HE HANDLES
THIS.
THIS IS REALLY SOMETHING.
AND HE CALLS THAT A PERFECT HIT.
AND THAT WAS EITHER A HIGH-FIVE
OR HE'S DRYING HIS DEODORANT.
I'M NOT SURE.
AND THEY'RE BOTH ESSENTIAL.
AND HERE HE GOES.
LOOK AT--OH.
YEAH, THAT CLOSE.
YEAH, RIGHT, RIGHT.
BUT HE'S JUST FINDING THE RANGE.
HE'S ACTUALLY VERY, VERY GOOD
WITH KNIVES, AND...
OH...
[cow moos]
LOOK OUT. LOOK OUT.
OH, NICE CATCH.
BOY, OH, BOY, OH, BOY.
I THINK BILL WAS WITH THE CIRCUS
FOR QUITE A WHILE.
AND, YOU KNOW, HE SHOULD THINK
ABOUT GOING BACK.
NOW I THINK HE'S GONNA--OH, NO.
CLOSE.
NOPE, NOPE.
OH, OH, OH, OH.
I THOUGHT HE HAD THAT ONE.
SO HE WANTED ME TO GIVE IT
A TRY.
NOT BAD.
ANOTHER HIGH-FIVE THERE.
AND I SHOWED HIM HOW TO DO IT.
SO HE THOUGHT HE'D TRY AN
UNDERHAND.
BEAUTY.
BEAUTY, BEAUTY, BEAUTY.
SUPER SHOT.
THIS IS A STUNT, USING THE
MIRROR.
YOU LOOK AT THE--FIND THE TARGET
IN THE MIRROR AND THEN
THROW--BUT BILL GETS SOMETIMES
CONFUSED ON HIS MOTOR SKILLS.
AND--OH.
AND--UH-OH.
[shattering]
UH, WELL, I'D ALREADY SHAVED
THIS YEAR ANYWAY.
AND...
AND WHERE IS IT?
NOW, THIS WAS A REAL MYSTERY
FOR A WHILE.
JUST COULDN'T FIND THE KNIFE.
CHECKED THE WHOLE AREA.
CHECKED IN BEHIND THE SHED EVEN.
CHECKED EACH OTHER.
AND BILL--
DIDN'T THINK IT WAS IN MY BACK.
I MIGHT HAVE KNOWN.
[air hissing]
OH, WE HEARD THAT.
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
OH, THERE'S THE KNIFE.
YEAH, THAT CLOSE, BILL.
YEAH, RIGHT.
YEAH, HERE'S A HIGH-FIVE.
"IT IS WINTER.
ON A CHILLY, COLD NEW YEAR'S
DAY, AS I WALK THROUGH THE SNOW
OUT BEHIND THE HOUSE, I MAKE
A NEW YEAR'S RESOLUTION.
THIS YEAR, WE'RE GETTING
INDOOR PLUMBING."
>> YEAH?
>> ALL RIGHT, AT THIS POINT IN
THE SHOW, WE GIVE HAROLD
A CHANCE TO SAY A FEW WORDS.
REMEMBER, LIFE DOESN'T ALWAYS
MAKE SENSE.
GO AHEAD.
>> PUBLIC SPEAKING.
THE NUMBER ONE FEAR OF FEARS
IS SPEAKING IN PUBLIC.
YEAH.
WELL, NOT LIKE THE PUBLIC
SPEAKING TO YOU.
IT'S, LIKE, YOU KNOW, YOU
SPEAKING TO THE PUBLIC.
LIKE THAT.
THAT'S THE DIFFERENCE.
OKAY, FINE.
WELL, I GOT A LITTLE TRICK FOR
YOU THAT OFTENTIMES
PUBLIC-SPEAKING PEOPLE USE.
THEY PICTURE THEIR AUDIENCE
NAKED.
[chuckles]
BARE NAKED.
YOU KNOW, I DO THAT SOMETIMES
EVEN WHEN I'M NOT SPEAKING IN
PUBLIC.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT, IF YOU'RE
REALLY GOOD AT IT, YOU CAN
PICTURE YOURSELF NAKED TOO.
NEAT, HUH?
THAT HELPS YOU GET RID OF ALL
THE NERVOUSNESS.
AND THEN YOU JUST FORGET
EVERYTHING, INCLUDING WHAT
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SAY.
SO WHAT DO YOU DO?
THERE'S ANOTHER TRICK.
YOU WRITE DOWN ALL THE WORDS ON
LITTLE 3x5 CARDS.
THEN YOU WON'T FORGET.
AND THEY'RE RIGHT THERE.
BUT HERE'S A HINT.
DON'T WRITE DOWN EXACTLY WHAT
YOU WANT TO SAY, BECAUSE--OH.
OH.
OOPS.
I WASN'T GONNA TALK ABOUT
PUBLIC SPEAKING.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO TALK ABOUT
BUYING A CAR.
[chuckles]
>> WE DO AIM A LOT OF MATERIAL
ON THIS SHOW TOWARDS TODAY'S
TEENAGERS, BECAUSE OUR SPONSORS
REGARD THEM AS THE FUTURE OF
THE COUNTRY.
THAT'S PRETTY SCARY, ISN'T IT?
NOW I'M NOT A PREJUDICED PERSON.
SO I'D JUST LIKE TO TALK TO ANY
OF YOU TEENAGERS WHO ARE NOT,
YOU KNOW, TOO DRUGGED-UP OR
BOOZED-OUT OR IN A JUVENILE
DETENTION CENTER.
I BELIEVE IN LIVE AND LET LIVE.
BUT WHAT IS WITH THOSE HAIRCUTS?
SHAVED HALFWAY UP THE SIDE OR
MAYBE A LONG PIECE HANGING DOWN,
OR YOU GOT THE INITIALS CARVED
IN UP THERE, OR "THIS SIDE UP."
I MEAN, WHAT IS THAT?
I'M NOT SAYING WHAT'S RIGHT
AND WHAT'S WRONG.
BUT THAT LOOKS STUPID, OKAY?
AND IT LOOKS VIOLENT.
I SAW A KID THE OTHER DAY.
HE LOOKED SO VIOLENT, I WANTED
TO JUST SMACK HIM ONE.
AND I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YOU'RE MAKING A STATEMENT ABOUT
HOW YOU DON'T APPROVE OF ADULTS.
WELL, SO WHAT?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD LEARN TO BE
MORE TOLERANT.
AND SMARTEN UP.
OTHERWISE, YOU'RE JUST GONNA
END UP IN THE ARMY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH A LOT
MORE OF OUR SPECIAL GUESTS
AND MORE OF OUR REGULAR FEATURES
AND THE EXCITING CONCLUSION OF
THE OUTHOUSE STORY.
>> THAT MIGHT BE ONE ITEM
TOO MANY.
>> THAT WAS A REALLY GOOD LUNCH
YOU MADE, UNCLE RED.
>> OH, THANK YOU, HAROLD.
>> WELL, WHAT WAS THAT ORANGE
STUFF ON MY SANDWICH?
>> WELL, THAT'S CHEESE.
>> THAT'S NOT CHEESE.
>> THAT'S SOME KIND OF CHEESE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN CHEESE LIKE
THAT EITHER.
>> WHAT IS CHEESE?
>> WELL, NOW, THAT'S A GOOD
QUESTION.
IT'S FROM A COW, ISN'T IT?
>> IT IS.
I THINK MAYBE IT'S, LIKE, OLD--
OLD PATS OF BUTTER.
>> COULD BE.
>> PUT THEM ALL TOGETHER,
AND YOU LEAVE THEM ON A COUNTER
FOR A COUPLE OF WEEKS, AND IT
TURNS INTO CHEESE.
>> WELL, WHERE DOES THE BUTTER
COME FROM?
I THOUGHT MAYBE FROM MILK.
>> WELL, YOU HAVE TO LEAVE MILK
OUT FOR A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
>> SO CHEESE IS JUST--YOU'RE
SAYING--MILK WITH PATIENCE.
>> EXACTLY.
AND IF YOU LEAVE IT OUT, IT'LL
HAVE PENICILLIN,
AND PATIENTS NEED PENICILLIN.
>> PERFECT.
>> YEAH.
>> I ALWAYS THOUGHT CHEESE WAS
KIND OF A URINE PRODUCT.
BUT MAYBE THAT'S CHEEZ WHIZ.
JACK.
JACK, COME ON UP HERE.
I KNOW YOU'RE DOWN THERE, JACK.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> OH, NOTHING.
WE WERE JUST, YOU KNOW--THOUGHT
WE'D DROP IN AND SEE HOW IT'S
GOING; THAT'S ALL.
>> I'M FINE.
I'M DOING FINE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, I'M STRONG.
>> YEAH.
>> MY BODY'S STRONG.
MY SPIRITS ARE STRONG.
AND MY MIND IS STRONG, JACK.
>> NO, NO, YOU'RE JACK.
I'M RED.
>> OKAY.
SURE, FINE.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, I'M JUST--
>> WELL, WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> WELL, JACK, YOU KNOW, PEOPLE
ARE--THEY REALLY RESPECT WHAT
YOU'RE DOING HERE, LIVING IN
THE CAVE, YOU KNOW.
BUT WE'RE KIND OF WONDERING WHY
YOU'RE DOING THIS.
>> WELL, THE END OF WESTERN
CIVILIZATION IS UPON US.
I MEAN, LOOK AT ALL THE NUT BARS
RUNNING AROUND.
YOU KNOW, IT'S COMING.
AND I KNOW WHEN.
>> WELL, JACK, IF YOU KNOW WHEN,
WHY DID YOU COME UP HERE
SO EARLY?
>> WHAT?
HOW DO YOU MEAN?
IS THIS A TRICK?
DON'T MAKE ME USE THIS, RED.
>> NO, TAKE IT EASY, JACK.
I'M JUST SAYING THAT IF YOU KNEW
EXACTLY WHEN THE WORLD WAS GONNA
END, THEN WHY WOULD YOU COME UP
HERE A YEAR AND A HALF EARLY,
YOU KNOW, TO LIVE IN A DARK,
DINGY, WET CAVE?
YOU KNOW, IT JUST DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE TO ME.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
>> I KNOW--I KNOW ROUGHLY WHEN.
ROUGHLY.
AND I WANTED TO GET SETTLED IN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL BUY THAT.
I'LL BUY THAT.
SO WHAT EXACTLY IS YOUR PLAN,
JACK?
>> PLAN?
>> YEAH.
WELL, YOU MUST HAVE A PLAN.
I MEAN, A GUY DOESN'T LEAVE HIS
HOME AND HIS FAMILY AND WALK
AWAY FROM A GOOD-PAYING JOB IN
AN ADVERTISING AGENCY, YOU KNOW,
WALK AWAY FROM EVERYTHING HE
OWNS AND EVERYTHING HE KNOWS
TO COME AND LIVE IN A CAVE.
HE DOESN'T DO THAT UNLESS HE HAS
A REALLY GOOD PLAN, YOU KNOW.
>> HE DOESN'T?
>> DOES HE?
UH, NO.
>> NO.
>> NO, HE DOESN'T.
IT'S CRAZY TO DO THAT.
>> RIGHT.
SO WHAT'S YOUR PLAN?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW,
THIS AND THAT.
I'M PLAYING IT BY EAR.
>> OH.
>> A PLAN ISN'T GONNA BE MUCH
GOOD WHEN THE WORLD COMES TO
AND END, IF YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M SAYING, AND IT'S COMING.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, WITH THE COLD WAR,
THE BOMBS, THE POLLUTION,
THE TAXES.
>> WELL, ACTUALLY, JACK,
THE COLD WAR IS OVER.
AND THEY GOT RID OF A LOT OF
THE BOMBS.
A LOT OF THE COUNTRIES ARE
DISARMING NOW.
AND I THINK JUST ABOUT EVERYBODY
IS WORKING ON THE ENVIRONMENT,
GETTING RID OF ALL THAT
POLLUTION.
>> OH?
>> YEAH.
>> SO WESTERN CIVILIZATION
ISN'T COMING TO AN END?
>> I DON'T THINK SO, NO.
SORRY.
>> WELL, I GUESS THE WORLD
AS WE KNOW IT ISN'T THE WORLD
AS WE KNOW IT, JACK.
>> NO, NO.
YOU'RE JACK.
I'M RED.
>> I'M TALKING TO MYSELF.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, JACK?
MAYBE WHEN EVERYBODY HEARD YOU
WERE LIVING UP HERE IN THE CAVE,
IT BROUGHT THEM ALL
TO THEIR SENSES.
YOU KNOW, IT'S POSSIBLE.
IT MIGHT'VE HAPPENED.
>> YEAH?
>> YEAH, IT COULD'VE.
>> IT COULD?
>> YEAH.
>> IT COULD'VE?
>> WELL, THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
THAT WAS MY PLAN.
>> IT WAS?
>> DON'T YOU SEE--
WELL, HOW COULD YOU SEE?
DON'T FEEL BAD.
THE PLAN WAS SO CLEVER,
IT FOOLED THE GREATEST MINDS
OF OUR TIME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> SEE, I KNEW THAT IT WOULD
END THE COLD WAR.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW, I KNEW THEY'D
DISARM.
I KNEW THEY'D START TO CLEAN UP
THE ENVIRONMENT.
I KNEW THEY'D GET RID OF
THE TAXES.
>> OH, NO.
NO, JACK, THEY STILL HAVE TAXES.
>> WHAT?
>> YEAH.
>> DARN.
>> THE MAN'S A GENIUS.
ALL RIGHT, SO ANYWAYS, I WANTED
TO FINISH UP THE STORY ABOUT
THE OUTHOUSE BLOWING UP.
WELL, OLD MAN SEDGEWICK HAD BEEN
STUFFING HIMSELF ALL DAY WITH
PRUNES AND BEETS.
>> UNCLE RED, I MEAN, OKAY,
I KNOW IT'S YOUR SHOW AND
EVERYTHING.
BUT I THINK THE OUTHOUSE STORY
IS JUST A CHEAP LAUGH.
I MEAN, I'M THINKING ABOUT OUR
AUDIENCE, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, BEFORE THEY COMPLETELY
EVAPORATE, MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST
CONSIDER THEM FOR A MOMENT.
WHAT ABOUT THE MORE MODERN,
INTELLIGENT VIEWER?
THEY'RE MATURE.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE GETTING BACK
TO EARTH THESE DAYS.
WELL, HOW ABOUT YOURSELF?
WEREN'T YOU WORKING ON, LIKE,
A COMPOST HUMUS DISTRIBUTION
SYSTEM?
>> YEAH, WELL, THAT WAS THE
OUTHOUSE BLOWING UP STORY.
THANKS FOR RUINING IT.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, IF MY WIFE IS
WATCHING, I'M GONNA BE COMING
STRAIGHT HOME AFTER THE SHOW.
BUT WE'RE NOT GONNA BE ABLE TO
PUT THE WALLPAPER UP TONIGHT,
'CAUSE MOOSE THOMPSON ATE
THE PASTE.
ANYWAY, UNTIL NEXT TIME,
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
AND ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND,
UM...
>> OH...
>> AND MY NEPHEW AND ALL THE
REGULARS UP HERE AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.