DID YOU KNOW YOU CAN MOW YOUR
THERE. LEAVE THAT ON
THERE FOR THREE DAYS.
IT'LL STUNT THE GRASS
TO JUST THE RIGHT HEIGHT.
THEN YOU FLIP AROUND
TO THE NEXT PATCH.
CUT YOUR MOWING TIME IN HALF.
AND WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
WITH ALL THAT TIME YOU SAVED?
WELL, USUALLY, WHEN
YOU FLIP THE BOARD OVER,
SHE'S COVERED
WITH GRUBS AND WORMS.
PICK THEM OFF AND GO FISHING.
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW!
AND NOW HERE'S THE MAN
WHO KNOWS WHEN TO HOLD 'EM
AND WHEN TO FOLD 'EM, THAT'S
WHY HE'S IN CHARGE OF THE LODGE
CHAIR, YOUR HOST AND HERO,
MY UNCLE RED GREEN.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT. BOY, OH, BOY.
BIG, BIG ACCIDENT UP
AT THE BRIDGE
OVER MERCURY CREEK
THERE, HAROLD.
I HEARD ALL ABOUT IT --
A TRUCK DRIVER
LOST CONTROL, DUMPING
HIS ENTIRE LOAD...
YEAH, SO DID THE TRUCK.
ONE OF THOSE FREAK
ACCIDENTS, REALLY, YOU KNOW.
THIS TIME OF YEAR, THE
SALMON ARE TRYING TO JUMP
THE RAPIDS THERE, AND
HE JUST HAPPENED TO BE GOING BY
WITH HIS WINDOWS OPEN.
OH, BOY, I HOPE
THE DRIVER
WASN'T HURT.
OH, NO, HE'S GOING TO BE OK.
HE TOOK A 5-POUND COHO
AT THE ADAM'S APPLE THERE.
HE'S IN THE HOSPITAL.
HE'S GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT.
LIKE I SAID, BUT HE CAN'T TALK.
WHAT A MESS.
I MEAN, THERE WAS
APRICOTS EVERYWHERE.
APRICOTS, HUH?
400 CASES OF THEM.
YEAH, WE'RE AFRAID THEY'RE GOING
TO GO BAD, SO WE PUT THEM ALL
IN THE MOOSE THOMPSON'S
GARAGE FOR SAFEKEEPING.
AND I'LL TELL YOU, THEY'RE
PRETTY GOOD EATING.
YOU'RE EATING STOLEN GOODS.
YEAH.
WELL, HOW DOES
IT TASTE?
WELL, LIKE AN APRICOT.
BUT YOU GET USED TO IT.
IT'S TIME TO PLAY
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
AND TODAY'S GRAND PRIZE IS FOR
ANYONE WHO'S EVER DREAMED
OF TAKING ALL THE ROAD MAPS
AND THROWING THEM AWAY,
AND JUMPING INTO A BRAND-NEW
4X4 VEHICLE, DRIVING ACROSS
THIS BIG BEAUTIFUL COUNTRY
OF OURS, HA, HA, HA...
IT'S A GARBAGE BAG.
GO AHEAD, THROW ALL OF YOUR
ROAD MAPS RIGHT IN THERE.
IT'LL HOLD UP TO 100 ROAD MAPS.
[chuckling]
ALL RIGHTY, UNCLE RED,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS TO GET
MR. DALTON HUMPHREY TO
SAY THE FOLLOWING WORD:
VEGETABLE...VEGETABLE.
ALL RIGHT,
HAROLD.
GO!
ALL RIGHT, DALTON,
MEAT AND...
GRAVY!
NO, UH, MEAT AND GRAVY AND...
STEAK, BIG STEAK.
NO, UH, NO, OK.
WITH A STEAK YOU HAVE...
BACON?
OK, NOW, DALTON,
BACON IS MEAT, OK?
THIS ISN'T MEAT,
BUT SOMETHING YOU EAT.
HOT DOG.
NO, UM, ALL RIGHT, NO.
MEAT IS PROTEIN, RIGHT, BUT
CORN, CARROTS AND PEAS IS...
UNEATEN.
OK, ALL RIGHT.
YOU GOT A CAULIFLOWER,
ASPARAGUS, SPINACH: THAT'S...
PUNISHMENT.
ALMOST OUT OF
TIME, UNCLE RED.
OK, DALTON, DALTON.
YOU KNOW YOUR DAD,
HE NEVER ATE A SALAD;
HE NEVER ATE
ANY GREEN STUFF HIS WHOLE--
JUST MEAT, ALL RIGHT.
AND AFTER 70 YEARS
OF EATING MEAT, HE'S...
A COMPLETE VEGETABLE.
THAT WAS THE WORST CASE
OF GLUTTONY I'VE EVER SEEN
SINCE THE GIANT MEATBALL NIGHT.
EVEN THE SALAD WAS DISGUSTING,
WITH 200 MEN SLURPING
ON ORANGE GOO.
YOU GUYS GOT TO STOP
EATING THOSE APRICOTS.
WE CAN'T, WE JUST CAN'T, HAROLD.
WE DON'T LIKE THEM, BUT YOU
CAN'T BEAT THE PRICE.
YOU WANT TO TRY ONE OF THESE,
HAROLD? THEY'RE PRETTY GOOD.
NO, THAT'S
ILL-GOTTEN FRUIT.
I'LL HAVE NO PART
IN TRAFFICKING OF HOT FRUIT.
NO! NO!
JUST A LITTLE
BITE, HAROLD.
NO!
NO, NO, NO.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S GREAT
KNOWLEDGE IN THESE.
JUST A LITTLE BITE.
YOU'LL LEARN
SOMETHING,
SOMETHING.
WELL, MAYBE JUST
ONE LITTLE BITE.
BITE, CAN'T
HURT YOU, HUH?
AH, SOUR.
EH? EH?
YOU DIDN'T KNOW
THAT BEFORE, DID YOU?
OH, WE GOT A GUY NAMED
SHORTY O'TOOLE
STANDS ABOUT 4 FEET ZIP
WITH AN UGLY FACE
AND CRAZY HAIR
AND A PERSONALITY
THAT'S REALLY A PIP
BUT SHORTY MARRIED
A BEAUTIFUL GIRL
WHO WORKS WITH HIM
DAY AND NIGHT
SHE COULD HAVE HAD
ANY MAN IN TOWN
BUT APPARENTLY
SHE'S AFRAID OF HEIGHTS
YOU KNOW, ONE OF MY WIFE'S
FAVOURITE EXPRESSIONS IS:
"GET A GRIP."
AT LEAST AROUND ME.
BUT, YOU KNOW, WHEN
YOU THINK OF IT,
TREADWEAR AND TIRE GRIP AREN'T
JUST MY WIFE'S CONCERNS.
SO THIS WEEK,
ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW YOU
CAN TURN REGULAR ALL-SEASON
DEEP-TREAD TIRES
INTO SMOOTH RACING SLICKS
USING THIS FLAME-THROWER.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S JACK UP
THE CAR AND GET TO THOSE TIRES.
[grunting]
ALL RIGHT,
THIS JACK DOESN'T SEEM
TO BE WORKING ALL THAT WELL.
AND EVEN IF IT WAS, IT WOULD
ONLY RAISE THE CAR UP
A FEW INCHES, WHICH
IS NO GOOD TO US.
WE NEED SOMETHING
TO RAISE THIS UNIT UP
TO A MORE WORKABLE LEVEL.
YOU KNOW, LIKE ONE
OF THOSE HYDRAULIC JACKS
THAT THE MECHANICS
HAVE, YOU KNOW.
SO THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE GOING TO DO.
WE'RE GOING TO BUILD ONE
OF THOSE SUPER-DUPER,
HEAVY-DUTY HIGH-TILTING JACKS.
WE'LL MAKE THE RACING
SLICKS ANOTHER DAY.
[crashing]
AND AT THAT TIME, I'LL SHOW
YOU HOW TO FIX A BARBECUE.
NOW, ALL WE GOT TO DO
IS JUST RAISE THE ANGLE
ON THE CAR THERE, SO YOUR
WHEELS ARE RIGHT AT EYE LEVEL.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE
TO DO ANY BENDING.
[chuckling]
[grunting]
BOY, YOU KNOW, EVEN THESE SMALL
CARS ARE STILL FAIRLY HEAVY.
ALL RIGHT, THAT SHOULD DO IT.
I'M NOT HEAVY ENOUGH.
WAIT TILL I TELL BERNICE.
ALL RIGHT, WE TALKED THIS OVER.
HAROLD SAID THAT
IF I WANT TO LIFT THE CAR,
MY LEVER'S GOING
TO HAVE TO BE LONGER.
QUITE A BIT LONGER.
THAT'S WHERE THIS ROPE
COMES IN HANDY.
AND YOU JUST PULL DOWN ON THAT
AND THE CAR GOES UP.
THERE, NOW ALL I NEED IS...
SOMETHING TO PUT ON THE END
OF THE BOARD TO HOLD IT DOWN.
HERE, BOY, HERE, BOY,
COME ON, COME ON.
[grunting]
[car alarm sounding]
IT TOOK US A LITTLE
WHILE AND A WHOLE LOT OF EFFORT
TO GET ALL THESE CONCRETE
BLOCKS STACKED UP HERE,
BUT, YOU KNOW, HAROLD'S YOUNG.
HE'LL BE ABLE
TO STAND UP STRAIGHT
IN A FEW DAYS, I WOULD THINK.
[grunting]
THERE WE GO.
THAT SHOULD GET
HER UP HIGH ENOUGH,
TO BE ABLE TO GET RIGHT
AT THOSE TIRES.
[crashing]
UH...ALL RIGHT.
I JUST HAVE ONE WORD
FOR THIS: PERFECT.
NOW YOU WORK ON ALL FOUR
WHEELS AT ONCE.
ROTATE THE TIRES,
CHECK THE BRAKES, EH?
SERVICE THE MUFFLER,
PICK UP LOOSE CHANGE
THAT FELL OUT OF THE SEATS.
YUP, THIS IS A BRILLIANT
SYSTEM, EH?
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T MIND
A LITTLE WARPING
AND RIPPLING IN YOUR ROOF.
AND I'M SURE BUSTER WON'T.
AND REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
LET'S SEE THEM STEAL THIS ONE.
I'M TALKING TO OLDER
GUYS ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT'S IMPORTANT TO YOU, THAT
YOU SOMETIMES TAKE FOR GRANTED,
THAT YOU RELY ON, THAT CAN
SUSTAIN YOU IN YOUR OLD AGE:
YOUR TOOLS.
NOW, WE DON'T ALWAYS TAKE THE
BEST CARE OF OUR TOOLS, DO WE?
SOMETIMES WE USE
THE WRONG TOOL FOR THE JOB,
LIKE THAT GARDEN HOE
THAT I MELTED
WHEN I CLEANED OUT
THE TRANSFORMER.
SOMETIMES WE LEAVE OUR TOOLS
OUT IN THE BAD WEATHER,
LIKE THAT RUSTY DRILL PRESS
THAT'S HOLDING UP
MY FRONT PORCH.
BUT YOU KNOW, UH, A TOOL
CAN BE A FRIEND,
D FRIENDSHIP
IN FACT IS A TOOL.
IT'S LIKE A RECIPROCATING SAW,
'CAUSE IT CUTS BOTH WAYS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS,
BUT I LIKE THE SOUND OF IT.
BUT I'M TELLING YOU,
IF YOUR TOOL IS A FRIEND,
YOU'LL HAVE A HAPPY LIFE.
IF YOUR FRIEND IS A TOOL,
YOU GOT A PROBLEM.
SO, YEAH.
SO, WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS,
YOU WANT TO PICK YOUR FRIENDS
THE SAME WAY
YOU PICK YOUR TOOLS.
YOU WANT TO LOOK FOR QUALITY,
RELIABILITY AND STRENGTH.
'CAUSE IF YOU TREAT
YOUR TOOLS RIGHT,
THEY'LL BE A FRIEND FOR LIFE.
BUT EVEN BETTER, TREAT
YOUR FRIENDS RIGHT,
YOU CAN BORROW THEIR TOOLS.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL...
WE'VE PROVEN THERE'S
SUCH A THING
AS EATING TOO MANY APRICOTS.
AND WE'VE PROVEN THERE'S
SUCH A THING AS EATING
WAY, WAY, WAY, WAY,
WAY TOO MANY APRICOTS.
BUT EVERY HOUR A COUPLE MORE
APRICOTS GO BAD.
AND WE'RE BARELY HALFWAY
THROUGH THE 400 CASES.
UNCLE RED, I GOT AN IDEA!
I GOT A GREAT IDEA.
WOULD YOU LIKE AN APRICOT?
OH...
'CAUSE I GOT THIS GREAT IDEA HOW
WE CAN USE THEM UP --
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE CAN HAVE AN APRICOT
FESTIVAL, HA, HA.
THAT'D BE GREAT, YEAH, YEAH.
WE COULD HAVE, LIKE, BAKED
GOODS WITH APRICOTS.
WE COULD HAVE GAMES
WITH APRICOTS.
KIDS COULD HAVE GAMES, TOO.
THEY COULD PLAY, PIN
THE TAIL ON THE APRICOT, HUH?
AND APRICOT BATTING CAGES
AND APRICOT MILKSHAKES --
KIDS LOVE APRICOT MILKSHAKES.
AND WE COULD HAVE LIKE CROWNING
OF THE KING AND QUEEN
OF THE APRICOT FESTIVAL.
[laughing]
YEAH, THE PRIZE WOULD GO
TO A COUPLE WHOSE PERSONALITY
AND APPEARANCE MOST RESEMBLES
THAT OF AN APRICOT.
WOULDN'T THAT BE FUN?
THAT'D BE FUN, HUH?
FOR THE MEN, WE GET
APRICOT WRESTLING.
THEY'LL WRESTLE
WITH ALL THE APRICOTS.
THAT'D BE
FUN, RIGHT?
HAROLD...
YES?
DON'T SAY THE
WORD APRICOT.
AM I PRONOUNCING IT WRONG?
APRICOT, APRICOT, APRICOT...
ALL RIGHT, MEN, AS YOU KNOW,
THIS IS A NEW MEMBER NIGHT.
MIKE HAMMER'S HERE,
AND MIKE, OF COURSE,
IS AN EX-CON WHO'S DONE SOME
HARD TIME AND REALLY DOESN'T
APPRECIATE YOU BRINGING IT UP
ALL THE TIME, SO BACK OFF.
ANYWAY, MIKE
HAS A GUY
THAT HE'D
LIKE TO PRESENT
AS A NEW MEMBER.
I THINK WE
CAN ALL GUESS
WHERE HE
MET HIM.
THANK YOU, MR. GREEN.
GENTLEMEN OF POSSUM LODGE.
I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET
AN ASSOCIATE OF MINE,
BUGSY HAMMERHAND.
NOW, BUGSY'S COMING OFF
A STRING BAD LUCK.
NOT ONLY WAS HE WRONGFULLY
CONVICTED OF THEFT,
BUT HE WAS ALSO UNABLE
TO SELL ANY OF THE STUFF.
OH, AND HE CAN GET US STUFF THAT
WE NEED FROM TIME TO TIME, TOO.
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T
MIND, YOU KNOW,
GETTING USED STUFF THAT HAS
THE SERIAL NUMBER FILED OFF,
OR IN THE CASE OF CARS, SOME
DAMAGE TO THE STEERING COLUMN.
NOW, ANOTHER PERK
IF BUGSY JOINS
IS THAT IF ANYTHING GOES
MISSING AROUND HERE,
WE'LL PRETTY MUCH
KNOW WHO HAS IT, RIGHT?
SO I URGE YOU TO GO AGAINST
YOUR INSTINCTS AND THE ADVICE
OF THAT PAROLE BOARD AND LET
BUGSY JOIN POSSUM LODGE.
THANK YOU.
YEAH.
GUYS, ALL
THOSE IN FAVOUR?
UH, ANOTHER THING IS,
ONCE BUGSY IS A MEMBER,
WITH HIS RECORD, IF ANYTHING BAD
EVER HAPPENS AROUND HERE,
THE COPS ARE GOING
TO THINK IT WAS HIM
AND ARREST HIM INSTEAD OF YOU.
AYE!
ALL RIGHT.
CONGRATULATIONS, PARTNER.
YEAH, HI, BILL. SEE THE SIGN?
OH, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, RED.
I GOT
AN IDEA. OW!
[moaning]
IT'S SAD. YOU GOT
ANY OTHER IDEAS?
THAT ONE, I THINK,
WAS NOT YOUR--
YOU'RE IN A FALLING ROCKS ZONE.
GOT AN IDEA.
NO, NO.
THAT WAS A BETTER IDEA.
WHAT'S THAT? I HOPE THAT'S ROPE.
OW, OW.
OH, OH, OH, MY GOSH, OH.
OH!
IT'S A FALLING ROCKS ZONE...
NO, I'M FINE.
DON'T THROW--
YOU MIGHT HAVE THROWN IT
A LITTLE HARD.
GRAB THE END OF THE...
JUST WATCH IT.
GRAB THE END OF THE...THE...
THERE IT GOES.
SHE'S HOOKED ONTO
A LITTLE BRANCH UP THERE.
OH, OH,
I GOT AN IDEA.
I CLIMB UP AND
GRAB THE ROPE
AND PULL MYSELF
RIGHT TO THE TOP.
IT'LL BE GREAT,
YOU SEE?
FUNNY, THEY JUST KEEP
COMING, DON'T THEY?
ALL RIGHT, AWAY YOU GO.
I'M GLAD I DON'T GET ANY IDEAS.
I'M JUST GOING
TO WAIT HERE AND...
THAT'S A GOOD SIGN.
I LIKE THAT SIGN.
THERE YOU GO, UP HE GOES.
SEE THE ROPE? THERE'S THE ROPE.
GRAB IT, JUST GRAB IT,
GRAB IT, GRAB IT.
AHA!
IT'S KIND OF THIN. CAREFUL.
OH.
THERE'S THE ROPE,
WHERE'S THE-- WHERE'S THE--
WHAT ABOUT THE BRANCH?
DID THE BRANCH STAY UP THERE?
THERE IT IS NOW.
ALL RIGHT. NO? NO GOOD?
GOT AN IDEA.
YEAH, WE'RE FINE,
WE'RE FINE, GOOD.
OK, A NOOSE.
WHOA.
WOW!
OH, MY GOSH.
THAT'S ONE OF THE BEST REVERSE
SHOTS I'VE EVER SEEN.
LET ME CHECK.
UGH, UGH, UGH.
WASN'T THAT-- SHE'S
NOT TOO SOLID, BILL.
SHE'S NOT TOO, UH, NOT
TOO, NOT TOO...OH, BOY.
WHAT'S ON THE OTHER SIDE...
IT'S GOING TO PULL
THAT ROPE UP.
IT'S GOING TO PULL THE ROPE UP.
LOOK OUT. THE ROPE'S
GOING TO GO UP.
THE HOOK, THE HOOK, THE HOOK.
OH, BABY.
OH, NO.
OH, OH, OH.
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
UH-OH.
[thud]
HERE'S
MY PANTS.
YEAH.
CHANGE THIS TO...
YEAH, I THINK IT'S CLINTON.
OH, I GOT TO HAND IT TO HAROLD.
THAT APRICOT FESTIVAL
WAS A HUGE SUCCESS THERE.
WE RAISED A WHACK OF DOUGH,
DIDN'T WE, HAROLD?
[moaning]
HAROLD.
OH, I DON'T
FEEL GOOD.
MAYBE SOMETHING YOU ATE.
MRS. THOMSON'S APRICOT PIE
SURE HAD A FUNNY
TASTE TO IT -- WHAT WAS THAT?
I THINK SHE USED
THE WRONG KIND OF ONIONS.
BUT ANYWAY, WE RAISED
OVER $200 ON THE DAY.
[knocking]
SEE WHO THAT IS, WILL YOU?
YEAH.
IT'S NOT VERY OFTEN
AT THE LODGE HERE...
WE ATE AS MANY APRICOTS AS YOU'D
EVER WANT AND THEN SOME,
AND WE STILL RAISED
A WHACK OF DOUGH.
IT WAS A WIN-WIN ALL THE WAY,
WHERE RARELY AT THE LODGE WE GET
SOMETHING THAT JUST WORKS OUT...
WE SINNED, WE SINNED, WE SINNED.
I SAID WE SINNED, AND YOU
WOULDN'T LISTEN. WE SINNED...
WHAT?
WAS THERE SOMEBODY LOOKING
FOR APRICOTS THERE, HAROLD?
YEAH, OH, YEAH.
IT'S THE TRUCK DRIVER.
HE WANTS TO TALK TO YOU.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
HE'S GOT A CLENCHED FIST.
AND HE'S NOT JUST
A TRUCK DRIVER, EITHER.
HE'S ALSO THE LOCAL
PRODUCE INSPECTOR.
YEAH, HE SAID THOSE APRICOTS
WERE UNFIT
FOR HUMAN CONSUMPTION.
HE WAS ON HIS WAY TO THE
HAZARDOUS WASTE DUMPSITE,
WHEN HE GOT IN THE ACCIDENT.
ALL RIGHT, WELL...
I'LL TALK TO HIM IN A MINUTE.
WHERE ARE
YOU GOING?
HOSPITAL.
I'M GOING TO HAVE
MY APRICOTS REMOVED.
WELCOME TO THE
EXPERT PORTION OF THE SHOW.
IT'S THE PART OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE EXAMINE
THOSE THREE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY.
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S A TRUISM,
ISN'T IT? ALL RIGHTY.
JOINING ME AND UNCLE RED IN
THE EXPERT PORTION OF THE SHOW
TODAY IS MOTHER NATURE'S
BOYFRIEND HIMSELF, RANGER GORD.
HELLO, EVERYONE.
IT'S GREAT TO BE BACK IN THE
REAL WORLD...OR EVEN HERE.
OK, OUR LETTER GOES LIKE THIS.
IT'S ADDRESSED TO OUR EXPERTS.
IT SAYS: "DEAR EXPERTS,
HOW ARE YOU?"
I'M A LITTLE UPSET
TODAY, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
BECAUSE I LOST MY FAVOURITE PAIR
OF SUNGLASSES, BUT YOU KNOW,
IT'S NOT THE END
OF THE WORLD, NO WAY.
THAT DOESN'T HAPPEN
UNTIL THE YEAR 2015.
IT'S IN NOVEMBER, ON A THURSDAY,
AND IT'S AFTER LUNCH, OK?
DON'T GET TOO UPSET
WHEN YOU LOSE SOMETHING.
YOU MUST REMEMBER TO REPLACE
THE THING THAT YOU LOST,
WITH SOMETHING NEW.
AND THE REAL TRICKY PART IS
YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER
TO REPLACE THE SAME THING
WITH THE SAME THING.
IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU CAN'T REPLACE
AN OLD PAIR OF SUNGLASSES
BY BUYING A NEW WAFFLE IRON, OK?
EXCUSE ME, I THINK A FUSE BLEW.
OH, NO, IT'S OK.
SOMEONE'S GOT IT.
OUR LETTER CONTINUES:
"I WAS HOPING YOU COULD
ANALYSE A DREAM FOR ME."
"I HAVE THIS RECURRING DREAM
THAT I'M RANGER GORD."
REALLY?
THAT IS VERY WEIRD,
BECAUSE SOMETIMES
I HAVE THAT EXACT SAME DREAM.
YOU, YOU, YOU DREAM
YOU'RE RANGER GORD?
YEAH, SOMETIMES.
ARE YOU SURE IT'S A DREAM,
RANGER GORD, BECAUSE YOU HAVE
TO REALIZE THAT...
YOU'RE RANGER GORD.
WELL, I MEAN I THINK
IT'S A DREAM.
IT STARTS OFF WITH THESE TWO
REALLY FOXY-LOOKING WOMEN.
SSS, OOOH, BABY.
THEY'RE LOOKING AT ME, SMILING,
AND THEY START WALKING
RIGHT TOWARDS ME.
OH, THIS IS DEFINITELY A DREAM.
I'VE HAD THAT DREAM.
I KNOW THAT DREAM.
I'M HAVING THAT DREAM RIGHT NOW.
REALLY?
YES, IT'S A GOOD DREAM.
OHHH...
[chuckling]
THEY PUT ON SNOWMOBILE SUITS
AND DO THE MACARENA
FOR 4 1/2 HOURS.
OOOH, BABY.
[chuckling]
IT'S A LITTLE
DIFFERENT THAN MINE.
WELL, AT LEAST HE'S NOT
HAVING NIGHTMARES.
OH, NO, WITH RANGER GORD,
THE SCARY PART DOESN'T START
TILL HE WAKES UP.
THIS GOVERNMENT HAS TO STOP
CUTTING FUNDING TO HOSPITALS.
300 HUNDRED GUYS AND
ONLY ONE STOMACH PUMP.
LOT OF THE GUYS
DIDN'T EVEN WAIT
WAIT FOR
THE PUMP.
MOOSE THOMPSON WAS IN THERE
FOR OVER AN HOUR.
YEAH, THEY SHOULD HAVE SWITCHED
TO THE FIRE HOSE
FOR HIM, I THINK.
BUT, YOU KNOW, HEY,
THERE'S GOOD NEWS HERE.
AND THERE WAS NO LONG-TERM
ILL-EFFECTS ON ANYBODY.
EVEN THE TRUCK DRIVER
IS OFF THE HOOK,
BECAUSE WE PROCESSED
ALL THE BAD APRICOTS
WITH OUR OWN DIGESTIVE SYSTEMS.
YEAH, WE STILL
HAVE THE PROFITS
FROM THE
FESTIVAL.
YEAH, THAT'LL HELP PAY
THE FINES.
FINES,
WHAT FINES?
WELL, THERE WAS
THEFT AND LITTERING,
AND SOMEBODY PARKED
MY VAN IN THE AMBULANCE SPOT.
[squealing]
MEETING TIME.
UM, YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN.
TAKE IT EASY,
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
AH, GIVE
ME A PUSH.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING.
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I LEARNED A VERY
VALUABLE LESSON THIS WEEK.
FRUIT KILLS.
FOR THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE, KEEP YOUR
STICK ON THE ICE.
HEY, TAKE YOUR SEATS.
ABOUT TO START THE MEETING.