IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW!"
AND NOW HERE'S A MAN WHO
DOESN'T JUST FLIRT
WITH DISASTER,
HE BUYS
HER A DRINK.
YOUR HOST,
YOUR HERO,
MY UNCLE,
RED GR-E-E-E-N!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIT OF DISAPPOINTMENT
UP AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK.
WE HAD OUR ANNUAL MAN
OF THE YEAR AWARD,
WHICH I KIND OF HAD
MY EYE ON THERE.
BUT FLINTY McCLINTOCK WON IT,
AND I COME IN SECOND.
WHAT DID YOU WIN
THE AWARD FOR?
MOST FERMENTED BEVERAGES
CONSUMED AT AN
INDOOR EVENT?
NO, HAROLD, THIS IS AN AWARD FOR
SPENDING A LOT OF TIME UP HERE.
I'M REALLY SURPRISED
THAT FLINTY BEAT YOU.
I MEAN, YOU SPEND A LOT
OF TIME HERE AT THE LODGE
DOING...
YOU KNOW, BEING HERE.
YEAH, WELL, FLINTY WAS
HERE 364 DAYS LAST YEAR.
WOW, THAT'S EVERY DAY BUT
CHRISTMAS I GUESS?
NO, WELL, HE WAS
HERE ON CHRISTMAS,
BUT HIS BRANDY
STUFFING EXPLODED,
AND HE SPENT 24 HOURS
IN THE TOP OF A TREE,
AND THE JUDGES WOULDN'T
LET HIM COUNT IT.
YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY, I'M KIND
OF GLAD FLINTY WON, YOU KNOW.
MAYBE IT WILL MAKE UP FOR
THE FACT THAT HIS WIFE
LEFT HIM TODAY.
WHAT?
YEAH.
HE DOESN'T
EVEN KNOW YET.
I GUESS HE DOESN'T
SPEND MUCH TIME AT HOME.
WELL, THAT'S NOT
VERY SUPPORTIVE.
THE GUY WINS MAN OF THE YEAR;
SHE'S NOT EVEN THERE TO
CONGRATULATE HIM?
COME ON, WHAT
DO YOU EXPECT?
HE IGNORED HER
FOR OVER A YEAR.
THERE'S A LESSON TO BE
LEARNED IN THERE, UNCLE RED.
FLINTY WAS FIRST
TO LOSE HIS WIFE,
BUT MAYBE YOU'LL
COME IN SECOND.
DON'T BE CRAZY, HAROLD.
MAYBE I'LL JUST
GO GIVE BERNICE
A PHONE CALL, EH?
HAROLD?
928 --
YEAH, OKAY, OKAY.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
KIND OF A WING-DING OF
AN EPISODE THIS TIME AROUND.
A LOT OF ENGINEERING
INVOLVED IN THIS SHOW,
I MEAN, WE'VE GOT THE OTHER
STUFF TOO, WHICH IS PRETTY
MUCH FILLER I GUESS YOU KNOW,
BUT THERE'S A LOT OF
REALLY GOOD ENGINEERING
PHYSICAL STUFF.
SO STAY TUNED AND LEARN.
AH, THE MINISTRY OF NATURAL
RESOURCES HAS ANNOUNCED
THAT ANYONE CATCHING FISH
AND THEN RELEASING THEM BACK
INTO THE WATERS OF POSSUM LAKE
WILL BE CHARGED WITH
CRUELTY TO ANIMALS.
GOOD TO KNOW.
HAROLD,
DID AUNT BERNICE SAY
ANYTHING TO YOU ABOUT
GOING ANYWHERE?
SHE'S NOT AT HOME.
I WAS JUST WONDERING.
NO, NOT TO ME,
YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, WHY WOULD SHE
SAY ANYTHING TO ME?
WEREN'T YOU HOME LAST NIGHT?
YEAH, I WAS HOME, HAROLD.
DID YOU HAVE DINNER
AT HOME LAST NIGHT?
OF COURSE
I DID, HAROLD.
WAS AUNT BERNICE
THERE THEN?
YEAH, YEAH, SHE WAS HOME.
SHE MADE ME TURN THE T.V. OFF.
WELL, DID SHE SAY
ANYTHING AT THAT TIME?
YEAH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT? SHE WAS
TALKING ABOUT BOSNIA.
NO, NO, THAT WAS THE
LADY ON THE RADIO.
I'M NOT SURE.
YOU DON'T EVEN
KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON
AROUND YOU, DO YOU?
WHAT WAS HER DAY LIKE?
WHAT WAS SHE WEARING?
AUNT BERNICE IS SUPPOSED
TO BE THE WOMAN YOU LOVE,
AND YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED AT THE DINNER
TABLE LAST NIGHT.
WELL, THANK YOU, GERALDO.
WELL, AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I DO KNOW WHAT WENT ON, OKAY?
WE HAD STUFFED PORK CHOPS;
WE HAD BAKED POTATOES, LOADED;
WE HAD CANDIED CARROTS,
AND WE HAD APPLE PIE
FOR DESSERT.
UNCLE RED, I'M TALKING ABOUT
WHAT YOU REMEMBER IN YOUR
HEART AND YOUR MIND,
NOT JUST IN
YOUR STOMACH.
WE ALL KNOW THAT
HAS TOTAL RECALL.
WE LOVE THE WORDS THAT
WEDDINGS BRING
LOVE AND HONOUR AND
A BEAUTIFUL RING
BRIDES AND GROOMS,
MAIDS AND MEN
MOM AND DAD
BARBIE AND KEN
BUT ONE THING'S TRUE
BOTH NEAR AND FAR
TWO WORDS THAT
SHOULD NEVER JOIN
ARE CASH AND BAR
IT'S TIME TO PLAY THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME,
AND THIS WEEK, WE'RE PLAYING
FOR FANTASTIC PRIZES.
Mr. DOUGIE FRANKLIN HAS
AN OPPORTUNITY TO WIN
A FIVE-PIECE BEDROOM SET WHICH
INCLUDES A BEDROLL, A BEDPAN
AND THREE MAGAZINES.
OKAY. UNCLE RED --
UNCLE RED HAS 30 SECONDS TO
GET  Mr. DOUGIE FRANKLIN
TO SAY THIS WORD --
COVER YOUR EARS --
MANNERS.
YEAH,
YEAH.
30 SECONDS, AND GO.
ALL RIGHT, DOUGIE,
WOMEN LIKE A
MAN WHO HAS...
A QUIET
EXHAUST SYSTEM.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
WHEN A MAN IS POLITE AROUND
WOMEN, THAT'S A SIGN  OF...
DESPERATION.
OKAY, OKAY, DOUGIE, YOU HAVE A
PERSON WHO BELCHES AND PICKS
THEIR TEETH AT THE TABLE...
MOM!
LET ME FINISH HERE.
SORRY.
WHEN SOMEONE BELCHES AT THE
TABLE, THAT'S A SIGN  OF BAD ...
BURRITOS.
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT
OF TIME, UNCLE RED.
ALL RIGHT DOUGIE, WHEN YOU BELCH
AT THE TABLE, YOUR MOM SAYS
MIND YOUR...
SPRAY.
OH, DISGUSTING.
WELL, ONLY IF YOU
HIT SOMEBODY.
COME ON,
I GOT MANNERS.
(FRANTIC BELL RINGING)
YOU KNOW, THIS CURRENT
RECYCLING CRAZE
HAS MADE ME FEEL A BIT GUILTY
ABOUT ALL THOSE YEARS I
NEVER RECYCLED ANYTHING
EXCEPT BEER AND
MY OWN COOKING.
SO THIS WEEK ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M TAKING ON A MAJOR
RECYCLING PROJECT.
NOW, I KNOW YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO SEPARATE OUT YOUR POP
CANS AND YOUR NEWSPAPERS
AND PLASTICS,
BUT THAT'S PRETTY WHOOSY,
SMALL POTATOES IF YOU ASK ME.
I WANNA DO SOMETHING THAT'S
A LITTLE MORE IMPRESSIVE,
I WANNA DO
SOMETHING BIG.
I'M THINKIN'...
HOW ABOUT A CITY BUS?
HOW ABOUT THAT?
HOW MANY POP CANS IS
THIS ONE WORTH?
I GOT THIS UNIT FOR 50 BUCKS.
50 BUCKS.
OH, YEAH, A LOT OF PARTS ARE
MISSING, AND IT DOESN'T
RUN TOO GOOD,
BUT 50 BUCKS?
BOY, OUR SOCIETY'S VALUES
ARE ALL SCREWED UP.
NOW, YOU COULD MAKE
ANYTHING OUT OF THIS.
YOU COULD MAKE A --
WELL, YOU'RE REALLY ONLY
LIMITED BY YOUR OWN IMAGINATION.
TELL YOU WHAT
I'M GONNA DO,
I'M GONNA TURN THIS THING
INTO A CIGARETTE CAR.
YOU KNOW HOW THEY'VE
GOT THE CIGARETTE BOATS
WHERE THE DRIVER SITS
WAY AT THE VERY BACK
THEN THE HOOD GOES WAY
OUT IN FRONT OF HIM?
I'M GONNA MAKE THE VERSION
OF THAT FOR THE ROAD!
YEAH, I'VE ALREADY GOT
THE BACKSEAT TO DRIVE FROM,
AND I'VE GOT THE BIG, LONG HOOD,
EXCEPT RIGHT NOW IT'S A ROOF.
ALL RIGHT. I HAD TO SWITCH TO
THE SAWS, AWHILE THERE,
'CAUSE I CUT THROUGH THE TORCH,
BUT I GOT HER ALL SET.
SHE'S PRETTY MUCH DONE NOW.
JUST GOT TO CUT DOWN ABOVE
THE WINDOWS AND DROP THAT
WHOLE ROOF DOWN,
AND THAT'S GOING
TO BE MY HOOD,
THEN I'M DONE.
THAT'S IT.
WELL, NO, I'VE GOT TO HOOK UP
THE STEERING AT THE BACK
AND THEN THE BRAKE AND THE GAS
AND THE CLUTCH, STANDARD,
THEN THE TRANSMISSION
AND THEN THE TURN SIGNALS,
GET HER SAFETIED,
THAT'S A WRAP.
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT,
THE WORLD'S FIRST CIGARETTE CAR.
IS SHE A BEAUTY OR WHAT?
NOT MUCH ON SEATING,
BUT YOU CAN'T BEAT
HER FOR LEG ROOM.
KINDA LOOKS LIKE A
BATMOBILE OR SOMETHING.
I COULD BE A SUPERHERO.
(IMITATING 'BATMAN' THEME SONG)
BUS BOY!
WELL, LET'S TAKE HER FOR A SPIN
BEFORE THEY TIGHTEN UP THE
TRANSPORTATION LAWS.
THIS ISN'T A STREETCAR
NAMED DESIRE,
IT'S A BUS CALLED HORSE.
I WANNA TALK TO YOU OLDER GUYS
OUT THERE FOR A SEC.
SOONER OR LATER YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO REPLACE THAT LAWN MOWER,
AND EVEN THAT ELECTRIC DRILL
THAT YOU BOUGHT WHEN YOU STARTED
DOING YOUR OWN DENTAL WORK.
AND, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE AT
THE AGE WHERE
THESE ARE PROBABLY THE LAST ONES
OF THOSE YOU'RE GONNA BUY FOR
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
THINK ABOUT HOW LONG
YOU'VE HAD THAT DRILL,
AND HOW MANY YEARS THAT
MOWER RAN FOR YOU, EH?
SO WHAT YOU'RE BUYING
NOW ARE NOT POWER TOOLS,
THEY'RE FUTURE HEIRLOOMS.
SO IF YOU WANT TO BE REMEMBERED
AS A GREAT GUY, GET THE BEST.
DON'T JUST GET
AN ELECTRIC DRILL.
TREAT YOURSELF TO A VARIABLE
SPEED CORDLESS WITH THE
EXTRA BATTERY.
AND DON'T JUST GET A LAWN MOWER.
GET A LAWN TRACTOR WITH
THE PADDED SEAT AND THE
DRINK HOLDER.
MAYBE EVEN EMBOSS YOUR
NAME ACROSS THE FRONT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE PRICE.
IT'S NOT YOUR MONEY,
IT'S THEIR INHERITANCE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU
ONE THING ABOUT MEN...
ONCE YOU GET OUR ATTENTION,
THERE'S NO STOPPING US.
YOU SAY THAT LIKE
IT'S A GOOD THING.
OH, IT IS, HAROLD.
I MEAN, EVER SINCE FLINTY'S
WIFE MADE A RUN FOR IT,
A BUNCH OF US LODGE MEMBERS
GOT TALKING AND -- MAYBE --
HEY, MAYBE WE'RE TAKING
OUR WIVES FOR GRANTED.
AND WE DECIDED TO HAVE
A SPECIAL LODGE WEEKEND,
HAVE ALL THE WIVES COME UP AND
JUST DO WHATEVER THEY WANT.
WHAT THEY WILL
WANT TO DO IS LEAVE.
I DON'T
THINK SO, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
I THINK THEY'RE GOING
TO WANT TO GO FISHING.
WHY? THEY NEVER DID BEFORE.
YOU WANNA
KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE WE NEVER LET THEM
DECIDE WHAT KIND OF FISH
TO FISH FOR, SEE?
THAT'S ALL
CHANGED NOW.
WE'RE SENSITIVE NOW.
WE'RE NEW MEN.
WELL, THEN, YOU'RE
GONNA NEED NEW FISH
BECAUSE THERE'S NONE
IN POSSUM LAKE.
SEE, IT'S NOT
ABOUT FISHING.
NO?
JUST SITTING IN THE BOAT TALKING
ABOUT WHATEVER THEY WANT
TO TALK ABOUT...
CARS, T.V. SHOWS, FAMILY.
I HOPE IT'S NOT
ABOUT FAMILY.
DON'T WORRY, I THINK THEY'LL
JUST WANT TO TALK ABOUT LEAVING.
NO, HAROLD.
NO, NO.
WE'RE TURNING ALL OUR CABINS
INTO HONEYMOON SUITES, HAROLD.
IT'LL BE FANTAS --
LOOK AT THIS,
I'VE GOT CHRISTMAS LIGHTS,
ALL RED BULBS.
AND I'M PUTTING THESE
CURTAINS OVER THE WINDOWS.
THEY'RE ROMANTIC AND
CHEAPER THAN GLASS.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST TAKE AUNT
BERNICE TO A NICE HOTEL?
OH, HAROLD, HOTELS DON'T
HAVE WHAT POSSUM LODGE HAS.
I KNOW. IF THEY DID,
THEY'D BE CONDEMNED.
ALL RIGHT. THIS HERE IS KIND
OF THE ANTIQUE ROADKILL
SHOW KIND OF DEAL,
WHERE LODGE MEMBERS BRING
IN SOMETHING OF VALUE,
AND WE GOT DALTON HUMPHREY,
WHO'S  KINDA AN EXPERT ON
CURIOS, COLLECTIBLES AND CRAP,
TELL THEM WHAT IT'S WORTH.
TAKE IT AWAY, DALTON.
THANK YOU, RED.
AND WITH ME TODAY HERE IS
BUSH PILOT, BUZZ SHERWOOD.
H-E-E-E-Y! HOW'S
IT GOING, HUMPSTER?
HOW'S IT HANGING?
A LITTLE LOOSER NOW, THANK YOU.
DID YOU BRING US
ANYTHING TODAY, BUZZ?
OH, YEAH.
IT'S LIKE ONE OF THOSE
WIND SPINNY THINGS.
YOU KNOW, YOU GET THEM ON THE
ROOF OF THE BARN, RIGHT?
A WEATHER VANE!
OKAY, OKAY.
WELL, WELL.
WHERE DID YOU GET THIS?
I FOUND IT...
STUCK TO THE PONTOONS
ON MY PLANE.
DO YOU KNOW WHO MADE THIS?
YEAH, I THINK IT'
A GUY NAMED SWEN.
SVEN?
NO, NOT SVEN... SWEN.
S-W-E-N,
SWEN.
NO, YOU SEE, BUZZ,
THESE ARE DIRECTIONS,
LIKE "N" FOR NORTH,
EAST, SOUTH, WEST,
LIKE THE COMPASS IN YOUR PLANE,
YOU KNOW, IF YOUR
PLANE HAD ONE.
OH, OKAY SURE.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
IT'S WORTH, MAN?
IT'S LIKE A BUNDLE?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NOT MUCH, NO, NO.
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW, IT'S DAMAGED.
SO, YOU KNOW, I WOULD
JUST GIVE IT TO ME,
THEN I WON'T BE INCLINED TO
WANT TO TELL ANYONE ABOUT
YOUR LITTLE INCIDENT,
LIKE THE AIRPLANE POLICE.
OH, SURE, MAN.
THAT'S COOL.
HEY, DO YOU WANT
TO BUY SOME LAUNDRY?
NO, NOT REALLY,
NOT UNLESS IT'S MY SIZE.
WELL, IT PROBABLY IS BECAUSE
IT WAS YOUR CLOTHESLINE.
HEIGH-HO, WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE EXPLORE THOSE THREE
LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
Audience:  I DON'T KNOW.
OKAY, JOINING ME AND UNCLE RED
ON THE EXPERT PORTION OF
THE SHOW THIS WEEK IS
Mr. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD OF
THE ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
THANK YOU.
WHERE OUR MOTTO IS...
IF YOUR EYES ARE STINGING,
MY PHONE SHOULD BE RINGING.
OKAY.
TODAY'S LETTER READS...
"DEAR EXPERTS, EVERY SUMMER
AND FALL, MY WIFE MAKES
FRUIT PRESERVES,
"THEY'RE PRETTY
MUCH INEVITABLE,"
OR DOES THAT SAY "INEDIBLE?"
THEY'RE EITHER
INEVITABLE OR INEDIBLE.
PROBABLY BOTH, HAROLD.
"HOW CAN I SHOW HER I REALLY
APPRECIATE HER PRESERVES
WITHOUT EATING ANY?"
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
I FIND THE FRUIT PRESERVES
ARE KIND OF LIKE NECKTIES,
IT'S SOMETHING YOU
GET AT CHRISTMAS
FROM PEOPLE WHO EITHER DON'T
LIKE YOU, OR ARE TOO CHEAP
TO BUY YOU A REAL GIFT.
EXACTLY.
FOR INSTANCE,
I GIVE MY MOM'S PRESERVES TO
CUSTOMERS WHO HAVEN'T PAID.
OH, YEAH. IT SENDS
A REAL MESSAGE.
OH, AND IF THEY EAT 'EM,
GENERATES A LOT MORE BUSINESS.
WINSTON, YOU BETTER
HOPE YOUR MOM'S
NOT WATCHING.
THIS SHOW?
NOT A CHANCE.
YOU KNOW, ANOTHER THING
WITH THE PRESERVES, YOU KNOW,
YOU GUYS COULD BE DONATING
THEM TO, LIKE, FOOD BANKS.
OH, COME ON, HAROLD, THOSE
PEOPLE HAVE ENOUGH PROBLEMS.
SEE, NO ONE SAID PRESERVES
HAD TO BE EATEN, EH?
AND MY MOM'S PRESERVES
MAKE GREAT PAINT.
OH, YEAH. THEY ARE COLOURFUL,
AND THEY STICK TO ANYTHING.
I USE IT TO UNDERCOAT
THE HONEY WAGON.
I THINK YOU GUYS ARE
MISSING THE POINT HERE
'CAUSE THE OPERATIVE WORDS THAT
THIS FELLOW WRITES ARE...
"HOW CAN I SHOW HER I REALLY
APPRECIATE HER EFFORTS?"
OH, RIGHT. OKAY.
WELL, I THINK, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE, LIKE, YOU KNOW,
TELL HER THE TRUTH.
MAYBE YOU JUST DON'T
LIKE HER PRESERVES,
BUT, YOU KNOW, CREDIT HER FOR
THINGS THAT YOU DO REALLY
APPRECIATE ABOUT HER.
WELL, THAT'S
A GOOD POINT
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW, CHANCES ARE,
SHE'S FAIRLY ATTRACTIVE.
WELL PRESERVED!
OH, RIGHT.
YEAH, I GET IT!
THIS WEEK ON
ADVENTURE WITH BILL,
HE INVITED ME
TO COME OVER.
HE WAS GONNA ACTUALLY
MAKE AN ELEVATOR HE HAD
AS HIS PROJECT.
YEAH, UP AND DOWN.
YEAH, VERY GOOD,
EXCELLENT.
THAT'S GOOD WORK, BILL.
HE NEEDED A CLOTHESLINE HERE,
SO I THOUGHT I'D SPEED
THINGS UP A LITTLE.
THERE WE GO.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
ALL RIGHT. NOW, I GUESS
THE CLOTHESLINE IS,
I WOULD IMAGINE,
PART OF THE ELEVATOR RIGGING.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS SOMETHING FOR
YOU YOUNGSTERS, YOU KNOW,
SOMETHING A LITTLE LATER IN
LIFE AND ALL THROUGH YOUR
LIFE...
YOU HAVE A BUDDY, YOU GO UP,
AND YOU JUST DO THINGS ON A
SATURDAY OR EVEN ON A TUESDAY
IF YOU HAVE MY WORK ETHICS.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT BRINGS
A LOT OF PLEASURE TO YOU.
AND BILL IS GOING TO --
YEAH, OKAY, I DRIFTED
OFF A LITTLE THERE.
I THINK IT'S THE MEDICATION
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
ANYWAY, HE'S GOING TO HOOK UP
THE PULLEY, THIS IS THE PULLEY
FROM THE CLOTHESLINE.
HOOK THAT ON TO THE BEAM
OVER THE SHED HERE.
YOU BETTER MAKE SURE THAT'S
SOLID, MAKE THAT SOLID,
THAT'S GOT TO SUPPORT
THE WHOLE WEIGHT THERE.
THAT WAS UNFORTUNATE.
YEAH, SHE'S GOOD, SHE'S GOOD.
THAT WAS GOOD TO
CHECK THAT OUT.
ALL RIGHT. THAT'S GOING
TO BE THE UPPER PULLEY.
NOW YOU NEED SOME KIND OF A --
HE'S GOT A WHEEL
IN HIS PANTS THERE
AND, OH, AN ENTIRE
CYCLE IN THERE.
I GUESS HE'S GOING
THROUGH THE CYCLE.
ANYWAY, THIS IS GOING TO
ACTUALLY BE THE VEHICLE THAT'S
GOING TO BE THE ELEVATOR.
UNBELIEVABLE.
SEE WHAT YOU CAN DO, KIDS,
WITH A LITTLE IMAGINATION?
HE RUNS THE ROPE UP AROUND THE
WHEEL, UP THROUGH THE PULLEY
AND DOWN THROUGH AROUND
THE WHEEL.
SEE? AROUND THE WHEEL,
AND IT'S KIND OF A LOOSE FIT,
BUT AS HE PEDALS,
IT WILL WIND UP THE CORD,
AND THAT'S THE CLOTHESLINE
AND PULL HIM UP TO WHEREVER
IT IS HE WANTS TO GO.
UP WHERE WE BELONG,
AS THEY USED TO SAY.
AND THE CHAIN BROKE.
THE CHAIN BROKE THERE.
THE CHAIN.
YEAH, THERE IT IS.
YEAH BROKEN.
ALL RIGHT, HE'S GOT THE
CHAIN BACK TOGETHER AND THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET CHAIN REPAIR.
THERE NOW, HE'S ALL SET
TO GO, AND AWAY YOU GO,
BILL, WAY YOU GO.
I AM REAL EXCITED
BECAUSE I'M NOT DOING IT.
LOOK AT THAT, EH?
LOOK AT THAT.
UP HE GOES.
WOW! HE'S SLIPPING A LITTLE,
BUT HE'S GETTING THERE.
THIRD FLOOR, LADY'S LINGERIE,
WEIRD GUYS ON KIDS' BIKES.
THEY'VE GOT THE WHOLE
RANGE IN THIS STORE.
AND WHEN HE WANTS TO STOP
ALL HE'S GOT TO DO IS
JAM ON THE BREAKS.
JAM 'EM ON.
THERE, THE CHAIN BROKE.
CHAIN BROKE.
GOING DOWN.
OH, BOY.
ARE YOU OKAY THERE, BILL?
NOW, YOU KNOW, ULTIMATELY,
IN THE ELEVATOR BUSINESS,
IT'S NOT THE UPS
AND DOWNS THAT GET YOU,
IT'S THE JERKS.
THE GUYS ARE ALL FIXING UP THEIR
CABINS FOR THE WIVES COMING UP.
IT'S REALLY STARTING TO HEAT UP.
WE'RE ACTUALLY MAKING A LITTLE
COMPETITION OUT OF IT,
SEEING WHO CAN BE THE MOST
THOUGHTFUL TO THEIR WIFE,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A MARRIED
MAN OF THE YEAR AWARD,
AND I GOT A REAL
GOOD SHOT AT IT.
YOU SHOULD SEE MY CABIN.
LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING OUT OF
ARCHITECTURAL DIGEST.
OR, ARCHITECTURAL
INDIGEST.
OH, COME ON, NOW, HAROLD,
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
I THREW TWINKLE LIGHTS
UP OVER THE RHINO HEAD.
OH, YEAH.
I GOT A COUPLE OF LAMPS THAT
ACTUALLY HAVE SHADES,
AND SINCE BERNICE
AND I DON'T SMOKE,
I'M TURNING THE ASHTRAYS
INTO SNACK BOWLS.
WELL, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO GO
SOME TO BEAT BUSTER HADFIELD.
YEAH, HE'S GOT LIKE SHAG
CARPETING AND COVERED
ORGAN SPEAKERS
AND A LAWN JOCKEY
THAT HOLDS INCENSE.
YEAH.
HE'S GOT THE WHOLE CABIN
DONE UP, LIKE, IN THAT
ZEBRA-STRIPED FUN FUR STUFF.
GEE, LOOKS SO COOL.
LOOKS LIKE THE INSIDE OF
SIEGFRIED AND ROY'S
DRESSING ROOM.
SEE, NOW, THAT'S
TOO MUCH, HAROLD.
SEE, WOMEN DON'T GO FOR THAT,
ESPECIALLY MARRIED WOMEN.
THEY LIKE THE SUBTLETY.
THAT'S WHY I'VE GOT JUST A
SINGLE ROSE IN A SHOT GLASS
ON THAT OLD HALL STAND
MADE OUT OF A COW'S LEG.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, I'VE GOT A
REAL COZY FIRE GOING IN THERE.
YOUR CABIN DOESN'T
HAVE A FIREPLACE.
WELL, I'M BEING CAREFUL.
YOU KNOW, AUNT BERNICE
LIKES THAT SINGER,
THAT JEWLEO ICICLES GUY?
JULIO IGLESIAS?
WHAT DID I SAY?
ALL RIGHT. WELL, OKAY, I'M
THINKING I CAN GET A POSTER,
MAYBE A COUPLE
OF HIS TAPES.
NO, NO, JUST BE
YOURSELF, UNCLE RED.
YEAH, BE THE MAN THAT
AUNT BERNICE MARRIED
OR, YOU KNOW, THAT SHE
THOUGHT SHE MARRIED,
OR THAT SHE WISHES
SHE MARRIED.
ACTUALLY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
BE THE OTHER GUY.
GO FOR THE OTHER GUY.
DOES AUNT BERNICE KNOW YOU'RE
PREPARING THIS LOVE NEST?
ACTUALLY, I WAS JUST GOING
TO GIVE HER A CALL NOW,
UNLESS YOU THINK MAYBE
I SHOULD MAKE IT A SURPRISE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, IF YOU WANT HER TO COME,
YOU'RE DEFINITELY GOING TO
HAVE TO MAKE IT A SURPRISE.
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING.
MY BUDDY EDGAR MONTROSE, HERE,
HAS BROUGHT IN SOMETHING
FOR US TO FIX.
WHAT HAVE YOU
GOT THERE, EDGAR?
OH, HI, RED.
I'M FINE.
THANK YOU.
OH, TODAY I BROUGHT IN THIS
STEERING WHEEL FROM MY CAR.
WOW, HAD A BIT OF
A CAR ACCIDENT, DID YA?
YEP, AND THAT'S THE BIT
OF THE CAR THAT'S LEFT.
WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE OTHER CAR?
WHAT OTHER CAR?
NO, NO, I MEAN THE --
OH, OH. NO, IT WAS
JUST MY CAR, RED.
YOU SEE, I WAS EXPERIMENTING
WITH ALTERNATIVE ENERGIES.
I WAS TRYING TO HARNESS
THE ENERGY OF THE SUN.
THAT'S UNUSUAL.
SOLAR POWER'S USUALLY
PRETTY SAFE.
NOT SOLAR POWER,
NUCLEAR FUSION.
YOU SEE, I WAS  READING
SOMEWHERE THAT THE CENTRE OF
THE SUN IS MILLIONS OF DEGREES
AND THE PRESSURE IS SO GREAT
THAT IT JUST FORCES HYDROGEN
ATOMS TOGETHER, FUSES THEM.
THAT'S WHERE YOU GET
YOUR ENERGY FROM.
SO YOU WERE TRYING TO RECREATE
THE CENTRE OF THE SUN
IN YOUR GARAGE?
WELL, THAT WAS THE THEORY.
I DIDN'T HAVE ANY HYDROGEN,
SO I HAD TO USE DYNAMITE.
THE HARDEST THING WAS FORCING
THEM STICKS DOWN INTO
THE GAS TANK.
SO DID YOU GET HER UP TO THE
MILLIONS OF DEGREES IN THERE,
DO YOU THINK?
I DUNNO.
MY THERMOMETER ONLY WENT UP TO
130, AND THEN IT JUST WENT.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK
I GOT IT QUITE RIGHT.
'CAUSE IT WAS A LOT
BRIGHTER THAN THE SUN
AND A LOT LOUDER.
WELL, THERE YOU GO, EDGAR.
BACK TO THE DRAWING BOARD.
OH, NO, MY DRAWING BOARD GOT
BLOWN HALF WAY TO PORT ASBESTOS.
WELL, HAROLD, IT'S
JUST NOT FAIR.
I MEAN, THE RULES OF
THE CONTEST WERE SET OUT
RIGHT FROM THE BEGINNING.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW,
UNCLE RED.
THESE DAYS YOU HAVE TO
ACCOMMODATE ALTERNATIVE
LIFESTYLES.
EVERYBODY WANTS TO TAKE PART
IN THIS MARRIED MAN OF THE
YEAR COMPETITION,
EVEN THE GUYS
THAT ARE SINGLE.
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK AND MOOSE
THOMPSON WANT TO MARRY EACH
OTHER JUST FOR THE CONTEST.
YEAH, BUT, YOU KNOW, THEY'RE
GOING TO GET THE MARRIAGE
ANNULLED ON MONDAY.
NOT ACCORDING TO
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK.
HE SAYS HE WANTS
TO HAVE A FAMILY.
IT DOESN'T MATTER, I'M ALL SET.
I'VE GOT MY CABIN
ALL READY FOR THE JUDGES.
I GOT THE LIGHTING,
I GOT THE MUSIC.
AS SOON AS I FIGURE OUT WHAT
KIND OF WINE GOES WITH
LICORICE, I'M DONE.
(POSSUM CALL)
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
THERE YOU GO THEN.
AND, BERNICE, IF YOU'RE WATCHING
THIS, I'M GOING TO COME HOME
STRAIGHT AFTER THE MEETING,
I'M GOING TO JUST PICK YOU UP
AND BRING YOU UP TO THE LODGE.
I'VE GOT A BIG SURPRISE WAITING
FOR YOU IN THE CABIN.
DON'T GET EXCITED,
IT'S ONLY DECORATIONS.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF, HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT THE LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTER]
Harold:  EVERYONE
TAKE YOU SEATS!
ALL RISE.
Everyone:
QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red:  SIT DOWN.
Harold:  OKAY, WE ONLY GOT
THE ONE ANNOUNCEMENT TONIGHT.
WELL, IT SEEMS THAT SOMEONE HAS
STOLEN ALL OF THE STUFF OUT
OF MY CABIN
AND REPLACED IT WITH
A BUNCH OF JUNK FURNITURE.
NOW, I'M TALKIN' ABOUT, LIKE,
MY VIDEO GAMES ARE MISSING
AND MY THIGH MASTER
AND MY RETAINER.
NOW, YOU CAN KEEP THE CHIA PET.
THAT'S OKAY.
BUT I WANT EVERYTHING ELSE
RETURNED TO CABIN 42
IMMEDIATELY.
Red:  HAROLD,
YOU'RE IN CABIN 43.
Harold:  OKAY, SO THERE'S
NO ANNOUNCEMENTS TONIGHT.