[breezy folk music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> THE TIME IS NOW, THE PLACE IS
HERE.
AND OF COURSE, IT'S BYOB.
WHAT ELSE WHEN YOU'RE AT THE RED
GREEN LODGE FOR THE RED GREEN
SHOW STARRING MY UNCLE AND THE
RENOWNED RACONTEUR.
WELL, HE'S A BIT LONGWINDED FOR
MY LIKING, BUT SHERIFF BURTON
WANTED WAY TOO MUCH MONEY.
ANYWAY, THE OWNER OF THE RED
GREEN LODGE, AND THE STAR OF THE
RED GREEN SHOW, MR. RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
THANK YOU, HAROLD, FOR THAT
INTERESTING INTRODUCTION.
I CERTAINLY HOPE I CAN LIVE DOWN
TO IT.
>> NO PROBLEM, UNCLE RED.
>> WHY DON'T YOU COME ON OVER
HERE A MINUTE, HAROLD.
I'LL INTRODUCE YOU.
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO HAVE NEVER
SEEN THE SHOW BEFORE, WHICH IS
ABOUT EVERYBODY, ACCORDING TO
THE RATINGS,
HAROLD HERE, IS THE
PRODUCER/DIRECTOR AND ALSO MY
NEPHEW, WHICH SORT OF TELLS YOU
THERE'S A BIT OF A HUGE FAVOR
INVOLVED IN THE SHOW HERE.
>> I THINK IT WOULD ONLY BE FAIR
TO ALSO MENTION THAT I CONTROL
THESE ELABORATE VIDEO EFFECTS
EQUIPMENT, WHICH KEEPS THE SHOW
YOUNG AND HIP.
[laughs]
I USE IT TO GO TO THE NEXT
SEGMENT OR IF I FEEL THIS
CURRENT SEGMENT IS FAILING TO
SUSTAIN THE INTEREST OF OUR
EVER-INCREASING VIEWER DEMAND.
>> NOT RIGHT NOW, HAROLD.
BECAUSE YOU INTRODUCED ME AS A
RACONTEUR, AND I HAVE TO RACONT
A WHILE BEFORE WE MOVE ON.
>> OH, OKAY, I'M JUST GONNA PLAY
WITH MY AXE A LITTLE BIT WHILE
YOU RACONT.
BUT I WILL BE LISTENING.
LARRY, YOU HEAR ME, RIGHT?
OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, UP AT THE
LODGE LAST NIGHT, IT WAS GETTING
LATE, BUT WE DIDN'T REALLY WANT
TO GO TO BED, AND THERE WEREN'T
ENOUGH DICE FOR YAHTZEE.
SO WE DECIDED TO HAVE
A WHITTLING CONTEST.
>> [laughs]
SORRY.
OH, WAS THAT YOU, LARRY?
>> ALL RIGHT, SO, WE ALL WENT
LOOKING FOR A PIECE OF WOOD THAT
WE COULD CARVE INTO SOMETHING.
AND WE SAID THAT 11:00 WOULD BE
THE CUTOFF.
YOU HAD TO HAVE YOUR ENTRY IN
BY THEN,
AND FIRST PRIZE WOULD BE THAT
YOUR ENTRY DIDN'T GO INTO THE
FIRE.
HAROLD, YOU TOOK US INTO THE
NEXT SEGMENT.
>> OH, SORRY, UNCLE RED.
LARRY, DON'T.
[light guitar and spoons music plays]
>> JAMS AND JELLIES
AND CANDIES AND SWEETS
NUTMEG AND EASTER EGG
IN ASSORTED MEATS
CHOCOLATES AND MACAROONS
AND VARIOUS
UNIDENTIFIED TREATS
I THINK IT'S TIME
SOMEONE WASHED THESE SHEETS
THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
GONNA TAKE YOU OUTSIDE AND SHOW
YOU HOW TO CHANGE A FLAT TIRE.
EVERYBODY GETS A FLAT TIRE QUITE
OFTEN ACTUALLY.
MAYBE YOU GOT IT FROM TAILGATING
ONE OF THEM GLASS DELIVERY
TRUCKS.
OR MAYBE YOU RUN OVER AN ANIMAL
WHILE HE WAS YAWNING.
I GOT THIS ONE FROM OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK PICKING HIS TOENAILS
AND THROWING THEM OUT THE
WINDOW.
ANYWAY, THE FIRST STEP HERE IS
TO GET THE HUBCAP OFF THERE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, THIS PARTICULAR
WHEEL HAS BEEN ON THE TRUCK
SINCE I BOUGHT HER NEW.
AND SOME PEOPLE SAY YOU SHOULD
ROTATE THE TIRES.
I DON'T REALLY UNDERSTAND THAT.
I MEAN, THEY GET ROTATED WHILE
YOU'RE--
I MEAN, SO I THINK SOME PEOPLE
JUST LOOK FOR WORK.
BUT WITH THEM BEING ON THERE
THAT LONG, THESE NUTS ARE RUSTED
ON THERE LIKE COWL FLAPS ON A
WAFFLE IRON.
SO WHAT WE NEED TO DO IS THROW
IN SOME PENETRATING OIL.
AND I SAY, YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE
GONNA PUT PENETRATING OIL ON IT,
THERE'S NO SENSE BEING SKIMPY
AND HOLDING BACK.
YOU GOT TO SOAK--YOU GOT TO
REALLY, REALLY SOAK IT IN THERE
AND YOU KNOW, WE LIKE SOAKING
THINGS IN UP AT THE LODGE.
I MEAN, FOR THE PRICE OF A CAN
OF THIS STUFF, YOU KNOW,
IT'S VERY, VERY COST-EFFECTIVE.
OH.
I LOVE THE SMELL OF THIS
STUFF.
YOU KNOW, IT'S STARTING TO
LOOSEN ME UP A LITTLE TOO.
WAIT A MINUTE.
OKAY, MAYBE I USED A LITTLE
TOO MUCH OF THE
PENETRATING OIL THERE.
ANYWAY, NOW WE GOT TO LOOSEN OFF
THE NUTS HERE.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'LL DO HER.
NOW I GOT THE TIRE IRON.
PUT THE TIRE IRON ON THERE AND
IT'S A SIMPLE TOOL, BUT IT'S
A USEFUL TOOL.
KIND OF LIKE MY BROTHER-IN-LAW.
ALL RIGHT.
[grunting]
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WHAT WE'RE FINDING NOW IS THAT
THE NUTS ON THIS WHEEL ARE
TIGHTER THAN SAY, THE DISCS ON
MY SPINE.
SO WE GOT TO SWITCH TO THE LAW
OF THE LEVER.
WHICH IS, IF IT'S NOT WORKING,
LEAVE HER.
ALL RIGHT, WHAT I DO NOW IS
STICK THIS PIPE ON.
THIS ADDS SOME LEVERAGE.
I CAN REALLY HORSE THIS DOWN
NOW.
REALLY HORSE HER.
REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY HORSE HER DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, IT'S GOING.
IT'S GOING, GOING, GOING, GOING,
GOING, GOING, GOING.
OH!
WELL, AS CONFUCIUS SAY, "IF AT
FIRST YOU DON'T SUCCEED,
SWITCH TO POWER TOOLS."
YOU KNOW, A ROCKET WINCH.
RACKET RINCH, RACKING SHRINCH,
REN--IT'S A WRENCH.
PUT THAT ON HERE.
AND WHOA!
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, WHAT WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO DO IS SWITCH TO AN INNOVATIVE
ALTERNATIVE TO THE NORMAL
TIRE-CHANGING TECHNOLOGY.
AND THIS WILL REQUIRE THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
WHAT WE DO IS, WE'VE DUCT-TAPED
THE SPARE TIRE RIGHT ON TO THE
FLAT THERE.
OF COURSE NOW, THIS IS ONLY
TEMPORARY UNLESS IT WORKS.
SO THAT'S GOT HER DONE.
REMEMBER, TILL THE NEXT TIME,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH THE
RESULTS OF THE WHITTLING
CONTEST.
>> IF THERE'S TIME.
WE CAN ONLY HOPE.
>> IT IS SPRING.
THE GROUNDHOG COMES OUT OF HIS
HOLE AND SEES HIS SHADOW.
IT IS THE SHADOW OF MY RIGHT
FRONT TIRE.
THAT MEANS WINTER WILL LAST
ANOTHER SIX WEEKS.
BUT NOT FOR HIM.
SO, AS I WAS SAYING EARLIER,
WE HAD THE JUDGING FOR THE
WHITTLING CONTEST, ABOUT 11:00.
STINKY PETERSON WENT FIRST.
HE HELD UP A TREE BRANCH THAT HE
CARVED OUT OF THE COFFEE TABLE.
DID A HECK OF A NICE JOB ON IT
TOO.
AND OLD MAN SEDGEWICK GOT UP.
BUT HE DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING TO
SHOW BECAUSE HE THOUGHT
WE'D SAID "WHISTLING CONTEST."
AND HE WAS REALLY MAD BECAUSE
HE'D GONE THE WHOLE EVENING
WITHOUT EATING CRACKERS.
AND HE HAD TAKEN HIS TEETH OUT,
WHICH EXPLAINED WHY MOOSE
THOMPSON COULDN'T GET
COMFORTABLE IN THE NAUGAHYDE
RECLINER.
>> EXCUSE ME, UNCLE RED.
I DON'T MEAN TO INTERRUPT THE
FLOW OF THIS FASCINATING STORY
YOU'RE ARTICULATING SO WELL, BUT
I WAS JUST WONDERING, I'VE GOT
A LITTLE PROBLEM.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THIS CONTROL
DOES?
>> NO, I DON'T, HAROLD.
>> IT DOES THAT.
>> HOW YOU DOING, MAN?
>> HELLO, RED.
HOW'D YOU LIKE TO TAKE A RIDE
IN THE RV?
DOLORES IS ALL READY TO GO.
>> DOLORES?
ARE YOU TAKING THE EX-WIFE?
>> NO, MY RV'S DOLORES.
MY EX-WIFE'S NAME IS SOMETHING
ELSE.
ANYWAY, SHE'S ALL GASSED UP,
OILED UP, WASHER FLUID UPPED,
BATTERY ACID UPPED, READY TO GO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WANT TO GET GOING, JUST JUMP
ON THE ROAD.
>> NO, NO, CAN'T DO IT.
I'M KIND OF TIED UP TODAY.
BUT I NEED THIS OUTBOARD MOTOR
FIXED, YOU KNOW.
>> OH, WELL, RED, JEEZ,
I'M A LITTLE BUSY, RED.
>> OH, MAN I'M REALLY STRAPPED.
I NEED THIS.
I NEED THIS DONE.
>> WELL, I GOT A LOT OF JOBS TO
DO, RED.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO TAKE
A NUMBER.
>> WELL, ALL RIGHT, WHERE'S
THE NUMBERS?
>> OH, RIGHT, YEAH, THAT'S THE
FIRST JOB I GOT TO DO IS FIND
A PLACE FOR THAT RACK WITH
NUMBERS.
>> WELL, MAYBE YOU COULD JUST
TAKE A QUICK LOOK-SEE.
I THINK IT'S KIND OF, THE PULL
CORD I THINK HAS COME OFF
THE WHEELS.
SEE, SHE'S KIND OF--
>> RIGHT, YEAH.
YEAH.
WELL, A NEW MOTOR'S GONNA COST
$1,200, RED.
>> YEAH, WELL I WAS KIND OF
THINKING WE'D JUST GET THIS ONE
FIXED.
WE'RE A LITTLE STRAPPED FOR CASH
AT THE LODGE.
>> OH, RIGHT, OKAY.
WELL, YOU BETTER GRAB MY TOOLS.
>> YEAH, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
>> THAT'S NOT GOOD FOR THE
MOTOR, RED.
>> OKAY.
>> WATCH THE RV.
>> YEAH.
WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST?
>> OH, I'LL GET AN APPLE BOX
HERE, RED.
THAT'S WHAT WE'LL DO.
AND THEN WE'LL JUST, UH...
>> OH, GREAT.
OKAY, GREAT.
THAT'S GREAT.
THAT'S SUPER.
>> PULL CORD.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA GET
MY TOOLS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
>> CAN YOU GRAB ME A ROOT BEER
IN THERE, RED?
>> YEA, SURE.
>> BOY, IF IT'S NOT ONE THING,
IT'S A ANOTHER IN THIS BUSINESS.
[light guitar and spoons music plays]
>> IF YOU'RE HAPPY
AND YOU KNOW IT
GET UP OUT OF YOUR CHAIR
GET IN YOUR CAR
AND GET THE HELL
AWAY FROM HERE
AS FAST AS YOU CAN
IF YOU'RE HAPPY
AND YOU KNOW IT
GET UP OUT OF YOUR CHAIR
GET IN YOUR CAR
AND GET THE HELL
AWAY FROM HERE
AS FAST AS YOU CAN
IF YOU'RE HAPPY
AND YOU KNOW IT
GET UP OUT OF YOUR CHAIR
GET IN YOUR CAR
>> ALL RIGHT, GET IN IT.
>>  GET THE HELL
AWAY FROM HERE
AS FAST AS YOU CAN
>> QUICKER THAN THAT EVEN.
>> ALL RIGHT, THAT WENT WELL.
>> OH, UNCLE RED, THIS IS SO
GREAT.
IT'S VIEWER MALE TIME.
THIS IS MY FAVORITE PART OF THE
SHOW AND MANY PEOPLE'S AS WELL,
'CAUSE THIS HAS GONE FROM
A POTENTIAL LIABILITY TO AN
OBVIOUS HIGHLIGHT IN THE
PROGRAM, TO WHICH I ATTRIBUTE
ONLY THE FACT THAT I HAVE ADDED
SO MANY PRODUCTION VALUES,
AND EVERYTHING THAT IS
HAPPENING IS DUE TO ME.
I TRULY BELIEVE THAT.
>> JUST READ THE LETTER, HAROLD.
>> I'LL JUST GET RIGHT TO THE
LETTER ACTUALLY.
YOU SEE, NOW THAT'S GOOD,
BECAUSE YOU'RE HELPING WITH THE
PACING AND STUFF.
THAT'S REALLY GREAT THAT YOU
REMIND ME OF THOSE THINGS.
THIS LETTER TODAY IS FROM
QUEBEC.
[laughs]
"DEAR ROUGE VERT, I'M TRYING TO
UNDERSTAND YOUR SHOW,
BUT THE LANGUAGE IS SO
CONFUSING.
COULD YOU PLEASE HELP ME?
TELL ME THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
A MOUNTAIN LION, A PUMA,
AND A COUGAR?"
>> WELL, HAROLD, BASICALLY,
THE SPELLING.
OTHER THAN THAT, THOSE THREE ARE
ALL THE SAME ANIMAL.
>> WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
LIKE, THEY'RE IN THE SAME FAMILY
OR SOMETHING?
'CAUSE THEY'RE NOT THE SAME
ANIMAL.
UNLESS OF COURSE YOU COMPLETELY
MISUNDERSTOOD MY MAMMAL VOLUME
OF THE TIME-LIFE BOOKS
I GOT AT THE IGA.
>> NO, THOSE ARE THE SAME
ANIMAL, HAROLD.
SEE, IN ENGLISH, WE HAVE SLANG
WORDS.
SO, WE'LL SAY GROUNDHOG
OR WE'LL CALL IT A GOPHER.
IT'S THE SAME ANIMAL.
OR A DEER, WE'LL CALL IT
A DOE OR A STAG OR A BUCK.
IF YOU HAVE A CAMEL WITH ONE
HUMP, WE CALL THAT A DROMEDARY.
IF THE CAMEL HAS THREE HUMPS,
WE CALL THE NATIONAL ENQUIRER.
AND OF COURSE WITH A BEAVER,
WE'LL CALL THAT A MUSKRAT
OR A BADGER.
BUT THEY'RE ALL THE SAME ANIMAL.
>> WHAT, REALLY?
>> OH, YEAH.
AND ANOTHER THING PEOPLE DON'T
REALIZE IS THAT A MOOSE AND AN
ELK AND A MOUNTAIN GOAT,
ALL THREE OF THOSE, THEY ARE
THE SAME ANIMAL.
AND ALSO A WOODPECKER.
ALL FOUR OF THEM ACTUALLY ARE
THE SAME ANIMAL.
>> OH, NO WAY.
NO, THAT CAN'T POSSIBLY BE.
I DON'T EVEN BELIEVE THAT.
NO WAY.
I THINK THERE'S A DRAMATIC
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A WOODPECKER
AND A MOUNTAIN GOAT.
>> WELL, ARE YOU CALLING ME
A LIAR, HAROLD?
>> OH, NO, NO, NO, UNCLE RED,
NO, NO.
I WOULDN'T CALL YOU A LIAR.
JUST, YOU KNOW, YOU COULD BE
OPERATING UNDER SHEER IGNORANCE.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
SOMETHING A LITTLE DIFFERENT
ON THE ADVENTURES WITH BILL
THIS WEEK.
BILL THOUGHT HE'D SHOW YOU THAT
HE'S A, YOU KNOW, A BIT OF
A SPORT.
A BIT OF A NATURAL, WELL--NOT
REALLY NATURAL ANYTHING I GUESS.
BUT HE THOUGHT HE'D SHOW YOU
ABOUT OF WATER SKIING.
YOU KNOW, I THINK MAYBE CLEANING
OFF THE DOCK MIGHT HAVE BEEN--
WELL, YOU KNOW.
ANYWAY, HE GETS HIMSELF
SET UP THERE.
THIS IS THE WAY HE'S GONNA
TAKE OFF.
NOW, HE WANTED TO EXPLAIN TO ME
THE HAND SIGNALS.
SPEED UP, SLOW DOWN.
GO STRAIGHT, TURN LEFT,
I GOT A CORD--
ANYWAY, WHATEVER.
AND THEN THIS STUFF, I'M JUST
AS GLAD I MISSED OUT ON.
ANYWAY, HE'S ALL SET, THROWS THE
ROPE IN, AND GIVES ME THE
SIGNAL.
AND I LOVE THIS PART.
I JUST LOVE JUST GIVING UP
THE GAS, AND YEAH.
WELL, THERE YOU ARE.
OH, OH, OH.
BOY, OH, BOY.
OH, THAT'S A SHAME.
THAT'S A SHAME.
SO HE PUTS SOME OF THE GOALIE
GLOVES ON.
LITTLE EASIER ON YOUR FINGERS,
BUT THEN I COULDN'T GET
THE SIGNAL.
BUT, ANY--OKAY, I GOT IT.
OH, LOVE THIS PART.
YEAH, YEAH.
AND AWAY WE GO.
BUT LOOKIT, HIS SKI GOT THE FIN
JAMMED BETWEEN THE BOARDS
ON THE DOCK THERE.
AND WHAT A SHAME.
WATER SKIING'S KIND OF
DANGEROUS.
HE TRIED TO GET A LITTLE CLOSER
TO THE EDGE OF, WELL, OH, OH--
MAYBE A LITTLE TOO CLOSE.
NOW HE SITS FARTHER BACK.
SO, HE WON'T, OH, LOOKS GOOD,
LOOKS GOOD, LOOKS GOOD.
OH, OH, OH.
OH, WELL, I THINK HE'S OKAY.
YOU OKAY, BILL?
YEAH. YEAH.
HE'S FINE. ALL RIGHT.
THIS WAS A MISUNDERSTANDING.
HE WAS BRINGING THE SKI IN.
AND HE GAVE ME THE SIGNAL,
MEANING HE HAD THE SKI,
BUT I THOUGHT THAT--
'CAUSE I LOVE THIS PART,
YOU KNOW, AND, OH, BOY.
I FELT BAD.
HE'S OKAY NOW.
NOW HE FINALLY FIGURED OUT, SIT
ON THE EDGE OF THE DOCK,
AND THAT WAY YOU CAN
CONTROL IT BETTER.
GIVE ME THE--THIS IS AWAY
WE GO.
OH, BOY.
LOVE THE BOAT.
LOVE IT.
WHAT HE DIDN'T NOTICE, I GUESS,
AND I DIDN'T EITHER, WAS THAT
THE ROPE WAS KIND OF TIED
AROUND.
AND I WAS KIND OF BUSY DRIVING
THERE, AND SO HE THOUGHT HE'D--
I THINK HE JUST KIND OF
GOT READY FOR A BIG JOLT THERE.
BUT IT WAS ACTUALLY, OH, OH.
OW.
AND, UH, BILL'S OKAY.
YOU KNOW.
HE'S TIED UP FOR THE WEEKEND.
>> OKAY, FIRST WE GOT TO FLIP
THE COVER OFF THIS MOTOR.
LIFT UP THE SIDE THERE
AND FLIP 'EM UP AND--
>> THIS HERE?
>> THAT'S IT.
>> OKAY.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
>> OKAY, NOW I NEED THE CORDLESS
DRILL.
>> OH, THAT'S RIGHT HERE.
>> AND I NEED THE BUFFING WHEEL.
>> OKAY.
>> NOW, I WANT YOU TO SLAP THESE
TOGETHER.
>> OKAY.
THIS JUST--THE NAIL GOES THROUGH
HERE AND CLIPS IN.
IS THAT HOW SHE WORKS?
>> THAT'S IT.
>> YEAH.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
>> NOW, CAN YOU TAKE THAT UP
TO THE FRONT AND JUST BUFF THE
BUMPER WHILE I FIX THE MOTOR?
>> YOU WANT ME TO DO THAT?
>> WELL, RED, I'M TAKING TIME
OFF FROM CLEANING THE RV
TO FIX YOUR MOTOR.
>> ALL RIGHT.
FAIR ENOUGH.
>> NOT TOO HARD.
>> WHAT?
>> DON'T TAKE THE PAINT RIGHT
OFF THE BUMPER.
NOT TOO HARD.
>> OH.
HOW'S IT GOING?
>> OH, JUST TAKING A BREAK.
LETTING THE LUBRICANTS GET TO
THE BOLTS.
>> OH, ALL RIGHT.
I'LL JUST GO FINISH UP THEN.
>> YEAH, JUST GET UNDERNEATH.
YOU GETTING IT UNDERNEATH?
I LIKE IT NICE AND CLEAN
UNDERNEATH.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
>> OKAY, RED.
I'M FINISHED.
>> GREAT, GREAT.
YEAH, ME TOO.
SO WHAT'S THE WORD HERE?
>> WELL, YOU SEE THE CORD THERE?
>> YEAH.
>> TAKE IT OFF.
TIE A KNOT IN THE END OF IT.
PUT IT BACK ON THE WHEEL.
IT SHOULD BE FINE.
READY TO GO.
>> WELL, WHAT DID YOU DO THEN?
>> WELL, I REPLACED THE HOUSING,
CLEANED OUT THE VALVES,
AND CLEANED UP THE PROP
BACK THERE.
>> OH, THAT WAS REAL FAST.
THAT WAS INCREDIBLY FAST.
THAT WAS ALMOST TOO FAST,
WASN'T IT?
>> WELL, CAN I TAKE YOU
FOR A RIDE NOW?
>> NO, I THINK YOU JUST DID,
GLEN.
IT IS SPRING.
AS I LOOK FROM MY WINDOW, I SEE
DOGS MATING ON MY FRONT LAWN,
CATS MATING ON THE SHED ROOF,
MOOSE RUNNING IN THE FOREST.
I WATCH, MILDLY BEMUSED.
THEN I GO TO THE WORKSHOP
AND DESIGN A NEW TRAILER HITCH.
>> I HAVE A DREAM.
I HAVE A DREAM.
DO YOU KNOW WHO SAID THAT?
>> LARRY HAGMAN.
>> HEY, WATCH IT, RED!
>> NO, "I HAVE A DREAM" WAS SAID
BY MARTIN LUTHER KING.
I HAVE A DREAM TOO.
IT'S A DREAM WHERE I'M RUNNING
DOWN A HALL AND I'M NAKED.
YOU KNOW?
AND I'M BEING CHASED BY
ALL THESE PEOPLE.
PEOPLE OF DIFFERENT CREEDS
AND COLORS AND SEXES AND INCOME
BRACKETS AND SEXUAL
ORIENTATIONS.
IT'S HUGE.
THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE
CHASING--IT'S LIKE A STADIUM
EMPTIED ON ME OR SOMETHING.
>> DOES THIS STORY HAVE A TWIST
ENDING, HAROLD?
LIKE, YOU KNOW, FOR EXAMPLE,
A POINT?
>> OH, YEAH.
YEAH.
[creature wailing]
I JUST THINK THAT PEOPLE
SHOULDN'T BE JUDGED BY THE COLOR
OF THEIR SKIN OR THE SHADE OF
THEIR SKIN OR THE CONDITION OF
THEIR SKIN.
SO MY POINT IS, I DON'T LIKE
BEING CALLED ZIT FACE.
>> YOU'RE SENSITIVE, HAROLD.
>> YEAH, BUT NO, BECAUSE I DON'T
THINK YOU SHOULD MAKE FUN
OF PIMPLES.
'CAUSE ACNE IS ONLY ONE LETTER
DIFFERENT THAN ACME,
WHICH IS LIKE THE BEST.
OR ONE LETTER MORE THAN THE WORD
"ACE," WHICH IS NUMERO UNO,
ALSO, THE BEST.
>> YEAH, I'LL AGREE WITH THAT,
HAROLD.
I THINK YOUR PIMPLES ARE
THE BEST I'VE SEEN.
>> EXACTLY.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE WE WON'T
HAVE TIME TO GET BACK TO THAT
WHITTLING CONTEST STORY.
SO, STAY TUNED.
OH, THAT'S A SHAME.
>> SO INSTEAD, I'M GONNA WHITTLE
HAROLD INTO SOMETHING USEFUL.
THAT'S A SHAME.
WHAT'D YOU DO AGAIN?
>> WELL, I JUST--I HAD--
I TOOK THIS OFF.
>> YEAH.
>> CLEANED IT.
>> I REPLACED THE HOUSING.
>> THAT'S THE SAME HOUSING.
>> YEAH.
WELL, NO, I TOOK IT OFF
AND PUT IT BACK ON.
THAT'S WHAT I MEANT
BY REPLACING.
>> WHY?
>> WELL, 'CAUSE IT NEEDED TO BE
TIGHTENED UP, YOU KNOW.
AND THEN, I TOOK THE VALVES
AND CLEANED THOSE UP, SO.
>> THERE'S NO VALVES IN THIS
MOTOR.
JUST A TWO-CYCLE.
>> OH, WELL, I MEANT THESE HERE.
I ALWAYS GET VALVES AND SPARK
PLUGS ALL MIXED UP ALL THE TIME.
I TOOK THEM OUT.
A LITTLE SANDPAPER AND PUT THEM
BACK IN.
>> YOU TOOK OUT THESE SPARK
PLUGS?
>> THAT'S THE ONE, YEAH.
>> THESE--WITHOUT TAKING
THE WIRES OFF?
>> OH, YEAH, THAT'S EASY ENOUGH
TO DO.
JUST GIVE IT A GOOD UNF ON IT,
IT COMES RIGHT OUT.
OF COURSE, WHEN YOU PUT THEM
BACK IN, YOU GOT TO GET
A HAMMER.
>> HOW MUCH YOU GONNA CHARGE ME
FOR THIS, GLEN?
>> OH, LET'S SEE, THERE'S MY
HOURLY RATE AND THE PARTS.
>> I'D LIKE TO SAY A FEW WORDS
TO YOU TEENAGERS OUT THERE.
I HOPE I CAUGHT YOU BETWEEN
MUSIC VIDEOS.
MY MESSAGE IS SIMPLE.
STAY IN SCHOOL.
SCHOOL GETS OUT AT 3:30.
STAY AN EXTRA HOUR.
IT WON'T KILL YA.
MAYBE YOU CAN GO DOWN
TO THE LIBRARY,
OPEN A THICK BOOK.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO READ IT.
IT JUST MAKES AN IMPRESSION.
ESPECIALLY IF THERE'S HARDLY
ANY PICTURES IN IT.
BELIEVE ME, YOU'RE A LOT BETTER
OFF STAYING IN SCHOOL, THEN YOU
ARE GOING OVER TO A FRIEND'S
GARAGE AND MAKING BOMBS OUT OF
GUNPOWDER AND COPPER PIPES.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA LOSE A FINGER
IN THE LIBRARY,
UNLESS SOMEBODY PUNCHES YOU IN
THE NOSE.
STAY IN SCHOOL.
YOUR TEACHERS DID, AND THEY'RE
NOT DOING TOO BAD.
THEY GET THE WHOLE SUMMER OFF.
STAY IN SCHOOL.
SO, ANYWAY, 11:00 ROLLED AROUND,
AND IT WAS TIME TO ADD UP ALL
THE VOTES FOR THE WHITTLING
CONTEST, AND, GOLLY,
WE HAD A SIX-WAY TIE
UNTIL WE DECIDED THAT YOU
COULDN'T VOTE FOR YOUR OWN,
AND THEN BUSTER HADFIELD
COME IN THIRD.
HE HAD WHITTLED A CANE OUT OF
A 60-FOOT OAK TREE.
AND THEN STINKY PETERSON TOOK
SECOND PRIZE WITH A DINNER PLATE
THAT HE'D WHITTLED OUT OF THE
OUTHOUSE DOOR.
ACTUALLY HE WOULD HAVE WON, BUT
THE FOOD KEPT FALLING THROUGH
THE MOON-SHAPED HOLE.
BUT THE BIG GUY, MOOSE THOMPSON,
TOOK FIRST PRIZE, WHEN, IN AN
ATTEMPT TO CARVE A BIG BLOCK OF
GRANITE, HE HAD WHITTLED HIS
WHITTLING KNIFE INTO AN ICE
PICK.
SO, IT WAS A GREAT--ANYWAY, IF
MY WIFE IS WATCHING, I'M GONNA
BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME AFTER
THE SHOW, SO LEAVE THE PORCH
LIGHT ON IF MY FOLKS ARE THERE,
AND I'LL JUST KEEP CIRCLING
THE BLOCK TILL THEY LEAVE.
AND IF MY FOLKS ARE WATCHING,
SEE YOU SOON.
THANKS A LOT FOR WATCHING, AND
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF, HAROLD, AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE AT THE
LODGE, KEEP YOUR STICK ON
THE ICE.