But.
Gather around your television set and make
sure they're turned on because this is the
wildest wildlife show on the air, bringing
you thrills, chills, spills
And a really nice
View of our hallway right around now.
The show that dares to be different only
because we can't afford to be the same.
And here he is, the man who's the most
effort of them all.
The star of the show and through a cruel
twist of DNA fate, my uncle.
Here he is, the legal owner of the Red Green
Show.
Ladies and gentlemen, Mr. Red Green Girl.
Thank you, and welcome
To Possum Lodge. Not fancy, but it's paid
for.
We've got a good show for you this week.
Although I have no idea what Harold meant by
the thrills, chills and spills
Go rat, I was referring to my directorial
digitalizing.
That's what gives the show its cutting edge
film
That makes me feel like cutting the edge of
your digits, Harold.
It's the state of the art al gore.
Oh, I don't know about art, but I know what
I like and that doesn't even come close.
And don't you even come close, either?
Try to keep that nonsense to a minimum.
Got a bit of a situation going on at the
Lodge this week.
We're kind of trapped in the lodge.
Nobody can go outside.
Well, are we being audited again?
No. Well, there's a there's a bear outside a
bear
Like a real bear.
I would quads and fangs and stuff like a
bear, a bear.
Like, what if a bear breaks down the door?
Like just balls us to death for no reason?
We should shoot it. We should shoot it.
Carol, Carol, Carol, you know, despite a lot
of misconceptions of which you are one that
bears don't just randomly, you know, mall
people and kill them.
Ok. If the bear comes in here and kills you,
it'll be to eat you.
But that's not going to happen, Harold,
because it'll sniff you first.
Now, this all got started when our cook,
Eddie made some honey raisin muffins.
Then he put them out on the back porch until
they stopped burning.
Oh, so like the bear was attracted by the
smell of Eddie's cooking.
No, no, no, no. Even bears aren't that
hungry.
I'll tell you what happened. Oh man.
Sedgwick and Buster Hatfield went down to the
store to buy some bear repellent.
And Duane, you know, being Duane sold them
bear Musk by mistake.
Ok? Now to a bear bear.
Musk is like a Madonna VIDEO And the Sports
Illustrated Swimsuit Issue all rolled into
one. So they came back here and they sprayed
out all over the place.
And now what we have is a is a pretty eager
male bear, you know, kind of drooling around
the lodge there. Wait a second.
If they spray like Bear Musk all around, he's
not sniffing for food.
Oh, you're probably right.
And if he comes in here, he won't be hungry.
Well, what say we just get rolling with the
show and then we could barricade the door?
Yeah, good idea.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
To the very sniffing around, Rick Van.
You see the way he's sniffing the trailer
hitch must be mating season.
Here comes no one is fun for you.
Yeah. Does he know about the bear?
I don't think so. I sure hope he sees it.
I don't think he does.
He doesn't even know about it.
They're still out there, guys.
Yeah. Yeah, he's stalking me.
No, no. Doesn't even know it.
Look at him dicking around with his siren.
Well, he knows about it now.
Oh, wow.
You sure can't motor.
Yeah. They moves pretty good for a dwarf.
Where's he going? Oh, shit.
Well, Bump House looks like,
Oh, you know, I never seen a man hurl a
barbecue before.
Well, I'm going to go get my camera.
This is excellent.
Oh, look, look. The boat house is a lot.
I told him we didn't need all those locks.
The beer's gaining on him.
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy.
Oh boy. Come on, come on.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh yeah.
No. Oh, yeah, sure.
Do you like a drink or anything, just help
yourself there.
Ok?
Starship Pantry one, 60 70 Investigate the
sighting of a bear near the lodge.
Light brown in color. Approximately 14 feet
tall.
Definitely male. What are you going to do
about it?
Not me. Quick.
If you're referring, not nothing.
Well, you're head of security there.
That's why you're dressed like a fire truck
or nothing.
Look, when it starts breaking into the lodge
member's car or swiping cutlery.
Hey, I'm there for you, buddy.
The bears trespassing?
No.
Well, actually. Helmet?
He's not. We're the ones who are trespassing
on his natural habitat.
See, because bears were here a long time
before us, and they will be here a long time
afterwards.
Not if no one goes out and shoots them.
Well, I hate. Ha ha.
I'm not allowed to carry a gun.
You can burn one of mine. I'm not even
allowed to hold a gun.
Why don't you go out and do one of those
karate type one dork moves you're always
talking about? That would tell them that
bears a maintenance problem.
You're in charge of maintenance.
You get rid of it. Maintenance.
What is the bear clog in the drains?
I must have missed that. No, but you are
responsible for clearing the pass in the
roadways so we can get to the vehicles.
Well, I shovel snow.
I rake leaves anything that moves.
You deal with right red.
Oh lord, you do guys settle this.
But whatever you do, sell it in a hurry
because sometime in the next two weeks,
somebody's going have to use that outhouse.
You heard him go kill the bear, you coward.
He didn't say that.
And don't you call me a coward, Mr?
Or else all or else what?
He didn't say I'd kill the bear.
Ok, I got the
Camera figured out already.
No, I'll go outside and do exactly what you
did before.
Ok, this time I'm ready.
Come on. Oh, well, it's Murray and Dwayne.
Oh, I got to get my wide angle lens for this
one.
Oh, I don't think so.
All they do now.
This is fun. Wow.
He was that fast when I was running faster.
Only your arms weren't flapping.
As I was walking through the woods one day, I
came upon a swag man jolly ing on his way.
He said he was waltzing Matilda to a Billy
bar.
And he refused to speak English, so I nailed
him.
This week in Handymen Corner, we're going to
show you how you can scare off a wild
animals, for example, bears, you know, bears
hardly ever take a swipe at anybody.
They're mostly noise and teeth, kind of like
Harold.
But you know what you got to do is you got
to find a way to to scare them off.
And what we're going to make today is call a
bear scare.
See, because in the animal kingdom now a lot
of the fights are avoided by one of the
animals making a big display.
You see a cat, but there's fur up, you know,
or a peacock or whip his tail out there or
dogs or snarling owned and show their teeth.
And the idea is you make yourself look real,
vicious and mean, or at least hard to
swallow. So what are you going to make our
bear scarier?
You're going to need some things you're
going to need.
You're going need some marbles and you're
going to need some Hawaiian shirts.
You're going to need a backpack, aluminum
tent pegs.
You're going to need some eyeballs, some
sash cord and some rubber gloves.
If you're looking for those things, you may
be able to find them all in Harold's closet.
Now, the first thing I'm going to show you
is how you make the counterweight to
noisemaker part of the deal.
You take a small town like this and you put
the marbles into the can.
All right. And then you put the small can
upside down into the big can.
Ok, and then you just cover that over with
the handyman secret weapon.
You make two of those and they're your
noisemakers.
They work now they're going to make our
visual display.
To do that, we take our backpack, put it
into the vise and I'm going to stick
on these eyeballs in the top of the vertical
supports.
Ok, so once we got our eyeballs on here,
we've added the pieces of PVC pipe to the
side and we and we really hoist her down
there with the of our secret weapon again,
duct tape and again, be generous with the
duct tape.
You don't spare the duct tape spoil the job.
All right now we take some one of our pieces
of sash cord runs it through the eyeball.
Ok, like this? The other end we've again
duct taped to the bottom of one of our tent
poles, and we dropped that down inside
inside the PVC pipe.
I've done the same thing on the other side
and when we pull the strings.
Well, I think you can see where we're going
with this.
We just finished packing in our plumage
here.
I take the ends of the pole cords and attach
them to our noisemakers.
Now I'm out walking through the woods and I
come across a bear or a wolf or helmet, and I
just do what the peacock vest?
Now that doesn't get you to the House
safely, I don't know what will.
I remember the women don't find you
handsome.
They should at least find your handy.
Lose my marbles here. Oh, God.
Chuck. So.
It is winter the bear sleeps not alone like
me, but with many other bears in some dark
den, I bet that doesn't smell too great.
All right. Back to the drawing board.
I know all the security guard now he wants
somebody else to go out there and shoot the
bear, but that's illegal unless the bear is
a danger.
And actually, with the large members being
all kind of trapped inside here and not being
allowed to go on the lake or on the
highways.
The danger level is is a way down.
So then Noel says that maybe helmets should
go out and argue with it because they've run
helmet. Just under that helmet wants us all
to dig a big tunnel like they did in that
movie, The Great Escape.
Then there was a big argument about who was
going to be Steve McQueen and Bruce Thompson
out there. Trying to last through the
barrier ended up being trapped up in the Pine
Tree.
You know, Uncle Brad, actually, you know,
bears aren't that dangerous.
I saw a movie downtown the other day and
there was like these two brown bears and
they're roaming around a national park.
They didn't maul anybody or nothing.
Actually, you know, they were more afraid of
the people than the people were of them.
And did they shoot the bears?
Oh, no,
No, no. See, no, just ranger, Smith told Yogi
and Boo Boo to put back those picnic baskets.
Oh, there you go, Harold, huh?
Huh, huh? But our bear isn't hungry, OK,
he's smelling Musk out there.
He's not going to be satisfied with dinner
and a dance.
Oh, you
Want, he wants a lady friend.
Well, we all want lady friends, Harold, but
we don't go around drooling and rubbing our
rumps up against the tree.
No, even I know that one won't work.
Well, you know it might, but it's not the
type of girls your parents would approve of.
No, right. So anyway, Helmut says that the
bear is so desperate for a mate that what we
can do is duct tape together, a couple of
air mattresses provide them with some fun for
a seat covers and then douse the whole thing
with Musk and throw her out there.
That might buy us enough time we can make a
break from my van.
In the meantime, I'll take us to the next
segment and they'll give us just enough time
that I can think of a brilliant plan.
This must be a really long segment.
I'll go into the storeroom and get the stuff.
I'm just going to cost a large this
15 dollars, so good.
I'll give you a 20 if you take a check.
Sounds good. Here's the tranquilizer, and
here's the bear repellent.
Let's go. Got a real big project for you this
week on Adventures with Bill.
You can see those little sticks in there.
What he's doing is he's actually going to
show you a little model of what it is that he
that he wants us to build.
She is going to build a little shelter, you
know, horizontal branch, and that's a little
one of those little dolls.
I didn't even ask about that.
It's none of my business, but I try and
build the full size model of that, not
including the doll first.
And so what we need is to get the chainsaw
going.
We got to cut out vertical horizontal branch
for.
Hmm. Oh, well, so what we're going to do is
instead of cutting it, we'll just use an axe
and just chopped, you know, those tools are
strong little trees compared to, say, an axe.
So what do we do now, bill?
Just Oh all right.
All right, pull it down. But you know, the
street of this tree, as I was agreeing a lot
of spring and a lot
Of it's amazing the power.
Oh, oh, oh.
Way up, there is a 70, 80 feet up there, and
you OK, well, you OK?
Yeah, yeah. All right.
All right. I figured if I shake the tree,
that'll help a little bit.
Whoa. He didn't seem to be enjoying that, do
you imagine?
Well, I thought I didn't, I didn't not.
Oh, sorry about that.
Well, I got him down, you know, and he's OK.
And of course, the good thing is now we have
enough branches to make our shelter.
So we picked these up and picked these up
and go over there and find just a fact that
we just found that thing just lying there,
that was I wish we hadn't noticed that.
Well, what the heck? And we lean the and
lean the branches up against it.
I just like the model. And then what Bill
wanted to do here was some way of securing
the branches right on there.
And this is when you know a lot of your
training with the with the Cub Scouts or what
have you, or maybe you did some sailing with
Captain Highline or whatever it was you can
you learn how to tie some really interesting
knots because you've got you've got trees and
branches coming at a whole lot of bills tied
one limb to many on.
Anyway, we got it all done, and by golly,
she's looking good and put the for sale sign
up and everything. So Bill goes inside and
got the gate on it.
What? But look, I feel like I.
Oh gosh, oh boy.
Oh boy, oh boy.
Well, no place like home, how's school going
this year, Harold?
Oh, great. Excellent.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
Best year ever. Oh yeah, yeah.
Football teams even winning.
Sure.
Oh great. Sounds like you're doing pretty
well, honey me.
Oh no, me, I'm. I'm just barely getting by.
School's doing good, though. I thought you
were asking about the school schools doing
good. I'm just, you know, struggling by.
As always,
I would think you'd be real good in school,
you know, because you got the glasses and
real gomer at sports and stuff, you know?
Yeah, I know you'd figure, you know,
computers in geography.
It's my television class.
You know, we're supposed to make a TV show.
Right. So we each got a hundred dollar
budget, so I made an episode of the Red Green
Show. Remember that extra one we made last
fall?
That one?
Oh, yeah, yeah. Well, how'd you do on that
anyway?
Got it.
D I d teach you.
I know where I spend the other 90 dollars.
And where did you spend it?
I got this really cool computer game vortex.
So cool. So cool.
Ok, I'm ready. How are you going to stop a
bear with that?
I stick it down his throat, then open it.
Oh yeah, the bears laughing at that.
We can all go to the bathroom, right?
Just don't open up here. It's bad luck.
Well, please hurry. We're going to have even
more bad luck.
Yeah, that's
Right. Nature's calling.
Who's ready to answer?
Hey. Ok, let's go.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa. Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Red. I'm head of security.
I should say, Let's go.
Ok, let's go. Wait, wait, wait.
I forgot something.
Oh, where's he going?
He said he forgot something.
You guys don't listen.
Reading material.
Oh! They all remember guys, animals can
smell fear.
All right. Yeah, they're not the only one.
Ok, when we get there, alphabetical order.
Ok, good, good. My name's Albert.
And Brown.
Well, the can of bear repellent was a big
disappointment, Dwayne pointed at the wrong
way and sprayed himself in the face drop the
can the bear ate it.
At least now, the bear won't eat Dwayne's
face, although I might try to tranquilizer
gun, but our aim was off.
We ended up hitting Moose Thompson at the
Pine Tree.
Uncle Ray, how long does it take for the
tranquilizer to take effect?
Just a little bit longer than it takes a bear
to maul a person from head to toe.
Is that just a gas uncle red, or is that what
it says in the instructions?
We can't go on like this much longer.
I mean, the washroom situation is getting
brutal around here.
A lot of the guys have been taking potted
plants up to their room.
Somebody's going have to show a little
bravery
Or stupidity
That you volunteering. Boy, that there really
isn't he?
No, no, no.
That's the sound of the wild possum.
The lodge meetings are about to begin.
Oh wow. We'll just see who is the lucky lodge
member who gets to sedate Winnie the Pooh.
I'm sure. Glad I'm not a lodge member.
Aren't we all?
Well, they say that a hero is just a
sandwich.
Let's go see who gets to hold the pickle.
We are.
My great, great, great.
All rise.
He is down the floor, recognize his helmet,
winter garden.
I would like to know why Noel hasn't done
anything about the barrier.
Yeah, why not?
Yes. Well, I'm not in charge of pest
control.
My job is to prevent theft.
Good point. Yeah, yeah.
Well, if you ask me, the bear stolen your
courage and.
Oh yeah, why don't you go out and talk to
him?
You might find out that your uncle or
something.
Hold on. Hold on.
Look, it's a well known fact that bears are
only in heat for two weeks.
I think we can hold out that long.
Hey, take yourself there, Murray, right?
Question question, what what does it mean?
Right? Well, herald and heat means the bear
has more than Georgia on its mind to get
that. Not a clue, right?
Animals only get in the mood to mate for a
short period of time once a year.
Oh boy, that'd make it easy, wouldn't it?
Boy, one more time for Nintendo.
Right?
Huh. What?
Shut up, Harold, anyway. I think we all
agree that it's up to North Hell to do
something about the bear, right? Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Why don't we put it to a vote?
No or help?
Sure. Excuse me.
Read, since you're the lodge leader, I think
maybe we should do something about the bear.
Ok, sure, somebody.
Sure.
Yeah. Well, I am doing something about it.
All those in favor of Noel taking care of
the bear.
Say I.
All those in favor of helmet.
Taking care of the bear. Say I.
Well, there you go there, don't you?
It's a tie. Great.
You know what we're going to do, Uncle
Uncle.
We'll have to make the deciding vote.
Well, I'm going to need some time to think
this over, so.
So while I'm deciding why don't we get
Murray and Dwayne to come up here and give us
the evening's entertainment?
Well, what we're going to do for you this
week, boys, we're going to tell you the story
of Goldilocks and the three bears.
All right.
Oh, it's funny how one scruffy bear who is
looking for love in all the wrong places and
disrupt so many lives.
What's that? Well, love exciting and new.
Come aboard. We're expecting you.
Same as our bear. It's not himself, lady
friend.
I think we're going to be able to go back
outside again real soon.
Anyway, if my wife is watching, I should be
able to get to my van and come home in about
two minutes. Just a guess.
Maybe you can check to see if you can find
our bearskin rug.
So until next time, on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole gang up here at Possum
Lodge and the Bear and his lady friend.
Keep your stick on the ice.
Yes. We are not doing the bare stuff yet.
Goldilocks or Goldie, I want to be the bear.
I know you want to be the bear, but you'll
be the bear later.
All right, we'll turn it around, OK?
The bear is in the forest, and tiger comes
up until this golden lock family's house.
Ok? So anyway, goes up to the door and
knocks on the door.
Wait, let me to talk about it.
It's a fairy tale and bears can do anything
but go outside.
Oh, come here. The bears can be Goldilocks.
Well, you want to be the bear.
He's an idiot and he wants to be the bear.
That's the way.
There's a friend of yours waiting outside.
Very attractive. There you go.
And that's the way
That we live.
Can I have his job in the store?
Most definitely you can't.
Yes, I have one of the pups.