Don't you hate it when
windshield washer technology
actually makes the windshield
harder to see out of?
You know there's
an old expression,
never send a boy
on a man's job
or if you're
a lodge member,
never send Harold
on any job.
So if you want
a clean windshield,
you need a man-sized
windshield washer.
You see this tiny,
little, puny thing here?
This is a standard
windshield washer pump.
This is for
little squirts.
We're going to take
that up a notch.
This baby will really fire
out the water.
And speaking of fires,
we're also going to
biggie size our nozzle.
I got my pump running off
the fan belt,
and I'm using a water cooler
bottle as my reservoir.
There were a whole pile
of these behind the 7-11.
Okay, I think we're ready
for a road test.
My windshield's dirty.
Thanks.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Thank you very much.
No, no, no.
I appreciate that.
Bit of a setback this week
up at the lodge.
Stinky Peterson has come up
with a new recipe
for pickled eggs
au gratin.
But he was shut down
by the environmental
protection agency.
Uncle Red!
We have to
clean up the lodge.
We did.
No, not just sort it
into heaps by smell... clean.
The Ontario Tourism Board
is coming into this area,
and they're going to be
inspecting all the resorts
so they can, you know,
rate them for their brochure
and we cannot afford
to have another rating
of "dangerous
to all life forms."
What are you talking
about, Harold?
Last year we got
three stars.
Those were 'X's!
We're the only triple-X
rated lodge in the
entire province.
That's why we had so few
people here, you know.
And the ones who did come,
we didn't want.
Well, who cares, Harold?
We get along fine up here
without all those
yuppie families coming up
with their kiwi suntan lotion
and their bottled water.
You know what, I feel like
they're from another planet.
Earth?
Red?
You ought to
see Caribou Lodge.
It's like the Ritz?
The hotel
or the cracker?
The resort.
They've cleaned
everything up.
There's no propane tanks
piled up everywhere.
There's no car engines
hanging from the trees.
There's no empties
on the roof.
Well, they're just trying
to suck up to the
tourist board.
I know that.
And they told me
to tell you
that they're going to kick
our butt in the ratings.
They're bragging that they're
going to make Possum Lodge
look like a dump.
Don't you worry.
You beat 'em to that.
Harold, we beat em
to almost everything.
We hardly ever lose a
competition to Caribou Lodge.
Okay, well then
you guys had better
decide to pitch in,
clean up to get
this place --
No, no.
We don't need
to pitch in.
All we got to
do is hire --
A cleaning lady?
Is that what you were
really going to say?
I guess not.
Because that's demeaning,
sexist and politically
incorrect.
Man, it's getting
so hard to be me.
Good.
Oh...
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Today's winner
receives this coupon
for a complimentary treatment
at Chang Lee's
Acupuncture palace.
"Apply for an
Acupuncture gold card
"and get extra points."
All right, Dalton,
cover your ears.
Red, you've got 30 seconds
to get Dalton Humphrey
to say this word...
All right, Winston.
And go!
Okay, Dalton,
your wife talks and you...
Cringe.
No, okay.
Okay, no.
I mean, she speaks
and then you...
Give in?
Okay, okay, what
about your daughter?
She tells you
a story and you...
Tune out.
All right, let's flip it
around the other way.
Let's say, when you talk
to your wife, she has to...
Interrupt.
Okay, okay, say you pull
up to a railway crossing,
you stop, look and...
Stall.
This is the opposite
of talk...
Peace.
Sweet, sweet peace.
No, no, but --
This is peaceful, okay?
You're in the forest.
You're standing by a tree
and you're doing something.
It rhymes with glisten.
Yeah, I can't say that
on television, it's --
Almost out of
time here, Red.
Yeah, okay, okay.
Dalton, when your daughter
wears her headphones,
what's she doing?
Oh, that's easy, trying
not to listen to me.
That's it!
RED: How many fish
have we caught?
GLEN: You mean all
of us all together?
A grand total including
what we released?
Yeah.
None.
And how many bites
have we had?
None, zero,
zilch, nada.
You know why?
Because there are
no fish in this lake.
Sorry, there's
Chemical Vat.
You don't know
that, Harold.
Yes, yes I do,
Uncle Red.
Fish cannot swim under
floating garbage.
This lake has the same
p.h. as a truck battery.
We've been fishing this lake
our whole lives, Harold.
Yes, and you've
throwing stoves
and outboard motors
and snowmobiles
in this lake all
your lives too.
The fish would
have to evolve
into titanium rhinos
to survive what
you've done to them.
RED: That's just
not right, Harold.
We still catch fish here
don't we, Glen?
GLEN: Yeah, yeah.
Buster Hadfield
caught something
here just a couple
of weeks ago.
Yes, he fell in
and caught diphtheria.
There are no fish
in this lake.
There are fish
here, Harold.
You know what you do?
You go get fish
in another lake
and them dip them
in here to preserve them.
Oh yeah?
Well, what do you think
about this, Harold, eh?
See what happens when you
have skills and use
the right bait?
Now, do you want
to throw that back,
or do you want to try
and clean it?
It's a fish.
You know, I think it was
Winston Churchill who said
"Never stand when
you can sit,
"Never sit when
you can lie down
"and never lie down
without the remote."
Sounds like
my kind of guy,
but I'm guessing he never
had to cut his own lawn.
What with him being King
of Ireland or whatever it was.
So this time I'm going to
show you how you can
cut your lawn
without using
any energy...
well, not any
of your own energy.
First think
you want to do,
get yourself one of these
self-propelled electric
lawn mowers.
I got this from Mike.
He's good for getting
stuff cheap
if you don't ask
too many questions.
You know what they say...
A good fence makes
a good neighbour.
Now, the electric units are
not as good as the gas jobs
but they're quieter.
And I find it hard
to sleep in the same yard
as an unmanned, self-propelled
gasoline mower.
Now, there's a bit of
complicated math involved
with this project.
The lawn mower's going to
wind around the wheel rim
and move itself
across the lawn.
But to prevent it
from missing a spot,
the circumference
of the wheel rim
has to be the same as
the width of the lawn mower.
The actual formula,
I believe,
is 2 pi R = coupe de grasse.
Perfect.
To calculate pi, just get
yourself a pie plate.
Okay, here's
the easy part.
Just plug the lawn mower
into the extension cord
and then tie it off
to the front of the mower.
The first time you
cut the lawn, now,
you'll have a few obstacles
you might have to get through,
So mount an
electric chain saw
on the front of the unit
and you want to plug
that in too.
Then you just
turn them both on,
and you're good to go.
Might want to move
the dog inside first.
Okay, this pretty much
looks like the centre
of the yard to me.
Even if it isn't,
it will be.
Just wind the extension
around the rim,
and then
go plug her in.
You want to keep the cord
good and high though;
otherwise, your automatic
lawn mower will have
the same history
as America...
just one revolution.
Other than that,
it's just like a computer,
plug and play.
Sure hope
it doesn't crash.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I want to talk
to you older guys
who've been married for
as long as you can remember --
or are allowed
to remember.
You know, it never
hurts to surprise your
significant other,
maybe buy her something
or make her something.
I suggest
buy her something.
Your wife knows how good
a handyman you are.
Heck, she's the one who
drives you to the hospital.
So buy her something.
In fact,
buy her flowers.
Now, most men think
flowers are dumb,
but get this:
women don't.
Bernice actually
likes flowers.
A bunch of flowers to her
is like, I don't know,
a '68 orange Dodge Charger
with a racing cam
and a Hurst shifter.
So I buy
Bernice flowers.
Most guys don't
think that way.
They get their sweethearts
something they'd like
themselves.
You ladies who receive
belt sanders for Christmas
know what
I'm talking about.
So if you want to make
your partner happy,
give her something
she may actually want
and she may give you
something you actually want.
Something that used to
happen in the back seat
of that '68 Charger.
Remember,
I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Have your septics
pumped our regularly.
An ounce of prevention...
is worth a ton of manure.
I'll be right with you!
Well, uh,
as you can see,
getting the lodge
cleaned up a little,
getting ready for the tourist
board ratings inspection.
We looked into getting
a cleaning la -- person.
But we found it
demeaning... for us.
We couldn't come up
with 150 bucks.
Uncle Red?
Wow!
You're really
cleaning up in here.
Have you cleaned up
your room, Harold,
because if the tourist
board sees the Ken and
Barbie dolls,
they'll rate us
as a day-care centre.
Those are Star Wars
collectible figurines,
thank you very much.
And my room is always
neat and tidy.
Well, that's because
nothing ever happens
in it.
Okay, Red.
Got the basement
all cleaned up.
Okay.
Oh, by the way,
can we get rid of
all these animal heads?
They are just
impossible to dust.
We can talk about it.
Say, you know what,
you look good.
Is that a new shirt?
No, you know,
I just washed it
but I'm using a new
fabric softener,
and I think it really
makes a difference.
Yeah, you know what,
it's real nice.
It really brings out
the colour in your eyes.
Would you two
like to be alone?
You know, you started
this, Harold.
No, no, no, no, no.
I just wanted the lodge
to have a better tourist
rating so we attract
better tourists.
We want to beat
Caribou Lodge!
Caribou Lodge
is not the point!
If we all get
good ratings
then there's enough
business for everybody.
Well, we know that,
Harold.
It just kind of fosters
the competitive spirit
if we can beat the crap
out of those morons.
No, it's not about that!
It has nothing to do with us
beating Caribou Lodge.
There is no competition.
Okay.
I'm serious, guys,
there is no competition.
That's a good one.
Besides, Caribou Lodge
has put in a hot tub.
Holy --
They can't do that!
It's not
a competition.
RED: We were going to have a
sleepout just under the stars.
The sky was looking
a little rough there.
Heard some thunder and
it looked like maybe
she might rain.
So Mike had the idea
of maybe putting up
some kind of a tarp.
He had a small tarp in --
What I thought was
a small tarp in his bag.
It's funny how
these things --
You know, as you unfold
them you realize
how huge something
like that --
And it seemed a little
heavier than a normal tarp.
Of course, that's because
there was a fry pan stuck
in the middle.
We got that out of there
and then Mike just tied up
the one corner to the tree.
I wouldn't --
Look out --
So later that day,
we got Mike up higher
in the tree
standing on Winston's
shoulders
who was unfortunately
standing on my shoulders.
You know, we did that okay
leaning against the tree,
but when it came
time to move
it was very hard to balance
and these guys are not --
It's not Cirque de Soleil
we got here, you know.
But anyway we did
get the tarp up,
and we got under it
in our sleeping bags.
She was raining down
there pretty good,
but it was just an
overnight thing.
By the next morning,
beautiful day, beautiful day
and we are dry as a bone
but we are looking up
and thinking, oh boy.
We collected some
rainwater overnight
and a certain amount of debris
that comes with any
kind of a rain.
So we're trying -- Mike said,
"oh no, come on back."
He's got an idea.
This is how you use
what nature gives you.
He takes out his knife
and he drops in and --
Not too sharp
there, Mike.
Ah.
So Mike's not too
sharp either.
What he's doing is making
a little camp shower.
So he's showering away,
and then the water
stopped there.
Something's
plugging it, Mike.
Oh, it's a pine cone.
Takes that out
and away he goes again.
Then she plugs up again
and this time it's a pop can
and Mike's had enough.
So Winston steps up
and his hat was dirty.
So he washed that
and we thought --
Oh.
There's a very large snake
indigenous to the area.
We get back to the campfire
and the water stops again.
Winston thinks it's like
a twig or something,
but of course
it's not really a twig,
it's the actual snake.
Then we hear him yell.
I'm not sure how
this part happened.
You might want to take the
kids out of the room for
this next part.
Finally, we think
we got it
'cause he says,
"okay, it's dead."
Good.
We're good.
This is not something
I like to do.
No, definitely
not but --
Now, Mike's been in prison,
so no problem.
And apparently it wasn't
dead it was just stunned.
And of course,
so was Mike.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Every man knows finding
evidence of a leak
on your garage floor
is a bad sign.
Especially if you
don't own a car.
Now, I can't help you
with that problem,
but if you do have a car that
leaks oil like mine does,
here's what you do.
Get yourself a
kitty litter box
and grab your old
high school gym bag.
Whoa... been awhile.
Okay, you reach
in there...
Rubber glove might
have been a thought.
Grab one of your old,
sweaty gym socks.
I sure hope
that's a sock.
I sure hope this is
my gym bag.
Okay, you stand the sock
straight up in the middle
of the kitty litter
and then you slide
the whole unit
under the leaky car.
The kitty litter would
probably work better
if this was a jaguar.
And there you have it.
Not only have you solved
your leaking problem,
you've also made your
very own scented candle.
That'll burn for months,
remember Kuwait?
[ INHALES ]
Smells like
the Indy 500.
Your garage smells good,
and you've got yourself
a dandy nightlight.
[ CAT MEOWS ]
Well, we're done.
We've got the lodge
looking mighty fine.
We had the inspection
and the new tourist
brochure came out today.
And the winner is...
I always wanted to say that.
I always wanted to say it.
"The winner is..."
and I've said it today.
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey!
Were you raised
in a barn?
Oh, sorry.
Wow, it looks great!
You know what,
it doesn't matter
what it says in
this brochure.
You did an excellent job
cleaning up the lobby
and everything else.
Yeah,
it was nothing.
It doesn't matter.
How'd we do anyway?
Okay, let's see.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Ashley's Place.
Bobby's Bunks.
Cathy's Cabin.
Harold, go to "P".
I already went.
No, in the brochure.
Oh, oh, okay.
For a second,
I thought --
I know.
Possum Lodge,
here we go!
Okay, okay.
Two stars,
that's not bad!
Way to go!
Not bad?!
Two stars after
we kill ourselves?
How'd Caribou
Lodge do?
That's really
not important.
No, I need to know!
How did Caribou Lodge do?
I need to know!
Okay, all right.
There's Emma's Eats.
Yeah.
Dew Drop Inn.
That's a nice place,
Yeah.
Oh, Caribou Lodge,
here we are.
One star?
Yeah baby!
How'd we beat them!?
I have no idea, Harold.
I don't know.
"Nice place but watch out
for the stuffed animal heads
"floating in the hot tub."
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Oh, there's the
meeting, Harold.
Away you go, away you go.
Away you go.
I'll be down
in a minute.
I'm just going to get
this place back to normal.
So if my wife is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting,
and I learned
a lot this week.
Oh sure, it's satisfying
to work and improve yourself,
but it's more satisfying
to point out somebody worse.
Which is how I stole you
from your boyfriend.
And to the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
Oh behalf of myself
and Harold
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge.
Keep your stick
on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Everybody!
C'mon guys, sit down.
Take a seat.
Find a seat, everybody.
Have a seat.
C'mon guys, sit down.
The meeting's coming to order.
All rise.
Quando Omni Flunkus Moritati.
RED: Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the Man's Prayer.
I'm a man,
but I can change,
if I have to...
I guess.
All right, men.
As you know, we've got
a new policy here
trying to clean up
the lodge,
so I'm looking for your
permission to order a swiffer.
All those in favour?
Okay, I said,
"order a swiffer"
not "order a stripper."