[bubbling]
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE HE IS,
THE JOLLY GREEN GENT,
THE MAN FROM PLAID,
THE PILLSBURY DOUGH BOY
WITHOUT THE DOUGH, MY UNCLE,
YOUR HERO, RED GREEN!
[applause and cheering]
BIG WEEK AT THE LODGE.
JUNIOR SINGLETON'S BEEN AWAY.
WHEN HE CAME HOME,
THE MILK IN HIS FRIDGE
HAD TURNED LUMPY AND FUZZY.
IT LOOKED LIKE LITTLE EGGPLANTS
DROWNED IN YOGHURT.
MILK SHOULDN'T GO BAD
THAT FAST
AS LONG AS THE FRIDGE
IS TURNED ON.
IT WAS TURNED ON --
IT WASN'T PLUGGED IN.
I DON'T THINK JUNIOR
UNDERSTANDS ELECTRICITY.
UNCLE RED,
DIDN'T HE WIRE THE LODGE?
YUP -- IT'S FINE UNLESS
YOU PLUG ANYTHING IN.
RATHER THAN THROW
THE MILK AWAY,
WHICH WOULD BE
A WASTE OF MONEY,
JUNIOR HAS DECIDED
TO MAKE HIS OWN CHEESE.
SO IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
A SHOW WITH CHEESE,
YOU'VE COME TO THE RIGHT PLACE.
[horns honking]
[geese honking]
[quacking]
(Red): BILL GIVES MY VAN
A MILK BATH.
WINSTON BRINGS
SOMETHING SPECIAL
TO THE SHOW-AND-TELL
DEPARTMENT.
THEN HAROLD -- UH, I THINK
HE HAS A MOUSE UP HIS LEG.
I'VE GOT SOME TERMITE DAMAGE
IN THE BARN.
[audience laughing]
I'M READY FOR ANYTHING NOW,
HAROLD.
JUNIOR'S
HOMEMADE CHEESE
GETTING A LITTLE RIPE, IS IT?
THE CHEESE
HAS ATTRACTED AN ANIMAL.
NOW IT'S LIVING INSIDE
THE WALLS OF JUNIOR'S HOUSE.
PROBABLY JUST A MOUSE.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
BUT, I BETTER TAKE THIS --
THERE MIGHT BE TWO OF THEM.
YOU'RE AFRAID OF A MOUSE,
A LITTLE, WEE, TINY MOUSE.
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S
A MOUNTAIN LION OR ANYTHING.
I'D PREFER A MOUNTAIN LION.
BIGGER IS BETTER --
THE SIZE OF THE ANIMAL
IS INVERSELY PROPORTIONAL
TO THE AMOUNT OF FEAR.
GUYS THAT WILL STARE DOWN
A BEAR,
GO NUTS WHEN THEY SEE
A THREE-INCH SPIDER.
I WONDER WHY? --
OH, I KNOW!
I BETCHA I KNOW WHY!
A BEAR CAN'T CRAWL INTO YOUR
UNDERWEAR WHEN YOU'RE SLEEPING.
[laughing and applause]
OH YEAH? --
TELL THAT TO MOOSE THOMPSON.
OH YEAH!
THAT WAS
FUNNY.
THAT WAS A BIG FELLA.
YOU'RE DRESSED LIKE
THE TERMINATOR
TO TAKE ON A MOUSE? --
HOW BIG IS IT?
OR SHOULD I SAY
HOW LITTLE IS IT?
IT'S ABOUT THE SAME SIZE
AT THAT ONE ON YOUR PANT LEG.
GET IT OFF!
(Red): WITH JUNIOR MAKING
THE HOMEMADE CHEESE,
BILL THOUGHT HE'D SHOW YOU
HOW TO MAKE CHEESE,
KIND OF AN EDUCATIONAL SEGMENT
ON THE SHOW THIS WEEK.
"STEP ONE: PURE MILK."
START WITH PURE MILK.
AND, TO A LOT OF THE KIDS
AT HOME, MAYBE,
OR SOME OF THE OLDER KIDS --
NO, YOU GOT THAT...
OK, START AGAIN.
A LOT OF EDUCATIONAL SHOWS
SHOW YOU
WHEN THINGS GO PERFECTLY.
THAT'S NOT THE WAY LIFE GOES.
A LOT OF TIMES
THINGS GO BADLY,
IT'S GOOD TO SEE
WHEN YOU MEET AN OBSTACLE...
WOULD YOU JUST...
ALL RIGHT, THAT WOULD BE
GOING IN THAT PAIL,
WOULD IT NOT?
HMM.
UH, SO THE IDEA IS
YOU GET THE MILK INTO THE PAIL.
ALWAYS HAVE EXTRA BAGS.
YOU CAN USE HEAT.
BILL, NO, NO, NO.
YOU'RE GONNA SCALD THE MILK.
THIS IS GOOD THOUGH.
TRIAL AND ERROR
IS A BIG PART OF EDUC--
WHAT'S GOING ON?
ALL RIGHT,
NOW THOSE ARE OPEN.
NOW WHAT?
OK, PLAN "B".
THIS IS STILL PURE MILK.
THESE ARE THE CARTONS.
THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
THE PLASTIC, FOR SOME KIDS,
MAYBE THEY'RE A BIT
HARD TO OPEN.
THESE HAVE GOT THE POUR SPOUT
UNIT ON THERE.
WE MAY NOT HAVE TIME
TO ACTUALLY MAKE THE CHEESE
DURING THIS SEGMENT.
WE'LL COME BACK LATER
AND MAKE THE CHEESE.
YOU GET THE MILK IN THERE.
WE'LL COME BACK -- OH.
YOUR WIFE'S RELATIVES
ARE COMING OVER AT 9:30.
YOU'D LIKE IT TO BE
A SHORT VISIT -- NO PROBLEM.
YAK WITH THEM
FROM 9:30 TO 9:45.
AT 9:45 YOU STOP TALKING,
THEY GET BORED, THEY GO HOME.
10:00, TRY AND GET THE WIFE
TO DO THE SAME THING.
10:15, GET THEM TO DO
THE SAME THING.
10:30, YOU START TURNING
THE LIGHTS OUT.
MAYBE TRY YAWNING REAL LOUD
AND FALL DOWN ON THE FLOOR.
10:45, SNEAK OUT
TO THE DRIVEWAY
AND START THEIR CAR.
11:00, YOU PUT ON YOUR PYJAMAS
AND YELL "GOOD NIGHT"
FROM UPSTAIRS.
DON'T FEEL GUILTY.
WE ALL NEED MORE SLEEP
AS WE GET OLDER.
THEY'RE RELATIVES.
THEY'LL FORGIVE YOU EVENTUALLY.
YOU DON'T OWE ANYBODY.
DARN RIGHT --
NO SENSE STAYING UP LATE
JUST BECAUSE OF SOME STUPID
NEW-YEAR'S-EVE TRADITION.
[applause]
OF ALL THE THINGS
THAT MATTER IN LIFE
NOTHING'S AS IMPORTANT
AS FRIENDS
PALS THAT
YOU CAN LEAN ON
AT THE BEGINNING,
MIDDLE AND END
I SHARE MY PROBLEMS
WITH MY FRIENDS
'CAUSE THAT'S
WHAT FRIENDS ARE FOR
NOW I OWE THEM
SO MUCH MONEY
THEY TEND NOT TO
COME AROUND ANY MORE
WHAT?!
NOTHING, HAROLD.
NOBODY LIKES UNWANTED PESTS
INVADING THEIR HOUSE.
THAT'S WHY THERE ARE SO FEW
FAMILY REUNIONS.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE FOUR-LEGGED KIND,
MICE, RACCOONS, BEARS.
I THOUGHT I'D USE
"HANDYMAN CORNER"
TO DETECT WHETHER OR NOT
YOU HAVE AN ANIMAL PROBLEM.
EVERYBODY'S HOUSE IS DIFFERENT.
YOUR LIVING ROOM MIGHT HAVE
A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT DECOR.
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
THE SIGNS OF ANIMAL
AND INSECT INFESTATION
ARE PRETTY MUCH THE SAME.
TAKE THIS BEAM.
WE'VE GOT SOME TERMITE DAMAGE.
IF WE LET THIS GO,
THIS COULD BECOME A WRITE-OFF.
THE FIRST THING WE WANT TO DO,
WE'VE GOT TO
KILL THE TERMITES.
[coughing]
NOT ONLY KILLED THE TERMITES,
PROBABLY TOOK A HEALTHY BITE
OUT OF THE OZONE.
TAKE A COUPLE OF BOARDS.
STRAP THEM UP
ON EITHER SIDE OF THE BEAM.
THIS WAY YOU RESTORE
ITS ORIGINAL STRENGTH.
[creaking]
THAT WAS MY FAULT.
I SHOULD HAVE DUCT-TAPED THAT.
DOESN'T MATTER THOUGH.
WE'VE GOT LOTS OF OTHER BEAMS
HOLDING THE BUILDING UP.
BUT SOMEBODY SHOULD
KEEP AN EYE ON THAT.
COULD BE DANGEROUS --
NO, IT'S FINE.
YOU MAY HAVE SOME ROOMS
YOU HARDLY EVER USE,
LIKE A FITNESS ROOM,
A GUEST ROOM OR A LIBRARY.
CHECK THEM ONCE IN A WHILE.
COULD HAVE
SOME UNWANTED VISITORS.
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR, EH?
DROPPINGS.
I HATE TO SAY "DROPPINGS"
ON TELEVISION, BUT,
IT'S BETTER THAN
THE OTHER TERMS.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
MOUSE DROPPINGS,
THEY'RE LIKE
THOSE TART-TOPPING THINGS.
RABBIT DROPPINGS ARE MORE LIKE
THE CHOCOLATE-COVERED RAISIN.
RACCOON DROPPINGS,
THAT'S A BIGGER CANDY BAR YET.
IF YOU FIND ENOUGH DROPPINGS,
IT WILL CURE YOUR SWEET TOOTH.
OH MY GOSH.
ALL RIGHT.
UH...
QUITE A QUANTITY OF HER THERE.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'VE HAD
A HERD OF SHETLAND PONIES
UP IN THIS AREA.
ANYWAY, IF YOU DO FIND
DROPPINGS IN YOUR HOUSE,
THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD SIGN
THAT THEY'RE
SNEAKING IN SOMEWHERE.
YOU MUST HAVE SOME HOLE
SOMEWHERE.
IF I DIDN'T KNOW BETTER,
I'D SAY WE HAD
A WALL MISSING HERE.
CHECK THE OUTSIDE OF YOUR HOME
FOR HOLES
ANIMALS COULD BE GETTING IN.
THIS MORTAR HAS FALLEN AWAY
FROM THESE STONES.
THAT HOLE'S BIG ENOUGH
FOR A MOUSE OR BAT,
EVEN A RACCOON
IF THEY'RE MOVING FAST ENOUGH,
LIKE THEY BOUNCED OFF
THE FENDER OF
A SPEEDING VEHICLE.
SOME OF THIS IS SURFACE WEAR.
DOESN'T GO THROUGH.
FIND OUT IF THE HOLE
GOES THROUGH.
GET A BIT OF WATER.
POUR THAT IN THERE.
IF YOU GET WATER
SHOWING UP IN YOUR BASEMENT
THAT WASN'T THERE
BEFORE YOU DID THE TEST,
WELL, THEN YOU'VE GOT
A PROBLEM.
CHECK YOUR WHOLE HOUSE
FOR ANY KIND OF CRACK,
EVEN THE SMALLEST HOLE
WHERE ANIMALS COULD GET IN.
DO THAT UNTIL
YOU RUN OUT OF WATER
OR YOU GET BORED
OUT OF YOUR MIND.
IF YOU'VE GOT ANIMALS,
YOU'RE BETTER TO DEAL
WITH THEM RIGHT AWAY
THAN TO LET HER GO
TO THE POINT WHERE
THEY START FIGHTING YOU
FOR USE OF THE BATHROOM.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OF COURSE, A FIRE IS A GOOD WAY
OF GETTING RID OF MICE.
I'D ONLY USE THAT
AS A LAST RESORT.
AND YOU WANT TO WAIT
TILL THE WATER DRIES.
[whistling nonchalantly]
STAY TUNED FOR MORE ADVICE
FROM DALTON AND I.
SOON YOU'LL FIND YOURSELF
GOING ON AND ON
ABOUT EVERY TOPIC
UNDER THE SUN.
YOU'RE GOING TO WONDER
"WHY AM I SUDDENLY
'THE ENCYCLOPEDIA BRITANNICA'
"IN SHORTS AND A T-SHIRT?
"AND WHY THIS OVERWHELMING URGE
TO TELL ANYONE WITH EARS?"
WELL, YOU'RE
A MIDDLE-AGED MAN NOW,
AND MIDDLE-AGED MEN
KNOW EVERYTHING.
OH YEAH.
MIDDLE-AGED MEN KNOW
THE BEST ROUTE ON ANY HIGHWAY
FROM ANYPLACE TO ANOTHER PLACE.
WE KNOW HOW TO FIX STUFF.
WE KNOW HOW TO CUT THE LAWN
PROPERLY.
WE KNOW EVERYTHING.
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO KEEP
THIS KNOWLEDGE TO YOURSELF.
I KNOW THAT YOU KNOW
YOUR NEIGHBOUR'S PLANTING
THAT SHRUB THE WRONG WAY.
I, TOO, HAVE SEEN MY WIFE
WALLPAPER THE BEDROOM
THE HARD WAY.
KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT.
WHEN THEY FIND OUT HOW SMART
WE ARE, THEY GET JEALOUS.
I DON'T KNOW WHO SAID
"A LITTLE KNOWLEDGE
IS A DANGEROUS THING."
I'M GUESSING IT WAS
A MIDDLE-AGED MAN.
WHATEVER YOU KNOW,
AND I KNOW IT'S A LOT,
KEEP IT UNDER YOUR HAT
AND YOU'LL KEEP YOUR FRIENDS.
BELIEVE ME -- I KNOW.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[applause and cheering]
WELCOME TO "THE EXPERTS"
PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THIS WEEK WE HAVE
TWO EXPERTS,
MY UNCLE RED,
AND MR. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD.
[applause and cheering]
THE LETTER GOES: "DEAR EXPERTS,
"MY WIFE SAYS
SHE WANTS A FACE-LIFT,
"BUT I THINK SHE LOOKS
JUST GREAT THE WAY SHE IS.
"HOW CAN I CONVINCE HER
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL?"
FIRST, YOU WANT TO
IS AVOID CERTAIN WORDS.
"SAGGY," "WRINKLED,"
"WEATHER-BEATEN".
[laughing]
TALK ABOUT HOW COSMETIC SURGERY
IS A WASTE OF
MEDICAL RESOURCES.
THIS IS MONEY DOCTORS
SHOULD BE SPENDING ON
THINGS LIKE LIVER TRANSPLANTS,
'CAUSE AS LONG AS YOU CAN KEEP
SOCKING BACK THE BOOZE,
YOU WON'T CARE
WHAT YOUR WIFE LOOKS LIKE.
[laughing]
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT
SELF-HELP GURU AND
KING OF THE INFOMERCIALS,
ANTHONY ANTHONY, SAYS.
HE SAYS WHATEVER
PEOPLE WANT TO HEAR.
ANTHONY SAYS
IF YOU LOOK AFTER THE SURFACE,
THE CENTRE
WILL LOOK AFTER ITSELF.
YEAH, ANTHONY ANTHONY
HAS ALWAYS SAID YOU ONLY FEEL
AS GOOD AS YOU LOOK.
IF THAT WAS TRUE,
THE GUYS AT THE LODGE
WOULD BE ALL DEAD.
I THINK YOU'LL HAVE TO
COME TO GRIPS WITH THE FACT
THAT PEOPLE JUDGE YOU
BY YOUR APPEARANCE.
TAKE ME --
IF IT WEREN'T FOR
MY GREAT LOOKS,
WOULD I BE WHO I AM TODAY?
THE KING OF THE SEPTICS?
EXACTLY!
HIT THE NAIL RIGHT ON THE HEAD.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE
WHAT THESE PEOPLE CAN DO.
THEY'VE GOT THAT THING,
UH, HIPPOSUCTION.
[laughing]
I MEAN,
THEY CAN EVEN GIVE YOU
A FANNY TRANSPLANT.
WORK THE PROBLEM FROM BOTH ENDS.
I'VE HAD THE FACE-LIFT,
THE TUMMY TUCK,
THE TUSHY IMPLANTS.
TUSHY IMPLANTS?
OH YEAH, CHECK THIS OUT.
GO AHEAD, RED,
FEEL THE QUALITY.
THANKS ANYWAY, WINSTON.
I'M SURE YOU'VE GOT
THE BEST SEAT IN THE HOUSE.
[laughing]
HAROLD?
OH,
OH-HO-HO.
ALL RIGHT, NO PROBLEM.
SUIT YOURSELVES.
I DISAGREE WITH
COSMETIC SURGERY.
PEOPLE REALIZE
THAT BEAUTY IS ONLY SKIN DEEP.
YOU HONESTLY BELIEVE THAT,
HAROLD?
HE'S COUNTING ON IT.
[applause]
OH, MAN.
I'LL TELL YOU,
THAT WAS A LIFE EXPERIENCE.
I HOPE YOU
DIDN'T KILL THAT MOUSE.
WE SURE
DID.
AW, THAT POOR THING WITH
LITTLE EYES AND NOSE
AND LITTLE EARS
AND THE CURLY TAIL?
NO -- SORRY, HAROLD,
I THOUGHT YOU SAID "HOUSE."
[laughing]
I GUESS WE WERE NERVOUS.
NOBODY WANTED TO GO INSIDE.
WE THOUGHT
WE'D SCARE THE MOUSE OUT
BY THROWING SHOVELS
AND GARBAGE CANS
AGAINST THE SIDE OF THE PLACE.
THAT DIDN'T WORK.
THEN WE THOUGHT WE'D PEEL
THE SIDING OFF
AND FLUSH HIM OUT THAT WAY.
JUNIOR DOESN'T HAVE SIDING.
YOU SHOULD HAVE MENTIONED THAT
A LITTLE EARLIER.
WE HAD THE FRONT EXPOSED.
STINKY PETERSON POINTED OUT
WE WERE AT THE WRONG HOUSE.
[laughing]
WE WERE AT
OLD LADY BENKMAN'S PLACE.
I DON'T CARE IF SHE DID
HAVE A MIGRAINE.
THERE'S NO EXCUSE FOR
THAT KIND OF LANGUAGE.
[laughing and applause]
(Red): ALL RIGHT, WE'RE BACK
MAKING CHEESE WITH BILL.
WE'RE READY FOR STEP 2 OF,
I THINK THERE'S 4.
THERE'S MORE THAN TWO, ANYWAY.
SO NOW HE'S SET TO PUT
THE VINEGAR --
THE SIGN SAID "ED RENNET" --
YOU READ IT.
HE PUT EXACTLY ONE CUP
OF VINEGAR --
HE'S GOT THE MILK
ALREADY IN THE PAIL.
APPARENTLY WHEN YOU ADD
THE ONE CUP OF VINEGAR
TO THE TWO QUARTS,
OR FOUR QUARTS -- I FORGET.
THAT IS THE RIGHT KIND OF
CHEMICAL PROPORTION
THAT GIVES YOU
EXACTLY THE MIX
THAT WILL EVENTUALLY
TURN INTO CHEESE.
[hissing and boiling]
THERE'S PROBABLY A CUP
IN THERE.
YOU CAN HEAR
THE CHEMICAL REACTION.
BOY, THAT SMELLED REAL SPECIAL.
HE PULLS IT OUT
AND IT'S FORMED KIND OF --
THESE ARE THE CURDS.
THEY LOOK LIKE CURDS,
DO T THEY?
WHAT WE GOT TO DO
WITH THAT IS...
BASICALLY YOU HAVE
CHEESE-TYPE THINGS.
YOU HAVE TO, OK,
"DRAIN EXCESS LIQUID (WHEY)"
WHY? -- WELL, BECAUSE
YOU NEED THAT OUT OF THERE.
SO, BILL HAS THIS NIGHTIE
IN HIS POCKET FOR SOME REASON.
HE SPREADS THAT OUT
ON THE TABLE.
AND, UH, THEN WE PUT
THE "WHY" IN THERE
ON THE WHERE,
AND WHEN WOULD BE NOW, AND NOW
HE TIES THAT IN A KNOT.
THE CHEESE PORTIONS ARE SOLID,
BUT THE UNCHEESE --
THE NON-CHEESE AREAS
ARE LIQUID.
SO YOU'VE GOT TO GET
THE NON-CHEESE PARTICLES,
ANYTHING THAT'S NOT CHEESE
YOU WANT OUT OF THERE
SO THAT YOU'RE LEFT WITH
JUST THE CHEESE.
BUT THERE'S QUITE A BIT IN THIS
THAT'S NOT CHEESE STILL.
THERE IS A FAIR BIT OF CHEESE.
IT'S THE NON-CHEESE AREA
THAT WE'RE WORKING ON.
BILL'S USING THE BOARDS.
THAT'S A CHEESE BOARD,
I GUESS YOU'D CALL THAT.
BILL HAS AN IDEA,
WHICH IS A SIGN OF
"DANGER IS APPROACHING
"SO STEP BACK."
AH, THIS IS THE BOBCAT
CHEESE-SQUASHING TECHNIQUE.
AND, UH, HE'S GETTING
THE LIQUID OUT OF THE CHEESE.
STAY TUNED.
WE'LL EVENTUALLY FINISH THIS.
MAN.
STAY TUNED FOR HAROLD MAKING
ANOTHER FASHION STATEMENT.
THERE'S ONE THING THAT MICE DO
THAT NO OTHER ANIMAL CAN DO.
THAT IS MAKE OTHER MICE.
BOY, ARE THEY GOOD AT IT.
SEEMS LIKE EVERY HOUR
THERE'S ANOTHER 100 MICE
SCURRYING AROUND
JUNIOR'S PLACE.
HAROLD WENT OVER
TO SEE WHAT HE COULD DO.
PROBABLY TRY AND REASON
WITH THE MICE.
[panting]
HOW DID GO?
GOOD, FINE, FINE, GOOD.
THERE'S A LOT OF MICE
OVER THERE, UNCLE RED!
THEY HAVE A BORING LIFE --
THEY EAT AND SLEEP.
THEY PROCREATE
JUST TO PASS THE TIME.
THAT MUST BE QUITE A LIFE, EH?
OH,
FOR...
[laughing]
(Red): MEANWHILE,
BACK AT THE CHEESE PROJECT,
WE'RE STILL TRYING TO SQUEEZE
ALL THE LAST BITS
OF NON-CHEESE --
I PRONOUNCED THAT AS "WHY,"
BUT IT'S "WHEY."
AND WHAT YOU WANT IS CHEESE
WITH NO WHEY.
IT LOOKS LIKE NO WAY TO ME.
WE'RE TRYING EVERYTHING.
THIS IS KIND OF A LESSON
FOR YOU KIDS
THAT MAKING CHEESE
IS KIND OF LIKE LIFE.
THE LONGER YOU WORK AT IT,
THE RIPER IT GETS.
WE'RE GOING TO INTRODUCE
THE CENTRIFUGAL -- WAIT A SEC.
BILL, I'D RATHER BE THE --
EXCUSE ME -- THANK YOU.
I WOULD RATHER BE THE SPINNER
THAN THE SPINEE.
I LIKE TO BE IN
THE CENTRE OF MY UNIVERSE,
PARTICULARLY WHEN
THERE'S CHEESE INVOLVED.
BILL IS MORE OF A SPECTATOR.
LOOK OUT, BILL.
OH, I'M SORRY.
ANYWAY, WE GOT ALL THE WATER
OUT OF THE CHEESE.
LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S PURE CHEESE.
THAT'S HEAD CHEESE.
OH, DON'T EAT THAT.
YOU'LL SPOIL YOUR DINNER.
OOO.
IT'S "MALE CALL".
THAT'S LOUD.
OK.
THE FIRST LETTER ON
"MALE CALL" GOES AS FOLLOWS.
IT'S A LETTER FROM BEB
IN NOW JORSOY.
WHAT?
I THINK THAT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
BOB IN NEW JERSEY.
BOB'S TYPEWRITER IS DOING
AN "O" AND "E" BACKWARDS.
HA.
OK, UH... "DEAR ROD,
"MY TYPOWRITOR
IS WERKING PREPORLY.
"THO 'O' AND 'E' ARO ROVORSOD."
I THINK HE MEANS
THE "O" AND "E"
ARE REVERSED.
"I ROALLY LIKO
"'THO ROD GROON SHEW'.
"IT'S LETS EF FUN
FER OVORYENO."
OVORYENO?
EVERYONE, EVERYONE.
"O" AND "E" ARE REVERSOD --
REVERSED.
THEY'RE REVERSED.
[laughing]
"MY WIFO, ELIVO..."
OH, THAT'S HIS WIFE, OLIVE.
"MY WIFO, ELIVO, AND I ONJEY
ALL THO CRAZY HIJINKS
"AND GEEFY JEKOS."
[laughing]
"AND I MUST SAY
THAT FUNNY NUTBAR BILL
"CRACKS UP
MY NINO-YOAR-ELD SEN, STOVO,
"WITH HIS ZANY ANTICS
AND FEELISH PLETS.
"ANYWAY, KOOP UP THE GEED WERK.
"WO THINK IT'S THE BOST NOW
"T.V. PREGRAMMO
SINCE 'BAYWATCH'".
[laughing]
"AND MUCH BOTTOR THAN
WATCHING SPERTS."
"BASICALLY,
"IT'S A TEUR DO FERCO."
TEUR DO FERCO?
TOUR DE FORCE.
EXCELLENT.
I MEAN "OXCOLLONT."
[laughing]
"LENG LIVO
'THO ROD GROON SHEW'.
"BOST WISHOS, BEB AND ELIVO."
WELL, BEB AND ELIVO,
THANKS FOR WRITING.
KOOP WATCHING.
WO LEVO YEUR CARDS AND LOTTORS
AND KOOP YEUR STICK
EN THO ICO.
WHAT'S
THAT?
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
OH, COOL.
I MEAN,
CEEL.
THE MICE ARE GONE?
YEAH, IT'S SAFE, HAROLD.
AH, GOOD.
I GOT TO GIVE JUNIOR CREDIT.
THROUGHOUT THE MOUSE PROBLEM,
HE WORKED ON
PERFECTING HIS CHEESE,
ADJUSTING THE FLAVOUR,
LOWERING THE FLASHPOINT.
[laughing]
THE MORE
HE WORKED ON THE CHEESE,
THE LESS THE MICE
BECAME INTERESTED IN IT.
MAYBE IT WASN'T CHEESE
ANY MORE.
ONLY TWO THINGS SMELL THAT BAD.
WE DECIDED TO
KEEP CALLING IT CHEESE.
[laughing]
JUNIOR NOTICED THE MICE WEREN'T
COMING INTO THE KITCHEN,
SO HE SPREAD THE CHEESE
AROUND OTHER ROOMS,
AND DROVE THE MICE OUT.
HE THREW IT ON THE PORCH.
IT WAS CARRIED OFF
BY BUZZARDS.
THAT'S AN EXCELLENT SOLUTION.
NO -- HE'S BEEN CHARGED
WITH BUZZARD ABUSE.
[squealing]
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
THIS REMINDS ME THAT
A MARRIAGE
IS LIKE A QUALITY CHEESE.
THE OLDER IT GETS,
THE SHARPER IT IS
AS LONG AS YOU KEEP
THE FRIDGE PLUGGED IN.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF, HAROLD,
AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause and whistling]
[possum squeal]
(Harold): OK, HE'S HERE,
HE'S HERE.
STAND UP, STAND UP.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN, GUYS.
(Harold): THE POSSUM LODGE
ROAD CREW IS PUTTING UP SIGNS.
THEY SAID THEY DON'T MIND
YOU SHOOTING AT THEM.
JUST WAIT TILL THEY'RE
BACK IN THE TRUCK.