Bernice thought
it would be nice
to have a concrete bench
somewhere in our yard.
Not here, you know,
but somewhere.
So now she's decided she
wants it on the other
side of the house.
That's where
the sun is.
I'm not quite sure how
sunlight affects concrete.
Maybe if we water it,
it'll grow into a building.
So now my challenge
is to find a way to move it
without spending money or
straining everything
I care about.
Now, I could ask
my friends to help,
but they're going
to want a payback someday.
So instead I'm just going
to use my extension ladder
and this power RV jack.
These things go up and down
at a moment's notice.
Those were the
good ol' days.
I mounted the control
for the power jack inside
so I can raise and lower
the back end of the car,
kind of a high-jacking.
I attached my extension
ladder to the top of the car
with the adjusting rope
hanging down through
the sunroof.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I've been called
to the bench.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ AUDIENCE CHEERING ]
Okay.
Easy now.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate it.
Big, big, big week
up at the lodge this week.
They're having
a folk art convention
down at the
community centre.
See this?
This is called folk art.
Actually, this is
a chunk of wood
that fell out of a
tree into a lake somewhere,
got bashed around by the waves
and got washed up on shore.
It was picked up by some
old hippy on his way home
from a Joan Baez concert.
He throws 29 cents worth
of urethane on it,
sells it at the
flea market for $79.95.
So I'm thinking,
hey, this is a rip-off,
and we're not in on it!
Uncle Red!
I found
this in my bed
and now my bed is all
soaking wet.
Oh, sure, blame it
on the driftwood.
Come on, my room stinks
now like the bilge
in Stinky
Peterson's boat.
Oh, sure, blame it
on the driftwood.
That's art, Harold.
This is not art.
I know art.
I got a B+ is art.
This is not art.
This is a piece
of grungy firewood.
And judging by
it's oily coating,
I'd judge it's out
of Possum Lake.
Yes, all right,
fine.
But once we dry out
and varnish it, Harold,
it's going to be worth
a small fortune
at the
Folk Art Convention.
Well, I agree with
the small part.
See this, Harold?
People pay real money
for crap like this.
Yeah, well that's a
nice piece of driftwood.
This is a chunk
off of somebody's dock.
You know, Harold,
if everybody
had your attitude
there'd by
no singing fish,
no black
velvet paintings,
no "I'm with stupid"
T-shirts.
Is that the kind of world
you want to live in?
Oh, yes.
Just take the driftwood
to your room and let
it dry, will you?
What is the problem
with you?
You know, I'm not putting
it back in my room.
I'm just going to leave it
right here in the stove.
Possum Lake water
doesn't dry very easily.
[ APPLAUSE ]
It's time for the
Possum Lodge word game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Tonight's winner receives
a one-year,
unlimited movie
movie rental pass
from Vern's Video Castle.
Some conditions apply...
"Winner must be over 18.
"Rentals are for
two hours only.
"No weekend or
holiday rentals.
"Excludes new releases,
recent releases
"or anything
with Michael Caine."
All right, Ed,
cover your ears.
Red, you've got 30 seconds
to get Ed Frid to say
this word...
All right, Winston.
And go!
Okay, Ed,
if your TV reception
is real bad,
you can't see what's
going on, it's...
'Cause I don't pay
for the dirty movies.
Okay, no, um.
Say you don't shave
for a couple of days,
then you look...
Incredibly macho.
No.
All right, take
a look at my beard.
You would say
it's a little...
Gay?
Uh...
all right, no.
No.
Okay, you have a kitten.
A kitten
is warm and...
Dangerous.
No, I'm talking about any
animal with soft fur is...
Dangerous.
Ed, not all animals
are dangerous.
Sure, Red.
What about
a chipmunk?
Almost out of
time here, Red.
Okay, okay, I know.
Something "wuzzy"
was a bear, okay?
Come on, it was
a nursery rhyme.
I can't remember
that far back.
Ever since the raccoon in
the sleeping bag incident,
you know, my memories
of childhood have been
pretty fuzzy.
There we go!
Where has
all the fun gone?
all the joy gone?
Where have all
the flowers gone?
I don't know.
What I know is that
all the hobbies have gone
to Harold's Hobby House,
where we examine the man
behind the hobby.
In tonight's case,
the man below the hobby --
would you mind
standing up, Glen?
It never ends with you,
does it, Harold?
Today's guest
is Mr. Glen Braxton,
of the Braxton Marina,
which -- well, that is
when it's open of course,
which I believe is every
third Tuesday of the month
without a full moon.
That's correct.
Today, I'd like Glen
to explain the connection
between his inner soul
and his hobby.
Glen.
It's a slot car set,
Harold.
Interesting...
But what does a
slot car set say to you?
Well, I don't know, I can't
hear it over that shirt.
I'm just trying
to prove a point
that there's a connection,
a correlation
between a man
and his hobby,
a reflection,
sort of.
Well, not
this hobby, no.
It's an old slot car set
I got when I was a kid.
It goes around and
around in circles,
and it's old
and it's slow
and the circuits
are burned out.
I mean, it's nothing
like me at all.
Of course not, no.
I'm just saying that,
you know, well,
maybe you could just
tell us a bit about
the cars.
Maybe their make
and their model.
Okay, well, that's
referred to as
the green one.
That'd be the yellow one,
that one there.
And specifically what
is it that you like
about slot cars?
Oh, well, actually,
I control them both
so, you know,
I never lose,
which is good.
And I like that electrical
smell that you can smell.
Yeah, yeah.
And I like that you
don't have to steer them.
You just let 'em go.
Just let 'em go.
That's it.
The letting go.
What?
Yeah, you like to let
things go, your person.
I don't have a person,
I have a bouvier.
I let her go wherever
it wants, actually.
I have proven
my point.
What?
A man in a rut.
A car in a slot.
A lifetime of
letting things go.
A psychological connection
between a man and his hobby.
Thank you, Glen.
So we're done then?
I'm letting you go.
Okay.
[ APPLAUSE ]
You know, there's a lot
of talk these days
about gas mileage
and engine efficiency
and all that crap.
If you ask me,
the best way to save gas
on a trip is to not go.
But of course,
if you're married,
you have to go.
So what you need is a way
to make trips fun.
Rather than focus
on miles per gallon,
think about
gallons per hour.
'Cause to me, burning a lot
of gas for a few minutes
has got to be the same
as burning a little bit
of gas for a whole hour.
Now, this is
a carburetor.
It controls how much gas
goes into the engine.
We're going to increase
the capacity a little
on this unit.
Okay, when you look
inside a carburetor,
you'll see an
open area here
where the gas and air mix
and there's the reservoir
which is a small tank
with a float in it
that opens a valve
and lets the gas flow.
Does that remind
you of something?
The toilet drain's a
little large for the
intake manifold,
but these toilet gaskets
are pretty flexible.
Made out of beeswax.
They're really easy
to work with...
if you're a bee.
I had to increase the
size of the gas line
to my new porcelain
carburetor.
So I went with
3/4" copper.
My wife always says,
Go with the flow.
I will.
Now, to control
the whole unit,
I ran a piece of wire
from the flush handle
down through the firewall,
hooked it onto the top edge
of my gas pedal.
So if you find
she's idling too fast,
just jiggle the handle.
Pretty sharp looking,
isn't it?
I call it
a kybo charger.
I just hooked up
the fuel pump
and I'm waiting for the
tank to fill up.
Okay, they say the proof
of the pudding is in
the eating.
Maybe that's not
the best analogy.
Hey, wait a minute,
this is a man's car.
So remember, if women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
And they'll
find me gone.
I read in the paper
about a company
whose stock price
just plunged lower
than Pamela
Anderson's neckline.
They may even go bust.
Well, naturally, people are
pretty ticked off
but this spokesman guy said
it was merely a necessary,
temporary market adjustment.
This is called P.R.
If you're a shareholder,
it's called B.S.
Personally,
I call it genius.
All of us middle-aged,
married guys need
a crash course
in this kind
of public relations.
Think about it.
Your wife catches you
asleep instead of
mowing the lawn.
That's not a nap,
that's a personal rejuvenation
efficiency enhancement.
Got nailed eyeing another
woman in the supermarket?
You were merely engaged
in benign comparative
product appraisal.
Used your wife's best
China bowl as an ashtray
at your poker game?
Sounds like value-added
asset re-purposing to me.
So let's all give this P.R.
business some serious thought.
You didn't put the dishwasher
back together wrong,
you restructured it.
You didn't
break the lamp,
you downsized it.
And if you're really
in trouble,
go for the ultimate
public relations ploy...
Honey, I'm an idiot.
No woman can
argue with that.
Remember,
I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
If your septics used to remind
you of
A Field of Dreams
but now it's more
like
Reservoir Dogs,
A River Runs Through It
or I Know What You
Did Last Summer...
call me.
[ CHUCKLING ]
We're close to being ready
for the folk art convention.
This is going
to be huge.
Is that beautiful
or what, huh, huh?
Who wouldn't want
one of these, eh?
And you'll never guess
what it's made out of.
Uncle Red?
How come all the lodge
vehicles are missing
their tires?
Tires are a dime
a dozen, Harold.
We've turned them into
something a little
more valuable.
A big, ugly eraser?
It's a pony, Harold.
It's a pony.
A rubber pony with
100,000 miles on it.
Harold,
this is art.
In fact, it's
steel-belted art.
You know what your
problem is, Harold?
You don't have the class
or sophistication
to appreciate highbrow art.
People love these,
Harold.
You know what they do?
They stick 'em
on their lawn,
and they look like...
A fat lady
bending over?
Now, is this your work,
or was it submitted
by the Group Of Seven?
We're going to mass produce
these, Harold.
I stack up the plywood,
cut them all at once
with the chain saw,
then I take them down to
the day camp and get the
kids to paint them.
They love them,
Harold.
And you know what?
They need to know
about capitalism.
Yeah, I think you need to
know about child labour laws.
C'mon, I cut them in
for a piece of the
action, Harold.
Now, c'mon, the folk art
convention starts in
a few minutes
and I need some help
getting these down there.
I've got 200 ponies.
I got 500 fat ladies.
I hope that's enough.
Oh, I think
you're safe.
RED VOICEOVER:
The boys decided to
have an ATV race.
First prize is 25 gallons
worth of gas,
which went up in
value every minute.
Bill, you're on the wrong
side of the start line.
You might want to do
one of your patented
174-point turns.
Oh, man, oh.
Are you going
to be long?
Okay, and Dalton was
the third participant.
He's on like
a riding mower.
Guys, the race started.
Do you want to get
involved with that?
Of course, they got
the much faster --
It takes them about two
seconds to blow by Dalton.
They get going so fast
they didn't notice
that the track actually
has a turn in it.
On the other hand,
Dalton was well aware
of where he was going,
so he could just
keep poking along.
Get on it, boys.
But we're dealing again
with the powerful machines.
It doesn't take long
to catch up to him,
and they got him right
at the mogul there,
and they hit it good,
maybe a little too good.
Yeah, that's
unfortunate.
And away we go, again.
Now, here again...
I think there's
a left-hand turn --
Guys, it's a
left-hand turn.
Oh boy.
Oh, okay.
That's Bill.
I guess Winston went
right through on his --
yeah, he did,
there he is.
He's back.
And Bill -- oh, oww.
All right, Bill thought
he'd try fencing.
Yeah, there you go.
And this time they're
getting pretty close
to the finish line.
They blow past Dalton
again, no problem.
But then the machine --
I'm getting a little bored
of this at this point.
But their machine's
still acting up,
and Bill can't figure out --
and then Winston looks
and there's the problem,
you're about
out of gas there.
And then Winston starts
doing --
he's actually got
less gas in his.
The thing is, can they
make it to the finish line?
They try humping and bumping
and humping along.
And Bill decided he's going
to try and move the
finish line up.
Well, that's just
not acceptable.
So then, Winston's going
to grab some of first prize
so they can
finish the race,
and then there's
an argument
and Dalton wins
the whole deal.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Isn't it funny how
you can have a document
like a gas bill
or a speeding ticket
or an eviction notice
and it's sitting
right here for weeks,
but as soon as
you go to get it,
it's fallen down
behind the fridge.
And I'm talking about
a real heavy fridge
that's been sitting there
since the delivery guy
brought it,
which is back in the days
when they had delivery guys.
What you need is a way
to roll your fridge
out easily
whenever you need to.
Okay, now sure,
they sell those special
appliance rollers,
but they cost
like ten bucks.
And what is the point
of fixing the fridge
if you can't afford to buy
anything to put into it?
Okay, this gives
me an idea.
Actually lots of ideas.
Okay, let's take
these beer bottles --
no, no, let's empty
no, let's get some
empty beer bottles.
You know, we have some
immature vandals around here
who spend the odd
Saturday night
winging beer bottles
at this vacant building.
Shows you how low people
can sink when they don't
have cable.
Nobody knows exactly
who the guys are
but people have
their suspicions.
Hey, there's my glove.
But no, I mean,
well --
Oh no, I guess I'm
innocent after all.
The good news is
I'm going to use
this old window frame
and a few empties
to free up my fridge.
See what
I've done here?
Hello, dolly.
This baby'll let me
roll out the fridge
anytime I want.
Problem solved.
And what
did it cost me...
nothing.
[ CRASH ]
The word, "pneumonia"
should have a silent
"P" in it.
Your back yard shouldn't.
The folk art convention
ended early.
We had some damage
but luckily it wasn't
a big turnout,
so neither of the
customers was hurt.
It's not over till
the fat lady burns.
You know, those kids
at the day camp
should never have
used oil paint.
Don't blame the kids!
It was your tire ponies!
It wasn't
my tire ponies,
it was the
planning committee.
Our display should have
been a lot closer
to the exit...
and a lot farther
from Edgar's Homemade
Fireworks booth.
And Edgar's Homemade
Fireworks booth
should have been a lot
farther from the
smoking lounge.
Yeah, well, we got the
fireworks under control,
but the tire fire
was another story.
Oh, there was
a lot of damage.
The lady with the
dog-hair mitts,
she lost half
her inventory.
You see those macrame
wall hangings?
They went like pinwheels.
And that lady who had the
375 little candles like that,
you know, like that,
like that?
Now, now...
one big one.
Actually, we would
have lost the whole
community centre
if it wasn't for
my collection of 500
bent over fat ladies.
Yeah, everybody
grabbed them
and tried to smother
the fire with them.
Then once the
fire was out,
they used them to board
up the windows.
I was real
proud of that.
Yeah, and all these women
came in and helped
everybody out.
Well, actually, they saw
all the fat ladies up
against the wall
and thought it was a
Weight Watchers meeting.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Oh, speaking of
meetings...
Yup, you go ahead, Harold.
I'll be right down, okay.
So if my wife is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting
and I've given up
on being an artist.
I'm now going to be
an art collector.
So you come out
into the driveway
and I'll let you see
my "van go."
To the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself,
Harold
and the whole gang
out here at Possum Lodge,
keep your stick
on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Everybody sit down.
Sit down.
Everybody, sit down.
C'mon, sit down,
you guys.
You got to sit down.
All rise.
Quando Omni Flunkus Moritati.
RED: Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the Man's Prayer.
I'm a man,
but I can change,
if I have to...
I guess.
All right, men, I've got
some good news for you.
I know we lost a bundle
on the folk art convention,
but I was talking to people
from the Canada Council,
and I told them that we're not
going to do that anymore,
so they're going to cover
all our expenses.
And as far as
they can remember,
it's the first time they've
ever paid an artist to stop.