♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN
ON TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD'S
GOING TO TELL YOU HOW TO
HURT PEOPLE'S FEELINGS,
BILL'S GOING DOWNHILL SKIING
AND I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO
MAKE A COMPLETE WALL
OUT OF STUDS.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: A POET ONCE WROTE
'A MAN'S REACH SHOULD
EXCEED HIS GRASP FOR
WHAT'S A HEAVEN FOR?'
WELL HERE'S A MAN FROM
THE FARTHEST REACHES OF
THE NORTH ON HIS LAST GRASP
MY UNCLE, YOUR HOST RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
AND THANK YOU HAROLD FOR THAT
LITTLE BIT OF LITERATURE,
IT REMINDED ME OF WHY
I HATED SCHOOL.
>>HAROLD: NO PROBLEMO
HERE'S A LITTLE POETRY
IN MOTION FOR YOU.
>>RED: IT'S BEEN KIND OF
A GOOD NEWS/BAD NEWS WEEK
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
NOW FOR ME IT'S BEEN
GOOD NEWS NOT BAD NEWS
BUT FOR SOME OF THE OTHERS
IT'S BEEN BAD NEWS
NOT GOOD NEWS.
>>HAROLD: EXCUSE ME UNCLE RED
DO YOU WANT TO GET ON WITH
IT BEFORE IT'S OLD NEWS.
>>RED: ALRIGHT FIRST
THE GOOD NEWS,
HAROLD YOU'RE LAID OFF.
>>HAROLD: WHAT? WHY?
WELL THAT'S NOT FAIR!
>>RED: AND NOW THE BAD NEWS
HE'S NOT GOING TO GO QUIETLY.
>>HAROLD: OH OKAY, OKAY
I'M SORRY ABOUT YOUR
BREAKING YOUR RADIO.
>>RED: WHAT WHAT'S
WRONG WITH MY RADIO?
>>HAROLD: NOTHING,
WHY WHO SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT RADIO,
WHAT? WHAT?
>>RED: WELL ACTUALLY
I'M NOT LAYING HAROLD OFF
FOR ANY OF HIS INCOMPETENCE
HERE IT HAS TO DO WITH FINANCES
THAT'S ALL, WE'RE A LITTLE
SHORT OF MONEY AND WE'RE
JUST GOING TO MAKE SOME
CUTBACKS THAT'S ALL
THERE IS TO IT.
>>HAROLD: WELL OKAY
IF THAT'S WHAT IT IS
YOU KNOW THERE'S A LOCAL
TV SHOW YOU KNOW UNCLE RED
AND IT'S LIKE A FUNNIEST
HOME VIDEOS RIGHT AND
WHAT THEY DO IS THEY SHOW
FUNNY HOME VIDEOS YOU KNOW
AND IF YOU WIN THE FIRST
PRIZE IS A $1000
JUST THINK OF ALL THE
FUNNY THINGS THAT HAPPEN
RIGHT HERE AT THE LODGE
DAY IN AND DAY OUT.
>>RED: LIKE WHAT THINGS?
>>HAROLD: LIKE WHAT?
OKAY, OKAY, ALRIGHT HOW ABOUT
THE TIME THAT YOU PARKED
THE VAN TOO CLOSE TO THE
SEPTIC TANK AND THEN
YOU STEPPED OUT AND...
>>HAROLD: OR YOU KNOW
THERE WAS THE TIME
JIMMY SINGLETON, HE BORROWED
UNCLE RED'S BRAND NEW RADIAL
ARM BANDSAW AND HE GETS IT
RIGHT BUT HIS SUSPENDER GETS
CAUGHT IN THERE AND IT JUST
BLEW OUT THE MOTOR AND IT
WAS BUT THAT'S NOT FUNNY
THAT'S THE THING YOU
KNOW THERE ARE SO MANY
OTHERS TO CHOOSE FROM.
YOU WANT IT THIS IS THE ONE
OKAY UNCLE RED BILL ON THE ROOF
THEY'RE FIXING THE ANTENNA
A STORM COMES.
>>HAROLD: PROBABLY A BAD
EXAMPLE ACTUALLY BUT HOW
ABOUT SOMETHING WHERE SOMEONE
ELSE GETS HURT YOU KNOW LIKE ME.
>>RED: OH YEAH, YEAH
WELL THAT WAS A GOOD ONE!
>>HAROLD: YOU LIKE THAT,
OKAY ALRIGHT WELL WE CAN
MAKE MONEY ON THAT UNCLE RED
BECAUSE I COULD GET THE
LODGE VIDEO CAMERA YOU KNOW
AND I COULD JUST SHOOT ALL
THE FUNNY, HUMOROUS THINGS
THAT HAPPEN AROUND HERE
WE'LL WIN FIRST PRIZE A $1000
WE'LL BE SOLID AGAIN
AND I CAN KEEP MY JOB.
>>RED: WELL YOU KNOW OTHER
THAN YOU KEEPING YOUR JOB
I REALLY LIKE THE SOUND OF IT
MIND YOU IT'S SOMETHING RIGHT
PROBABLY THE WHOLE THING IS
GOING TO BLOW UP IN MY FACE.
>>HAROLD: WELL THAT'S EXCELLENT
I COULD THROW THAT IN TOO.
♪ I SPIED A YOUNG LADY ♪
♪ WALKING DOWN THE STREET ♪
♪ A PRETTY YOUNG THING ♪
♪ I'D A CHANCE TO MEET ♪
♪ SHE WIGGLED HER HIPS ♪
♪ AND BATTED HER EYES ♪
♪ CAN YOU BEGIN TO IMAGINE ♪
♪ MY SURPRISE WHEN IT ♪
♪ TURNED OUT IT CAME ♪
♪ TO MY ATTENTION ♪
♪ IT OCCURRED TO ME ♪
♪ SHE WASN'T YOUNG OR PRETTY ♪
♪ SHE WAS A MIDDLE AGED GUY ♪
♪ IN SHOW BUSINESS ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE GOING
TO SHOW YOU HOW TO BUILD
A FRAMING WALL WHICH IS THE
FIRST STEP IN TURNING THAT
DARK, DANKY, STINKY, MUSTY,
SWAMP OF A CELLAR OF YOURS
INTO A BRIGHT WARM MODERN
FRIENDLY SPACIOUS FAMILY ROOM
WHERE THE KIDS CAN GO AND
DO STUFF THEY DON'T WANT
YOU TO KNOW ABOUT.
OR YOU COULD SAY PUT A
DECORATOR WALL IN UPSTAIRS
OR PERHAPS YOU AND YOUR SPOUSE
ARE GOING THROUGH ONE OF
THOSE LOW POINTS IN A MARRIAGE
WHERE IT'S JUST A PARTITION IN
THE BEDROOM WOULD KEEP
YOU LEGALLY LIVING TOGETHER
WITHOUT CREATING OUT
AND OUT WARFARE.
SO THE FIRST THING YOU'RE
GOING TO NEED TO DO IS
A FEW OF THE 2 BY 4'S AND
SOME OF THE 3 1/2 NAILS
GET THE SHARP ONES
AND ONE OF THESE BABIES
RIGHT HERE, A POWER HAMMER.
WHAT'S A POWER HAMMER
YOU'RE ASKING?
WELL A POWER HAMMER IS
BASICALLY A GUN THAT
FIRES NAILS.
YOU'VE GOT TO LOVE A TOOL
THAT USES GUN POWDER DON'T YOU?
WELL LET'S START BY CUTTING
UP THE 2 BY 4'S
I LOVE THE SMELL OF FRESH PINE.
YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU GET
THEM ALL THE SAME LENGTH
AND HERE WE GO,
OH FOR CRYING OUT LOUD!
(SAW WHINING & LABOURING)
THERE WE GO AND THERE WE GO,
BOY THAT SMELLS GOOD
DOESN'T IT HUH?
NOW GOLLY MAYBE I SHOULD
HAVE MEASURED THOSE FIRST
YOU KNOW WHY DON'T I CUT
THOSE AGAIN.
ALRIGHT, ALRIGHT,
LET'S START AGAIN.
OKAY THIS TIME EVEN UP
THE ENDS 'CAUSE YOU WANT THEM
ALL TO BE EXACTLY THE SAME
LENGTH THAT'S THE WHOLE POINT
OF IT AND I GUESS THEY
WERE THE SAME LENGTH.
OH WELL WE'LL JUST BUILD
A SHORTER WALL NOW THAT'S OKAY
BECAUSE THE WALLS IN THE
BASEMENT ARE REAL SHORT ANYWAY.
(SAW WHINING)
OKAY NOW THESE ARE YOUR
UPRIGHTS OR AT LEAST THEY
WILL BE WHEN THEY'RE UPRIGHT
AND YOU CUT THESE SO THAT
THEY'RE EXACTLY THE SAME
HEIGHT AS YOUR CEILING
MINUS 3 INCHES.
OKAY JUST LIKE HAROLD'S CAREER
WE'RE GOING TO START AT THE
BOTTOM THE ONLY DIFFERENCE
BEING WE'RE GOING SOMEWHERE.
OKAY THIS HERE IS WHAT
I CALL A FOOTER ACTUALLY
IT'S A 3 FOOTER AND WE'RE
GOING TO ANCHOR THIS TO
THE FLOOR USING
THE POWER HAMMER.
YOU KNOW ACTUALLY THESE
UNITS USE THE SAME CARTRIDGE
AS A 22 CALIBER RIFLE,
YOU COULD GO HUNTING WITH
ONE OF THESE POWER HAMMERS
YEAH YOU COULD GET YOURSELF
A DEER AND TACK HIS HIDE
TO THE TREE ALL IN THE ONE GO.
ALRIGHT THAT'LL BE ENOUGH
AND YOU POP THESE IN THE
BACK HERE AND THEN YOU
JUST PUT HER IN PLACE
PUSH HER DOWN AND
LET HER GO.
(LOUD RICOCHET OF HAMMER GUN)
DID I MENTION EAR
PROTECTION AT ALL?
YOU REALLY WANT TO USE
EAR PROTECTION WITH THIS
EAR PROTECTION IS PRETTY
WELL A MUST.
SO THIS IS GOING TO TAKE
A WHILE SO WHY DON'T YOU
GO BACK TO THE SHOW
I'LL KEEP BUILDING AND WE'LL
COME BACK WHEN I'M ALL DONE.
DOES SOMEBODY WANT TO
GET THAT PHONE?
>>HAROLD: IT'S THAT TIME ONCE
AGAIN WHERE WE EXPOSE THOSE
3 LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN
HAVE SUCH DIFFICULTY SAYING
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT
IS MY UNCLE RED AND HIS BEST
FRIEND IN THE WHOLE WIDE WORLD
OKAY MR. DOUGIE FRANKLIN.
>>HAROLD: 'DEAR EXPERTS
I CONSIDER MYSELF TO BE
AN ABOVE AVERAGE DRIVER
HOWEVER THE JUDGE WHO TOOK MY
LICENSE AWAY SUGGESTED I MAY
NOT BE AS GOOD AS I THINK I AM.
EXACTLY HOW DO YOU TELL IF
YOU'RE A BAD DRIVER OR NOT?'
>>RED: WELL DOUGIE THIS SOUNDS
LIKE IT WOULD BE RIGHT DEAD
CENTER IN YOUR AREA
OF EXPERTISE.
>>DOUGIE: NO KIDDING RED
I MEAN YOU WANT TO KNOW
SOMETHING ABOUT BAD DRIVERS
I AM YOUR MAN, I MUST RUN
INTO ONE OR 2 OF THOSE SUCKERS
HEAD ON ONCE A MONTH.
YEAH BUT LISTEN LET'S START
RIGHT AT THE VERY VERY BEGINNING
OF WHERE THE PROBLEM LIES
I BLAME IN ON YOUR DRIVER
EDUCATION SYSTEM.
>>RED: I'M WITH YOU THERE
DOUG I AGREE 100 PERCENT.
>>DOUGIE: ABSOLUTELY
I MEAN YOU KNOW A KID
SPENDS 4 YEARS IN SCHOOL
LEARNING HOW TO CONTROL
A PENCIL WHICH HAS NO MOVING
PARTS GOES ABOUT ONE MILE
AN HOUR AND IS NOT KNOWN
TO BURST INTO FLAMES
WHEN SHE ROLLS.
WHAT I'M SAYING HERE IS
WE'RE NOT TEACHING OUR KIDS
RIGHT AND HOW CAN WE?
YOU KNOW I MEAN THESE TEACHERS
ARE TALKING THEORY,
YOU WANT TO KNOW HOW
TO DO SOMETHING GO TO
SOMEBODY WHOSE BEEN THERE
GO TO HELL AND BACK AND TELL
THE STORY LIKE MY FAMILY
WE HAVE HAD EVERY TYPE
OF ACCIDENT IMAGINABLE.
WE HAVE HAD YOUR HEAD ON
YOUR REAR ENDER
YOUR SIDE SWIPE
YOUR ROLLOVER
YOUR ROLLOVER WITH A CONVERTIBLE
YOU NAME IT, WE HAVE DONE
THEM ALL.
WE SHOULD BE TEACHING THE KIDS,
YOU PUT ME, MY BROTHER AND
MY DADDY IN FRONT OF A
CLASSROOM AND I GUARANTEE YOU
YOU WILL BRING DOWN THE NUMBER
OF BAD DRIVERS ON THE ROAD.
>>RED: YEAH BY 3.
>>RED: WHAT YOU'VE GOT TO
DO IS ATTACH THIS PART
OF THE WALL TO THE FOOTER
BY NAILING NAILS UP THROUGH
FROM UNDERNEATH.
ALRIGHT IF YOU'RE DOING
THIS I WOULD SUGGEST THAT
YOU NAIL THIS PART ONTO THE
FOOTER BEFORE YOU ATTACH
IT TO THE FLOOR
THAT'S AN EXCELLENT TIP.
ANYWAY YOU GET THE IDEA
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME REMEMBER
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I COULD
DO WITH THIS IS JUST GO DOWN
TO THE BASEMENT AND JUST
KEEP FIRING NAILS UNTIL
I HIT THE WALL.
(LOUD BOOM OF HAMMER GUN)
>>RED: SORRY HAROLD!
>>RED: WE'RE STILL WORKING ON
THESE FUNNIEST HOME VIDEOS
SO I THOUGHT I'D GO SEE
RANGER GORD.
YOU KNOW GORD I WAS THINKING
YOU'RE UP HERE AND YOU'LL
BE ABLE TO SEE 40 MILES
AND EVERYTHING.
I GUESS YOU MUST SEE
A LOT OF FUNNY THINGS
HAPPEN DO YOU?
>>GORD: OH YEAH MY LIFE
IS NON-STOP COMEDY AND FUN.
>>RED: OH.
>>GORD: YOU SEE A LOT
OF FUNNY THINGS OVER
THE COURSE OF 6,000 DAYS.
>>RED: YEAH WELL YOU KNOW
IF WE CAN GET SOME OF THOSE
FUNNY THINGS ON TAPE
WE CAN WIN A PRIZE
ON A TELEVISION SHOW.
>>GORD: REALLY?
>>RED: YEAH.
>>GORD: WHAT SHOW
REAL PEOPLE?
>>RED: I DON'T BELIEVE
THAT ONE'S ON ANYMORE
THIS IS I BELIEVE IT'S
CALLED 'A FUNNY HOME VIDEO'
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>>GORD: YOU KNOW WHAT
A GREAT SHOW IS, 'VEGAS'.
>>RED: I DON'T KNOW THAT ONE.
>>GORD: OH YEAH I'M SURE
IT'S STILL ON DAN TANNA AND
HIS SEXY OLD VINTAGE T-BIRD
AND HIS REAL SEXY
ASSISTANT BEATRICE.
>>RED: OH YEAH, WELL ANYWAY
GORD WHAT KIND OF FUNNY
THINGS DO YOU SEE THE
TOURISTS DOING UP HERE?
>>GORD: TOURISTS?
>>RED: YEAH.
NO TOURISTS DON'T
COME THIS FAR NORTH.
>>RED: OH.
>>GORD: BUT ONCE THERE WERE
THESE 2 PINE TREES GROWING
RIGHT OUT THERE.
>>RED: OH YEAH, YEAH.
>>GORD: AND SO THE 2 TREES
WERE GROWING.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH.
>>GORD: AND ONE TREE STARTS
TO GROW A LITTLE FASTER
THAN THE OTHER ONE.
>>RED: OH FOR GOSH SAKE.
>>GORD: AND SO IT'S TALLER.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>GORD: BUT ONE NIGHT THERE'S
A WINDSTORM AND IT BLOWS
THE TOP BRANCHES OFF
THE TOP OF THE TREE.
>>RED: OH YEAH, YEAH.
>>GORD: SO ALL OF A SUDDEN
THE TALL TREE IS ACTUALLY
SHORTER, CAN YOU IMAGINE
HOW THAT TALL TREE FELT
BEING SHORTER.
>>RED: YOU KNOW GORD
THAT MIGHT NOT PLAY ALL
THAT WELL ON TELEVISION.
>>RED: WELL THIS IDEA OF RAISING
MONEY WITH A FUNNY HOME VIDEO
HAS TURNED INTO A KIND OF
GOOD NEWS/BAD NEWS THING.
THE GOOD NEWS IS WE'RE
GETTING LOTS OF SUGGESTIONS
FROM THE GUYS,
THE BAD NEWS IS NONE
OF THEM ARE ANY GOOD.
LIKE BUSTER HADFIELD CLAIMS
HE GETS BIG LAUGHS AT HIS
FAMILY FUNCTIONS BY PUTTING
UNDERWEAR ON HIS HEAD,
THIS SHOULD GIVE YOU AN IDEA
OF HOW HIS FAMILY FUNCTIONS.
>>RED: HOW ARE WE DOING
ON THE TECHNICAL END
THERE HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: OH WELL JUST LET
ME START BY SAYING IT'S
TOTALLY MY FAULT.
>>RED: WELL THAT'LL
SAVE A LITTLE TIME.
>>HAROLD: WELL THIS IS ONE
OF THESE SITUATIONS WHERE YOU
WISH YOU HAD A VIDEO CAMERA
WITH YOU BECAUSE IT'S
REALLY QUITE FUNNY.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU NEED A BATTERY
TO MAKE THE CAMERA ACTUALLY
FUNCTIONABLE YOU KNOW THE
BATTERY THING THE BATTERY
YOU KNOW THAT THE BATTERY.
>>RED: THE BATTERY.
>>HAROLD: THAT'S THE
ONE THE BATTERY YEAH.
WELL SEE IT'S CUTE ACTUALLY
'CAUSE YOU KNOW IN THE BIZ
YOU KNOW THE TECHNICAL SHOW BIZ
THE PARLOT IS SUCH A TERM
OF THE BATTERY IS A CHOCOLATE
BAR RIGHT YOU KNOW THAT IT'S
A CHOCOLATE BAR 'CAUSE IT
LOOKS LIKE A CHOCOLATE BAR
YOU KNOW AND WELL ACTUALLY
IT TASTES MORE LIKE NICKEL
AND CADMIUM BUT ANYWAY IT'S
FUNNY BECAUSE YOU KNOW BEING
A CAMERAMAN WHEN THE BATTERY
DIES YOU WOULD TURN TO
THE ASSISTANT IN THIS CASE
BILL AND I WOULD SAY
YOU KNOW ASSISTANT PUT IN
ANOTHER CHOCOLATE BAR
YOU KNOW AND IT'S SO FUNNY
BECAUSE I THOUGHT HE WAS
GOING TO PUT ANOTHER
BATTERY YOU KNOW.
>>RED: THERE IS CHOCOLATE
IN THE CAMERA?
>>HAROLD: EXACTLY.
EVERYWHERE YOU KNOW
WELL THE FUNNY PART IS
YOU CAN'T GET THE NUTS
OR THE RAISINS OUT.
>>RED: OH SO WE
HAVE NO CAMERA.
>>RED: AT THIS TIME, NO.
>>RED: TODAY'S
'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'
BILL IS GONG TO TEACH ME
HOW TO DO A LITTLE DOWNHILL
SKIING SOMETHING I'VE NEVER
DONE AND I THINK BILL IS
PRIMARILY A TEACHER.
NOW THIS WAS INTERESTING
IN ORDER TO SAVE TIME
HE HAD ACTUALLY PUT HIS SKIS
ON BEFORE HE CAME OUT OF
MY VAN TO DO THE SKIING.
SO I THOUGHT IT WAS INTERESTING
I GUESS IT WILL TAKE QUITE
A WHILE TO GET THE SKIS ON
AND WHAT HAVE YOU BUT YOU KNOW
I'M NOT REALLY SURE EXACTLY
HOW MUCH TIME THIS SAVED
IN THIS PARTICULAR CASE.
ANYWAYS THERE HE IS ALRIGHT
ALRIGHT BUT YOU KNOW AND
YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU
TEACH YOUR STUDENTS AND THEN
I GUESS HAVE THE CHOICE OF
EITHER DOING WHAT YOU SAY OR
PICKING A BETTER WAY,
I THINK I MIGHT I GO WITH
A DIFFERENT WAY ON THIS
BUT AGAIN I'M RECEPTIVE
BILL KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING HERE
AND NOW WE GO AND THEN.
>>BILL: OH!
>>RED: OH HE'S CAUGHT NOW
THERE'S ANOTHER THING YOU SEE
HE'S SHOWING THE EXAMPLE OF
WHAT CAN GO WRONG
I THINK THAT'S A VALUABLE LESSON
OH THERE'S AN EXAMPLE THERE
AND THAT'S PROBABLY NOT
SOMETHING YOU'D CHOOSE TO DO
BUT IF YOU SHOW IT TO THE
STUDENTS THAT'S THE MARK OF
AN EXCELLENT TEACHER.
ANYWAYS HE'S GOT LOTS MORE
SKIS OUT IN THE VAN AND
A LOT OF POLES, OH! OH!
NOW THAT WAS A SAFETY LESSON
AND YOU KNOW THAT'S ONE I'LL
REMEMBER FOR QUITE A WHILE.
BILL'S GOOD THAT WAY,
NOW YOU'VE GOT AN AWFUL
LOT OF POLES THERE BILL
YEAH I'LL TAKE THAT AND THEN
OH WELL I GUESS HE KNOWS
WHAT HE'S DOING.
NOW HE PUTS THEM DOWN
LIKE JEAN CLAUDE KILLEY
YEAH YEAH ALRIGHT ALRIGHT
NO TIPPING!
ANYWAY NOW HE'S SHOWING
ME HOW TO GET THE SHOES HAVE
THE HOLES IN THEM WITH THOSE
LITTLE PINS AND THE PINS
LINEUP WITH THE HOLES IN
THE SPECIAL CROSS COUNTRY
SKI THINGS THEN HE CLIPS
THAT DOWN, NO DOWN THERE.
HE'S SHOWING US WHAT CAN
GO WRONG, ACTUALLY I WASN'T
PAYING THAT MUCH ATTENTION AT
THIS POINT I WAS JUST TRYING
TO USE SOME LOGIC AND
COMMON SENSE.
I WAS GETTING MINE ON ALRIGHT
I GUESS MAYBE THAT IS AN
EFFECTIVE WAY TO TEACH
HE SHOWS YOU THE WRONG WAY
AND THEN YOU KIND OF YOU
KNOW YOU FEEL GOOD ABOUT IT
AND I WAS YEAH YOU'RE DOING
FINE AND I WAS FEELING REAL
GOOD AND I THOUGHT THIS MIGHT
BE AN INTERESTING WAY TO
MEET SWEDISH WOMEN TOO.
AND HE'S MOVING ALONG THERE
I'M NOT QUITE SURE WHAT THIS
WAS ABOUT I GUESS HE WAS JUST
KIND OF MARKING HIS PATH WHAT
HAVE YOU BUT I GUESS THIS
WOULD EXPLAIN WHY ALL THE
POLES WERE THERE BUT AS I
SAID I WAS LOOKING MORE
FOR THE SWEDES!
ANYWAY THE STEEP HILLS
BOY THEY ARE A CHALLENGE
THAT'S A TOUGH ONE.
HE WAS USING THE POLES
TO KIND OF...
NOW AGAIN I THINK AS
A TEACHER HE WAS SHOWING
US ALL THAT THINGS CAN GO WRONG,
I THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO
SLIDE ALL THE WAY BACK TO
THE BEGINNING OF THE COURSE.
>>BILL: AH!
>>RED: NO HE GOT LUCKY THERE.
HE'S SO SMART AND THEN
I'M GOING ALONG AND ALL OF
A SUDDEN I HEAR A NOISE
AND I'M THINKING WHAT'S
THE TEACHER SHOWING US?
WELL FOR GOSH SAKES
THE TEACHER'S GOT A SENSE
OF HUMOR BUT BILL THE VAN!
THE VAN! BILL THE VAN!
>>BILL: OH!
>>RED: OH WELL I LEARNED
A GREAT DEAL THERE
AND THANK YOU BILL AND ACTUALLY
IT'S A GREAT SPORT
I'M HAVING A GOOD TIME
AND I ACTUALLY MISSED HIM
THERE SO I'M GETTING BETTER
THAN I USED TO BE.
AS FAR AS THE TEACHER'S
CONCERNED IT LOOKS TO ME
LIKE IT'S CLASS DISMISSED
RIGHT BILL, OH YEAH.
>>HAROLD: HERE'S A PART
OF THE SHOW THAT'S DEDICATED
AND PRODUCED BY TEENAGERS.
DORK, DUFUS, GEEK,
THESE NAMES HURT
TELL ME ABOUT IT...
HOW DO YOU STOP PEOPLE
FROM VERBALLY BELITTLING YOU?
WELL IF IT'S YOUR PARENTS
YOU'VE GOT TO BE TACTFUL
IF IT'S BULLIES DON'T SAY
THINGS LIKE STICKS AND STONES
WILL BREAK MY BONES BUT
NAMES WILL NEVER HURT ME
BECAUSE THEY'LL GO RIGHT TO
THE STICKS AND STONES PART
YOU KNOW BUT IF THEY ARE
COOL PEOPLE THEY'RE THE TOUGHEST
BECAUSE WHAT DO YOU SAY TO THEM?
I MEAN THEY'LL CALL YOU
LIKE HEY TOOLHEAD
AND THEN YOU SAY TO THEM
THERE'S NOTHING TO SAY
TO THEM THERE'S, NO, NOTHING
RIGHT SO WHAT I'VE DONE IS
I'VE DEVELOPED A LIST OF
NASTY NAMES TO GET TRUE
REVENGE OF THE NERDS.
GET READY TRY SOME OF THESE
ON FOR SIZE THE NEXT TIME
YOU GET BELITTLED.
HOW ABOUT DREB
OR FOR THE GUY WHOSE
REALLY INTO CLOTHES
HEY FASHIONOID
FOR THE HANDSOME MAN, CLEFTO,
FOR THE PRETTY GIRL, PLASTY,
HERE'S JUST A GROUP OF RANDOM
ONES THESE ARE JUST FOR FUN
NINER, SPOON MOUTH,
GOOFBALL, WHIZBANG,
HEY LUNKHEAD.
>>RED: WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
THERE HAROLD FAMILY TREE?
>>BUZZ: COOL!
>>RED: ARE YOU BURNING
HER HAROLD?
ALRIGHT GETTING READY TO
DO OUR FUNNY HOME VIDEO STUFF
WE THOUGHT I'D VISIT OUR PAL
HERE BUZZ SHERWOOD BECAUSE
HE'S ALWAYS LAUGHING,
HOW ARE YOU DOING BUZZ?
>>BUZZ: PRETTY GOOD RED!
>>RED: THAT'S NOT FUNNY OH!
>>BUZZ: HEY HAROLD
HOW ARE YOU?
HEY IS THAT THING ON?
>>RED: YEAH.
>>BUZZ: HEY LOOK AT THIS
LOOK AT THIS, I'VE BEEN
WORKING ON SOMETHING.
WATCH THIS.
(LOUD FLATULENCE NOISES)
MY GRANDMOTHER DID
THAT IN VAUDEVILLE.
>>RED: NO THAT'S NOT
NO, NO, NO.
>>BUZZ: OH I'VE GOT AN IDEA
I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
>>RED: NO, NO, NO, WHAT?
>>BUZZ: YOU TAKE THIS.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>BUZZ: SMASH IT OVER
MY HEAD REALLY HARD
GO AHEAD, GO AHEAD.
>>RED: OH NO, NO, NO, NO.
>>BUZZ: COME ON DO IT
THIS IS FUNNY OKAY
I'LL GET A CHAIR.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>BUZZ: AND I'LL FALL OUT
OF THE CHAIR THAT'LL BE FUNNY.
>>RED: NO THAT'S NOT FUNNY
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
>>BUZZ: OKAY.
>>RED: WHAT ELSE
HAVE YOU GOT?
>>BUZZ: TOOLS,
I CAN JUGGLE TOOLS WATCH THIS.
>>RED: NO, NO, BUZZ, BUZZ.
>>BUZZ: ARE YOU READY HUH?
HAVE YOU GOT THIS HAROLD,
ARE YOU READY HAROLD?
OH DID YOU GET THAT HAROLD?
>>RED: BUZZ! BUZZ!
>>BUZZ: WHAT?
>>RED: IS THERE MAYBE SOME
KIND OF A CUTE LITTLE STUNT
OR A TRICK OR SOMETHING
YOU CAN DO?
>>BUZZ: A CUTE STUNT?
>>RED: YEAH SOMETHING CUTE.
>>BUZZ: YOU MEAN LIKE
A LOOP DE LOOP INTO
A HAMMERHEAD STALL INTO
AN UNCONTROLLED DIVE.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH CAN YOU DO THAT?
>>BUZZ: WELL SURE THAT'S
WHAT HAPPENED TO MY
LAST PLANE, YOU REMEMBER.
>>RED: OH SURE, YEAH.
>>BUZZ: OH I GOT IT!
I GOT IT! I GOT IT!
I WAS GOING TO TAKE THIS UP
INTO THE PLANE AND DROP IT
ON OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S
BUT I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>BUZZ: HOLD THAT.
(HUM OF PROPELLER)
>>BUZZ: THROW IT INTO
THE PROPELLER.
>>RED: WELL NO I DON'T THINK
I WANT TO DO THAT BUZZ.
>>BUZZ: MAN YOU'RE SUCH
A WHOOSIE, GIVE IT TO ME!
GIVE ME THE WATER
GIVE IT TO ME GIVE ME THIS
MY PLANE! MY PLANE RED!
GET MY PLANE I GOT TO.
(ENGINE STALLS)
>>BUZZ: OH COME BACK!
COME BACK!
>>RED: ARE YOU GETTING
THIS HAROLD?
THIS IS GREAT STUFF.
>>RED: WELL THERE'S EVEN MORE
GOOD NEWS AND BAD NEWS
ABOUT THE FUNNIEST HOME
VIDEO CONTEST.
>>HAROLD: WE WON DIDN'T WE?
YES WE WON!
I KNEW WE'D WIN!
I KNEW, I KNEW,
I SAID WE'D WIN AND WE WON!
I GET TO KEEP MY JOB!
SO TELL ME THE GOOD NEWS
TELL ME.
>>RED: THE GOOD NEWS IS
THE TELEVISION PEOPLE
DOWN THERE TOOK A LOOK AT
OUR TAPE AND HAVE DECIDED
NOT TO PRESS CHARGES.
>>RED: WELL THEY PROMISED
NOT TO SAY ANYTHING TO
THE AUTHORITIES OR
THE HUMANE SOCIETY.
>>HAROLD: WE DIDN'T
WIN DID WE?
(WHINING) WE DIDN'T WIN.
>>RED: THE BAD NEWS IS THAT
WHEN THE TAPE CAME BACK
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK TOOK IT OUT
FOR PROCESSING, SO NOW WE'VE GOT
NO TAPE WE'VE GOT NOTHING TO
SELL NO WAY TO RAISE MONEY
AND I GUESS WE'RE NOT GOING
TO HAVE A SHOW NEXT WEEK.
>>HAROLD: PROCESSING?
HE TOOK IT IN FOR PROCESSING!
YOU PROCESS FILM,
YOU DON'T PROCESS VIDEO TAPE
I MEAN ANY IDIOT KNOWS THAT.
>>RED: WELL I KNOW
YOU DO HAROLD.
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK IS NOT
UP TO SPEED ON THESE NEW
FANGLED GIZMOS LIKE
THE VCR OR THE WHEEL.
SO NOW ALL WE'VE GOT IS THIS
OLD TAPE HERE WITH JUST ALL
THE MISTAKES AND OUTTAKES
AND SCREWUPS WE DID.
>>HAROLD: OH IDEA!
MAYBE WE JUST PUT LIKE CREDITS
ON THE FRONT OF IT AND THE BACK
IT COULD BE NEXT WEEK'S EPISODE.
>>RED: WELL HAROLD MAYBE
THERE IS ROOM FOR YOU
AROUND HERE, HUH?
>>HAROLD: ANYTHING TO
KEEP MY JOB.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH MEETING TIME.
>>RED: YEAH HAROLD YOU TAKE
THIS AND SETUP THE VCR.
>>HAROLD: OH OKAY.
>>RED: THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
BOY NEXT WEEK'S SHOW IS
GOING TO BE A REAL
HUMMER ISN'T IT?
(LOUD CRASHING & BANGING)
(HAROLD WHINING IN PAIN)
>>RED: WELL THAT'S JUST MY LUCK
HE HURTS HIMSELF AND
I DON'T HAVE A CAMERA!
ANYWAY IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING AND MAYBE
WE CAN DIG UP THAT OLD FILM
WE'VE GOT OF YOUR DAD
REMEMBER WHEN HE WENT
PARASAILING IN THAT
ELECTRICAL STORM.
AND IF WE CAN'T FIND IT
MAYBE WE CAN JUST SHOOT
A NEW ONE, I MEAN HE'S
BACK IN THE PINK SINCE
THE OPEN HEART SURGERY
TELL HIM THERE'LL BE $500 BUCKS
IN IT FOR HIM AND TO THE REST
OF YOU ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND WHAT'S LEFT OF HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>ALL: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORITATI.
>>RED: ALRIGHT BEFORE WE
START THE MEETING TONIGHT
HAROLD PUT THAT TAPE IN
THE VCR WE'RE GOING TO
TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT WILL
BECOME NEXT WEEK'S SHOW
AND JUST HAVE YOUR
ATTENTION OVER THERE.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca