IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE MAN WHO INSPIRES US
TO BOLDLY GO WHERE
NO HANDYMAN HAS GONE BEFORE,
THE PSYCHIATRIC WARD,
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
I WAS HOPING TO SHOW YOU
A BOAT PROJECT
WE'RE WORKING ON,
BUT WE'VE HAD A SET-BACK.
WE GOT
A NEW BOAT?
JUNIOR SINGLETON GOT
A BIG GRAVEL BARGES.
GONNA TURN HER INTO
A BASS BOAT -- 40-TON CAPACITY.
BIG ENOUGH FOR THE WHOLE LODGE.
JUST.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED
A BIGGER MOTOR TO PUSH IT.
WE'VE EACH GOT ONE.
YOU FIT THEM
ALL THE WAY AROUND THE SIDES.
EVERYBODY'S GOT
THEIR OWN MOTOR.
YEAH.
BUT IF EVERYBODY HAS
THEIR OWN MOTOR,
HOW YOU GONNA STEER IT?
POINT YOUR MOTOR
WHERE YOU WANNA GO,
AND IF YOU CAN GET ENOUGH
HORSEPOWER TO AGREE WITH YA
YOU'RE GONNA GET THERE.
TALK ABOUT DEMOCRACY
IN ACTION --
SO WHAT'S THE HOLD-UP?
THERE'S NO REAL NICE WAY
TO PUT THIS,
BUT, JUNIOR'S
NO LONGER WITH US.
HE'S GONE.
JUNIOR SINGLETON'S DEAD?
NO, HAROLD, IT'S WORSE.
HE'S IN LOVE.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MESSAGE BEING,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
JUNIOR SINGLETON'S
REALLY SERIOUS ABOUT A GIRL?
WHERE DID THEY MEET?
THEY MET AT ONE OF
TOOL-SWAP-MEET THINGS.
HER NAME IS NOREEN,
AND SHE WAS THERE
TRYING TO TRADE HER
BUTTERFLY IMPACT WRENCH,
AND ALONG COMES JUNIOR
WITH HIS FLEXIBLE-HEAD RATCHET
WITH TWO NUTS MISSING.
LOVE AT FIRST SWAP.
THEY GOT NOTHING IN COMMON.
I MEAN, SHE'S METRIC,
HE'S IMPERIAL.
CAN'T WORK.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU
DON'T WANT IT TO WORK,
UNCLE RED.
WE SHOULD HAVE
SEEN THIS COMING.
WE SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
THERE WAS A GIRL INVOLVED.
HE'S BEEN SO HAPPY LATELY,
SHAVING EVERY DAY,
EATING PROPERLY.
SAYING "EXCUSE ME,"
NO MATTER WHO DID IT.
(Laughing)
HE LOOKS THE SAME.
I SAW HIM GOING INTO NORTON'S
FEED AND VIDEOS.
HE WENT IN TO GET
"OUR MAN FLINT"
STARRING JAMES COBURN.
HE CAME OUT WITH "XANADU"
STARRING OLIVIA NEWTON-JOHN.
THAT'S WHAT LOVE WILL DO.
WHY CAN'T JUNIOR WORK ON
THE BOAT AND SEE NOREEN?
ONCE NOREEN IS THERE
THEY GET INTO
THE MUSHY-FACE STUFF
AND YOU CAN'T CONCENTRATE.
YOU'LL UNDERSTAND
ONCE PUBERTY KICKS IN.
LATER, WE'RE GONNA HAVE
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL".
THESE BOYS ARE GOING TO
FORD THE STREAM.
IF I'D HAVE GONE
WITH THE VAN,
I WOULD HAVE DODGED THE STREAM.
A LITTLE AUTOMOTIVE HUMOUR.
THIS IS SOME KIND OF CAMP.
IT'S CERTAINLY NOT HIGH CAMP,
AND HOPEFULLY NOT "MEIN" CAMP.
IT'S JUST CAMP.
THEY'RE GONNA GET
A LITTLE DRINKING WATER.
THE WATER UP HERE IS LIKE
CRYSTAL-SPRING CLEAR.
YOU CAN TAKE IT RIGHT OUT OF
MANY OF THE LAKES AND STREAMS.
THIS ISN'T ONE OF THEM THOUGH.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
ALL RIGHT, YEAH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, FINE, YOU'RE FINE.
BILL, BEING AN AVID CAMPER,
HAS
WATER PURIFICATION TABLETS.
THAT LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING
THAT HAS BEEN RE-LABELLED BY...
BY...
THAT SUGGESTS TO ME
THAT'S PROBABLY NOT --
OK, THEY'RE FINE.
THERE WE GO.
YOU JUST PUT
A FEW OF THOSE TABLETS
IN WITH YOUR WATER --
NOT TOO MANY NOW, BILL.
NO, I THINK YOU NEED TWO.
JUST THE TWO, TWO, TWO...
THEN YOU PUT THE WATER IN
AND YOU GET
A CHEMICAL REACTION.
THIS MAY BE WHY IT'S...
UH... BOYS, THAT'S A...
FELLAS, I THINK YOU PUT
A LITTLE TOO MUCH.
YOU'RE GETTING TOO MUCH,
TOO MUCH -- YOU MIGHT WANNA
GET THE TOP OFF.
YOU'VE GOT TIME.
TAKE THE TOP OFF.
GET IT OFF, GET IT OFF,
GET IT OFF.
THAT WAS ONLY A SUGGESTION.
YOU SHOULD HAVE LEFT
THE TOP ON THERE, GUYS.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
ANYWAY, WHAT THEY HAVE THERE
IS CRYSTAL CLEAR RAIN,
AND CRYSTAL CLEAR FOG,
WHICH IS WHAT BILL AND HAROLD
ARE IN MOST OF THE TIME.
OH YEAH.
YOU STILL GOT A COUPLE --
THERE YOU GO.
YOU CAN AT LEAST PURIFY
YOUR OWN SALIVA, RIGHT, HAROLD?
HOPEFULLY
IT WILL STERILIZE HIM.
OH, THE MOUNTAIN IS HIGH
AND THE VALLEY IS LOW
IT'S THE LAWS OF NATURE
THAT MAKE IT SO
IF THE VALLEY
IS HIGH
AND THE MOUNTAIN IS LOW
YOU'RE EITHER UPSIDE DOWN
OR DRUNK OR BOTH
LOW
SHE TOLD YOU
WHERE TO PICK HER UP.
SHE TOLD YOU TO WRITE IT DOWN.
YOU TOLD HER
YOU DIDN'T NEED TO.
WHERE HAS THAT GOTTEN YA?
LOOKING FOR A HOUSE
THAT MAY HAVE YOUR WIFE IN IT.
THIS IS NOT YOUR FINEST HOUR.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
REDEEM YOURSELF BIG-TIME.
THIS IS WHAT YOU GOTTA DO.
RENT ONE OF
THOSE PORTABLE SIGNS,
THE ONES YOU TOW
BEHIND YOUR CAR.
MAKE UP A MUSHY SIGN
JUST FOR HER.
HOOK IT UP --
START DRIVING AROUND.
HONK YOUR HORN.
SHOUT HER NAME.
WHATEVER DRAWS A CROWD.
HOPEFULLY YOU'LL BE IN
THE RIGHT GENERAL AREA,
AND SHE'LL HEAR YOU COMING.
UNFORTUNATELY,
SO WILL ALL THE NEIGHBOURS.
THEY'LL ALL COME OUT,
AND YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
PICK HER OUT IN THE CROWD.
YOO-HOO, HONEY.
YOU WILL BE PROFESSING
YOUR LOVE
IN FRONT OF PEOPLE
YOU'VE NEVER MET,
BUT SHE'LL NEVER SUSPECT
YOU FORGOT WHERE SHE WAS.
SURE, YOU'LL LOOK LIKE A DORK,
BUT IT'S BETTER THAN HER
FINDING OUT THE TRUTH.
THE IMPORTANT THING
IS THAT YOU FOUND HER.
AND YOU'VE DONE SOMETHING
THAT COULD BE VAGUELY CONSTRUED
AS ROMANTIC.
WE KNOW YOU'RE NOT ROMANTIC --
YOU'RE JUST STUPID.
THE BEAUTY OF WOOD FURNITURE
IS YOU CAN PAINT IT
ANY COLOUR YOU WANT,
BLACK, ORANGE, PURPLE,
WHATEVER GOES
WITH YOUR CURTAINS.
THIS CHAIR IS ONE BERNICE AND I
CALL OUR GUEST CHAIR.
A LOT OF MEMORIES
IN THIS CHAIR,
NOT HAPPY ONES.
IF I'M GOING TO STRIP
THAT CHAIR,
THERE HAVE GOT TO BE
10 COATS OF PAINT,
SO I'M GONNA NEED SOMETHING
POWERFUL TO TAKE THAT OFF.
REMEMBER, WHEN
YOU'RE TAKING THESE OFF,
YOU'RE TALKING...
KIND OF CORROSIVE-- OH!
VERY CORROSIVE STUFF.
I WOULD SUGGEST YOU GO WITH
THE PROTECTIVE-- AH!
I WOULD RECOMMEND THAT YOU GO
WITH THE PROTECTIVE GLOVES,
UNLESS YOU REALLY ENJOY
A GOOD BURN.
AND, UH, YOU MIGHT WANNA WEAR
AN APRON, TOO, TO AVOID INJURY.
OR ARREST, OR FROSTBITE.
THERE WE GO.
WE GOT THE CHEMICAL ON THERE.
NOW WE, UH...
THE STUFF HAS STRIPPED
THE INSTRUCTIONS OFF THE CAN.
HMM?
WHAT?
WE WAIT?
ALL RIGHT,
HAROLD SAYS WE WAIT.
I'VE BEEN WAITING
UPWARDS OF TWO MINUTES.
NOTHING BUGS A HANDYMAN MORE
THAN A STRIPPER
THAT WORKS TOO SLOW.
I THINK WE GOTTA SPIKE UP
OUR CHEMICAL MIX,
THROW SOME NORMAL STRIPPER IN.
I GOT THIS OTHER,
SPECIAL STUFF.
GOT THIS FROM MY GRANDFATHER.
THEY FOUND IT IN THE BARN
AFTER THE COW DIED.
OH BOY, SHE'S PRETTY THICK.
THAT SHOULD DO THE TRICK.
OH MY!
GET THAT ON THE CHAIR.
WE GOT A FEW LAYERS OFF.
I'D SAY WE'RE BACK TO
ABOUT 1978.
BUT WE'RE STILL NOT DOWN TO
BARE WOOD.
SO I THINK WE NEED TO SWITCH
TO SOMETHING STRONGER.
I GOT A GREAT MIX
GOING IN HERE.
I GOT BLEACH.
I GOT CAUSTIC SODA.
I GOT DRAIN CLEANER,
NAIL POLISH REMOVER,
AMMONIA, PEROXIDE,
AND SIX BOTTLES OF
MR. GOUDA'S SNAPPY POP.
ALL I NEED TO DO
IS TAKE MY CAR BATTERY
AND JUMP START
THE WHOLE SHEBANG.
BY GOLLY.
BETTER GET THIS ON THE CHAIR
BEFORE IT EATS THROUGH THE POT.
THERE WE GO.
CHAIR'S SMALLER THAN I THOUGHT.
MUST HAVE BEEN
MORE PAINT ON THERE...
THAT CHEMICAL IS...
WE HAVEN'T JUST REFINISHED
THE CHAIR.
WE'VE ACTUALLY FINISHED IT.
REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
DOESN'T SURPRISE ME.
RELAX -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT MORE OF IT.
I WANNA TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT YOU'RE PROBABLY
ALREADY AWARE OF.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT
HOW MANY THINGS
THERE ARE TO KNOW,
YOU DON'T KNOW MANY OF THEM.
WHEN YOU WERE A TEENAGER
YOU KNEW EVERYTHING.
BUT DIDN'T YOU FIND THAT
THE SMARTER YOU GOT
THE LESS YOU KNEW.
NOW YOU CAN BARELY FIND
YOUR CAR KEYS.
A LOT OF GUYS LEARN
ALL THERE IS TO KNOW
ABOUT SOME OBSCURE TOPIC,
LIKE STUDEBAKER HOOD ORNAMENTS,
THEN TRY TO WORK THAT
INTO EVERY CONVERSATION.
THEY'LL SAY "THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES,
"THAT'S A PERSON THAT
PEOPLE LOOK TO, A SYMBOL.
"YOU KNOW WHAT IT
REMINDS ME OF?
"HOOD ORNAMENTS."
HERE'S A BETTER IDEA.
TRY DO WHAT WOMEN DO.
IT'S CALLED LISTENING.
WOMEN HAVE MASTERED THE ART
OF LISTENING TO PEOPLE
GO ON AND ON ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT NO ONE HAS
ANY INTEREST IN.
THINGS LIKE HOOD ORNAMENTS.
SO TRY LISTENING TO SOMEONE.
THEY WON'T MIND THAT
YOU'RE NOT SAYING ANYTHING.
THEY'LL THINK YOU'RE AGREEING
WITH THEIR OPINIONS,
AND, IN THEIR MINDS,
YOU'LL BE BRILLIANT.
HERE'S THE BEST PART.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PRETEND
TO BE SMARTER
THAN THE PERSON
YOU'RE LISTENING TO.
CHANCES ARE YOU'RE NOT.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YA.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WHAT STARTED AS A GREAT IDEA
IS A BIG PAIN IN THE NECK.
WE GOT JUNIOR
WORKING ON THE BOAT AGAIN.
NOW HE BRINGS NOREEN
WITH HIM.
SHE IS THE YOKO ONO
OF BASS BARGES.
(Audience laughing)
UNCLE RED, YOU'RE
JUST UNCOMFORTABLE
HAVING WOMEN AROUND.
NO, I'M NOT, HAROLD.
IF MY WIFE, BERNICE,
WAS WORKING--
OK, THAT'S A BAD EXAMPLE.
BUT THERE ARE
PLENTY OF WOMEN WHO WOULD BE
AN ADDITION TO THE TEAM.
LIKE THAT WOMAN ON "HOME TIME"
OR MARTINA NAVRATILOVA --
SOMEONE LIKE THAT.
BALONEY, BALONEY, BALONEY,
BALONEY, BALONEY!
NOREEN'S A REAL HELPFUL
KIND OF PERSON.
SHE GOT THE GENERATOR STARTED
WHEN YOU GUYS
COULDN'T.
SHE KNOWS
WHEN YOU'RE LOST.
THAT'S GOT NOTHING
TO DO WITH IT.
SHE'S JUST NOT ONE OF THE GUYS.
HUGGING AND KISSING
MAKES EVERYBODY FEEL BAD.
THE GUYS WHO DON'T HAVE GIRLS
FEEL BAD.
THE MARRIED GUYS START THINKING
ABOUT WHAT COULD HAVE BEEN,
OR SHOULD NEVER HAVE BEEN
IF THERE WAS A KIND,
COMPASSIONATE GOD.
IF YOU GUYS GOT PROBLEMS
IN YOUR RELATIONSHIPS,
IT'S ALWAYS YOUR FAULT.
YOU GUYS COULD CHANGE.
WE DON'T WANT
TO CHANGE!
WHY DO YOU THINK
WE STARTED THE LODGE?
(Siren)
POSSUM 911 -- PLEASE STATE
YOUR MEMBERSHIP CARD NUMBER!
OH, UH, HI, HAROLD.
UH, IS RED THERE?
UH, HI, MR. ROTHSCHILD,
WHAT'S UP?
OH, NOTHING, YOU KNOW?
JUST... JUST DRIVING AROUND.
OK, SO WHAT'S THE EMERGENCY?
UH, NO... NO EMERGENCY, HAROLD.
WELL, YOU DID DIAL
THE 911 POSSUM LINE.
OH, DID I? OH, SORRY.
I THOUGHT I WAS CALLING 411,
ACTUALLY.
YEAH, INFORMATION.
OK, WHAT KIND OF INFORMATION
WOULD YOU LIKE, SIR?
IS... IS RED THERE OR, UH...
IT'S OK TO ADMIT THAT
YOU'RE LOST, MR. ROTHSCHILD.
I CAN GIVE YOU DIRECTIONS.
LOST?! HAH!
PLEASE, HAROLD, I'M NOT LOST.
NEVER BEEN LOST
A DAY IN MY LIFE.
YOU'RE LOST,
IF YOU'RE THINKING THAT WAY.
IS RED THERE?
YEAH, I'M HERE, WINSTON.
I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE JUST
DRIVING AROUND TONIGHT.
YEAH, JUST, UH, YOU KNOW,
COMING BACK
FROM AN ESTATE SALE
OVER AT GREEN SLIME HARBOUR,
AND NOW I'M JUST KINDA
GOING HOME.
JUST NOTICED THAT THEY TOOK
THE OLD WATER TOWER DOWN.
NO, IT'S STILL THERE.
IT'S JUST WEST OF FLINTY
McCLINTOCK'S SCRAP METAL YARD.
RIGHT.
OH... OH, WEST
OF FLINTY'S PLACE... YEAH.
YEAH, WHICH IS JUST NORTH
OF THE LODGE.
OK.
YOU KNOW, WINSTON,
ON A COMPLETELY
UNRELATED MATTER,
WE'RE HAVING PROBLEMS HERE
WITH THE ELECTRICAL.
A LOT OF SHORTS AND THE LIGHTS
ARE FLICKERING REAL BAD.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE HECK'S GOING ON.
OK! WOW! LOOK AT THAT!
THEY SURE ARE SPARKING, THERE.
YEAH.
WELL, BOB'S YOUR UNCLE,
MOLLY'S YOUR AUNT.
I CAN SEE 'EM FROM HERE.
THANKS, RED --
I'LL BE RIGHT OVER.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S JUST A RIGHT
TURN, A LEFT, AND ANOTHER LEFT.
NO, ANOTHER RIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID!
(Red): TIME FOR
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL".
THE TWO LADS ARE GONNA CROSS
THE STREAM.
MY DAD ONCE TOLD ME
THAT THE JOURNEY OF LIFE
IS CROSSING A STREAM,
AND SOMETIMES YOU GET ONTO
A WIGGLY ROCK
AND YOU GOTTA GET OFF THAT
RIGHT AWAY.
HE SAID, "THE MOST DANGEROUS
ROCKS ARE THE BIG FLAT ONES,
"'CAUSE YOU WANT TO LIE DOWN
AND SUN YOURSELF ON THEM."
THAT WASN'T A DANGEROUS ONE.
YOU WANT TO SUN YOURSELF
ON A BIG ROCK.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MOVE ON,
BUT YOU GOTTA MOVE ON.
OH, THERE YOU GO.
MOVE ON, HAROLD, MOVE ON.
AWAY YOU GO -- ATTABOY.
SO BILL TAKING
THE BACKPACK OFF.
RESOURCEFULNESS IS THE SECRET
TO ALL CAMPING TRIPS.
HE WHIPS OUT...
WHAT IS THAT, NOW?
THAT WOULD BE...
THAT WOULD BE A ROPE.
WE HAVE A ROPE IN HIS PANTS.
BE INTERESTING TO WATCH BILL
GET DRESSED IN THE MORNING.
NO, PROBABLY NOT
AFTER BREAKFAST -- ANYWAY,
HE THROWS THAT ACROSS.
AND HE LASSEES--
RESOURCEFULNESS --
THERE WE GO AGAIN --
LASSOS A TREE THING
THAT WAS HANGING THERE,
PROBABLY FROM
A PREVIOUS TRIP OF THEIRS.
HE HAS HAROLD GO
AND TIE THE OTHER END.
HAROLD DOES THOSE FANCY KNOTS
HE LEARNED FROM WATCHING
"THE SMURFS".
THERE YOU GO, HAROLD --
END OVER END,
UP AND OVER, INSIDE OUT.
WHAT BILL'S GONNA DO IS
JUST USE THAT--
THERE WE GO.
OH, MY GOSH.
HE'S GONNA USE THAT TO HOLD
HIMSELF UP, TAKE THE WEIGHT.
YOU GOTTA REALIZE
THAT PROFESSIONAL CAMPERS
WOULD USE A WIRE CABLE
OR A PRE-...
A PRE-STRETCHED...
MAYBE NOT A COTTON.
MAYBE SOMETHING THAT
DOESN'T HAVE THE GIVE.
BILL HAS NOT PREPARED
AS WELL AS HE SHOULD HAVE.
AM I RIGHT?
YEAH, YEAH!
ANYWAY, I SEE -- HE'S STAYING
WITH THE THEORY, YOU KNOW?
BILL HAS A WAY
OF IGNORING THE EVIDENCE.
HAROLD HAS THE EVIDENCE
AND I IGNORE THAT, MYSELF.
HE GOT ACROSS,
THAT'S THE MAIN THING.
THERE'S THE RESOURCEFULNESS
KICKING IN.
LIKE A TOWEL, BILL?
WHERE DID THAT COME FROM?
WELL, NOW, WAIT A SEC.
HOW DID HAROLD GET ACROSS?
YOU WERE ON THE OTHER SIDE.
HOW DID YOU GET--
OH, RESOURCEFULNESS!
(Laughing)
IT'S A BRIDGE, BILL.
HUH? YEAH.
THROW IN THE TOWEL.
THROW IT IN, THROW IT IN.
AND DON'T WORRY, FOLKS.
WHEREVER THEY GO,
THEY'LL BE LOST.
HERE ARE SOME CARTOON DRAWINGS
SENT BY SOME VIEWERS.
WELL, GOOD NEWS.
WE GOT OUR BARGE AND
OUR JUNIOR BACK ON TRACK.
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED
OF YOURSELF.
WHY? JUNIOR AND LITTLE NOREEN
HAD A FIGHT.
NOTHING TO DO WITH ME.
THEY'RE NOT EVEN ENGAGED
AND SHE'S ASKING JUNIOR
ABOUT HAVING KIDS.
SHE SAID SHE WANTED TO BUILD
LOCKERS FOR LIFE-JACKETS.
WHEN DID YOU SEE
ADULTS WEARING LIFE-JACKETS?
(Audience laughing)
SHE WAS GETTING JUNIOR
ONTO A SLIPPERY SLOPE.
YOU COULD TELL HE WASN'T
COMFORTABLE WITH THE SUBJECT.
WELL, WHO WOULD BE?
ALL THE LODGE MEMBERS
GOADING HIM ON,
POKING HIM IN THE RIBS.
I LOVE WHEN THEY HAVE
THOSE POLITE FIGHTS.
"DEAR...
"I THINK YOU'RE WRONG."
"NO, NO,
NO, NO.
"IT'S YOU
THAT IS WRONG."
"NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
"LET'S GO DISCUSS THIS
IN THE CAR."
"FINE, FINE, FINE, FINE!"
AND ALL THROUGH
THE CLENCHED TEETH.
CLENCHED TEETH, LIKE THAT.
IF JUNIOR GOT ANY MORE CORDIAL,
HE'D SNAP HIS UPPER PLATE.
I HOPE
THEY'RE OK.
YEAH, SURE THEY ARE.
THAT'S THE SECOND STAGE
OF A RELATIONSHIP -- ANGER.
RELATIONSHIPS HAVE STAGES?
YOU GOT DENIAL,
THEN YOU GOT ANGER,
THEN YOU GOT BARGAINING...
THOSE ARE THE STAGES
OF DEATH AND MOURNING.
AND MARRIAGE, HAROLD.
OH, YEAH, AND MARRIAGE.
IT'S THAT PART OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE EXAMINE
THOSE THREE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO DIFFICULT TO SAY.
(Audience):
"I DON'T KNOW!"
I LOVE WHEN THEY DO THAT.
ALL RIGHT, JOINING MY UNCLE RED
ON THE EXPERT PORTION
IS HIS BEST FRIEND,
MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
APPLAUSE, APPLAUSE, APPLAUSE.
(Applause)
OK, UM... OK, OK, OK, OK!
"DEAR EXPERTS, I AM A STUDENT
AT A HIGH SCHOOL
"IN A FARAWAY PLACE,
NOT NEAR POSSUM LAKE.
"UNLIKE YOUR HANDSOME NEPHEW,
HAROLD,
"I AM HAVING TROUBLE
AT SCHOOL WITH BULLIES.
"WHAT CAN I DO ABOUT THIS?
"SIGNED, IVAN IVANOVITCH."
(Audience laughing)
WELL, IVAN, YOU MAY NOT BE
AS HANDSOME AS HAROLD,
BUT YOU HAVE EXACTLY
THE SAME HANDWRITING.
(Harold):
THAT'S ODD.
(Laughing)
OK, UH, IVAN.
IVAN...
YOU KNOW.
ALL RIGHT.
IVAN, THE BEST WAY
TO DEAL WITH BULLIES
IS TO LEARN ONE OF THEM
SELF-DEFENCE THINGS.
THEY GOT THE JUDO
AND THE TAE KWON-DO.
YEAH, AND
THE FAH-SO LA-TI-DO.
PARDON ME, HAP?
FAH-SO LA-TI-DO.
IT'S A MARTIAL ARTS TECHNIQUE
THAT I DEVELOPED
WHEN I WAS DWIGHT EISENHOWER'S
BODYGUARD.
(Audience laughing)
(Harold): I NEVER HEARD
OF FAH-SO LA-TI-DO.
I SANG IT A FEW TIMES.
I ONLY TAUGHT IT
TO A FEW PEOPLE.
IT'S A TECHNIQUE
THAT COMBINES KARATE,
JUDO, NINJA, AND, UH,
RHYTHMIC GYMNASTICS.
(Audience laughing)
RHYTHMIC GYMNASTICS?!
ISN'T THAT WHERE YOU DO
THE GYMNASTICS
WITH THE RUBBER BALL AND BATON
AND YOU WAVE
THEM BIG RIBBONS AROUND?
THAT'S THE ONE.
I GOT A SILVER FOR THAT
IN THE '52 OLYMPICS.
I THOUGHT
RHYTHMIC GYMNASTICS
WAS A FEMALE
COMPETITION.
(Audience laughing)
I KNOW -- I SNUCK IN
WITH THE RUSSIAN WOMEN.
(Laughing and applause)
WELL, THE BARGE IS READY AND
JUNIOR'S ALL SET TO CAST OFF.
WHOA!
WHAT ABOUT HIS GIRLFRIEND --
IS SHE GOING?
NO, NOREEN'S WITH HER FRIENDS
AND JUNIOR'S WITH HIS.
AW, THEY BROKE UP.
NO, THEY HAD THEIR FIGHT --
THAT WAS THE BARGAINING PART.
NOW THEY'RE INTO THE FINAL
STAGE -- ACCEPTANCE.
NO MORE FALSE PRETENCES,
NO MORE BEING
ON YOUR BEST BEHAVIOUR.
(Laughing)
THAT WAS JUNIOR'S
BEST BEHAVIOUR?
NO, HAROLD, THEY'VE REACHED THE
BEST PART OF A RELATIONSHIP.
THEY'RE COMFORTABLE
WITH EACH OTHER.
THEY'RE NOT SPENDING TIME
TOGETHER.
THEY'RE GIVING EACH OTHER
SPACE.
THEY'RE TAKING EACH OTHER
FOR GRANTED.
THEY ACCEPT THE PERSON
FOR WHAT THEY ARE.
WHEN I'M MARRIED,
I'LL SPEND TIME WITH MY WIFE,
TEND TO HER NEEDS,
AND BE THERE FOR HER.
WHEN I HAVE A ROLLS ROYCE,
I'LL WASH AND WAX IT EVERY DAY.
(Audience laughing)
(Laughing)
YOU'LL NEVER HAVE
A ROLLS ROYCE.
RIGHT.
(Laughing and applause)
(Possum squeal)
OH!
MEETING TIME, HAROLD.
AWAY YOU GO, AWAY YOU GO.
I'M JUST KIDDING YOU!
YOU'LL PROBABLY GET MARRIED.
HEY, LYLE LOVETT MARRIED
JULIA ROBERTS,
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
YEAH! YEAH!
MIND YOU,
IT ONLY LASTED ABOUT AN HOUR.
(Laughing)
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING RIGHT HOME
AFTER WE DO SOME FISHING.
I'M PLANNING TO IGNORE YOU,
TAKE YOU FOR GRANTED,
NOT TALK TO YOU,
AND I'M HOPING YOU'RE IN
A ROMANTIC MOOD, TOO.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
(Red): ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
(Harold): UP AND AT 'EM,
DO YOUR BUSINESS.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN.
JUNIOR SINGLETON WANTED ME
TO ANNOUNCE THAT HE HAS
AN '82 PACER THAT HE WOULD LIKE
TO TRADE FOR A GARBAGE CAN...
OR A GREMLIN CONVERTIBLE.