YOU EVER NOTICE HOW WINDING
YOUR WINDOW DOWN BY HAND
MAKES YOU LOOK
LOWER MIDDLE CLASS?
HERE'S A CHEAP WAY
TO FIX THAT.
FIRST OF ALL, WHAT
YOU WANT TO DO IS
GET THE WINDOW WINDER
RIGHT OFF THERE.
THROW THAT AWAY.
NEXT, GET YOURSELF ONE
OF THESE BATTERY-POWERED
HAND MIXER-TYPE UNITS HERE.
YOU EVER NOTICE ON THESE
HOW THE BLADES GO IN
OPPOSITE DIRECTIONS?
REMEMBER THAT.
I'M GOING TO BE REFERRING
BACK TO THAT LATER ON.
THESE ARE REAL CHEAP,
ESPECIALLY IF THE BLADES
ARE MISSING.
OKAY, NOW, TO WIND
THE WINDOW UP,
ALL I DO IS STICK ONE
OF THESE BLADE RECEPTACLES
OVER THE WINDOW WINDER SHAFT.
AND THEN JUST
HIT THE BUTTON.
AND HOW DO I WIND IT DOWN?
WELL, THAT'S WHERE THAT
REVERSING DIRECTION THING
COMES IN THAT I WAS
REFERRING TO EARLIER.
I JUST POP THAT ON.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
GOT A BIT OF A
FINANCIAL SITUATION
GOING ON AT THE
LODGE THIS WEEK.
IF ANY OF YOU HAVE
SENT IN YOUR DUES OR
MADE A DONATION
OF ANY KIND,
WE DIDN'T GET IT.
I WENT DOWN TO THE BANK.
I ASKED TO SEE THE
POSSUM LODGE ACCOUNT,
THEY HANDED ME A
LITTLE JAR WITH COINS IN IT.
[ LAUGHING ]
WHAT ARE YOU
GUYS DOING HERE?
WE WERE DOING
A LITTLE ADVERTISING.
YEAH, WE WERE JUST KIND
OF HOPING, YOU KNOW,
TO TAP INTO THE POWER
OF TELEVISION'S EXPOSURE
TO MEET SOME
FOXY LADIES.
OH, MAN.
YEAH, WE'VE BEEN
HAVING A BIT OF TROUBLE
MEETING THE
LADIES AROUND HERE.
THAT'S BECAUSE
THEY KNOW YOU.
I'D LIKE TO
HELP YOU GUYS,
BUT I'VE GOT TO RAISE
SOME CASH FOR THE LODGE.
WELL MAYBE THAT'S AN AREA
WE CAN HELP YOU OUT
BECAUSE, I MEAN, LIKE,
I'VE GOT MY OWN SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING BUSINESS.
I'VE BEEN RAKING IT IN
PRETTY GOOD LATELY, RED.
I HEARD THAT.
YEAH.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I'VE GOT ENTREPRENEUR
WRITTEN ALL OVER ME.
WELL, MAYBE IF YOU HOSE IT OFF,
YOU COULD GET A DATE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
DATE!
THAT'S IT!
A BACHELOR AUCTION.
A BACHELOR AUCTION?
YEAH.
YOU AND ME AND SOME
OF THE OTHER FELLOWS
WILL GO INTO IT,
AND WOMEN WILL BID FOR
THE RIGHT TO SPEND AN
EVENING WITH US.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT DOING IT FOR MONEY.
LIKE, I PROMISED MY MOM
I'D STAY OUT OF
THE FAMILY BUSINESS.
NO, NO, NO.
THE LODGE GETS
THE MONEY, NOT US.
OH, OKAY.
WE GET THE DATES!
WELL, WHAT DO THE
WOMEN GET OUT OF IT?
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
KEEP THAT AS
A SURPRISE.
YEAH, GOOD POINT.
YEAH, GOOD PLAN.
TIME TO PLAY THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
TODAY'S PRIZE
IS A COUPON FOR THREE KISSES
AT BRENDA'S KISSING BOOTH
AT THE POSSUM LAKE FALL FAIR.
BRENDA'S PLEASED TO ANNOUNCE
THAT THE TESTS CAME
BACK NEGATIVE,
SO SHE'S BACK
IN BUSINESS.
THAT'S BRENDA'S
KISSING BOOTH,
KISSES ONE DOLLAR.
ASK ABOUT
OUR OTHER PRICES.
RED, YOU'VE GOT
30 SECONDS TO GET --
HAROLD TO GET,
THAT'S RIGHT --
TO GET HAROLD
TO SAY THIS WORD.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET HAROLD TO
SAY THIS WORD.
AND GO.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
YEAH.
OKAY, FOR A MAN, THIS IS
THE WORST THING TO BE.
JUDGMENTAL.
NO, I WAS THINKING
MORE ALONG THE LINES OF
YOU KNOW, DORK,
MORON, GOOFBALL.
OH! OH!
YOUR FAMILY TREE.
THAT'S INTERESTING
COMING FROM ONE
OF THE MAJOR KNOTHOLES
ON THAT TREE.
REMEMBER THAT GIRL
YOU WENT WITH IN COLLEGE?
WHAT DID SHE CALL YOU?
COLLECT.
NO. NO. NO.
WHAT NAME DID
SHE CALL YOU?
POOKY-PANTS.
THIS IS GOING
TO TAKE FOREVER.
CHOP CHOP HERE, RED.
YOU'RE JUST ABOUT
OUT OF TIME.
OKAY, HAROLD,
GUYS LIKE YOU
ARE REFERRED TO AS --
THE FUTURE.
NO, NO, HAROLD,
THIS IS AN INSULT.
AN INSULT?
OH, THAT'S DIFFERENT.
I WAS GOING
TO SAY GEEK.
YEAH!
[ BELL RINGING ]
TALKING ANIMALS TO
WITH THE LOCAL
ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER
ED FRID.
ED HAD BROUGHT US IN
AN ELECTRIC EEL TODAY.
C'MON UP HERE, ED.
C'MON, ED.
OKAY, SURE.
NO BIG DEAL.
SO WHAT DO THESE
ELECTRIC EELS EAT,
ANYWAY?
YOU KNOW,
ELECTRIC EELS
ARE ACTUALLY
A SPECIES OF FISH.
BUT YOU KNOW,
WE CALL THEM EELS
BECAUSE --
BECAUSE THEY
LOOK LIKE EELS.
THEY'RE ALL
SMOOTH AND BLACK.
THEY GOT THE SHARP TEETH
AND THE BEADY EYES, EH?
AND THEY'RE ALWAYS LOOKING
LIKE THEY'RE UP TO SOMETHING,
LIKE THEY'RE PLANNING
SOMETHING BEHIND YOUR BACK.
JUST LIKE AN EEL.
OKAY, NOW, THAT'S
GOOD INFORMATION,
BUT I ASKED YOU
WHAT THEY EAT.
OH, OH, RIGHT.
YEAH.
HERE'S WHAT HAPPENS.
A LITTLE FISH
COMES SWIMMING BY,
AND THE ELECTRIC EEL
WILL ELECTRIFY THE WATER
ALL AROUND IT.
LIKE THAT,
AND IT EATS THE LITTLE
FISH WHILE IT'S STILL
IN SHOCK.
OH.
THESE THINGS
CAN DROP A HORSE.
YEAH.
UP TO 600 VOLTS COMES
OUT OF THESE BABIES.
HOLY SMOKE.
YOU DON'T WANT
ONE OF THESE IN
THE BATHTUB WITH YOU.
NO, I WOULDN'T
ADVISE THAT.
NO.
NO, THAT'S NOT
A GOOD IDEA.
DON'T EVER BATHE
WITH ELECTRIC EELS.
BECAUSE THE
TEETH ALONE --
ALL RIGHT, ED.
ED, I WAS JOKING.
ED, IT WAS A JOKE.
DON'T --
DON'T EVER JOKE
ABOUT ELECTRIC EELS.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
FINE. FINE.
SO WHAT TEMPERATURE
DO YOU KEEP THE WATER
AT THERE FOR THE EEL?
OH, I DON'T KNOW,
JUST SORT OF WARM,
I GUESS.
YOU OKAY, ED?
YEAH, I'M GOOD.
YEAH.
I'M GOOD.
WHERE ARE WE?
YOU WERE JUST
TELLING THE PEOPLE
ABOUT THE FISH
YOU BROUGHT IN HERE.
YEAH.
REALLY?
OKAY.
WELL, AS
YOU CAN SEE,
THE FULL-GROWN
DOLPHIN
LOVES TO
PLAY WITH PEOPLE.
MANY OF THEM
HAVE THEIR OWN
TELEVISION PROGRAMS.
LIKE YOU, ED.
FIRST OF ALL,
I'M NOT ED.
AND THAT'S
NOT A DOLPHIN.
YES, IT IS.
THAT'S FLIPPY THE DOLPHIN.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH.
HE LOVES TO
BE PETTED TOO.
COME HERE, GUY.
NO, NO, NO.
ALL RIGHT, NOW.
ED -- ED -- ED.
I THINK WE'LL HAVE YOU
COME BACK ANOTHER DAY
WITH ANOTHER ANIMAL.
HOW'S THAT?
SOUNDS GOOD,
FLIPPY.
YOU KNOW, EVERY
ONCE IN AWHILE
YOUR WIFE WILL
LET YOU KNOW THAT
IT'S TIME TO GET RID
OF SOME OF YOUR JUNK.
YOU'LL KNOW THE TIME
BECAUSE IT STARTS TO GET COLD.
YOUR MEALS ARE COLD,
YOUR BED IS COLD,
AND EVERY TIME SHE LOOKS AT YOU
THE FURNACE KICKS ON.
THAT'S WHEN YOU KNOW IT'S TIME
TO CLEAN OUT THE STORAGE SHED.
NOW, I SUPPOSE YOU COULD
JUST THROW THIS STUFF
INTO A RAVINE, OR WHATEVER,
BUT IS THAT WHAT
A RESPONSIBLE PERSON DOES?
NOT ACCORDING
TO THE COPS.
NO, NO, TODAY'S HANDYMAN
GETS RID OF HIS JUNK
BY TURNING IT
INTO SOMETHING USEFUL.
YOUR WIFE CAN RELATE.
IT'S BASICALLY WHAT
SHE DID WITH YOU.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE
WHAT WE'VE GOT HERE.
CHAIR WITH NO LEGS;
GOT A LAWN MOWER
MISSING THE FRONT WHEELS;
GOT A CHUNK OF
AN EXTENSION LADDER;
AND A KID'S BIKE.
I SHOULD BE ABLE TO
MAKE SOMETHING OUT OF THIS.
IF AT FIRST YOU
DON'T SUCCEED,
USE MORE DUCT TAPE.
JUNK?
I DON'T SEE ANY JUNK.
I SEE A TOP-FUEL
ELIMINATION RAIL DRAGSTER.
OKAY, MAYBE WE DON'T HAVE
THE SHORT BLOCK 350 CHEVY
WITH THE DUAL QUADS
AND HEADERS ON THERE.
BUT A LAWN MOWER ENGINE
DOES ONE THING
JUST AS GOOD
AS ANY V-8,
IT MAKES A LOT OF NOISE,
ESPECIALLY IF WE
DE-INSTALL THE MUFFLER.
AND STICK IN
A LOW BACK PRESSURE
FUNNEL UNIT IN THERE.
ANYWAY, THE REAL
SECRET IS THE FUEL.
I PUT A GALLON OF STUFF IN
LEFT OVER FROM JUNIOR'S STAG.
I'M NOT SURE
WHAT IT IS,
BUT IF IT GOES THROUGH THAT
ENGINE AS FAST AS IT
WENT THROUGH JUNIOR,
WE'LL BE LOOKING
AT A LAND SPEED RECORD.
A CHAIR WITH NO LEGS
MAKES A PERFECT SEAT,
AND A LAWN MOWER HANDLE
MAKES A PERFECT STEERING WHEEL.
AS IT'S A DRAGSTER,
YOU DON'T STEER IT ANYWAY.
I'VE GOT ALL THE
CONTROLS AT MY FINGERTIPS...
IGNITION, THROTTLE
AND MULCH.
SO I'M BASICALLY
READY TO GO.
SO REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
I'VE GOT TO BURN
SOME SERIOUS RUBBER.
NEVER THOUGHT I'D SEE THE DAY
WHEN I'D BE TALKING ABOUT
CHEST IMPLANTS FOR MEN,
BUT THAT
DAY HAS ARRIVED.
OKAY, HERE'S THE DEAL.
GUYS ARE GETTIN' LITTLE PLASTIC
BAGS FULL OF SEA WATER
IMPLANTED INTO
THEIR CHESTS
SO THEY'LL LOOK LIKE
ARNOLD SCHWARZENEGGER
WITHOUT DOING
THE EXERCISING.
YOU LOOK LIKE A BARRACUDA,
BUT YOU ARE, IN FACT,
A JELLYFISH.
OKAY, THIS IS ONLY
ASKING FOR TROUBLE.
LIKE SAY YOU'RE
OUT ON THE STREET,
YOU'RE ALL PUMPED UP
WITH YOUR NEW PECKS,
SOME HOOD GRABS
SOME OLD LADY'S PURSE
AND TAKES OFF RUNNIN'
RIGHT TOWARDS YOU.
EVERYBODY'S YELLIN',
STOP HIM!
'CAUSE YOU'RE THIS
BIG MUSCULAR GUY, RIGHT?
YOU GOTTA DO SOMETHING.
SO YOU STEP IN
FRONT OF THIS THIEF,
AND HE RUNS
RIGHT INTO YOU.
BLAM!
YOUR IMPLANTS EXPLODE
LIKE EGGS ON A WINDSHIELD.
HE GOES BY,
YOU START CHASIN' HIM.
YOU SOUND LIKE TWO
RUBBER BOOTS FULL OF WATER.
AFTER ABOUT A BLOCK,
YOU DROWN FROM
THE INSIDE.
SO FORGET THE IMPLANTS.
MY GRANDFATHER
ONCE TOLD ME,
NEVER LET YOUR MIND WRITE A
CHEQUE THAT YOUR BODY ISN'T
PREPARED TO CASH.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLIN'
FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WELL, WE GOTTA
THINK OF SOME WAY
OF SWEETENING THE POT.
THE AUCTION'S
TONIGHT,
AND SO FAR IT'S
JUST MIKE AND ME IN IT.
OH, MAN.
[ AUDIENCE WHISTLING ]
Red:
THAT'S A NICE SUIT
YOU GOT THERE, MIKE.
WELL, THANKS.
YOUR TAILOR EXPECTING
TO PUT ON A LOT OF
WEIGHT AND HEIGHT?
VERY FUNNY.
IT'S NOT CUSTOM MADE.
I GOT IT OFF THE RACK,
AND I WAS IN KIND OF A HURRY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WAS THE STORE
ABOUT TO CLOSE?
NO, IT WAS
ABOUT TO OPEN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
YOU KNOW, WINSTON,
IF MIKE'S GONNA BE
WEARING THAT TO
THE AUCTION,
YOU BETTER SPRUCE
UP A LITTLE BIT;
OTHERWISE, YOU'RE NOT
GONNA GET ANY BIDS.
OH, WINSTON'LL
BE FINE, DALTON.
NO MATTER HOW
GOOD MIKE LOOKS,
HE'S ONLY GONNA
GO HOME WITH
ONE WOMAN.
WELL, WE DON'T
KNOW THAT.
MIND YOU, IF IT WAS
MORE THAN FIVE,
IT WOULD BE
MY PERSONAL BEST.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELL, I MIGHT BE ABLE
TO GIVE YOU A RUN FOR
YOUR MONEY, PAL.
DON'T FORGET I DIDN'T
MAKE IT BIG IN THE
SEWAGE BUSINESS
BY BACKING AWAY
FROM CHALLENGES.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
I'M GONNA GO OUT
AND SEE IF I CAN'T DRUM UP A
COUPLE MORE BACHELORS
BECAUSE I LOVE TO SEE PEOPLE
I KNOW BEING HUMILIATED.
[ LAUGHING ]
I THINK I'M JUST GONNA STAND
HERE AND LOOK GOOD.
[ LAUGHTER ]
FIVE WOMEN, MIKE?
UH, YEAH,
IT WAS A LADIES'
BASKETBALL TEAM.
OH, MAN.
DID YOU MAKE TO
THE PLAYOFFS?
NO, I FOULED OUT.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, WE'RE HERE
TO SOLVE A PROBLEM
BETWEEN DALTON HUMPHREY
AND HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
DALTON, WHY DON'T YOU
GIVE US YOUR SIDE?
[ SIGHS ]
THAT MAN
IS A LIAR.
COULD YOU BE MORE
SPECIFIC AT ALL?
I DRAW YOUR ATTENTION
TO EXHIBIT "A."
RED, COULD YOU
PLEASE HOLD THAT UP?
NOW, THAT IS A MAN'S
WHITE GLOVE THAT BELONGS
TO HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
HE CLAIMS THAT IT WAS
ORIGINALLY THE PROPERTY OF
NONE OTHER THAN
NAPOLEON BONAPARTE.
HE WANTS TO DONATE IT TO
THE POSSUM LAKE CURIO AND
NATURAL ODDITIES MUSEUM,
AND I AM THE ONE WHO HAS
TO AUTHENTICATE IT.
THIS YOUR GLOVE, HAP?
GIVE IT
TO ME, RED.
LET ME HAVE
A LOOK.
YEP.
YOU SEE?
SEE THAT "M" ON THAT TAG?
THAT STANDS
FOR
MAIN,
AND THAT'S
FRENCH FOR HAND.
I THINK THAT "M"
STANDS FOR MEDIUM.
I BELIEVE THAT'S
FRENCH FOR 42-D.
YOU SEE WHAT
I'M SAYIN', RED?
HE'S LYIN' THROUGH
HIS TEETH.
THERE'S NO WAY THAT NAPOLEON
GAVE HIM THAT GLOVE.
WELL, THAT'S OBVIOUS.
NAPOLEON DIED A THOUSAND YEARS
BEFORE I WAS BORN.
THIS GLOVE WAS GIVEN TO ME
BY HIS GREAT GRANDSON,
BOB BONAPARTE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I SAVED HIS
LIFE ONE NIGHT
WHEN HE CAME INTO A
SATAN'S CHOICE MEETING
WEARING HIS
MIME COSTUME.
I'VE NEVER BEEN A BIG
FAN OF MIMES MYSELF.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
THEY DON'T TALK.
WELL, LOOK AT
THAT GLOVE.
IT'S NOT ANTIQUE,
IT'S BRAND NEW!
YEAH, IT IS IN
PRETTY GOOD SHAPE, HAP.
WELL,
OF COURSE IT IS.
THIS WAS ON THE HAND
THAT HE ALWAYS KEPT
INSIDE HIS JACKET.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT IT,
NAPOLEON CONQUERED EUROPE
SINGLE-HANDEDLY.
RED, CAN'T YOU
DO SOMETHING?
I MEAN, THAT GLOVE
BELONGS TO HAP,
NOT NAPOLEON.
I THINK I CAN PROVE IT
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
LOOK, I REST MY CASE.
SORRY, DALTON.
HE'S GOT A PRECEDENT THERE.
IT THE GLOVE DOESN'T FIT,
IT BELONGS TO THE FRENCH TWIT.
Red:
UH, YOUNG WALTER
CALLED US UP.
HAD AN EMERGENCY
OF SOME KIND.
HE WAS STUCK,
APPARENTLY, SOMEWHERE'S,
AND DALTON AND I
COME UP THERE --
I DON'T KNOW WHETHER
HE WAS IN A TREE,
OR THERE'S A RAVINE
CLOSE TO THE ROAD THERE.
I THOUGHT MAYBE HE MIGHT HAVE
FALLEN DOWN THE RAVINE.
MAY THAT WAS --
BUT, UH, --
NO, HE WASN'T
DOWN THERE.
THAT STICK HAD BEEN SITTIN'
DOWN THERE FOR A COUPLE
OF WEEKS.
DON'T KNOW WHERE
THAT WAS FROM.
BUT, UH, DUNNO WHERE
THE HECK HE IS.
OH, WAIT A MINUTE.
UH-OH.
OH, MAN.
WHAT?
JUST USE THE --
USE THE --
BRING 'ER DOWN
WITH THE CONTROLS.
HIT THE DOWN --
JUST BRING 'ER DOWN
WITH THE CONTROL.
HIT THE CONTROL.
OH, THEY'RE NOT WORKING.
OH, THE CONTROLS
AREN'T WORKING.
OKAY.
DON'T WORRY.
C'MON.
C'MON, DALTON.
HERE, BOY.
C'MON, BOY.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW WE HAD A SPECIAL LADDER
WE GOT FROM
THE R.K.O. STUDIOS.
THESE ARE HARD
TO COME BY, BELIEVE ME.
THEY'RE A GREAT UNIT,
YOU KNOW.
IF YOU CAN GET AHOLD OF ONE,
THEY'RE UNBELIEVABLE.
A GREAT SYSTEM.
BUT YOU NEED THAT KIND OF
LENGTH WHEN YOU'RE GOIN'
UP THE --
REAL HEAVY, AND LEVERAGE
IS MAJOR HERE.
GET 'ER UP.
I THINK IT'S GONNA
BE JUST PERFECT.
JUST PERFECT.
HANG ON, WALTER.
HELP'S ON ITS WAY.
HERE IT COMES --
OH, NO.
OH, OH, OH, OH!
AND DOWN THE RAVINE.
OKAY, NOW, IF WE CAN HOOK
ON TO ONE OF THE LEVERS
OR AN EDGE,
ANYTHING STICKING
OUT OF THIS --
NOW, YOU STAND BACK, WALTER.
GET BACK AWAY.
WE'RE GONNA TRY TO LASSO ONTO
A PIECE OF THE METAL,
AND WE CAN PULL
THE WHOLE UNIT DOWN.
JUST GET HER UP THERE.
HOOK ONTO SOMETHING
THERE, DALTON.
HOOK ONTO SOMETHING.
YEAH, YOU'LL
BE ALL RIGHT.
OH, UH, YEAH.
WELL, UH,
OH!
OH, OH, OH!
GIVE 'ER A GOOD ONE!
AND, OH, MY GOSH!
WELL, OH!
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
HE'S DOWN, YOU KNOW.
OH, AND HE'S GOOD.
AND HE'S GOOD.
AND HE BROUGHT
THE LADDER BACK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, A LOT OF
THE YOUNG GUYS GROW UP
MISSIN' OUT LEARNIN'
HOW TO USE THEIR HANDS
BECAUSE THEY FIGURE
ANYTHING THEY NEED
THEY CAN JUST GO OUT AND
BUY AT A STORE, YOU KNOW.
WELL, I'LL TELL YA,
IT'S NO KINDNESS TO LET
A YOUNG GUY GROW UP
TO BE A WUSS.
SO TODAY WE'RE
GONNA SPEND --
HERE,
GIVE ME THAT.
WE'RE GONNA SPEND
SOME QUALITY TIME
LEARNIN' HOW
TO BUILD A --
WHAT ARE
WE GONNA DO?
YEAH, YEAH.
OKAY.
OKAY, BUT WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
WHAT DOES IT
LOOK LIKE?
WHAT -- WHAT -- WHAT --
WHAT IS IT, HUH?
WHAT DOES THAT LOOK LIKE?
DON'T TOUCH IT!
DON'T TOUCH IT.
YOU'LL BREAK IT.
OKAY, IT'S
A BIRDHOUSE.
IT'S A BIRDHOUSE.
WE'RE GONNA BUILD
A BIRDHOUSE.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, THE FIRST THING WE
WANNA DO WITH THE BIRDHOUSE
IS NAIL THIS SIDE
ONTO THE BOTTOM.
AND I'M GONNA NEED
SOME HELP WITH THIS.
I'M GONNA NEED SOME HELP,
SO ARE YOU GONNA HELP
OLD DALTON WITH THIS?
ARE YOU GONNA?
SURE YOU ARE!
OKAY, YOU HOLD THAT GOOD.
JUST HOLD IT ANYWHERE.
NO, NOT THERE.
NO, NO, THAT'S NOT
STEADY ENOUGH.
JUST HOLD IT --
NO, NO, NOT THERE!
I TOLD YOU
NOT THERE.
OH, GIVE THAT TO ME.
[ LAUGHING ]
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
THE FIRST THING
WE GOTTA DO,
GET A NAIL
STARTED, RIGHT?
GET THE NAIL IN,
GIVE 'ER A LITTLE TAP OR TWO.
TAP, TAP, TAP.
OKAY, AND NOW WE'RE READY TO
LINE UP THE BOTTOM.
WE'LL GET A GOOD --
AH!
OH, BOY,
THAT DID HURT.
YOU DON'T WANNA DO THAT
TOO OFTEN, DO YOU?
OKAY, I JUST SHOWED
YOU THAT,
SO YOU CAN SEE
WHAT WILL HAPPEN IF
YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL.
ALL RIGHT?
I THINK THAT'S ENOUGH
WOOD SHOP FOR TODAY.
GO OFF AND --
OFF YOU GO.
JUST DON'T GROW UP
TO BE A WUSS!
BYE BYE.
NICE BOY,
HE'S JUST NOT THAT HANDY.
SOMETHING YOU'RE
BORN WITH, I GUESS.
[ BELL RINGING ]
OH, MAN.
Audience:
WAH-O-O-O!
ALL RIGHT.
SETTLE DOWN.
SIT DOWN,
WINSTON.
OKAY.
WELCOME TO THE FIRST
ANNUAL POSSUM LODGE
BACHELOR AUCTION.
WE'RE ALL SET TO --
OH, ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
I'VE JUST BEEN
INFORMED THAT OUR, UH,
FIRST ENTRY IS A BIT
OF A SURPRISE VISITOR
AND A LATE ENTRY,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHO IT IS.
BRING HIM IN
WHOEVER HE IS.
OUR FIRST BACHELOR,
COME ON IN.
Audience:
WAH-O-O-O!
[ WHISTLING AND APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, HERE
GOES NOTHIN'.
UH, WILL ANY OF YOU
GIVE US 50 BUCKS?
OH, MAN.
ALL RIGHT.
HOW ABOUT $100?
HOW ABOUT $200?
THAT'S OKAY.
NO HARD FEELINGS.
HOW ABOUT $300?
OKAY, LET'S SPEED THIS UP
BEFORE YOU LADIES REGAIN
YOUR SENSES.
HOW ABOUT $500?
SOLD!
THE WINNER, IF WE CAN
CALL HER THAT,
IS THIS LADY RIGHT HERE
IN THE FRONT ROW.
OH, MY GOSH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
NEXT BACHELOR.
WINSTON, DO YOU WANNA
STAND UP HERE?
CAN WE START THE
BIDDING OFF AT,
SAY, $100?
$100?
OKAY, HOW ABOUT
50 -- 50 --
YOU KNOW WHAT,
I'M GONNA GROUP
THE NEXT TWO ITEMS.
MIKE,
GET UP HERE.
AND, UH, LADIES,
YOU JUST START THE --
ANYBODY GIVE ME A --
TELL ME WHERE I SHOULD
START THE BIDDING.
I'LL BID $10.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK
ANYBODY'S THAT DESPERATE
FOR A DATE, DALTON.
IT'S NOT A DATE.
I NEED HELP CLEANIN'
OUT MY WAREHOUSE.
SOUNDS GOOD
TO ME.
YOU GOT 'EM BOTH
FOR 10 BUCKS.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, THERE'S THE MEETING.
C'MON, GUYS.
YEAH, YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
I'LL BE COMIN' STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETIN',
AND I'M SO GLAD I STAYED
FAITHFUL TO YOU OVER THE YEARS.
I TELL YOU, BEING
MARRIED IS TOUGH ENOUGH.
DATING'S EVEN WORSE.
I CAN'T IMAGINE DOIN' BOTH.
HATS OFF TO
FRANK GIFFORD, HUH?
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHIN'.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND ALL
THE ELIGIBLE BACHELORS UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
closed captioning performed
by INTERCAPTION CANADA
www.intercaption.com.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
TAKE YOUR PLACE.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU GO AHEAD.
I'M NOT HERE.
I AM NOT HERE.
YOU'RE NEVER HERE.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
BOW YOUR HEADS FOR
THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.