You know, as I get older,
I find that my reflexes
are really
slowing down
and my reaction time to, say,
an approaching brick
or a propane fireball
is really too slow
to be effective.
So what was happening is
I'm getting a lot of
head injuries,
and I'm afraid it's going
to start ammenting me
fectally --
I mean, affect --
no, that's right,
ammenting me fectally.
Ow!
So here's a
cheap, easy way
to protect what just
recently has become
the most important
part of your body...
your brain.
Get yourself one of these
inflatable kids' life rings.
You can just grab
this off any kid,
but don't be a bully,
make sure it's a kid
who can swim.
This life ring is going
to become my brain bag.
I'm just letting
the air out of it
so I can fill it with,
that's right,
shaving cream.
It's kind of
like an air bag
but I'm not an air head,
so I'm using shaving cream.
I mean you could
use whipped cream,
but I want to
survive close shaves.
I don't want to get
whipped or creamed.
See, I still got
my sense of humour.
It hasn't ammented
me fectally.
Okay, I've connected the
shaving cream to
the life ring
by going through this
motion detector.
Now, if anything
approaches my head,
the detector will fill the
life ring with shaving cream
and cushion my melon so
that nothing can bean me.
Here, let me know you.
Let's say I was putting
in a supporting wall
and some of the duct
tape let go...
Sorry, instinct.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
All right. All right.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
A bit of a setback up at
the lodge this week.
The town of Port Asbestos
has come up with a new
tourist attraction,
the World's
Biggest Marshmallow.
This thing is huge.
They've got it
mounted on display
on the top of a hill,
90 feet in the air.
I mean, you can
see it for miles.
So everybody's going there
instead of coming here.
Now, I know it
shouldn't bother us
because in Canada everybody's
nice, you know.
I think some days I'm just
not that Canadian.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Hello.
Care for a Port Asbestos
marshmallow?
No, and quit
helping the enemy!
They're not the enemy.
They created attraction
for the whole area.
See my cool shirt?
Yeah, Harold, you do
have a soft spot,
but the sign
is two feet low.
You shouldn't
be jealous.
You should congratulate
them on a very successful
tourism campaign.
Well, okay,
I'll tell you what,
they've made the world's
biggest marshmallow,
we'll have the world's
biggest bonfire and toast 'em.
How's that?
[ GIGGLING ]
Hey, I think you just
said something smart.
Really?
Yeah I know, I'm as
shocked as you are but...
That's what we should do.
We should have the
world's biggest something.
Well, you're the world's
biggest something,
but nobody would
pay to see it.
Anyway, we don't have
anything here, Harold,
and Port Asbestos
just lucked out,
finding that
huge marshmallow.
It's not a real
marshmallow, Uncle Red.
Did you not see
where they put it?
Well, yeah, on that hill
where the water tower
used to be.
It must have cost
a fortune to move
that, eh?
That is the water tower.
They just painted it to
look like a marshmallow.
Well, that's not
going to fool
anybody.
Uncle Red, that's
what we need to do.
We need to paint our
water tower to look like
an attraction of some sort.
Like what?
I don't know maybe
something medical.
It looks like
a... umm...
a suppository.
Oh, yeah, sure,
great idea.
The world's largest
suppository
and we live where
they stuck it.
Oh yeah.
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Tonight's winner receives
a free savings account at
Possum Lake Savings & Loan,
where you don't get
any of our loans
and we get all
of your savings.
All right, Dalton,
cover your ears.
Red, you've got 30 seconds
to get Dalton Humphreys
to say this word...
All right,
Winston.
And GO!
All right, Dalton,
you have your wallet,
your wife has her...
Hand out.
Okay, no, but she carries
her money in her...
Tight little fist.
No, no, this is
something your wife
always carries with her.
A grudge?
Okay, no.
This is something a woman
gets everything in.
A divorce!
Okay, no, okay, okay.
A French woman calls this
her porte monnaie,
but an English woman
calls it her...
No, no, no!
Okay, Dalton,
a woman never goes to the
powder room without her...
Friend?
Okay, okay.
This is something that
women have, okay?
Sometimes they have
shoulder straps
and they can be bulky,
it might be made of leather,
or it might even bulge
out at the seams.
It's called a...
Halter top.
No, no, no.
Red, almost out
of time, here.
Yeah, okay.
Okay, Dalton,
where does your wife
keep her credit cards?
She hides them where
she knows I won't look.
And where is that?
On her person.
Yes? Yes! Yes!
DALTON:
You know the great
thing about fishing?
It's the sounds.
RED: Amen.
Nobody talking
at you, you know,
jabbering on and on
complaining about
everything
the way my daughter
does as if, you know,
whatever happened there's
always a kerfuffle
about it.
You know, it's like
the end of the world
because she dropped
her mascara in the toilet
and now she has to go
a whole day without
painting those
Count Dracula lines
around her eyes.
Forget that maybe there
are bigger issues
in the world
than, you know,
her eyelashes!
Of course, she's been
so spoiled and catered
to all her life,
Dalton! Dalton!
I just get sick --
Dalton!
What!?
What's so great
about fishing?
Oh.
Yeah, right.
MIKE: Besides, you should
be saying this
to your daughter
not to us.
DALTON:
I can't talk to her,
she won't listen to me.
You don't talk to her,
she doesn't need to.
You know,
parenting is one of
the most difficult
things you'll ever do.
It's next to
unlocking an ATM.
My parents were great.
I should call
them sometimes.
Well, my parents
lied to me.
They pretended they
had a happy marriage,
so I wanted to try it.
Thanks a lot.
Well, I had quite
a few dads
so I saw a lot of
different parenting
approaches.
Ignoring me was the
most common one.
But there were
a few of them
who took the
time to pass on
life skills.
I think it's called
aiding and abetting.
Well, my parents were
pretty strict, you know.
I was a pretty
miserable child,
not the happy-go-lucky
guy you know.
RED:
Boy, my parents weren't.
They let me do
anything I wanted.
MIKE: Well, that just
goes to show you,
parents can do anything
and they'll screw it up.
Yeah, I think
the truth is
nobody knows how to
be a good parent.
You just try to let your
kid know that you care
about them,
and do the best you can.
You know, that might
be the wisest thing
you've ever said.
Gimme five.
Ha!
Who's your daddy?
I have no idea.
[ APPLAUSE ]
You know, one of
the worst problems
you can have on a car
is lousy brakes.
A brake job is expensive
so naturally,
I have a better idea.
We had some relatives stay
with us last weekend.
I'll spare you the
grisly details,
but I did end up taking
them to the airport
nine hours before
their flight,
and they didn't mind.
But I noticed that when
the planes come in
they have these
flaps that they use
to help slow them down
when they're landing.
Like Junior Singleton does
with his ears when he's skiing.
They're big flaps that kind
of pop out of the body
and slow the plane down.
Old Man Sedgwick had
something pop out of his body,
sure slowed him down.
But that got me thinking,
can we add big
flaps to a car?
How would we do that?
If flaps are good enough
for an F-18 or a F-16,
they're good enough
for a F-O-R-D.
But we need more than
just the hood to open
so hook up a couple of
clothes line pulleys
and run a rope from the
hood ornament
down to each of your doors
and even the trunk lid.
Okay, are there any more
flaps on this car?
Too bad it doesn't
have a sunroof.
Hmm...
[ CHUCKLES ]
Okay, my new air brakes
are going to bring the car
to a screeching halt.
Okay, well maybe not
screeching because it's air,
but I'll be
able to stop
to the sound of
the wind I've made.
That's not right.
Anyway, you can see how easy
it is to make your own, fancy,
environmentally-friendly way
to stop your car.
When it comes to making
your own brakes,
don't let anybody
stop ya'.
Whatever...
Remember, if women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
Now if you'll excuse me,
it's time for my lunch
or I should say,
my lunch brake.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Men have a reputation for
not being very good
communicators,
but you'll never
hear us say that.
Oh sure, we're not always
too good at expressing
our feelings.
But if we're planning
to actually do something,
you always
hear about it.
For instance, when a guy
gets up from the table
to go to the bathroom,
he never just quietly
excuses himself.
He tries to keep everybody
up to speed by saying,
a gotta take a wiz.
Loud enough to be heard
by everyone at the table
and ideally the
entire restaurant.
Now, he doesn't have to
do this, no one asked him to,
but he does it out
of common courtesy
just in case you think he's
leaving to invade
Turkmanistan.
However, one area of
communication men excel at
is letting you know
how they feel.
Not emotionally
of course,
let's be real,
you know.
I'm talking about how
we're feeling physically,
especially if it's bad.
If a guy has a bad back,
bad cramps, bad ache
or bad gas...
you're going
to hear about it.
We're good communicators.
We're just really
bad listeners.
They should criticize
us for that,
or maybe they did.
Remember,
I'm pulling for you.
We're all in
this together.
At Rothschild's,
we take full responsibility
for your septic system.
The suck stops here.
Well, we've all been
wracking our brains
trying to think of
something we could make
that would be the biggest
one in the world.
Possum Lake qualifies as
the world's largest
stagnant pond,
not too many merchandising
opportunities there...
maybe mosquito repellent
or something.
Now, Harold's working on
the world's largest
roll of duct tape
but that's a
man's project
so I'm sure he's
having problems.
Uncle Red?
Oh, yeah,
yeah, yeah.
I'm losing all the
hair on my knuckles.
Oh yeah, how
about your palms?
[ CHUCKLES ]
I don't think it's
a very good idea.
No, no, although if
tourists do come up here,
they'll never leave.
The world's
largest fly strip.
Don't worry
about it, Harold,
I've got the answer.
This is a scale model
of the kind of silos
we have all around
the area here.
We just paint these up
and call it like,
the world's largest
nail or something.
Oh, I know.
I've got an idea.
The ladies
will love this.
What?
The world's
biggest lipstick.
Well, yeah, yeah,
and you could stand
beside it
and we'd have the
world's biggest lipstick
and the world's
biggest dipstick.
Uncle Red, you know we have
these creative sessions.
You're supposed to
be sensitive to the
feelings of others.
Oh yeah?
Okay, here's what
we're doing, Harold.
I'm thinking we paint all
the silos all different
colours, okay,
and we call them the
world's biggest
crayons, eh?
The kids'll love it,
the parents'll love it.
What about seniors?
Well, they hate
everything.
They'll just come up
and complain, you know.
Hey, Gramps, c'mon up and
see another stupid waste
of money
that would've never
been allowed in
your day.
You know,
that kind of thing.
I think you're onto a real
winner of an idea here.
Pardon me?
Wow, that was weird.
Yeah, that's very weird.
I like your idea.
Oh, boy.
I think we should
do what you say.
Wow.
I know, that's...
Okay, well...
let's go, I guess.
Am I losing it?
You never had it,
Harold.
[ APPLAUSE ]
RED:
Mike had invited Bill
to come out a play squash.
Bill had never
played squash before
and was not familiar
with the game,
but he had the sweatsuit on
so Mike got down
to his shorts and...
I'm not sure the Bill
knows how to get down
to his --
that's not what we mean by --
that's unfortunate,
there must have been
a gravity spot there.
Anyway, Mike's got
the outfit on.
Bill, what are
you wearing?
Bill, what is that?
No, that's not.
There's something --
That's just wrong, you know.
So, of course, Mike has
the regular squash racket.
Bill doesn't know what
a regular squash racket is
so he apparently
had brought a banjo.
No, that's not...
so he puts that aside
for the moment.
He did actually have
a real squash racket.
Now, Mike puts
the goggles on.
Bill has -- what have you
got there in your hand?
It's an... owww...
That's an odd
place to carry --
No, that's not where
the racket goes, Bill.
Not at all, no.
Now, again, when Bill
heard the word squash,
he thought that you played
with a real squash,
which he had
brought with him.
No Bill, no, that's not --
You play with a little,
round...
There, it's a little,
round squash ball.
Okay, so now they got to
decide who's going to serve.
Apparently what they do
is they've got the label
on one side and nothing
on the other
so you spin it and
somebody picks it.
Mike picked
the label side.
So Bill spins the racket
and away it fli --
and uhh...
and Mike just kicks
it over, finally.
Okay, so it's the other side
so I guess that means
Bill's going to serve.
So Bill gets up,
goes up there, comes back,
Mike volleys, no ball.
Where's the ball?
It's in his racket.
Okay.
All right.
Easy, easy easy.
Okay, now it's
Mike's serve.
He fires it up, high,
comes down bounces below
going up into his shorts.
No, I hope that's
not an injury.
No, he's okay.
Mike's going to hit it.
Bill says no.
Okay, the mark is still --
I'm not going to ask.
It's none of my business.
No, no, no, no.
Moving right along.
Okay, so where
they go again.
Nice couple of
volleys here.
Up and she goes and then
Mike volleys her back and --
On this one, got a little
too close to the wall.
Okay, now what.
Oh, I know, the banjo.
So he gets the banjo out.
He serves her up there
and then --
When Mike swings,
he hits the light switch.
Okay, so now they're
playing squash --
Okay, now this is --
Now, you know, you know.
Okay, okay, this is wrong.
This is -- ohh....
So Bill comes over,
flips the light on.
Oh boy...
And that see through outfit
is not working for him at all.
There's the ball and that's
how squash got it's name.
Remember when you got your
VCR so you could tape
all those shows you
didn't have time to watch
only to realize that you
the tapes either?
Of course now you've
got a DVD.
So what do you do
with all your old tapes?
Well, you could mail
them to a friend.
Just drop them into a bag
and then seal them up with
your new string dispenser.
Or how about this one,
a cassette clock?
Just mount a clock motor
on to one of the reels
and then mark off the
seconds, minutes and hours
onto the tape
with a white pen.
The clock motor runs so slow
that a 180-minute tape
takes exactly 12 hours
to get to the end,
so then you just take
the motor off one
and move it over to
the other reel
and wind the
whole thing back.
I mean the numbers are
going by outside-down
but I'm sure you
get used to it.
Here's another one,
here's a hint for you.
You know, every cassette has
a ratchet inside
that stops the tape from
slipping back the other way.
Well, there's a button
way down deep inside.
If you can push that with
something like a golf tee,
it lets the tape
come out freely.
Have you figured
it out yet?
That's right...
Okay, now for reeling
her back in,
use the window winder
from the driver's side
of a '62 Chev Belair.
If you can't get a Belair
you could substitute
a Pontiac Strato Chief.
Newer models
might work too,
if I owned one,
I'd know for sure.
Oh, I got one!
Now, if you're left-handed
you could just flip
the rod over
but you'd have to
reel the other way
so you'd need the window
winder from the passenger side.
Oh man, I've caught
this fish before.
It's a re-run.
[ APPLAUSE ]
This brain storm of mine
is going to put Possum Lake
on the Michelin Guide.
We're going to be the top
tourist destination
in the world.
Oh sure, you can go to Rome
if you want to see
the Eiffel Tower,
but it you want to see
the world's biggest crayons,
you're going to have
to come right here.
Uncle Red?
Yeah?
I'm here
with bad news.
Harold, you here
is bad news.
Well, you know this idea
of painting the silo,
how I couldn't think of
anything that might
go wrong?
Yes.
Well, I thought
of something.
Well it's too late,
Harold,
the silos are
all painted.
See, that's the problem.
Yeah, 'cause silos,
they're usually silver
to reflect the sun's heat,
but now that since
you've painted them
and I'm guessing
not white, right?
Well, uh, no, green
and brown and purple
and flat black.
Oh, flat black...
Can you imagine the heat
that's building up
inside that silo?
Well, so what?
I mean,
what's in them?
Corn!
[ EXPLOSIONS ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Meeting time.
Yeah, you know, you
should get a head start.
You may need
extra butter.
Wow.
Okay, if my wife
is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting.
I tried making the world's
biggest crayons,
and I came this close to
being the world's
biggest dufus.
Thank goodness
for Harold.
And to the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself
and Harold
and the whole gang up here
at Possum Lodge...
keep your stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Sit down. Sit down.
Sit down back there.
Meeting's coming
to order, guys.
Everybody's got to sit down.
Sit down.
All rise.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
RED: Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the man's prayer.
I'm a man,
but I can change
if I have to...
I guess.
Okay men,
the bad news is
that until all the explosions
have stopped,
we're going to have to stay
down here in the basement.
The good news is,
it's movie night.