Live from the depths of the wilderness where
they can't see the forest for Louise, it's
the red green show starring the man the
Indians call the old guy who drives that ugly
van on TV that we see the greatest living
woodsman since Davy Crockett.
And he's buried now.
So there you go on that one.
Ladies and gentlemen, your friend and my
uncle, the star of the Red Green Show.
Here he is now, ladies and gentlemen.
Mr. Red Green Guy.
Thank you, and I welcome the Possum Lodge.
I'm red green, the head of the head of the
Lodge.
It's a job that I don't take lightly, but
should.
Harold is not only my nephew, he's also my
producer and director.
And that means I can do stuff like this.
But he's not much of a nephew, either.
Anyway, had an interesting wake up at the
lodge.
The guys decided to take up birdwatching,
which we always used to think of as kind of a
sissy thing to do. But then they found out
that birdwatchers carry wind skins and and
they don't get accidentally shot, so it
sounded pretty good.
Plus, the guys figured they can do it
sitting on the couch by the big picture
window. And any sport that happens close to
the fridge is real popular at Possum Lodge.
Wow, that's great.
How many different birds have they seen?
Well, as of this morning, two hundred and
seventy nine stinky, you wanted to be able to
count the eggs in the omelet this morning.
But oh man, Cedric said no eggs.
It was too hard to look at two hundred.
Wow, that's amazing.
Well, you know, takes birdwatchers years to
see that money.
They saw him just in a few days.
Wow, that's incredible to see that many
different species.
How do you mean different species?
Well, you know, different. Not the same.
You know, like yellow breasted.
So and so's and red throated doohickey.
Oh wow. I don't know without hair.
I know they like they saw 47 birds at once
when a flock of seagulls went through last
night's garbage.
Oh no. Uncle Red, you don't count the
individual birds.
You count the individual species.
Oh oh of.
Then they haven't seen two hundred and
seventy nine birds.
They've seen
Three
Point and then they kind of upset.
They may drop birdwatching when they find.
Find out about this. What about what about
sucking back on wine skins?
You know, is that a sport you're like like
an armchair athlete would do well?
Yeah. Well, like wine tasting, maybe.
Yeah. But you know, you can't just like,
slosh it down.
You got to like, you got to sniff the
bouquet, enjoy the color, study it.
If you will sniff the cork, take a little
swill of wine into your mouth, winch it
around and then just spit it out.
Oh, you spit it out. Well, that's a food
fight.
That's got to be a sport.
Well, yeah, OK.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Excellent that you write that.
No, no sign of him anywhere, Dr.
Murray. Oh, Bill, this is great.
My backside tingling.
Let your hands do. And he hit some man with
a baseball bat.
Well, you got to try this doc, you know,
what's up?
I ordered a new fish locator to restore a
fish locator.
Oh yeah, that sort of takes the sport
Out of it. And I hope, though, it's the kind
of sonar looking to analyze the maybe.
Outside it outside
To do that.
Look, I didn't know you were in the Navy
Dock.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Medical officer on the first solar powered
submarine.
Very hush hush.
The whole thing. Oh yeah, it was the the
world's first environmentally friendly sub
world. Mm hmm. None of your nuclear power
for us.
No, sir. Just a sun powered sub carrying 20
ICBM.
That's amazing.
Oh, you look me right in the eye when you
said that.
Of course. Louisa Morris.
Well, there it is, Harold.
Oh, come to Papa PBB.
Be careful with that. Come on. We have we we
haven't gotten paid for that yet.
All right. Good. Ok, I want you to go get
that battery from out of the truck.
All right. Out Trout.
The doctor is in.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I think a little money needs to change hands
right now.
Oh hey, relax, Murray.
I'll pay you back on the fish I catch.
Oh hey, you said it in paper itself?
Well, I did say that I think it'll pay for
itself to you.
No, I'm not that lucky.
I need that money up front.
How am I going to catch fish without a fish
locator?
How do you normally catch fish?
He normally doesn't. Oh, well, I'll be
outside if anybody's looking for me.
I got the battery out of the truck.
Oh, not that battery, the little
rechargeable battery and the shiny new box on
the front seat. Oh well, now come on.
Don't go taking that thing back, Murray.
You're never going to sell it. I'm just
going to want to buy it, huh?
All right. So why don't you just let me use
it until I earn the money to pay for it?
Hey, Doc, your fish locator come
There that came in, came and went, came and
went, Yeah, red.
Can I borrow three hundred dollars?
Sure. Not for me, though.
Ok, who'd like an order of fresh piping hot
from the oven cheese dreams?
Those are cheese nightmares, Eddie.
Oh, how about a cheese, Jim Murray?
Oh no. Thanks, Eddie, I'm driving Doc.
Can I get? Yeah. Hmm.
Well, if I ate one, would you give me $300?
Wow.
Say yes. You'll never live to collect it.
Got him, Duane.
Care for a snack? Sure.
See you, ED. Remember you and I were talking
about me getting you a good supply of fresh
fish. How would you be willing to pay
handsomely for said supply?
Well, I was wondering if I could get an
advance on that.
Well, I mean, I I really could use some
Atlantic salmon or some Pacific lobster meat,
so I could make it. I could make a salmon
patty.
Well, I was thinking more of a fish out of
the lake.
Possibly. You mean those scrappy little bass
and sunfish?
I mean, they are so full of chemicals.
If you drive them off, you can throw them in
the fire and use them for artificial lungs.
So these are great tuna puffs.
Cheese dreams.
Sunny, very funny.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, hold up, hold up.
Brett, read the lodge, could you?
The fish locator, huh? Hey, I'm sure we got
it for three hundred bucks in the kitty
somewhere.
Well, we would have you paid your dues
anyway.
That's between you and Murray.
All right. You can have your fish locator as
soon as you find your money locator.
All right. I need that.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Lovely to look at potato hole.
You break this thing and it's sold to you.
But. You promised to buy my fish.
You promised to eat the cheese dream.
Of all the smells that are known to man.
There's nothing like home cooking that can
do things and nothing else can.
The smell of home cooking can get you out of
bed.
The smell of home cooking, getting raise you
from the half dead.
I remember one day our house burned down
Down
And you could smell our home cooking all the
way to town.
Hi.
This week on
Andy My Corner, I want to show you how to
check your transmission.
I got this engine out of my vehicle here
when I tried to do an oil change and luckily
enough, the transmission come with it so we
can take advantage of that now.
The first step here to get the training off.
Call it a tranny is to loosen the bolts.
All right. Now I bring the trainees down
here at this end.
Yeah, yeah. Here we go.
Ok, now these are these are a nine 16 volt,
but this is only a half inch wrench.
I think we can make it work.
Ok, OK, OK, OK, OK, OK, well, now it would
it does help if you got somebody to kind of
study the motor.
Oh, wait, I'm at. The other end of this is
nine 16.
Ok. Ok. Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ok, now I wasn't exactly sure everything
which bolts held the transmission on, so I I
just pretty well undid everything I could
find.
I just kind of pried us out of here.
Come on.
I got it here.
Just OK.
Ok. Ok. All right.
Let's get this off then.
Ok, let's see what we got here.
Ok. We got a.
And that seems all right, and I have one of
these.
This this year, this doesn't look no, no, I
guess that's OK.
Yeah. These and this and this.
Yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah.
And this seems. Yep, yep.
Well, it looks OK.
So I would say if you take your transmission
apart and take a look at this and then take a
look at yours and whatever, it doesn't look
like this.
Make yours look like this and and then
you'll be OK.
So until next time, women don't find a
handsome, they should at least find your
handy. Does anybody know if this is the
transmission?
It is winter. It's only half over, and
you've gone through almost all of your
firewood, all because your wife won't wear
wool socks.
Man, bad enough, I got the bank, the
government and the in-laws begging me for
money. Now I got Doc Render hit me up for a
loan.
You know, Uncle
Fred, I'd be happy to give Doc the money, but
all you have to do is just, you know, give me
a raise.
All right. What about this here? Why don't I
give you a cut in pay and then doc and lend
you money?
Or even this will just keep things status quo
ish the way they're working now,
And I could work with that.
Yeah. Well, I thought you might be able to
help anyway.
Doc was just hitting up. Absolutely
everybody.
Oh man. Sedgwick said he couldn't partake
because he's got his money tied up in pork
futures, which basically means he's bought
bacon for tomorrow's breakfast and steak.
He's got all his money in one of his old
socks.
The doc said he'd even take that as long as
Stinky washed it first.
But he said, No, I didn't want to give them
laundered money.
That's disgusting.
A fish locator.
Ok, where's our priorities?
Uncle Ray? Where's your priorities?
Mine. Well, they're not important.
Are we making educational tools for our
children?
I think not, sir.
No. Rather, we're making these silly, flashy
gadgets that we don't even need.
We're wasting our technological advances.
We could be saving lives.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I could get on with the
show, lil.
Yeah, OK, you got to see this one.
This is so cool.
I just discovered it. Oh, cool.
What part?
Cool. Oh yeah.
Yeah, that machine is a real lifesaver.
Anything out there?
Oh, I don't know.
I'm awful busy. I've got to get a snack
ready for the bird watchers.
What is that black pudding or licorice
pancakes?
Toast little on the burnt side, isn't it,
that
People would ask me?
No, no, no, no. Actually, I was wondering
about this deal you got with Doc to pay for
his fish locator. No, I don't think Doc can
catch anything other than suckers, you know
what I mean?
Don't worry about that.
No, the deal's off.
We couldn't come to an agreement. Oh, it was
not funny
At that time was not turned on.
You know that?
Oh, well, they're like, Oh my cake.
Oh, well, a little bit icing, you know,
nobody will notice.
Yeah. Well, it goes good with the toast now,
anyway.
The toast.
My toast. A little butter in.
Nobody will notice.
I guess not, no.
You know, I must have lost my concentration
while I was poking little holes in the
bratwurst sausage.
And I missed that.
Well, you were standing right there, red.
You see, you have to poke holes in about
where sausage, otherwise they'll explode.
Everybody knows that.
I don't think he did it. It.
I poked holes in the sausage.
So little ketchup.
Nobody noticed.
Bell told me to meet him behind the line.
There is going to show me how to camouflage
himself.
I don't know. Well.
By golly, he's pretty good at it.
So that's what we're going to do on this
week's adventures with Bill.
I was looking at a tree you used and there
was an apple in there and Adam and Eve kind
of a relationship we had at that moment that
Apolo and I brought in these cans of spray
paint. You had the white coveralls on and
the lid was kind of stuck on mine.
There we go. Now what he does is just to
kind of spray paint some random patterns all
over his coveralls. He asked me to do the
back.
I'm only too happy to help out on these.
Hoping it'll mean they'll end sooner.
But he's got he had, I guess, two colors
nine and then we switch colors around that
sort of can't really tell that in the in the
black and white, but those are different
colors. And I was done and he was done, and
there he was.
I did a little different style in mine, but
I like it.
Now we're going to make some camouflage our
hats so you can't see our heads.
He's got to have something like mine, but
course not exactly the same as my lucky hat,
but in some ranches around there and I
thought I did kind of a nice job on mine and
bills. Well. You know, it was built.
We're ready to go out through the long grass
and whatever, and you how difficult it is to
spot a person moving like that.
Bill feels a little easier.
And this is something I had never
experienced before.
You just put a mirror into the tall grass
and then you can you can know what you do is
you angle it in such a way that you crouched
down behind it and a passing animal or what
have you say, a truant officer or whatever
can't tell the reflection from the real
thing. So it just looks like there's nothing
there.
And I said I couldn't believe that that
looked even as close as I was, that we'll
just look like normal grass and so on and
everything.
And and of course, I knew Bill is just just
behind the mirror.
It's just a fantastic, you know?
But I know he's not in the mirror when I say
to check this, I don't know where bill with
Bell,
Bell, Bell.
Now there he is.
Well, there's been some interesting changes
of events here.
The bird watchers club is officially changed
its charter to become the Wine Spinners Club,
which was it was funny the first two or
three hundred times, but then it kind of wore
a little thin and and by then the coach was
so drenched with wine you could pass out just
from the fumes. The guys may go back to
birdwatching.
Excuse me, I'll go ahead. But did you hear
how Doc Render is going to raise the money?
There's $300 and he needs.
He's having a lottery.
Oh, tickets are a buck each.
I bought ten and first prize is a quarter of
a million dollars.
That's a lot of money. The only video games
I can buy with that.
Oh hell, I don't like to sound negative, but
that sounds like a major crock to me.
I don't happen to think so.
They'll be drawing the winning ticket
tonight at the Lodge meeting.
Oh, and I feel lucky.
You don't look like a hero.
Hey, that's it. That's the sound of the
possum the meeting's coming to order.
Just think of it, Uncle Red. Soon I can go
from being a normal average guy just to being
a quarter of a millionaire.
I'm guessing he'll still be a quarter of an
average guy.
I don't know if Doc can pull this thing off,
but if he does, I think we should give him a
national deficit.
Great. Great. Great.
Yeah.
I wouldn't doubt that 12 kind of things
going.
All right.
All right, that's not. All right.
Seriously. Okay, all right.
We start the meeting. We're starting the
meeting.
Bird people want
A lot more time to act right now.
Not really. Come on.
Really, don't even
Shut down the Wine Tasting Council meeting.
Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
Oh, boy.
Well, that was good. That was good.
That was OK. That was a good one.
That was a good one. But the other one was
shot up there on the floor.
Recognize the doc. Render.
Thank you, Richard.
Thank you. Thank you, fellas.
Now would what anybody else like to buy a
lottery ticket on?
Your chances of winning are one in one
hundred and fifty.
I never win anything.
I bought 10.
What anybody else want to buy?
Just anybody else? Take one.
Save your money, Dwayne.
It's a scam scam, scam scam.
It is not a scam.
All right. Now read Why don't you go ahead
and grow the lucky number?
All right. They can drop you down there.
Keep it in the family, Uncle Fred.
All right. Here's our lucky winner.
Listen up. Number one.
Oh, two. Just want to make
Sure that's fair.
This is so great. I'm going to buy like my
own show.
I don't even need to buy this anymore.
I got my own show. I'm going to buy like a
house on a hill and a boat with a CD player
and a jeep. A read one to read.
Take this job and shove it.
I don't want to. I don't do well now.
Here you go here. Look at the site
blackjack.
That's huge. Look at this one dollar.
What one dollar was offered.
That's one dollar. I suppose I'm supposed to
be a quarter of a millionaire.
That's that's like two hundred and forty
nine thousand nine hundred ninety nine short
doc. Oh, no, no, no, no.
Harold Harold first prize in the lottery was
a dollar a month for a quarter a million
months. Oh, what's that?
Oh, do you read the fine print there?
No, well, it's there.
Well, that is brilliant.
Good for you, Doc.. Wait, how come we didn't
think of that?
So I'm not like rich.
No, you're not Harold. You're not a
millionaire.
You're a dollar heir and one who's just
shoved this job.
I got. We're here.
There you go. There's one hundred and sixty
bucks, just over half of what I owe you.
Great. Dwayne saw the fish locate in half
and give it to him, but come on.
Well, read my lips doc, I said Three hundred
dollars.
Oh, wait. I'm going to get down there.
You're wine tasters. Why don't you go back
to birdwatching?
Huh? Ok. Really?
Not unless maybe you combine the two.
What you do is you guys buy the other half
of this locator when doc here is not fishing,
huh? You can strap the locator to the roof
of the lodge and use it to spot bird.
You guys up. So the guy with
50 drunken friends.
Thanks, fellas. Yeah.
All right, if there's if there's no other
large business, forget it.
Come on,
Give us an evening's entertainment.
Hey, bro.
So now what's the matter?
Well, Bill, possums, Romans, countrymen, lend
me your ears.
I know that we're not holding elections for
the leadership of the Lodge, but consider
this if elected, I promise to put a chicken
in every pot hot pot.
Well, I guess that's the first time we've
ever had a happy ending for this show.
And it's not actually like the happy ending
as other shows.
You know where everybody learns something
and they have a hug.
Speaking with you? My wife is watching me.
I'll be coming straight home after the
meeting and and I actually have learned
something and I got just the hug to prove
it.
Until next time on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole gang up here at Possum
Lodge, if we stick on the ice.
If I am elected, I promise to get my mom to
drive you guys everywhere.
You really good. She's got a neat car.
You know, I also promise to hold my breath
every two years starting making election
promises. We have an election here.