[breezy folk music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> IT'S REALLY HARD TO THINK OF
SOMETHING NEW TO SAY WHEN YOU'RE
INTRODUCING THE SAME PERSON AND
THE SAME SHOW ABOUT 800 TIMES IN
A ROW, BUT I GUESS THAT'S WHAT
MAKES ME A PROFESSIONAL, AS THEY
SAY IN THE BUSINESS.
SO WELCOME THE STAR OF
THE RED GREEN SHOW AND MY
UNCLE THROUGH SOME TYPE OF
RELATIONSHIP WITH MY DAD.
THE MAN OF THE HOUR, EVEN
THOUGH IT'S ACTUALLY ONLY 30
MINUTES INCLUDING COMMERCIALS
AND SUCH.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH, AND
THANK YOU, AND WELCOME TO THE
SHOW.
WHY DON'T I JUST START IT OFF BY
INTRODUCING OUR
PRODUCER-DIRECTOR AND ALSO MY
NEPHEW, BY SOME SORT OF STRANGE
RELATIONSHIP WITH MY BROTHER.
COME ON OVER HERE, HAROLD.
LIKE I SAY, HAROLD IS THE
PRODUCER AND DIRECTOR.
DON'T LET THIS FANCY GIZMO RIG
HANGING AROUND HAROLD'S NECK
FOOL YOU.
IT'S SOME SORT OF A SPECIAL
EFFECTS MACHINE THAT HE USES
TO DO KIND OF BAD THINGS TO
THE SHOW, REALLY.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
WITH THIS AWESOME PIECE OF
PERSONAL HARDWARE, I CAN CONTROL
THE SPEED THE OF THE SHOW.
I CAN TAKE US TO DIFFERENT
SEGMENTS IF IT STARTS DRAGGING
OR SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, THAT CAN HAPPEN.
>> JUST AS LONG AS I GET A
LITTLE WARNING, RIGHT?
>> OH, NO PROBLEM, BIG GUY.
[laughs]
UNCLE RED.
SORRY.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO ANYWAY.
GOT TALKING UP AT THE LODGE THIS
WEEK.
THERE'S SOME NEW THING ON THE
MARKET.
IT'S CALLED A JET SKI, WHO I
THOUGHT PLAYED FOR LOS ANGELES.
BUT APPARENTLY THIS IS SOME
OTHER TYPE OF A JET SKI THAT
GOES ON TOP OF THE WATER, WHICH
NOBODY HAS DONE THAT I KNOW OF
IN THE LAST COUPLE OF THOUSAND
YEARS.
SO THE BUNCH OF US AT THE LODGE
DECIDED TO GO DOWN TO THE MARINA
AND CHECK IT OUT.
WHAT KIND OF A WARNING WAS THAT?
>> WELL, YOU SAW MY HANDS MOVE
TO THE CONTROL.
WELL?
>>  LISTEN TO THE WORDS
OF THIS VERY SPECIAL SONG
DA, DA, DA, DA
DA, DA, DA, DA, DA
LISTEN VERY CLOSELY
THEN YOU CAN SING ALONG
DA, DA, DA, DA
DA, DA, DA, DA, DA
PLAY CLOSE ATTENTION
IT'S NOT AS EASY
AS IT SOUNDS
DA, DA, DA, DA
SYNCHRONIZATION
INCREMENTAL
DA, DA, DA, DA
THERMONUCLEAR
QUANTUM PHYSICS
DA, DA, DA, DA
>> EIGHT MORE TIMES.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> NOW, THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN
CORNER, WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
TO USE DIFFERENT TOOLS FOR
DIFFERENT JOBS.
AND WHEN I SAY THAT, WHAT I MEAN
IS NOT NECESSARILY A DIFFERENT
TOOL AND A JOB.
I MEAN A TOOL THAT'S MAYBE USED
IN A DIFFERENT JOB, BUT MAYBE ON
A DIFFERENT TOOL WITH THE--
WITH THE JOB.
IT'S MAYBE A DIFFERENT JOB
INVOLVED WITH THE TOOL.
WELL, I HOPE THAT CLEARS
THAT UP.
SO LETS SAY, FOR EXAMPLE, YOU
HAVE A BUNCH OF NAILS THAT YOU
WANT TO HAMMER IN, BUT FOR SOME
REASON OR OTHER, YOUR HAMMER IS
OUT IN THE MIDDLE OF A LAKE,
THROUGH THE RESULT OF SOME SORT
OF A DOMESTIC SQUABBLE.
SO INSTEAD OF A HAMMER, WHAT YOU
USE IS A SUBSTITUTE HAMMER,
SOMETHING LIKE, SAY, A PIPE
WRENCH.
WORKS GOOD.
OR MAYBE YOU CAN'T USE A PIPE
WRENCH BECAUSE IT'S IN YOUR CAR
HOLDING THE RADIATOR ON.
YOU MIGHT TAKE A LOOK AT USING
AN AX OR A HATCHET, SOMETHING
THAT HAS A FLAT BOTTOM.
BUT THE THING HERE IS, I REALLY
WOULD BE CAREFUL ON THE UPSWING.
I'M NOT SURE YOU'RE THE KIND OF
THE PERSON THAT WANTS THE
CREASES IN YOUR FOREHEAD TO RUN
UP AND DOWN.
ANOTHER SUBSTITUTE HAMMER IS A
FLASHLIGHT.
NOT EVERYBODY THINKS OF THIS,
BUT IF YOU GET ONE OF THESE,
WHICH HOLDS THREE OR FOUR
BATTERIES, IT'S GOT SOME WEIGHT
TO IT.
AND THE BEAUTY, OF COURSE, OF
THIS IS YOU CAN DO IT AT NIGHT
WITH THE POWER OFF, AND HOW MANY
THINGS CAN YOU SAY THAT ABOUT?
SO WHAT YOU DO IS, YOU SHINE THE
FLASHLIGHT ON THE NAIL AND THEN.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO GO A LITTLE
EASY FOR A WHILE WITH THAT ONE.
ONE OF MY FAVORITE SUBSTITUTE
HAMMERS IS, OF COURSE, THE
LEVEL, BECAUSE WHAT YOU CAN DO
IS, YOU CAN LEVEL UP THE WOOD,
MAKE SURE IT'S RIGHT WHERE YOU
WANT IT, AND THEN PUT IT IN
PLACE WITH THE SAME TOOL, LIKE
THAT.
YOU CAN TAKE THE SAME APPROACH
WITH SCREWING.
YOU DON'T HAVE A SCREWDRIVER?
I CAN GET YOU A SCREWDRIVER FOR
TEN CENTS.
IT'S A DIME.
FITS IN THE SLOT, AND IF YOU'RE
NOT REAL FOND OF THE SKIN ON
YOUR FINGERS, THIS CAN BE A
DANDY LITTLE TOOL.
BUT IF THAT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH
FOR YOU, HOW ABOUT A CHISEL?
IT'S GOT THE NICE FINE EDGE ON
IT THERE.
WELL, WHAT I DO USUALLY IS JUST
TAKE A HAMMER, I JUST SAY TO
MYSELF, "THESE AREN'T REALLY
SCREWS.
THEY'RE JUST NAILS WITH
THREADS."
AND THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S HOW THAT WORKS.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK, AND I'LL
GET ON WITH THE REST OF JET SKI
STORY.
>> I'LL GIVE YOU ALL A WARNING.
>> IT IS SUMMER.
WE HAVE HAD NO RAIN.
THERE IS NO WATER, NO FRUIT, NO
VEGETABLES.
NOT A DROP FOR OUR CROPS OR OUR
LIVESTOCK.
IF IT WASN'T FOR THE BREWERY,
THIS COULD BE SERIOUS.
SO ANYWAY, THE BUNCH OF US WENT
DOWN TO THE MARINA AND CHECKED
OUT THIS JET SKI THING.
WELL, IT ZOOMS ALONG ON TOP OF
THE WATER, YOU KNOW.
IT KIND OF LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY
MATED A PONTOON AND A
MOTORCYCLE, WHICH WOULD HAVE
BEEN A HECK OF A RACKET IF YOU
WERE IN THE NEXT ROOM OF THE
MOTEL, I TELL YOU.
BUT ANYWAY, MOOSE THOMPSON TAKES
A LOOK AT IT, AND HE SAYS HE CAN
BUILD SOMETHING LIKE THAT OUT OF
A SNOWMOBILE.
WELL, THAT SOUNDED LIKE A REAL
DUMB IDEA TO US, BUT THEN AGAIN
OUR SNOWMOBILE IS WORTHLESS, SO
WE SAID "FINE" AND SOLD IT TO
HIM.
>> UNCLE RED.
WARNING TIME.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
>> I WAS JUST GETTING TO THE
INTERESTING PART, HAROLD.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
WE'RE IN IT NOW.
>> MORNING, GLEN.
>> HI, RED.
JUST ON MY WAY TO DISNEYWORLD.
WANT TO COME WITH ME?
>> YOU'RE GOING TO DISNEYWORLD?
WHO'S GONNA RUN THE MARINA?
IT'S THE MIDDLE OF THE HIGH
TOURIST SEASON HERE.
>> WELL, YOU'RE HERE.
YOU CAN DO IT.
YEAH, THE KEYS ARE IN THE CASH
REGISTER.
>> I GOT A LODGE TO RUN, GLEN.
I CAN'T--I CAN'T RUN YOUR--
YOUR MARINA.
YOU CAN'T FLY OUT TO
DISNEYWORLD.
THIS IS CRAZY.
>> WELL, RED, I GOT TO RAMBLE.
I'M A RAMBLING GUY.
I'LL SEE YOU IN FIVE WEEKS.
>> WHAT ABOUT MY ENGINE, GLEN?
YOU TOLD ME YOU'D HAVE MY ENGINE
FIXED THREE WEEKS AGO.
WHERE IS IT?
>> WELL, IT'S RIGHT THERE, RED.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHAT'D YOU DO TO HER?
>> WELL, I HAD TO REPLACE THE
COUPLING AND THE SHAFT, THE
PROP.
YEAH.
SHE'S FINE NOW, THOUGH.
SHE'LL RUN LIKE A FINE SWISS
OUTBOARD.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU ACTUALLY FIXED SOMETHING?
YOU ACTUALLY REPAIRED SOMETHING
THAT YOU SOLD SOMEBODY?
IT'S A BIG DAY HERE.
>> DID I PACK THAT CREAM SODA?
>> GLEN?
GLEN?
GLEN, WHAT IS THIS?
>> WELL, RED, I COULDN'T MATCH
THE PAINT EXACTLY.
I MEAN, IT'S--THEY STOPPED
MAKING THESE JUST AFTER THE
WAR--THE FIRST WAR, I THINK.
>> NO, NO, IT'S NOT THE COLOR,
GLEN.
IT'S THE SIZE.
THAT-THAT-THAT LOWER UNIT, THAT
COME OFF A BATTLESHIP OR
SOMETHING.
THERE'S NO WAY THIS MOTOR'S
GONNA DRIVE THAT PROP.
>> WELL, THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE
WRONG, RED.
I TESTED IT MYSELF ALREADY.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD FOR
SLOW-SPEED TROLLING.
I'LL SEE YOU WHEN I GET BACK,
RED.
>> NO, GLEN.
WAIT, NO, GLEN, GLEN, GLEN!
GLEN, THIS IS NO GOOD, GLEN!
THE TRANSOM'S GONNA RIP RIGHT
OFF MY BOAT.
GLEN.
[grunts]
[horn honks]
>> RED, YOU ALMOST DENTED MY
BUMPERS.
WHAT ARE YOU THE KIND OF MAN
THAT'LL DENT A MAN'S BUMPERS?
>> BUT THE MOTOR'S JUST NO GOOD,
GLEN.
THIS IS NOT GONNA WORK.
>> RED, IT'S FINE.
I TESTED IT, OKAY?
>> BUT IT'S NOT THE SAME ENGINE.
THIS IS NOT CORRECT.
>> I KNOW THAT.
THEY STOPPED MAKING THAT ENGINE
WHEN THEY DISCOVERED STEEL, RED.
LOOK, I'M A GREAT MECHANIC.
WHEN A GREAT MECHANIC TAKES
SOMETHING INTO A SHOP, HE PULLS
SOMETHING OUT, ALL RIGHT?
HAVE I EVER DONE ANYTHING LESS
THAN PERFECT FOR YOU BEFORE?
>> WELL, WHO KNOWS, GLEN?
EVERY TIME I COME HERE, YOU MAKE
ME FIX MY OWN STUFF.
>> LOOK, THIS IS WHERE I'M
STAYING AT DISNEYWORLD, ALL
RIGHT?
THE POLYNESIAN TROPICAL JUNGLE
THEME INN.
>> PUT YOUR ROOM NUMBER ON
THERE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'LL BE PARKED AT THE HAPPY
TAHITIAN WING.
YOU GOT ANY TROUBLES, CALL ME,
OKAY?
ONLY IF YOU GOT TROUBLE.
>> THAT'S A PARKING SPOT NUMBER.
I'LL HAVE YOU PAGED AT
FANTASYLAND.
[groans]
[folky acoustic guitar music]
THERE ONCE WAS
A MAGIC WORKHORSE
AN ENCHANTED CLYDESDALE
NAMED GARTH
HE FROLICKED
IN THE AUTUMN MIST
IN A LAND CALLED SIMCOE
HE HAD THREE WISHES
AND HE LEFT ON THEM
ON THE ROAD
I STEPPED IN ONE
BELIEVE ME
IT'S NOT ALWAYS GOOD
WHEN YOUR WISHES COME TRUE
THANK YOU.
LIKE TO TALK ABOUT SOME OTHER
SUBSTITUTE TOOLS NOW.
LET'S SAY YOU GOT A PIECE OF
WOOD LIKE THIS.
YOU WANT TO DO SOME SORT OF A
FANCY DADO CUT IN IT BUT YOUR
CHISEL IS ALL BUNGED UP BECAUSE
SOMEBODY USED IT AS A
SCREWDRIVER.
WHAT YOU DO IS TIT FOR TAT, AS
WE SAY, PUT THE SCREWDRIVER AND
USE YOUR SCREWDRIVER AS A
CHISEL.
THEN JUST TAKE IT OUT AND GO...
ALL RIGHT, WELL, WE'LL GET BACK
TO THAT LATER.
ALL RIGHT, FOR EXAMPLE, YOUR
LEVEL IS NOT WORKING TOO WELL
ANYMORE BECAUSE SOMEONE USED IT,
SAY, AS A HAMMER, SAY, WHAT YOU
CAN USE IS A PENCIL CRAYON.
YOU PUT IT ON THE--ON THE
TABLE.
STOPS ROLLING,
THAT'S LEVEL.
ANOTHER SUBSTITUTE TOOL, LET'S
SAY YOU WANT TO--YOU WANT TO
CUT A PIECE OF WOOD, AND YOUR
SAW IS WHO KNOWS WHERE?
STUCK IN SOMEONE'S TIRE,
PERHAPS.
TAKE AN X-ACTO KNIFE.
SCORE THE WOOD ON BOTH SIDES.
HERE AGAIN, I SHOULD CAUTION
YOU.
NEVER HOLD WOOD BETWEEN YOUR
KNEES WHILE YOU'RE CUTTING IT
WITH AN X-ACTO KNIFE UNLESS
YOUR FAVORITE SONG IS THE FIRST
CUT IS THE DEEPEST.
OKAY, YOU GOT HER SCORED
ON BOTH SIDES.
PROP HER UP AGAINST--AGAINST
THE SIDE OF YOUR WORK BENCH
OR YOUR WIFE'S CAR, AND GET
WHAT I CALL THE SUBSTITUTE SAW.
THE SLEDGEHAMMER.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, IT DOES GIVE A
BIT OF A--A BIT OF A ROUGH
FINISH, BUT I THINK A LITTLE
SANDPAPER ON THAT, AND IT'LL
COME OUT NICE.
AND IF YOU DON'T HAVE SANDPAPER,
OF COURSE, YOU CAN USE A BRICK.
A BRICK ALSO WILL SUBSTITUTE AS
A HAMMER, AND IF YOU HAVE 50
BRICKS, YOU CAN MAKE A VISE.
JUST REMEMBER THAT A HANDYMAN
NEVER BLAMES HIS TOOLS.
HE JUST GRABS SOMETHING ELSE.
SO, UNTIL NEXT TIME, KEEP THIS
IN MIND.
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
>> WELL, EXCELLENT TIMING,
UNCLE RED.
IT'S TIME FOR MALE CALL.
TIME TO ANSWER SOME LETTERS.
TIME TO TIE ON THE OLD FEED BAG,
IF YOU WILL.
[laughs]
YOU WANT TO READ THE FIRST
LETTER OR YOU WANT ME TO READ
IT?
THAT WAY, WE CAN JUST KEEP
THINGS CLIPPING ALONG.
>> YEAH, THAT'LL BE FINE,
HAROLD.
DON'T GET ALL EXCITED THERE.
>> I'M NOT NEARLY AS EXCITED AS
YOU THINK.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> "DEAR MR. GREEN,
I'VE BEEN WATCHING YOUR
SHOW FOR A WHOLE EPISODE NOW,
AND I REALLY THINK IT'S THE
GREATEST THING TO HIT TV SINCE
WRESTLEMANIA.
I LIKE WRESTLING.
I USED TO LIKE HOCKEY, BUT NOW I
THINK IT'S TOO VIOLENT.
NOW I LIKE WRESTLING, BUT MY
WIFE SAYS IT'S JUST FAKE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
IS WRESTLING FAKE OR WHAT?"
[chuckles]
EXCELLENT QUESTION.
>> UH, HAROLD, YOU KNOW WE'VE
HAD COMPLAINT BEFORE ABOUT THE
WRESTLING BEING FAKE, AND LET ME
JUST STRAIGHTEN THIS OUT.
WRESTLING IS A SPORT.
IT GOES WAY BACK.
IT'S REAL OLD.
IT WAS ALL THE WAY BACK TO THE
GREEKS AND THEY'RE REALLY OLD,
YOU KNOW?
IN FACT, THE FIRST OLYMPICS WAS
NOTHING BUT WRESTLING.
COURSE, NOW, IN THOSE DAYS, THEY
WERE NAKED.
>> REALLY?
>> OH, YEAH.
BUCK NAKED.
>> [laughs]
YOU CAN'T FAKE THAT.
>> NO, AND IT MADE FOR SOME
EXCELLENT HOLDS.
BUT THEY HAVE EXCELLENT HOLDS
NOW TODAY, AND LET ME JUST
ASSURE THIS VIEWER THAT HE IS
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
WRESTLING COULD NOT POSSIBLY BE
FAKE.
>> WELL, IN MY OPINION,
WRESTLING IS, LIKE, HUGELY FAKE.
>> WELL, THE VIEWER DIDN'T WRITE
A LETTER TO YOU, NOW DID HE,
HAROLD?
>> GOOD POINT.
>> AND HE NEVER WILL.
BELIEVE ME.
>> WELL, HIS WIFE MIGHT.
[laughs]
I HAVE ANOTHER LETTER HERE,
UNCLE RED.
SAYS "I REALLY LIKE YOUR TRUCK.
WHERE'D YOU GET IT?"
SIGNED, "WONDERING IN WAWA."
>> WAWA.
THAT'S A GREAT LITTLE TOWN.
THEY HAVE ENORMOUS GOOSE UP
THERE, HAROLD.
IF YOU EVER WANT ENORMOUS GOOSE,
YOU KNOW YOU CAN GO TO WAWA.
>> YEP.
UNCLE RED, THEY--THEY ASKED
ABOUT YOUR TRUCK.
>> OH YEAH, WELL, THE TRUCK.
THAT'S AN INTERESTING STORY.
YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T ACTUALLY BUY
THAT TRUCK.
I TRADED A GUY FOR A 12-POUND
PICKEREL, AND I THOUGHT I GOT A
GOOD DEAL, BUT THEN WHEN I
PULLED INTO THE GARAGE, THE DARN
BRAKES FAILED.
>> YOU GOT BRAKES IN YOUR
GARAGE?
>> NO, THE BRAKES IN THE TRUCK,
HAROLD.
>> WELL, YOU MISPLACED YOUR
MODIFIER.
>> WELL, I ALWAYS SIT LIKE THIS.
IT'S COMFORTABLE.
>> WELL, IF WE'RE READY TO GO TO
THE NEXT SEGMENT, WELL, LET HER
ROLL.
YOU MADE A GRAMMATICAL ERROR.
>> THAT WASN'T ME, HAROLD.
IT WAS THE CHAIR.
>> [yelling]
[grunts]
>> BILL WAS IN THE AREA, SO I
DECIDED TO SWING BY THE LODGE.
HE HAD A LITTLE SOMETHING
SPECIAL IN HIS PANTS TODAY.
IT WAS SOMETHING, I BELIEVE,
FROM SOUTH AMERICA.
THEY'RE CALLED--
WHOA-WHOA-WHOA-WHOA-WHOA, ALL
RIGHT, HE'S ALL RIGHT.
THEY'RE CALLED BOLOS, AND THAT'S
LIKE A STONE, SOME TYPE OF A
ROCK, THEY TIE ON A STRING AND
THEY USE THIS ACTUALLY AS A
WEAPON.
THEY SWING IT AROUND THERE.
LOOK OUT, BILL. LOOK OUT.
SWING IT AROUND.
I LIKE IT.
IT'S KIND OF--YOU KNOW, IT'S
ALMOST LIKE A BOOMERANG-TYPE
THING.
I GOT IT TO GO PRETTY--LOOK
OUT, BILL.
LOOK OUT.
OH-OH-OH OW.
>> AHH!
>> WELL, IT TAKES A LITTLE
GETTING USED TO.
BILL WAS--I GUESS, WAS SHOWING
ME SOME OF THE THINGS THAT CAN
GO WRONG WITH THEM.
HE GOT IT ALL CLEAR AND WENT
THIS WAY WITH IT.
A LITTLE DIFFERENT APPROACH, YOU
KNOW, THE VERTICAL RATHER THAN
THE HORIZONTAL THROW, AND WE
SUDDENLY REALIZED THAT THE
STONES HAD COME RIGHT OFF.
COULDN'T FIGURE OUT WHERE THEY--
THEN I HEARD, AND THEN--
BILL, LOOK OUT. WE GOT TO--
BILL, WE GOT TO GO.
WE GOT TO--
BILL, BILL, GOT TO GO
GOT TO GO.
GO.
OKAY.
NOW BILL DECIDED TO SET UP A
LITTLE TARGET WITH SOME GLASS.
>> [groans]
>> AND THEN HE DECIDED TO SET IT
UP AGAIN, AND I WAS GONNA
TAKE--TAKE THE FIRST SHOT AND
SEE IF I COULD SWING OUT AND HIT
THE--HIT THE JARS OR WHATEVER.
AND I TRIED A LITTLE DIFFERENT
APPROACH.
I TRIED THE BOUNCE TECHNIQUE,
AND IT WORKED REAL GOOD, I
THOUGHT.
AND NOW BILL'S TURN.
BILL HAD A LITTLE BIT OF,
YOU KNOW, CONTROL--
OH, THANK YOU, BILL.
TRY HER AGAIN.
IT'S CLOSE. IT'S CLOSE.
I SHOULD HAVE SKIPPED IT AGAIN.
BILL, I THINK HE HAS A TROUBLE
KNOWING, YOU KNOW, WHAT
DIRECTION--OH, OH, THAT WAS
OUR BACKHOE.
OH-OH-OH-OH, BOY.
OH, THE CAMERAMAN WAS OKAY.
SO BILL TRIED THIS, AND HE GOT
SOME SORT OF A STRANGE THING
GOING ON.
HE STARTED TO RISE UP LIKE A--
ALMOST LIKE A HELICOPTER, I
GUESS, BUT THE THING'S SPINNING
AROUND.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE--HARDLY
BELIEVE THIS WAS HAPPENING, BUT
I WAS THERE, AND IT MUST HAVE
BEEN HAPPENING, AND I WAS THERE.
AND HE WAS GOING WAY, WAY UP
THERE.
GEE, I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT, YOU
KNOW, AND HE WAS ENJOYING IT,
THOUGH.
HE WAS ENJOYING IT,
HAVING A GOOD TIME.
SO, YOU KNOW, I PROBABLY
SHOULDN'T HAVE WAVED AT HIM,
BECAUSE HE THOUGHT HE HAD TO
WAVE BACK AND THEN THAT WASN'T
SO SMART.
>> [yelling]
[groaning]
>> AND THEN I COULD HEAR THE
BOLOS COMING DOWN.
BILL. BILL. BILL. BILL. BILL.
OH, BOY.
BUT I REALLY DID ENJOY WORKING
WITH THE BOLOS, AND I TOOK THEM
WITH ME.
I MIGHT PLAY WITH SOME ANOTHER
DAY.
IT IS WINTER.
THE FUN OF THROWING SNOWBALLS AT
OLD PEOPLE.
THE JOY OF WRITING YOUR NAME IN
A SNOWBANK IN YELLOW.
MORE DANGEROUS FROM THE ICE, YET
SAFER 'CAUSE YOU CAN SEE
EVERYONE'S BREATH AND AVOID
WALKING INTO IT.
>> UNCLE RED.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT WAS IT LIKE WHEN YOU
WERE MY AGE?
>> MENTALLY OR PHYSICALLY?
>> I DON'T GET THAT.
>> OKAY, SO PHYSICALLY.
WELL, IT WAS DIFFERENT, YOU
KNOW.
I MEAN, WHEN I WAS A TEENAGER,
MY AFTERSCHOOL JOB WAS PIN BOY.
>> WOW!
REALLY?
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
PIN BOY.
WHAT WAS THAT?
LIKE A SUPERHERO OR SOMETHING?
>> NO, HAROLD, I WAS--I WAS A
PIN BOY IN A BOWLING ALLEY.
>> OH.
>> YEAH, I HAD TO WORK SIX HOURS
JUST TO EARN ENOUGH MONEY TO BUY
MYSELF A SODA AND A BAG OF
CHIPS.
>> WHAT FLAVOR?
>> USUALLY AN ORANGE SODA.
>> NO, NO, NO, UNCLE RED.
WHAT FLAVOR CHIPS?
>> WELL, WE DIDN'T HAVE FLAVORED
CHIPS.
JUST PLAIN CHIPS.
>> WHAT?
YOU DIDN'T HAVE FLAVORED CHIPS?
YOUR LIFE MUST HAVE BEEN SAD.
I MEAN, YOU DIDN'T HAVE, LIKE--
YOU DIDN'T HAVE KETCHUP
OR SOUR CREAM AND ONION, DILL
PICKLE, SALT AND VINEGAR, RANCHO
COOL?
LIFE WITHOUT FLAVORED CHIPS?
YOU DIDN'T HAVE ANY FLAVORS?
>> IS RANCID A FLAVOR?
>> YOU MUST HAVE BEEN LIVING IN
THE STONE AGE.
WHAT?
HOW COME?
WAS IT, LIKE, THEY JUST DIDN'T
HAVE, LIKE THE TECHNOLOGY OR
SOMETHING, OR WAS IT SHORTAGES
AFTER THE WAR?
HOW COME?
MAYBE SOME--MAYBE SOMEBODY
JUST DIDN'T THINK OF IT?
THEY HAD TO WAIT FOR SOMEONE TO
WALK ALONG AND HAVE A DREAM?
>> YEAH, YEAH, OKAY, HAROLD.
BUT NOW, A 5¢ BAG OF CHIPS COSTS
YOU A BUCK 69.
>> YES, THAT IS TRUE, BUT YOUR
BREATH SMELLS LIKE YOU HAD AN
ENTIRE MEAL.
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
I THINK YOU'LL ENJOY THE END OF
THE JET SKI STORY.
>> WELL, AT LEAST IT'LL ALL BE
OVER AND DONE WITH, AND THAT
PART IS ENJOYABLE, SO I AGREE.
>> HE WAS BUILT LIKE A PEAR
KIND OF STOCKY AND SHORT
HIS REAL NAME WAS LEONARD
BUT WE JUST CALLED HIM WART
NOBODY LIKED HIM
HE WAS EXTREMELY OBNOXIOUS
BUT HE WAS KIND OF FUN
TO SLAP
AND HE ALWAYS LOST BIG
AT POKER
SO WE LET HIM STAY
IT IS AUTUMN.
YESTERDAY, THE SKY OVERHEAD WAS
ALIVE WITH GEESE.
TODAY THE DUCKS CIRCLE OVERHEAD
IN GROWING FLOCKS.
TOMORROW, THE SKY WILL BE DARK
WITH BLACKBIRDS.
THE NEXT DAY, ROBINS OR PERHAPS
CROWS.
I THINK I NEED TO FIND A
DIFFERENT PLACE TO PARK MY CAR.
WELL, THAT WATER IS COLD.
WOULDN'T WANT TO GO
SKINNY-DIPPING HERE.
THAT WOULD SHRINK YOUR LEVI'S.
>> YEAH, YOU'D GET USED TO IT.
WHEN I WORKED UP IN THE YUKON,
WE'D GO SPEARFISHING UNDER THE
ICE.
>> OH, YOU MEAN ICE FISHING,
WHERE YOU CUT A HOLE AND FISH
THROUGH IT?
>> NAH, THAT'S KID'S STUFF.
NO, WE'D CUT A HOLE AND DIVE
THROUGH.
SOMETIMES YOUR HEART WOULD STOP
FOR A FEW MINUTES, BUT IT WAS A
LOT OF FUN.
>> ARE YOU TELLING ME THAT YOU
SWAM AROUND IN ICE-COLD WATER
CHASING FISH WITH A SPEAR GUN?
>> YEAH, WE HAD THIS CEREMONIAL
HEADDRESS COVERED IN WORMS TO
ATTRACT THE FISH, AND THE FISH
WOULD COME AROUND, AND YOU'D
SPEAR 'EM AND SLIP THEM INTO
YOUR UNDERWEAR.
WHEN YOUR SKIVVIES WERE FILLED
WITH COD, YOU'D COME UP FOR AIR.
I ONCE HAD A WHOLE PANT LOAD OF
FISH ITCHING TO GET OUT, CAME UP
FOR AIR, AND MY HOLE HAD FROZEN
OVER.
>> I'M NOT SURPRISED.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
>> ONLY THING I COULD DO.
HOOKED THOSE FISH ONTO MY BELT
LOOPS, AND THEY TOWED ME INTO
OPEN WATER.
>> ARE YOU SAYING YOU HAD BELT
LOOPS ON YOUR UNDERWEAR, HAP?
>> [chuckles]
IF YOU WERE EVER UP IN THE
ARCTIC, YOU'D KNOW BETTER THAN
TO ASK A QUESTION LIKE THAT,
RED.
>> WELL, WASN'T A BAD QUESTION.
JUST CURIOUS, THAT'S ALL.
>> NO.
STORY'S OVER.
WHEN YOU START TO NITPICK ON THE
DETAIL, TAKES THE FUN OUT OF THE
TELLING.
>> WELL, SO ANYWAY, MOOSE
THOMPSON MADE HIS OWN LITTLE
HOMEMADE JET SKI OUT OF OUR
SNOWMOBILE AND ABOUT NINE LIFE
JACKETS, AND THE THING'S SITTING
DOWN ON THE DOCK, JUST REVVING
THERE, YOU KNOW.
AND HE WAS READY FOR A LONG RUN,
SO HE HAD ABOUT NINE UNWRAPPED
KETCHUP SANDWICHES KIND OF
JAMMED AT RANDOM INTO THE GLOVE
COMPARTMENT, AND HE HAD HIS HIP
WADERS FULL OF EXTRA GAS, WHICH
IS NOTHING NEW, YOU KNOW.
BUT ANYWAY, MOOSE GETS ON THERE,
AND HE HITS THE THROTTLE, AND
OFF SHE GOES, AND THEN, BY GOD,
HE SLAMMED SO HARD DOWN ON THE
LAKE THAT THE SANDWICHES ALL FLY
OUT OF THE GLOVE COMPARTMENT,
AND THE SEAT JAMMED SO FAR UP
THE HIP WADERS THAT CAN'T GET
OFF, ALL RIGHT.
[laughs]
HE STARTS CIRCLING AROUND
'CAUSE HE SOON REALIZED THAT
THE ONLY WAY YOU CAN STAY AFLOAT
IS TO KEEP HER WIDE OPEN, YOU
KNOW, AND MEANWHILE THE FISH ARE
EATING HIS LUNCH AND TURNING
BELLY UP.
WELL, YOU KNOW, EVERY TIME HE
GOES BY THE DOCK, HE YELLS
SOMETHING AT US, BUT WE'RE OF
COURSE LAUGHING SO HARD WE CAN'T
HEAR HIM, YOU KNOW.
ROUND AND ROUND HE GOES, AND OF
COURSE, FROM SHORE, YOU KNOW,
HE'S KICKING UP ABOUT, OH, I'D
SAY A 12-FOOT WAKE.
ALL WE'RE SEEING IS, LIKE, A
HUGE SWELL WITH MOOSE'S HEAD ON
THE TOP, WHICH IS ACTUALLY A
PRETTY GOOD DESCRIPTION OF MOOSE
EVEN ON DRY LAND.
WELL, YOU KNOW, HE SAID TO US
THAT HE WAS GONNA MAKE IT ALL
THE WAY ACROSS THE LAKE, AND WE
GOT TO GIVE HIM CREDIT.
HE WAS HALF RIGHT.
ANYWAY, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M GONNA BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE SHOW, AND MAYBE
I'LL BRING A BOTTLE OF WINE.
WE CAN FRY UP SOME BACON OR
SOMETHING.
SO THANK YOU ALL FOR WATCHING.
HOPE YOU ENJOYED SHOW, AND UNTIL
NEXT TIME, ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD THERE AND THE REST
OF THE GANG UP AT THE LODGE
HERE, KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[applause]
IT IS SPRING,
A TIME FOR ME TO FACE THE
REALITY THAT I AM AS OLD AS THE
LODGE ROOF.
WE HAVE A LOT IN COMMON,
THAT ROOF AND I.
WE BOTH LEAK, WE BOTH HAVE
SHINGLES, AND WE BOTH END
IN THE GUTTER.