You ever notice how
technology sucks us in
and then ridicules us?
Like back in the '50s,
if you were the first one
to have a TV antenna
on your roof,
you got a lot of respect.
These days, if you're the
last house to have one,
you get a lot
of bird droppings.
You know it's ugly
and you know you're
not using it anymore
'cause now you're on cable
or even better, you're on
your neighbour's cable,
but how do you get
the antenna off there?
You're getting a little
long in the tooth
to be climbing up on the roof
what with the bad knees
and the higher
center of gravity.
But you still
got imagination.
So go down to the wreckers
and get yourself
a steering wheel.
Not just any
steering wheel...
the kind that has the
personal airbag in the middle.
You know the ones where
if you hit a pothole
the bag explodes and breaks
your nose so you don't get hurt.
Now just slide the steering
wheel into a garbage can,
and then aim the whole unit
at the TV aerial.
Now you need a projectile
of some kind.
Here's a hint, don't think
of it as an antenna,
think of it as a headpin.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Thank you very much.
Well, thank you.
No, no.
I appreciate that.
Big, big week up at
the lodge this week.
I bought a side of beef,
478 pounds of vein-
clogging cholesterol.
Yep.
I bought a whole half a cow
including one horn
and two hooves.
Yeah.
Got it for 38 bucks.
Don't ask, I didn't.
So now we're going
to have a massive cookout,
light a shed on fire,
get a gallon of BBQ sauce
and a paint roller
and we're good to go.
Uncle Red!
What? What? What?
I was downstairs.
I was downstairs, right?
There's like a cow
in the freezer.
It winked at me.
Harold, it
didn't wink.
It's only got
one eye, okay.
I bought half a cow.
How many times have
I told you,
don't half
a cow, man.
I said half a cow.
I said that.
I said it.
You know how
tongs work, Harold?
Yeah, okay,
all right.
I don't know why you need
that much red meat anyway.
You know, being a vegetarian
is much healthier.
Oh yeah, well that cow
was a vegetarian.
How's her health?
You like math,
try these
numbers, okay?
I got that side of pure
beef for 38 bucks, okay?
It'll feed 300 lodge members
at 10 bucks a head.
Okay, that's a $3000 return
on a $38 investment.
I got 2962,
what did you get?
That's close enough.
Okay, all right.
Why, what's
the problem?
Well, I just wondered who
would sell you an entire
side of beef for $38?
Flinty McClintock.
What!
No, nope, don't make
a big deal out of this.
I might want
to buy more.
Have you ever considered
that perhaps that
the meat is BAD?
You know, like it's all
gristly or something?
It's 478 pounds of beef
and it cost $38, Harold.
Stop looking for trouble.
So Flinty McClintock,
one of the few successful
entrepreneurs in
the entire area
just didn't know
the value of the meat.
Well, I don't even care.
When I'm happy I don't look
for ways to kill the mood.
So you figure you just
got this great bargain
from Flinty
because, hey, sometimes
you should just let
an idiot
do what he
needs to do.
Yeah, exactly.
Well, do what you
need to do then.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Tonight's winner
receives this coupon
for procrastination
therapy.
Please note that tomorrow's
meeting has been postponed.
All right, Mike,
cover your ears.
Red, you've
got 30 seconds
to get Mike Hamar
to say this word...
All right, Winston.
And GO!
Okay Mike, what do you
call it when you've got
a bunch of guys all
wearing the same uniform?
A chain gang.
Ah, okay, okay.
The NHL, the NFL, the NBA
are all made up of what?
Letters.
Yeah, okay, okay.
But all of the
players are on...
Steroids.
Okay.
Mike, you know, when you
were a kid at recess,
you were
picked by a...
Witness.
Okay, okay, okay.
Sometimes the coach will
say to the players,
there's no "I" in...
Potato?
No.
Okay, no.
There's another
expression okay,
"take one for the..."
Road!
You guys are almost
out of time here.
I know, Mike.
Your brother played semi-pro
football on one of these.
Oh, a weekend pass.
No, I'm talking about
the Port Asbestos Inhalers,
that was his...
Well, I don't
know, Mr. Green,
because I never went
to those games.
The stadium was always
teeming with cops.
There we go!
It was in there!
When you first get married
you figure, at last,
I have someone to bring
me drinks and snacks
and whatever I want
whenever I want it.
Then you find out she's
thinking the same thing,
which is why
you have kids.
But then they move out,
and after you
finally admit
that dogs and cats are not
all that trainable,
you're faced with
the big decision...
Give up your dreams
or build a robot.
For my robot I'm going to use
this wireless video camera
that sends a
signal to my TV
so that I can direct the unit
to wherever I want it to go
from the comfort of
my own living room.
I just need to
mount the camera
on something
strong but light.
The exact opposite
of every guy I know.
How easy was that?
Everything else I'll get
from my own back yard...
or somebody's back yard.
Meet my new
ladder robot,
SEE-THRU-PEEPHOLE,
and like so many of Man's
great inventions,
I had to make a bit
of a compromise here.
See, I'm using this radio
antenna for his
extendable arm
but I needed a way for
it to move up and down
and side to side.
I thought there might be
a way to mount the unit
onto a windshield wiper
motor for the up and down
and then to mount
that WHOLE thing
onto another wiper motor
for the side to side.
I'm sure there's
a way to do that,
but I was starting to get
a really bad headache.
So instead I
mounted the antenna
on just one wiper motor
but at kind of an angle
so it goes up and down
and side to side
at the same time.
It does two things at once
but not very well.
Kind of like when
Madonna took up acting.
I'm running everything
off a car battery
and I control the wiper motor
and the antenna and the camera
with this
custom controller.
They're actually just
garage door openers
but you'd never know.
Just need a couple more things
to make him completely human
like a fondue fork
for the end of his Canadarm
so he can stab things
and a crowbar to guarantee
unrestricted access.
The only job left
is to figure out a
way to make him mobile.
Problem solved.
I got a couple of heavy-duty
radio-controlled toys
and mounted them
as the robot's wheels.
The clothes make him
look almost human...
like Moose Thompson.
He can go forwards,
backwards
and I can steer it
which is always helpful.
Heck, if I put one vehicle in
drive and the other in reverse,
I could make him spin
right on the spot.
And thanks to my
video camera,
I can see everything he's
doing right here on my TV
And that's how you make
your very own robot valet.
So remember, if the women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
And now for
a demonstration,
my cyborg will bring me
a nice, light repast.
This is like one
of those doctors
doing a fancy
surgical procedure.
This is a snackandectomy.
Houston, the
eagle has landed.
[ MOTORS WHIRRING ]
BERNICE:
Thank you, dear.
I want to talk
to you guys out there
who leave everything
to the last minute.
You know who you are.
By the time you got around
to buying your wife
a birthday present
the only shops open were
the 7-11 and the liquor store.
Remember how upset she was
with the bottle of gin
and the Pez dispenser?
I think I know why men leave
things to the last minute...
sports and movies.
In any professional game,
the closer they get to the
end the longer it takes,
all the time outs and
penalties and commercials.
No sports fan has any idea
of what two minutes left
means in real life.
And to a man, movies are
kind of like being intimate.
The best things
happen at the end.
Until then, there's really
no need to pay much attention.
But in the last
60 seconds of a movie,
the hero bites
through the steel chains,
leg wrestles a dinosaur
and rescues a beautiful maiden
just before she marries
the game show host.
But this procrastination
habit of yours
is making life difficult for
the people you care about
and you should
work on that
but you won't.
So instead, turn
your watch ahead.
And if you're really bad,
turn your calendar ahead.
Remember, I'm
pulling for you.
We're all
in this together.
Household appliances
are great,
but when it
comes to sewage,
your Hoover
isn't worth a damn.
Well, the beef barbeque
is a sell out,
300 guys,
10 bucks a head.
Boy, some men just
love beef, eh?
Moose Thompson asked
for a drumstick.
Uncle Red!
I think you have
a problem here.
Yeah, I know but it wasn't
nice to lock you out.
No, I'm talking about
that cheap beef
you bought from
Flinty McClintock.
I think there may be
something wrong with it.
Why is there always
something wrong
with everything
I do, Harold?
Just bad luck, I figure.
I don't --
Harold, take a look
at this hamburger, eh.
That's right off
the side of beef.
Look how
perfect that is.
Appearance
isn't important.
Well, of course
you'd say that.
Tell me, what's wrong
with that quarter-pounder.
Have you ever heard
of Mad Cow disease?
I just got back from
Flinty McClintock's herd.
They don't look right.
Well, you just said
appearance is not
important.
No, but posture is.
Have you ever noticed
those cows?
They can't even
stand up straight.
Maybe that just means
it's lean meat.
No, I saw those cows,
they walk in circles
and they bark.
Uncle Red, you know,
I sent a sample
of this meat
off to the lab, okay.
Why don't we just wait
for the results to come back?
Harold, there's nothing
wrong with the meat.
Don't ruin my barbeque.
Oh, nothing wrong
with the meat.
No.
Nothing wrong
with the meat.
No.
Okay, well, then you
eat some yourself.
Well, I will.
I'll do that.
Okay.
I'll take a bite and then
you just see if I get weird.
How will I tell?
[ APPLAUSE ]
RED: Bill and I were
just cleaning up our
campsite there
and packing everything up
into a wheel barrow
and my job was to
put out the fire.
I was just going to kick
some dirt on to the fire --
Never good enough
for Bill, you know,
Mr. Safety's got
a problem --
Bill, that's not water,
that's gas.
Don't be pouring that
on the fire.
So he just chucks --
notices starts to pour gas
right into the pile
of dirt over there
and then I carry on packing
things up and he picks up
the can of water
which unfortunately
was also gas.
Throws my bed roll
on top of it.
Thank you very much
for that, Bill.
Okay, plan C.
I just ignore Bill sometimes,
it's just easier and safer.
He goes into
the shed and gets
I believe some type of
fire extinguisher...
yeah, fire extinguisher
and a little --
one of those small units.
They pack a punch
those little jobs.
Okay, all right, plan D.
A bigger fire extinguisher.
These are the CO2.
What they do is they put
carbon dioxide out
and that smothers the fire
by taking all the oxygen
out of the air.
So Bill's just going
to do that to --
No, Bill, there's a pin.
There's a pin on the unit.
You pull the pin --
Yeah.
So now Bill took a lungful
of carbon dioxide.
He needs some air
I figure just little --
Give him a little bit of air
and he's fine but
the fire's still going.
So where are we now?
Plan E, plan E.
Yeah, all right.
Meanwhile, I'm almost finished
getting the place cleaned up
and ready to go.
He's got some --
Okay, baking soda, that's
another fire retardant.
Speaking of retardants.
Nope, didn't do it.
Didn't do it, Bill.
So now what are
we going to do?
No no Bill.
No, no, Bill, no, no.
You're just spreading cinders
all over the place there.
No, we've got to...
Oh good, good call.
There we go.
That's the best use that
coffee ever had, believe me.
All right, plan F, this one
scares me just by the letter.
So Bill goes into the shed
and he gets
a couple of shovels.
The idea is we're going
to use the same idea
as kicking the dirt on
but if we get a shovelful...
So he gives me one shovel
and says, you go over there.
Get some dirt from over there.
I'll get dirt from right here.
I think you --
Right where the gasoline
had spilled into the... YEAH.
Meanwhile,
just very simple,
I come over with some dry,
clean dirt and just
put it on there.
She's out.
Done.
Everything's cool.
Gone. Done.
Done, Bill, done.
See.
If you leave it to a pro,
everything works out.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Okay, here's a predicament
that many of you may
find yourselves in.
Let's say your
mother-in-law's coming over
but wait, there's more.
You don't have a picture
of her on display
or at least not on display
in a way she would appreciate.
The problem is,
you need to have
certain pictures around
when a person comes over
but you don't want to be
subjected to their mug
on a permanent basis.
So here's what you do.
Take a picture
out of the frame,
flip it around
to the other side.
That becomes
your screen.
That screen is for your
hidden slide projector.
So you just fill this up
with whatever pictures
you need for your
family get-togethers
but you also have your own
favourites in there
for when
they're not here.
Which, if you play
your cards right,
is most of the time.
For example, I've got some
slides of Bernice's mom
from our trip to the zoo
about a month ago.
I'll just pop
one of those up
and keep peace
in the family.
[ KNOCK AT DOOR ]
That's Bernice's mom now.
C'mon in, Mom.
I got your picture out.
She's going to love this.
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
C'mon Harold, this is
perfectly good --
This is
THROW IT ALL ON!
GET RID OF IT ALL!
But it's -- it's --
look at that, it's --
EVERY LAST BIT OF IT!
You can't trust it.
There you go.
Almost.
All of it.
Perfect.
I can't believe it.
478 pounds
of beef, man...
I put all the meat
on the campfire,
just couldn't serve
it to the people
what with all that
Mad Cow thing going on
and I gave them
all a refund.
Yeah, only after I told
them all about the problem.
You know, you did
the right thing.
You should do
that more often.
Yeah, maybe I should but
I think you'd miss me.
Well, I'm proud
of you.
You know, even before we
got the test results back,
you know, you did the
right thing and that's
very good.
I could just give
you such a hug.
No, no, Harold.
No, no. NO!
I'm very proud of you.
Well, you know,
Harold, in fairness,
you were the one who
pointed out the problem
and I know sometimes
I can be a little
difficult.
You're impossible.
I know sometimes I can
be a little difficult
but you pushed
through that
and I guess,
in a way --
I mean, a way
of looking at
would be to say,
you know
I'm kind of,
you know,
well -- I'm --
I'm -- I'm --
I'm proud of
you too, Harold.
Red,
we're okay!
Is this
a bad time?
No, no, no,
no, no, no.
What do you
mean, we're okay?
The results are back.
It's not
Mad Cow Disease.
No, the feed corn
at the cattlery
was in the
silo too long
and it turned
to alcohol.
The cows were drunk.
Oh no, no, no.
Not drunk,
marinated.
You know
what that means,
We can serve the
beef after all.
Yeah!
Might be a little
too well done.
And too
hard to find.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Meeting time.
Why, thank you,
Harold
and as always,
it's such a treat
to have you
to tell
me what to do.
You're welcome.
So if my wife is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting.
I did something today
I'd never done before...
I erred on the
side of caution.
That won't be happening
any time soon.
For the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of
myself and Harold
and the whole gang up
here at Possum Lodge...
Keep your stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Okay, everybody,
have a seat now.
C'mon, guys.
Guys, c'mon,
take your seats.
Sit down.
Everybody sit
down over there.
C'mon guys,
sit down.
Okay, sit down.
All rise.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the man's prayer.
I'm a man
but I can change
if I have to
I guess.
Okay, men, the side
of beef blowing up
has made a bit of an impact
into our community.
We figure about 200 pounds
of hamburger hit Possum Lake
so... the fish may not
be biting for a while
and Stinky Peterson got
drilled in the face
with a rump roast.
His wife says he
never looked better.
And the dog
comes to him now.