ALLOT OF TIMES A NEW PRODUCT
WILL COME ON THE MARKET
AND ONE OF THE GUYS WILL SAY
BOY, THAT IS SO SIMPLE, WHY
DIDN'T WE THINK OF THAT?
WHICH I CHOOSE TO TAKE
AS A COMPLIMENT.
BASICALLY WE HAVE NO RESPECT
FOR THE CREATIVE PROCESS.
OUR ATTITUDEIS IF SOMEBODY
THOUGHT OF IT,
ANYBODY COULD HAVE THOUGHT
OF IT, INCLUDING ONE OF US.
WE WERE JUST TOO BUSY WATCHING
T.V. OR EATING OR SOMETHING.
IT'S NOT SMART OR CORRECT
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT MAKES US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red: ON TODAY'S SHOW,
BILL IS GOING
TO THROW THE DISCUS
RIGHT INTO  MY WINDSHIELD
WIPER, THANK YOU, BILL.
DOUGIE I GUESS HAS PICKED UP
SOMETHING OFF THE CARPET.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT HE'S DOING THERE.
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW TO
MAKE A STRETCH ROWBOAT,
AND BUZZ IS GOING TO
DRY CLEAN HIS PLANE.
AND NOW HERE'S A MAN WHO
PROVES WHERE THERE'S A WILL,
THERE'S A WILDERNESS,
MY UNCLE RED GREEN!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AND NOW MEET
THE GUY WHO PROVES
WHERE THERE'S A WILL
THERE'S A WON'T,
MY NEPHEW AND DIRECTOR
BY MARRIAGE, HAROLD.
YEEHAW!
OH MAN.
BIG STUFF UP AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
ONE OF THE LOCAL
CHURCHES IS HAVING
THEIR ANNUAL FISHING
FUNDRAISER CONTEST THING,
THE CATCH A CATFISH FOR
CONFIRMATION CONTEST.
AND ALL THE PROCEEDS
ARE GOING TO GO
TO THEIR BIBLE IN
EVERY MOTEL ROOM FUND.
SO OUT ON POSSUM THE LAKE WE
GOT TO HAVE 500 FISHERMEN
OUT THERE,
CASTING, TROLLING,
WHATEVER.
MOOSE THOMPSON IS SO CONVINCED
HE'S GOING TO CATCH A
GREAT BIG CATFISH
THAT HE TOOK THE WINCH OFF HIS
TRUCK AND HE SOLDERED IT
TO A GREAT BIG
METAL FLAG POLE.
WOW! HOW MANY FISH HAVE WE
REELED IN SO FAR?
NONE.
IN FACT,
IF THIS KEEPS UP,
IT MIGHT TURN INTO THE
BIGGEST BAIT CONTEST.
I FIGURE WE GOT TO CATCH A
CATFISH EVENTUALLY,
'CAUSE CATFISH
ARE BOTTOM FEEDERS,
AND YOU CAN'T GET MORE
BOTTOM THAN POSSUM LAKE.
UNCLE RED, THERE AREN'T ANY
CATFISH IN POSSUM LAKE,
THEY LIKE FRESHWATER.
OH, YOU'RE JUST WHINING
BECAUSE THE CATFISH ARE
SMARTER THAN YOU, HAROLD.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I'M JUST NOT
INTERESTED IN FISHING
BECAUSE I AM A
TELEVISION PRODUCER.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT,
HE'S ALREADY A
BOTTOM FEEDER.
AND, YOU KNOW, THESE WINGS
THEY'RE REALLY STRONG.
YOU KNOW THE OTHER NIGHT
WE WERE HAVING A PARTY,
I HAD 7 PEOPLE ON THIS
THING DANCING.
GREAT PARTY.
GOOD THING WE DIDN'T HIT
ANY AIR POCKETS.
WHOA!
WELL, YOU CAN
SEE THE EFFECT
OF THE MODELING SCHOOL
IN THE WAY SHE
WALKS AND SHE SITS
BUT THERE SIMPLY
IS NOT A LADY-LIKE WAY
TO GET RID
OF WATERMELON PITS
NO, YOU CAN'T
REALLY HIDE THEM
THERE'S NOWHERE
TO PUT 'EM
AND EATING THEM
IS REALLY TOUGH
SO I SAY YOU HORK BACK
AND SPIT THEM AT THE WAITER
AND EVENTUALLY HE'LL STOP
SERVING THE STUFF
WELL, HERE IT IS,
TWO DAYS TO GO TILL THE
BIG WEEKEND CAMPING TRIP.
NO KIDS, NO HOUSEWORK,
NO RESPONSIBILITIES
AND NO WAY YOU'RE
GOING TO GET TO GO.
BECAUSE YOU HAVEN'T
TOLD HER YET.
AND WHEN YOU DO,
SHE'S GOING TO BLOW
A HEAD GASKET.
WHY IS IT THAT MEN
LEAVE EVERYTHING TO
THE LAST MINUTE?
I THINK WE JUST TRY
TO COVER OUR BACKSIDES
BY SAYING WE LIKE
TO BE SPONTANEOUS.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I THINK IT IS?
I THINK WE'RE
AFRAID OF THE WOMEN.
NO, NO, RED,
I DISAGREE.
I THINK
IT'S JUST 'CAUSE,
WELL, WE'RE REALLY JUST
KIND OF ASHAMED OF
OURSELVES.
ANYWAY, WE'RE GOING
TO GIVE YOU AN EXCUSE
SO YOU'LL BE ABLE TO GO
TO A TRIP, ALL RIGHT?
LIKE YOU GOT TO, SAY,
COME UP WITH A DYING
RELATIVE OR A FRIEND.
PREFERABLY ONE
OUT OF TOWN.
YEAH, ONE SHE'S
NEVER HEARD OF.
AND YOU'RE GOING TO
SAY SOMETHING TO
THE EFFECT OF,
HE'S GOING TO BE ON
HIS DEATH BED ON
FRIDAY NIGHT,
AND I'LL OF COURSE BE
TAKING MY GOLF CLUBS
AND MY FISHING TACKLE
JUST IN CASE THERE'S
SOME WEIRD MUSIC
AND A BOLT OF LIGHTNING
COMES DOWN AND HE'S UP
ON HIS FEET ON SUNDAY
LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING TO DO.
SHE'S GOING TO SEE THROUGH
THAT LIKE A SCREEN DOOR.
SHE'LL KNOW
YOU'RE LYING.
WELL, AND THAT'S THE
TRICK TO BAD LYING.
I MEAN, YOU GOT TO LET
YOUR LOVED ONE THINK
SHE FIGURED IT ALL
OUT FOR HERSELF.
THAT WAY SHE'LL GET MAD
AND GET IT ALL BLOWN OFF
IN A BIG HURRY
BECAUSE YOU'RE JUST
SO PATHETIC AND STUPID.
THEN, OF COURSE, YOU CAN
GO OFF WITH THE GUYS
FOR A WHILE
AND, YOU KNOW,
SHE'LL HAVE A COUPLE OF
DAYS TO COOL HER JETS
AND MAYBE REALIZE HOW
MUCH SHE WANTS, NEEDS
AND MISSES YOU.
BUT DON'T STAY
AWAY TOO LONG
BECAUSE SHE MIGHT REALIZE
HOW MUCH SHE REALLY WANTS,
NEEDS AND MISSES YOU.
"FOR SALE -- FOR SALE,
DO IT YOURSELF MINK COAT,
"MINK STOLE, MINK JACKET
AND MINK HAT.
"KIT INCLUDES ONE MALE MINK,
ONE FEMALE MINK,
"THERE'S A BAG OF MINK FOOD
AND ONE CAGE.
"SOME ASSEMBLY REQUIRED."
YOU KNOW, WITH EVERYBODY
OUT ON POSSUM LAKE
TRYING TO CATCH
THEMSELVES A CATFISH,
I THOUGHT I WOULD SHARE WITH
YOU ONE OF THE SECRETS OF
FRESHWATER FISHING.
JUST ONE WORD: IMAGE.
YOU GOT TO LOOK
LIKE YOU'RE THE EXPERT.
IT DOESN'T CATCH
ANY MORE FISH,
BUT IT SURE INTIMIDATES
THE OTHER FISHERMEN
AND FISHERWOMEN AND
FISHERKIDS AND SO ON.
AND IT MAKES THEM
LOSE THEIR CONCENTRATION,
THEY START DOING STUPID
THINGS, YOU KNOW,
STICKING THEIR HOOKS
IN THEIR THUMBS
OR TRYING TO SCALE FISH
WITH THE OUTBOARD MOTOR.
OR EVEN WORSE,
THEY TRY TO COPY YOU,
AND THAT PRETTY MUCH
GUARANTEES FAILURE.
NOW, I GOT A COUPLE OF FISHING
BOATS ON A TRAILER HERE.
I DID HAVE THEM ON
A TRAILER.
WELL, IT LOOKED
LIKE A 1-7/8
BUT I GUESS THAT WAS
A 2-INCH HITCH.
THERE'S ONLY TWO WAYS
REALLY TO CREATE AN IMAGE.
ONE IS TO LIE,
WHICH HAS BEEN PRETTY MUCH
OVERUSED SINCE THE NIXON ERA,
AND THE OTHER ONE IS TO HAVE
REAL IMPRESSIVE LOOKING
FISHING EQUIPMENT,
BUT THAT TAKES
A LOT OF MONEY.
SO TODAY I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW YOU CAN USE A
REAL CHEAP METHOD
TO LOOK LIKE A
RICH SUCCESSFUL FISHERMAN.
YOU'VE ALL SEEN A
STRETCH LIMO.
YOU HEARD OF ONE OF THEM DC
STRETCH EIGHT AIRPLANES.
HOW ABOUT A STRETCH
FISHING BOAT?
ALL'S YOU NEED IS A CHAIN SAW,
AND YOU CAN TURN A PAIR OF
PUNTS INTO A TWO-HULLER.
THERE WE GO.
NOW WE GOT ALL OUR PIECES TO
MAKE OURSELVES A REALLY
BIG FISHING BOAT.
HERE IS AN EXTRA BONUS...
WE MANAGED TO MAKE
OURSELVES AN ANCHOR.
THAT WAS LUCKY.
NOW WHAT WE GOT TO DO IS
SEPARATE OUR BOW OUT
FROM OUR STERN
TO START STRETCHING HER OUT.
SO LET'S GET THE BOW
OUT OF THE WAY.
ALRIGHTY.
TRY TO LINE-UP
THE CUTS THERE.
NOW WE GOT THE STERN
OUT THROUGH THERE.
[ GRUNTING ]
ALL RIGHT.
NOW ALL WE GOT TO DO
IS COME IN HERE AND
TAKE OUR MID SHIP
AND MOVE IT BACK INTO
OUR MID SHIP.
[ GROANING ]
THERE WE GO.
NOW, OF COURSE, CONNECT
ALL THE PIECES TOGETHER
USING, SAY,
RIVETS OR WELDING
OR, YOU GUESSED IT,
THE HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
NOW, THE PADDLES
HERE HAVE GOT TO GO
BECAUSE YOU CANNOT BE POWERING
A CRAFT OF THIS NATURE AND
TRY TO LOOK AFFLUENT
IF YOU'RE DRIVING
ALONG WITH PADDLES.
SO I WOULD RECOMMEND YOU
GO WITH AN OUTBOARD MOTOR
ON THERE OF SOME NATURE.
MAYBE 100 HORSEPOWER,
MAYBE EVEN MORE,
DEPENDING ON HOW
BAD YOUR SEAMS LEAK.
OH, WELL...
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE A COUPLE
OF PIECES LEFT OVER HERE.
WE HAVE A BOW,
WE HAVE A STERN.
YOU KNOW HOW I
HATE LEFTOVERS.
I GOT AN IDEA.
THERE WE GO.
WHAT'S BETTER THAN A
STRETCH FISHING BOAT?
HOW ABOUT A STRETCH FISHING
BOAT WITH A BEMINI TOP, HUH?
KEEPS THE SUN OFF YOU
AND YOUR COOLER,
KEEPS THE RAIN OFF.
TALK ABOUT IMAGE,
YOU LOOK LIKE CLEOPATRA
BARGING YOUR WAY
DOWN THE NILE.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME,
HAPPY FISHING.
AND REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
OH HERE'S
ANOTHER BONUS...
SHE DOUBLES AS A LIFEBOAT.
THAT'S PROBABLY THE MOST
IMPORTANT FEATURE OF ALL.
Red: COMING UP, WE'RE GOING
TO CLEAN OUT BUZZ'S PLANE,
AND I'M GOING TO SPLIT SOME
WOOD WHILE I TALK TO
THE TEENAGERS
SO IT WON'T BE A
COMPLETE WASTE OF TIME.
I WAS IN TOWN THE OTHER DAY
AND SAW A BUNCH OF KIDS
ON THOSE ROLLER BLADES.
YOU KNOW WHAT
ROLLER BLADES ARE?
THEY'RE THOSE LITTLE SKATES
THAT HAVE COUCH CASTERS
ON THEM INSTEAD OF BLADES.
NOW, LOOK, I DON'T LIKE TO
MAKE JUDGMENTS ABOUT
YOU TEENAGERS
AND YOUR FREE TIME
AND HOW YOU WASTE IT,
BUT ARE YOU GUYS
CRAZY OR WHAT?
SKATES ARE FOR ICE,
NOT FOR PAVEMENT.
WHEN YOU FALL ON ICE SKATES,
OKAY, YOU'RE GOING
TO SLIDE FOR A WHILE,
YOU MIGHT SCON YOUR NOGGIN ON
THE GOAL POST OR SOMETHING,
BUT YOU'LL GET OVER IT,
YOU KNOW, YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
CARRY ON A CONVERSATION,
PERHAPS HAVE CHILDREN
OF YOUR OWN SOME DAY.
WHEREAS YOU FALL ON THE
ROLLERS BLADES ON THE
PAVEMENT THERE
AND YOU'RE GOING TO LEAVE A
TRAIL OF SKIN AND FLESH
THAT WILL MAKE IT REALLY HARD
TO IDENTIFY THE BODY AT THE
END OF THE SKID MARK.
WITH A GRITTY SURFACE LIKE,
SAY, CEMENT OR PAVEMENT,
THE COEFFICIENT OF FRICTION
IS REALLY WORKING AGAINST
YOU THERE.
SO FOR GOSH SAKES
TAKE IT EASY.
IF YOU HAVE TO BE ON WHEELS,
HOTWIRE A CAR
OR SOMETHING.
"WANTED ANY AND ALL
KATHY LEE GIFFORD ALBUMS.
"WILL PAY CASH FOR YOUR
KATHY LEE GIFFORD RECORDS,
"INCLUDING
HER BEST OF ALBUM
"AND KATHY LEE SINGS HER
FAVOURITE CHRISTMAS CAROLS.
"CONTACT THE POSSUM LODGE LAKE
SKEET SHOOTING CLUB."
OH THAT'S NOT EVEN --
WELL, WE JUST REELED
IN OUR FIRST FISH
IN THE CATCH A CATFISH FOR
CONFIRMATION CONTEST,
AND, MAN, IT'S A BEAUTY.
47 FEET LONG.
47 FEET?
ONE FISH?
YEAH, 47 FOOT CATFISH.
THAT WOULD HAVE TO BE A RECORD
I WOULD THINK OF SOME KIND.
THAT'S NOT A RECORD,
THAT'S SOME KIND OF
MUTANT FREAK OF NATURE.
WELL, YOU WOULD
KNOW, HAROLD.
I TELL YOU, TO REEL IT UP
ONE OF THE BEACHES,
THEY HAD TO USE FLINTY
McCLINTOCK'S TOW TRUCK.
FIRST TIME A TOW TRUCK
HAD BEEN USED TO
BRING IN A FISH
AS FAR
AS I WOULD KNOW.
WOW! WHO MANAGED TO REEL IN
AND LAND A FISH THAT SIZE?
OH, DON'T TELL ME.
MOOSE THOMPSON AND HIS CUSTOM
MADE FISHING ROD, RIGHT,
THE ONE THAT HAS THE WINCH
SOLDERED TO THE FLAG POLE?
NO,
OLD MAN SEDGWICK.
CAUGHT IT ON HIS ANCHOR
USING STINKY PETERSON
AS BAIT.
I'M GUESSING THERE'S
A STORY HERE.
IT'S A NORMAL FISH
STORY, HAROLD.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK
THROWS THE ANCHOR OVER,
THE ANCHOR CHAIN TANGLES
AROUND STINKY'S FOOT,
OVER HE GOES,
FISH SWALLOWS STINKY,
DIES, FLOATS TO SURFACE,
THEY TOW THE FISH IN,
FISH BELCHES,
OUT COMES STINKY.
UNBELIEVABLE.
STINKY SAID YOU SHOULD
HAVE SEEN THE ONE
THAT GOT AWAY.
JUST A NORMAL
FISH STORY.
OH, YEAH, CAPTAIN A-FLAB
AND MOBY DOINK.
HERE WE ARE WITH
BUZZ SHERWOOD OUR
RESIDENT BUSH PILOT
AND DARE DEVIL
EXTRAORDINARY.
RED, YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE ONLY AS
YOUNG AS YOU FEEL.
THAT'S TRUE.
I'M GOING TO BE GOING
UP IN THE PLANE WITH
BUZZ TODAY,
SO BUZZ TELL US
A BIT ABOUT IT.
IS THIS, WHAT,
A CESSNA 150, IS IT?
ACTUALLY, RED,
THIS IS A KIT PLANE.
I BUILT IT AROUND AN
OLD VOLKSWAGON BEETLE
I USED TO HAVE.
ACTUALLY,
I HAD NINE OF THEM.
HEY, HOP ON.
ALL RIGHT.
AGE BEFORE BEAUTY.
YOU GOT A BIT
OF STUFF HERE, BUZZ.
THROW IT OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, AFTER TODAY I'M
GOING TO SELL BEAUTY,
AND I'M GOING TO
BUY A SUBMARINE.
WHAT, WHERE ARE YOU GOING
TO FIND A SUBMARINE?
DOWN ON POSSUM LAKE.
I WAS DOING SOME LOW LEVEL
TROLLING THIS MORNING,
YOU KNOW, IN THAT CATCH A
CATFISH FOR CONFIRMATION
CONTEST.
YOU GO TROLLING
FROM AN AIRPLANE?
YEAH, WITH THIS.
SCARES THE BEJEEZUS OUT
OF THE CONTESTANTS.
ANYWAY, I SEE SOMEONE
HAS BEACHED THEIR SUBMARINE
OVER ON ROCK REEF POINT.
I EVEN TOOK A
PICTURE OF IT, SEE.
THAT'S NOT A SUBMARINE.
THAT'S THE BIG CATFISH
OLD MAN SEDGWICK CAUGHT.
WOW! NO KIDDING!
YEAH.
WELL, KEEP THE GEIGER
COUNTER IN THERE.
WE GOT TO CHECK
THIS MUTANT OUT.
ALRIGHTY.
WOW! THAT WAS
THE GREATEST.
MAN, HAROLD, YOU MISSED
SOME GREAT STUNTS.
I MEAN, TECHNICALLY
THESE PLANES AREN'T CAPABLE
OF DOING THOSE
KIND OF MANEUVERS,
BUT THE PEOPLE THAT WRITE
THE TECHNICAL MANUALS,
THEY'RE A BUNCH
OF WIMPS!
WELL, THANKS, BUZZ.
I REALLY, REALLY ENJOYED THAT
RIDE AND VERY EDUCATIONAL.
YEAH, IT WAS
EDUCATIONAL FOR ME TOO.
I HAD NO IDEA HE KNEW
THOSE KIND OF WORDS.
"FOR SALE, USED BARBECUE" --
IT'S A GAS BARBECUE
THAT'S FOR SALE.
"THE TANK IS RUSTED,
THE BURNERS ARE RUSTED,
"THE HOSES ARE RUPTURED,
THE GLASS IS CRACKED
"AND THE WHEELS ARE BROKEN.
"$300 OR BEST OFFER."
"WINTER WARMTH," BY ME.
"WE ALL SCARF DOWN 7
BOWLS OF LODGE CHILI,
"THEN WE'RE OFF TO SIT
IN THE ICE FISHING HUT,
"WHERE IT'S
MINUS 10 DEGREES,
"WIND CHILL FACTOR,
MINUS 30."
IT'S MAIL CALL.
I GOT A LETTER HERE
FROM VINCENT COOMBE.
VINCENT HAS DRAWN
A PICTURE OF YOU
AND I, HAROLD.
BOY, HE SURE GOT
YOU RIGHT, DIDN'T HE?
HE MADE YOU A
LITTLE THIN THOUGH.
I GOT A LETTER HERE
FROM MATTHEW BABY
FROM EDMONTON.
MATTHEW IS ONE OF
OUR YOUNGER VIEWERS.
AND MATTHEW WRITES:
"SOMETIMES MY SIBLINGS SAY
THAT THE RED GREEN SHOW
IS FOR IDIOTS."
OH, NO, NO,
I DON'T THINK SO.
DOES YOUR FAMILY WATCH
THE SHOW, HAROLD?
NO.
SEE!
ALRIGHTY, HERE'S A
LETTER HERE FROM --
HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
HERE'S A LETTER
HERE FROM KAREN
AND SHE SAYS: "YOUR SHOW IS
JUST LIKE WHAT IS HAPPENING
"HERE IN AU TRAIN WITH
US AND OUR NEIGHBOURS."
WELL, KAREN, I WOULD
SUGGEST YOU MOVE,
SAY, BEIRUT OR
SOMEWHERE SAFE.
GOOD ADVICE.
OH, UNCLE RED, LISTEN TO THIS,
LISTEN TO THIS, LISTEN TO THIS,
SOUNDS JUST LIKE
THE POSSUM VAN.
"P.S. ONE PERSON UP HERE
ACTUALLY BURIED AN OLD VAN
"AND USED IT
FOR A SEPTIC TANK."
WELL, I'M NOT PLANNING ON
DOING THAT WITH THE
POSSUM VAN, HAROLD
OH, I KNOW, NOT YOU,
BUT I THOUGHT MAYBE THE
GUY WHO SOLD IT TO
YOU DID THAT.
WELL, SOMETHING A LITTLE
BIT SPECIAL THIS WEEK.
BILL IS HAVING HIS
VERY OWN  VERSION
OF THE POSSUM LODGE
OLYMPIC GAMES.
HE'S GOT THE TORCH THERE.
WHOA. WHOA. WHOA. WHOA.
YEAH, WATCH YOURSELF
THERE, BILL.
A LITTLE HAIRCUT COMIN'.
YOU GOT TO LOVE THAT.
ANYWAY, HE HAD THE VARIOUS
EVENTS, LIKE --
THAT'S A HAMMER THROW.
IS IT THE PENTATHALON?
WHAT THE HECK IS THAT?
ANYWAY, YOU SWING THAT
AROUND AND THE IDEA IS,
I GUESS, IT'S THE
CENTRIFUGAL FORCE,
THEY CALL THIS,
AND YOU LET THAT GO AND THEN
WHATEVER GOES THE FARTHEST,
YOU MEASURE THE DISTANCE.
NO, NO, THE OTHER WAY,
BILL, THE OTHER WAY.
BACK OVER TOWARDS --
YEAH, TOWARDS THE VAN.
OH. OH.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, THIS
IS ANOTHER EVENT THAT THE
GREEKS MADE VERY FAMOUS,
AS THEY DID WITH SO
MANY OF THEIR HABITS.
THIS WAS THE DISCUS.
IT'S IN YOUR OTHER
HAND THERE, BILL.
BILL IS NOT GREEK.
THAT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS BY,
ESPECIALLY THAT POSE THERE.
HE SPINS AROUND AND --
OKAY, BILL, STAY
INSIDE THE CIRCLE.
UP SHE COMES
AND IS COMING --
BILL, BILL, BILL, BILL,
BILL, BILL, BILL!
OH.
STRIKE TWO.
AND WHAT'S THIS?
OH, THE SHOT PUT,
THE SHOT PUT.
VERY HEAVY -- OH. OH.
THESE ARE VERY
HEAVY LITTLE BALLS
AND YOU TRY AND THROW
THEM AS FAR AS YOU CAN.
THE OLYMPICS SEEM TO BE
KIND OF A THEME HERE,
YOU JUST PICK UP STUFF AND
THROW IT AS FAR AS YOU CAN.
THOSE GREEKS MUST HAVE HAD
TROUBLE WITH THEIR NEIGH --
YOU KNOW, I'M THINKING OF
PICKING UP SOMETHING
AND THROWING IT AS
FAR AS I CAN TOO
AND IT'S STANDING
BESIDE ME.
NO YOU DON'T.
NO. NO. NO.
NO MEANS NO.
NO.
OH.
TRY THE UNDERHANDED LIKE
TAKING YOUR KID BOWLING
OR SOMETHING.
OH BOY.
THANK YOU, BILL.
AND WHAT'S THIS NOW?
OH THE JAVELIN.
NOW I LOVE THIS.
I LOVE THIS -- OH!
I LOVE THE IDEA OF BEING
ABLE TO GO OUT AND HUNT
WITH AN ACTUAL SPORTING
EQUIP -- OH!
HE'S CAUGHT HIMSELF
UP IN THERE.
YEAH.
YOU ALL RIGHT THERE, BILL?
I'M TRYING
NOT TO LAUGH.
OH, LET ME HELP YOU.
I'LL STAND ON YOUR FOOT.
THERE YOU GO.
PULL THAT OUT OF THERE.
NOW YOU CAN CARRY THE -- OH.
SO BILL'S DECIDED THAT
HE CAME IN NUMBER ONE,
THE JUDGES RULE OTHERWISE,
SO BILL IS NUMBER TWO.
AND SPEAKING
OF NUMBER TWO...
STAY TUNED, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
WILL BE HERE
TO PUMP YOU OUT,
AND YOU WANT TO BE CLOSE BY
WHEN THE CATFISH EXPLODES.
"THE MATING SEASON," BY ME.
"SPRING, THE MATING SEASON,
THE COURTING RITUAL,
"THE PRIMPING AND
PREENING BY THE MALE,
"THE TEASING AND EVENTUAL
CONSENTING BY THE FEMALE,
"THE DECISION AS TO WHO
PAYS FOR THE ROOM."
NEXT, "WOULD THE OWNER OF AN
'85  LESABRE WITH A BLUE DOOR,
"PRIMER RED TRUNK,
GREY PRIMER FENDER,
"MISSING REAR LEFT FENDER,
WHITE HOOD AND A RUSTED ROOF,
"WOULD YOU PLEASE BUY A
NEW CAR, FOR PETE SAKE?"
OH, OKAY!
WELL, THAT HUGE CATFISH
OLD MAN SEDGWICK REELED
UP ONTO THE BEACH
HAS TURNED INTO
A REAL ATTRACTION HERE.
I CANNOT BELIEVE PEOPLE
DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
BETTER TO DO
THAN STAND AROUND
LOOKING AT DEAD FISH.
JUST LIKE OLD
MAN SEDGWICK LOOKING
IN THE MIRROR, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW WHAT HE'S
GOING TO DO WITH IT?
FEED AFRICA FOR A YEAR?
NO, HAROLD, HE WANTS
TO MAKE MONEY WITH
THE THING.
UNCLE RED, YOU CANNOT MAKE
MONEY OFF A DEAD CATFISH.
NOW, HAROLD, THAT'S
EXACTLY THE REASON
YOUR GENERATION
CAN'T FIND JOBS.
WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO IS
WE WERE THINKING MAYBE
OF COVERING IT WITH
SHEET METAL, MAKE IT
A TOURIST ATTRACTION...
CARL THE CHROME CATFISH.
THAT WAS BEFORE WE GOT
THE FISH OIL IDEA.
EXCUSE ME, FISH OIL?
YEAH, FISH OIL.
LIKE THEY HAVE
COD LIVER OIL,
WHY NOT SEDGWICK'S
CATFISH GALL BLADDER OIL.
IT'LL BE A MEDICINE.
WHO'S GOING
TO PRESCRIBE IT,
DR. KEVORKIAN?
NO, HAROLD, WE'RE GOING
TO GET RICH HERE.
YOU KNOW WHALE OIL THEY USE
THAT FOR COSMETICS AND PERFUME,
WHY CAN'T THERE BE
CATFISH COSMETICS?
YEAH, YOU CAN CALL IT
FISH FACE.
LAUGH IF YOU
WANT, HAROLD,
YOU WON'T BE LAUGHING WHEN
YOU SEE OUR COLOGNES
IN EVERY STORE.
CATFISH PERFUME,
IT'LL REEL IN
THE SUCKERS.
I'LL TELL YOU, HAROLD,
THAT FISH IS A WINDFALL.
YEAH, BUT ONLY
IF YOU'RE UPWIND.
SINCE WE'RE COMING OUT
WITH OUR NEW LINE OF
CATFISH COLOGNES
AND FISH FRAGRANCES,
I THOUGHT I'D TALK
TO LOCAL ENTREPRENEUR
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD.
IF YOUR SEPTIC
OVERFLOWS
JUST CALL WINSTON
WITH HIS HOSE.
YEAH, WINSTON, YOU'VE
MADE A REAL SUCCESSFUL
BUSINESS HERE, HAVE YOU NOT?
RED, I LIKE TO
THINK I'VE GONE
FROM EFFLUENCE
TO AFFLUENCE.
SO, WINSTON, WE'RE
STARTING A NEW THING HERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS THE
MOST IMPORTANT THING
WHEN YOU GO
INTO BUSINESS?
IS IT THE RELIABILITY
OF THE SERVICE,
THE DEPENDABILITY,
THE HONESTY,
WHAT IS THE
REAL SECRET?
NO, NO, THE SECRET IS
HAVING A CATCHY
FLASHY NAME
THAT FOLKS
CAN REMEMBER, EH?
OH YEAH.
I LEARNED THAT FROM
A COURSE I ONCE TOOK
CALLED THE ULTIMATE
SUPER SUCCESS STORY,
IN ONE EASY STEP TO RICHES,
FAME AND GLORY -- OH!
I WAS GOING TO CALL MY
COMPANY TIDY TOITY, EH?
OH, YEAH, I HAD THIS
LITTLE ANIMATED CHARACTER
CALLED MR. TIDY TOITY,
AND HE'D BE SITTING THERE
HOLDING A BIG HUNK OF HOSE
IN TWO FEET
OF SEWAGE, EH,
BUT IT WAS TOO,
AH --
WELL, YOU KNOW...
YEAH.
CUTE.
YEAH, CUTE.
THEN I WAS GOING TO CALL
IT McDRAINAGE, EH,
BUT SOME MAJOR FAST
FOOD CHAIN THREATENED
TO SUE ME.
SURE.
I SEE, WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING IS
THE SECRET TO SUCCESS IS
FOR US TO FIND OURSELVES
A CATCHY NAME.
EXACTLY.
YOUSE GUYS ARE
LOOKING FOR A NAME
FOR PERFUME, RIGHT?
SO IT'S GOTTA
BE A HOT NAME THAT
SUGGESTS ROMANCE.
I'M THINKING
SIN OR FLING.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
BUCK NAKED AND DRUNK.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YEAH. YEAH.
ANYWAY, LISTEN, THERE'S
A WHALE OF A STENCH DOWN
BY THE BEACH RIGHT NOW.
I BELIEVE SOMEONE'S
IN NEED OF MY SERVICES.
OH, NO, NO, THAT'S JUST
A BIG CATFISH OLD MAN
SEDGWICK CAUGHT.
THAT THING'S BEEN LYING OUT
IN THE SUN ALL AFTERNOON.
REALLY?
YEAH.
HEY, THAT GIVES ME A GOOD
IDEA FOR THE NAME OF
YOUR PERFUME, EH?
HOW ABOUT SWOON?
WELL, THAT'S IT
FOR THIS FISH,
SO THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF THE FISH AND
KEEP YOUR FISH ON...
UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED,
UNCLE RED WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE FISH -- OH, HELLO!
THERE'S A FISH --
ARE YOU --
WHAT HAPPENED?
CATFISH?
OH HI, HAROLD.
THE 47-FOOT FISH,
UNCLE RED, WHAT HAPPENED?
GONE. GONE.
GONE?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, A LITTLE DIZZY
FROM THE CONCUSSION, HAROLD.
CONCUSSION?
BOTTOM FEEDER,
HAROLD, CATFISH,
MOOSE SOLDERING, PROPANE,
LEFT THE TANK GOING,
STILL GOING,
FALLS INTO THE LAKE,
DID I SAY STILL GOING?
STILL GOING.
AND CATFISH COMES ALONG
AND A BIG CATFISH.
47 FEET.
3 FEET. 3 FEET.
3 FEET. GOOD ONE.
SWALLOWS THE PROPANE,
STILL GOING.
INFLATES, HAROLD,
REALLY BIG.
47 FEET.
ALL PROPANE, HAROLD.
MOOSE CUTTING IT
WITH A CHAIN SAW.
SPARK.
BOOM. BOOM. BOOM.
RAINED FISH FOR 30,
40 MINUTES, HAROLD.
I'M FINE.
I KEPT MY CLOTHES.
BUT MOOSE, THE CHAINSAW,
THE OVERALLS,
THE BODY HAIR,
HIS FUTURE FAMILY,
GONE.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
UNCLE RED, THAT WAS
THE CRY OF THE POSSUM.
IT'S MEETING TIME, OKAY?
IT WAS HORRIBLE,
RAINING FISH.
WE'LL JUST GET YOU CLEANED
UP AND THEN WE'LL GO TO
THE MEETING, OKAY?
YEAH, BOOM,
AND THEN FISH.
FISH AS FAR AS YOU
CAN SEE, HAROLD.
WELL, IF MY AUNT BERNICE
IS WATCHING,
UNCLE RED WILL BE OKAY
IN A FEW MINUTES.
AND FOR THE REST OF YOU, ON
BEHALF OF MYSELF AND UNCLE RED
AND EVERYONE ELSE UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND KEEP
YOUR STICK ON THE ICE, OKAY?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
ALL RIGHT, WE DON'T
KNOW WHAT IT IS,
BUT HOPEFULLY SOME DAY
IT'LL BE OUT OF HERE
WE WON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT IT.
HAROLD, CAN YOU
EXPLAIN THIS AT ALL?