[loud blowing sound]
YOU KNOW, SOME OF THE NEWER,
MORE EXPENSIVE CARS
HAVE A SYSTEM THAT
LETS THE DRIVER KNOW
THERE'S SOMETHING IN HIS WAY
WHEN HE'S BACKING UP.
I GUESS REAL WEALTH MEANS
NEVER HAVING TO LOOK IN
YOUR REAR VIEW MIRROR.
MY LEVEL OF WEALTH MEANS
NOT EVEN HAVING A REAR
VIEW MIRROR.
BUT I FIGURE,
HEY, WHAT THE HECK?
I CAN AT LEAST ACT WEALTHY.
[engine turning over]
[tuba blast]
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE THAT.
WELL, BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
RUMOUR HAS IT WE'RE GOING
TO GET A NEW BAR IN TOWN
BECAUSE RIGHT NOW WE
JUST HAVE THE ONE...
THE BROKEN SPIRIT.
THERE'S NO COMPETITION,
SO THEY GOT A REAL ATTITUDE.
GET THIS...
THEY WON'T SERVE YOU
UNLESS YOU CAN PAY.
UNCLE RED!
[cheers and applause]
IT'S SO GREAT.
THE BAR'S IN TOWN.
YOU KNOW WHAT
IT'S CALLED?
THE GO GO BAR.
I LIKE THE SOUND
OF THAT, HAROLD, EH.
YOU THINK BERNICE
WILL LET ME GO?
WELL, YOU DON'T
GO TO IT.
NO, YOU EAT IT.
IT'S AN ENERGY BAR,
GO GO BAR.
YEAH, AND THEY'VE ASKED
ME TO DO THE MARKETING
IN THIS AREA.
GO GO BAR!
GO GO AWAY,
HAROLD.
HAROLD, YOU GOTTA
HOOK US UP
WITH SOME MORE OF
THESE GO GO BARS.
OH, YEAH, YOU GOTTA
GET US AS MANY AS
YOU CAN SPARE.
I HAVEN'T FELT THIS
GREAT MY WHOLE LIFE.
USUALLY THE SEWAGE BUSINESS
JUST SUCKS THE ENERGY
RIGHT OUTTA ME.
WELL, THERE'S A DELIVERY
COMING THIS AFTERNOON.
I'LL HAVE THEM SENT RIGHT
OVER TO YOUR PLACES.
OH, SEND 'EM TO THE
STORE, NOT TO MY HOME.
'CAUSE IF ANN MARIE SPENDS
THE DAY EATING ENERGY BARS,
BY BEDTIME I'M
A DEAD MAN.
NOT A BAD WAY
TO GO, THOUGH, DALTON.
YOU GUYS EVEN KNOW
WHAT'S IN THESE
THINGS?
WELL, THEY'RE
ALL NATURAL, RED.
YEAH, THEY GOT ELECTROLYTES
FOR ENERGY;
GINSENG FOR, UH --
OH!
MEMORY;
AND GINGER ROOT
FOR GENERAL HEALTH.
HEY! I COULD BE
THEIR MASCOT.
ALL HAIL
GENERAL HEALTH.
OH, YEAH?
YOU LOOK MORE
LIKE MAJOR DUFUS.
[applause]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
TONIGHT'S WINNER RECEIVES THIS
EXCITING BREATH MINT GUN.
IT'S PERFECT FOR PARTY
GUESTS WITH HALITOSIS.
JUST GET 'EM LAUGHING,
THEN NAIL 'EM WITH A CANDY
RIGHT BETWEEN THE TONSILS!
[applause]
OKAY, ED,
COVER YOUR EARS.
RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET ED FRID TO SAY
THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, ED,
YOU KNOW THIS ONE.
WHAT DO YOU CALL
A GROUP OF LIONS?
TROUBLE.
NO, OKAY, THIS IS
SOMETHING THAT A MAN HAS
THAT SHOULD NEVER
BE TAKEN AWAY FROM HIM.
HIS LEG.
NO, UM...
OKAY, ED, YOU'RE AN EFFECTIVE
ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER,
SO THIS BRINGS
YOU LOT OF...
MEDICAL ATTENTION.
NO, OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
EVERY PERSON SHOULD HAVE.
OH! AN ESCAPE ROUTE!
OKAY, YOU'VE HEARD
A MAN SAY,
I MAY NOT HAVE
A LOT OF MONEY,
BUT AT LEAST I'VE
GOT MY...
OWN TEETH.
ALMOST OUTTA TIME, RED.
YEAH, OKAY.
OKAY, ED, WHAT COMES
BEFORE A FALL?
STEPPING ON A RAT.
STEPPING ON A RAT?
LOOK, IT HAPPENED, OKAY?
I DON'T TAKE ANY PRIDE IN IT.
THERE YOU GO!
[quirky upbeat music]
OH, HI, EVERYBODY.
RANGER GORD HERE
WITH ANOTHER ONE OF MY
CRITICALLY ACCLAIMED
ANIMATED SHORTS.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
ASKING YOURSELF...
WHICH CRITIC GAVE
ME THE ACCLAIM?
OH, WELL, SORRY, FOLKS.
I DIDN'T REALISE THIS WAS
LET'S CALL GORD'S BLUFF NIGHT.
SO I MADE IT UP.
BIG DEAL.
IT'S CALLED HYPE.
THOSE HOLLYWOOD BIG SHOTS
DO IT ALL THE TIME.
OH, YEAH, BUT WHEN
GORD DOES IT,
OLD BUDDY GORD, YOU GOTTA CUT
HIM DOWN TO SIZE, DON'T YOU?
[heaving sobs]
ANYWAY, THIS ONE'S CALLED,
ALL ABOUT THE NORTHERN LIGHTS.
SO SIT BACK AND ENJOY.
HERE WE GO.
[quirky upbeat music]
HEY, EVERYONE.
TODAY I'M GOING TO
TEACH EVERYONE ALIVE
ABOUT THE MIRACLE OF
THE NORTHERN LIGHTS.
ALSO KNOWN AS
THE AURORA BOREALIS.
ISN'T THAT INTERESTING?
ACTUALLY, YOU'RE STARTING
TO BOREAL US ALREADY.
HA! A SMALL JOKE
FROM A SMALL MAN.
AMUSINGLY, ANCIENT PEOPLE
CAME UP WITH ALL KINDS
OF RIDICULOUS EXPLANATIONS
FOR THE LIGHTS,
THINKING THEM ANIMAL SPIRITS
OR AN OMEN OF WAR.
OF COURSE, NOW WE ALL
KNOW THE REAL CAUSE.
OH, ELECTRONS FROM
THE SOLAR WINDS
INTERACTING WITH THE
EARTH'S MAGNETIC FIELD?
Gord:
VERY NAIVE, HAROLD.
NO, THE LIGHTS ARE ACTUALLY
THE SPIRIT OF AURORA,
GREEK GODDESS OF THE DAWN,
REACHING ACROSS
THE HEAVENS
TO COMMUNICATE WITH
HER ONE TRUE LOVE...
ME.
LOOK!
THERE SHE IS NOW.
TO THE HORIZON LINE.
OH, FALSE ALARM.
IT'S JUST AN
OUT-OF-CONTROL BONFIRE.
COME ON.
LET'S GO.
OH-AHH, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
PUT IT OUT, GORD.
DO I TELL YOU HOW TO
DO YOUR JOB, HAROLD?
[thunder clap]
WELL, YOU'RE IN LUCK.
RAIN'S TAKING
CARE OF IT.
YES, BUT WITH THESE
LOW LYING STORM CLOUDS,
WE'LL NEVER SEE AURORA.
HERE, YOU TWO CLIMB THIS
SURPRISINGLY TALL TREE
AND TAKE A PICTURE OF
HER TO SHOW EVERYONE.
OH-AHH, SHE'S YOUR
TRUE LOVE, GORD.
WHY DON'T, UM,
YOU DO IT, HUH?
CLEARLY YOU KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT WOMEN, HAROLD.
I'M PLAYING HARD TO GET.
COME ON.
NOW, DO IT.
[thunder clap]
[Red and Harold screaming]
OH, THAT WAS FAST.
LET'S SEE THE PHOTO.
I THINK MY FILLINGS
HAVE MELTED.
HANG ON.
STORM'S CLEARING.
OH, FORGET IT, GORD.
WE CAN'T SEE THE LIGHTS.
AND EVEN IF WE COULD,
IT'S JUST A BUNCH OF CHARGED
PARTICLES IN THE ATMOSPHERE.
IT'S NOT A GODDESS.
OH, REALLY, RED?
AND WHAT
DO YOU CALL THAT?
[choral music]
[voice echoing]
GORDON, I'VE MISSED YOU.
WELL, I MISSED
YOU TOO, AURORA.
WHY HAVEN'T
YOU CALLED?
WELL, GEE, BABY, YOU KNOW,
THIS IS MY BUSY TIME OF YEAR.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE EVER DOUBTED HIM.
WELL, TRULY,
WE ARE THE FOOLS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THANKS FOR SHOWING UP,
DOLL FACE.
YOU REALLY KNOW HOW
TO LIGHT UP A ROOM, HUH?
[laughing]
[quirky upbeat music]
[applause]
WE'VE ALL SEEN
THESE PICKET FENCES
THAT PEOPLE THINK ARE
QUAINT AND RUSTIC
AND GIVE A SENSE
OF EASY LIVING
IN A RELAXED
RURAL ENVIRONMENT.
BUT LET'S NOT FORGET
THE MAIN PURPOSE OF A FENCE
IS TO KEEP SOMETHING IN
OR SOMETHING OUT
OR BOTH.
SO THIS TIME ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW TO
TURN YOUR PICKET FENCE
INTO A BILLBOARD
THAT'LL SEND A CLEAR
MESSAGE TO YOUR NEIGHBOURS
AND THE WORLD IN GENERAL.
FIRST THING YOU WANNA DO IS
TAKE THE PICKETS OFF THERE.
ALL YOU NEED FOR THAT
IS A HAMMER.
AND MAYBE
SOME WOOD GLUE.
OKAY, I KNOW I SAID
WOOD GLUE,
BUT YOU KNEW
I WAS KIDDING.
NOW YOU WANNA REMOUNT ALL
YOUR PICKETS ON THERE
USING JUST ONE SIX-INCH
SPIKE IN EACH ONE
AND JUST HELD
IN ONE PLACE
SO THE PICKET CAN KIND OF
PIVOT FROM THERE.
AND, YEAH, YOU CAN USE A
SMALLER NAIL IF YOU WANT TO.
I PREFER THE BIGGER TARGET,
BUT, HEY,
IT'S YOUR THUMB.
OKAY, I GOT ALL MY
PICKETS MOUNTED ON THERE,
AND THEN I'VE ATTACHED
FISHING LINE TO EACH ONE.
THAT'S HOW I CONTROL IT.
BY THE WAY, THESE ARE
WOODEN PICKETS.
THEY'RE NOT WILSON PICKETS.
HOO! HOO!
GOOD GOD, Y'ALL!
OW.
THESE FISHING LINES ARE ALL
ATTACHED TO MY BILLBOARD
CONTROL PANEL.
THIS IS WHERE ALL
THE THINKING CAME IN.
THAT TOOK A WHILE.
EACH LINE IS ATTACHED
TO A RING HERE,
AND WHEN I WANNA
FORM A CERTAIN LETTER,
I JUST PULL THAT RING DOWN
TO THE PEG ACROSS FROM
THAT LETTER,
AND THAT TURNS MY PICKET
FENCE INTO A BILLBOARD.
FOR EXAMPLE, LET'S SAY YOU'VE
GOT SOME NEW NEIGHBOURS
MOVING IN NEXT DOOR
AND YOU WANNA USE
YOUR FENCE TO SAY HELLO.
OKAY, BUT THEN MAYBE AFTER
THEY'VE LIVED THERE FOR
A LITTLE WHILE
YOU FIND OUT THEY LIKE TO FOOL
AROUND WITH FIREARMS
IN THE BACKYARD.
WELL, THAT REQUIRES
A CHANGE OF SIGNS.
OH, WAIT.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
AND THEN WHEN YOU
FINALLY REALISE
THESE ARE REALLY
NOT YOUR KIND OF PEOPLE,
DON'T SIT ON THE FENCE.
LET THEM KNOW.
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[horn honking]
[cheers and applause]
[quirky upbeat music]
I WANT TO TALK TO ALL
YOU DADS OUT THERE
WHO SAY STUFF
TO YOUR KIDS LIKE,
SHOOT FOR THE STARS
OR STRIVE TO BE NUMBER ONE.
OH, I KNOW ALL
YOU'RE TRYING TO DO
IS POUR GASOLINE ONTO
THE SOGGY KINDLING OF
ADOLESCENT AMBITION,
BUT ARE YOU
HELPING THE KID
OR ARE YOU JUST SETTING HIM
UP FOR A LIFETIME OF
DISAPPOINTMENT?
'CAUSE TO HAVE
A REAL GOOD LIFE
DEPENDS MORE ON GEOMETRY
THAN IT DOES ON AMBITION.
SEE, SUCCESS TO ME IS
KIND OF LIKE A PYRAMID --
IT'S LIKE YOUR
OWN BODY SHAPE.
KINDA GOT YOUR
LITTLE POINT AT THE TOP
AND REAL WIDE
AT THE BOTTOM.
AND YOU DON'T WANT TO GET
TOO MANY PEOPLE OUT THERE
BECAUSE, WELL, IT
JUST DOESN'T WORK,
AND IT'S TOO MUCH
LIKE A GOVERNMENT.
AND ASK YOURSELF
THIS QUESTION,
DO YOU WANT YOUR KID TO
BEHAVE THE WAY THE GUYS
AT THE TOP DO?
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
INSTEAD, GIVE 'EM THE SAME
ADVICE THAT MADE YOU THE
MAN YOU ARE TODAY...
SHOOT FOR THE MIDDLE.
I'M TELLING YOU,
FOR MOST OF US,
THE MIDDLE IS WHERE
YOU WANT TO BE,
BECAUSE IN LIFE THE ODD TIME
YOU STUMBLE NOW AND THEN,
AND IF YOU'RE IN THE MIDDLE,
NO MATTER WHICH WAY YOU FALL,
YOU GOT SOMEBODY
TO LAND ON.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
SOMETIMES IN LIFE,
THINGS START TO LOOK GRIM.
YOUR SEPTICS GET FILLED
TO WELL PAST THEIR BRIM.
SO CALL ME RIGHT NOW,
AND I'LL GIVE THEM A SKIM,
BEFORE A WALK ON THE LAWN
TURNS INTO A SWIM.
WELL, BOY,
I HAVE TO ADMIT,
I'VE TURNED RIGHT AROUND IN
THIS WHOLE ENERGY BAR THING.
I'VE BEEN EATING HAROLD'S
GO GO BARS HERE,
AND THEY'VE GOT A
REAL KICK TO THEM.
OH, YEAH.
I'LL TELL YA,
I'M MORE ALERT,
AND I'M GETTING
MORE STUFF DONE.
I'M EVEN LISTENING TO
PEOPLE WHEN THEY'RE
TALKING TO ME NOW.
AND I'VE STOPPED SNORING,
ACTUALLY STOPPED
SLEEPING ALL TOGETHER.
UNCLE RED,
HAVE YOU GOT A MINUTE?
WELL, LET ME JUST
CHECK MY DAYTIMER.
YOU HAVE
A DAYTIMER?
YEAH, I'M A BUSY
GUY, HAROLD.
WE'RE MAKING A LOT OF
CHANGES TO THE LODGE, OKAY?
Harold:
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
HOW ARE
YOU NEXT JULY,
SAY, THE 23rd
AROUND 3:15?
GOOD. YEAH. FINE.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL PUT
YOU DOWN FOR 3:15.
I'LL HAVE MY PEOPLE
SET IT UP, OKAY?
YOU HAVE PEOPLE NOW?
HERE THEY ARE NOW.
DALTON, WANT TO
MEET WITH HAROLD NEXT
JULY 23rd AT 3:15.
WE'LL GIVE HIM
TEN MINUTES, OKAY?
WHAT DO
YOU GOT FOR ME?
OKAY, DID A MARKET
ANALYSIS ON THE
LODGE PROPERTY,
AND THE CONDO DEVELOPMENT
LOOKS LIKE THE WAY TO GO.
HAVE YOU LOST
YOUR MIND?
EXACTLY.
LISTEN TO
DALTON HERE.
THE COMMERCIAL SECTOR
IS WHERE IT'S AT.
I SAY WE TURN THIS DUMP
INTO A MINI-MALL.
NO. NO.
HOW 'BOUT THIS, GUYS...
WE PUT A CONDO DEVELOPMENT
ON TOP OF A MINI-MALL?
KA-CHING!
LET'S MEET TONIGHT
ON THIS, OKAY?
HOW 'BOUT 3:00 a.m.?
THAT WAY WE CAN CHECK
THE CANADIAN DOLLAR
WHEN THE LONDON
MARKETS OPEN.
BUT I'M GOING TO NEED
SOME MORE GO GO BARS.
ME TOO.
YES, ME TOO.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
WAIT! WAIT!
YOU GUYS HAD BETTER CUT
WAY BACK ON THE GO GO BARS.
C'MON. NO WAY
YOU GOTTA KEEP THOSE
GO GO BARS COMING,
HAROLD.
I DON'T HAVE ANY!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I DON'T HAVE ANY.
IT WAS JUST A TEST.
THAT'S ALL THEY SENT ME.
CAN'T YOU SEE WHAT'S
HAPPENING HERE?
YOU GUYS ARE ADDICTED
TO THE GO GO BARS.
NO!
NO.
NO. NO.
I CAN QUIT ANY
TIME I WANT.
I HOPE SO BECAUSE THERE
ARE NO MORE GO GO BARS.
THAT'S COOL.
FINE.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I AM OKAY WITH IT!
I'M GOOD.
Red (voice over):
WE HAVE AN AREA OUT
BEHIND THE LODGE
THAT SEEMS TO COLLECT A LOT
OF GARBAGE FOR SOME REASON.
ONCE IN A WHILE WE
GOT TO CLEAN HER ALL UP,
AND WALTER AND I WERE BACK
THERE TRYING TO GET HER
CLEANED UP A LITTLE BIT
AND WE HAD NO IDEA
WHERE THE GARBAGE --
DALTON HAD COME BY
ON HIS WAY TO THE DUMP
IN A PICKUP TRUCK,
AND APPARENTLY THERE
IS A POTHOLE THERE,
AND WE DIDN'T SEE IT --
AND THIS MAY BE
WHERE THE GARBAGE --
AND OF COURSE WE DIDN'T
SEE IT COME ALONG,
BUT WE JUST KIND OF
IGNORE THAT AND CARRY ON.
BUT WALTER NOTICED THAT THE
BOARD THERE HAD A NAIL IN IT.
HE THOUGHT THIS MIGHT COME IN
HANDY FOR PICKING UP PAPERS
AND WHAT HAVE YOU,
SO WE TRIED IT --
JUST TRIED ONE, YOU KNOW,
WE COULD PROBABLY PICK UP
FOUR, FIVE OR SIX MORE
ALL ON THE ONE GO.
SO THAT'S KIND
OF SMART THINKING.
MEANWHILE I'M NOT PAYING A
WHOLE LOT OF ATTENTION
TO WHAT HE'S DOING.
I'M JUST PICKING UP GARBAGE
AND PUTTING IT INTO THE BAG,
AND THEN HE COMES
OVER WITH THE THING
AND WANTS ME TO HOLD
THE BAG FOR HIM.
HE'S GOING TO --
OKAY, THAT'S FINE.
THAT'S FINE.
JUST DO IT.
JUST DO IT, WALTER.
ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
AND THEN HE
COULDN'T GET THE --
HE COULDN'T ACTUALLY GET
THE STICK BACK OUT OF
THE THING.
AND HE COULDN'T FIGURE OUT
WHY IT WOULDN'T COME OUT.
SO I HAD TO POINT OUT TO HIM
WHERE ACTUALLY THE PROBLEM
WAS COMING FROM.
AND I HAD A PRETTY GOOD
IDEA OF WHERE IT WAS.
AND THEN OH, BOY.
OH, BOY.
YOU KNOW, IT'S LIKE SO
MUCH OF THE HOTTER FOOD.
IT'S NOT THE HELLO, BUT THE
GOOD-BYE YOU REMEMBER.
SO, UH, WE JUST
KEPT ON CLEANING IT,
BUT DALTON COMES
BACK THE OTHER WAY,
AND THIS TIME HE'S
GOT A GARBAGE CAN,
AND THIS TIME IT WAS WALTER'S
TURN TO HAVE A LITTLE FUN.
AND YOU KNOW
IT'S A FUNNY THING.
I HEARD ABOUT SOMEBODY ON THE
AIRPLANE HAD A PROBLEM WITH
KIND OF AN AIRTIGHT FIT,
AND THIS IS
THE SAME THING.
WALTER WAS GOING THROUGH --
KIND OF A SUCTION GOING
ON THERE,
AND, UH, CAN'T GET IT OFF,
SO HE COMES OVER TO
ME FOR HELP.
AND I HAD NOTICED ON THE
FIRST LOAD OF GARBAGE
THAT CAME IN HERE
THERE WERE SOME JUMPER
CABLES AND SO --
I THOUGHT ONE HANDLE'S
POSITIVE, THE OTHER
HANDLE'S NEGATIVE,
AND THEN -- I THINK THE
BATTERY STILL HAD A
LITTLE BIT OF --
YOU DON'T NEED
A LOT OF JUICE
TO BLOW A GARBAGE CAN OFF A
GUY'S HINDQUARTERS, USUALLY.
AND, OKAY,
THERE SHE GOES.
SO THAT WORKED WELL.
SO, MEANWHILE,
DALTON'S GOT A 2 X 4
AND THE HUBCAP COMES
RIGHT OFF HIS WHEEL.
WELL, THE 2 --
WELL IT'S MORE OF A -
THAT WAS MORE OF A 2 X 10.
BUT WHEN THE HUBCAP HIT,
HE SUDDENLY REALIZED
THIS GARBAGE WAS
COMING FROM THE ROAD,
AND I NOTICE THAT
IT'S DALTON'S PICKUP.
THAT'S WHERE ALL
THE GARBAGE IS COMING FROM.
SO NOW I GOT AN IDEA --
AND I'M DANGEROUS
WHEN I GOT AN IDEA.
SO WE CLEANED UP
THE WHOLE AREA,
GOT HER ALL INTO
ONE GARBAGE BAG.
GOT THAT INTO
THE GARBAGE CAN.
AND I TOLD WALTER, PUT THAT
ON THE END OF THE 2 X 10.
AND THEN WE'LL
EACH GRAB AN END,
AND WE'LL TAKE
HER OVER TO THE ROAD.
AND WHAT I'M GONNA DO IS
PUT MY END OF THE
PLANK RIGHT OVER THE
ACTUAL POTHOLE
AND JUST KIND OF STAND BACK
AND WAIT TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
WHAT WE'LL DO IS GET DALTON
TO TAKE HIS OWN GARBAGE BACK.
AND TO MAKE SURE IT
NEVER HAPPENS AGAIN,
I USED THE HUBCAP
TO FILL THE POTHOLE.
[quirky upbeat music]
EVER NOTICE WITH
THESE SMALL BARBEQUES
THAT WHEN YOU RUN THE
FLAME WIDE OPEN FOR A WHILE,
THE PROPANE TANK
GETS ALL FROSTY?
I'M SURE THERE'S A SCIENTIFIC
EXPLANATION FOR THAT,
BUT WHO CARES?
THE MAIN ISSUE IS HOW CAN
WE USE THAT SITUATION
TO MAKE OUR LIVES BETTER?
SO LET'S SAY YOU'RE GOING TO
MAKE YOURSELF A HAMBURGER,
AND YOU'D LIKE TO HAVE A
COLD DRINK TO GO WITH IT.
IT CAN BE ANY KIND
OF DRINK YOU WANT,
AS LONG AS IT HAS THE PLASTIC
HARNESS HOLDING ALL THE
CANS TOGETHER.
THE FERMENTATION
IS OPTIONAL.
MAKE A SLIT IN THE PLASTIC,
RIGHT UP THE MIDDLE.
THEN YOU CAN
SLIDE THE WHOLE UNIT
OVER THE FROSTY PART
OF THE PROPANE CYLINDER.
PUT YOUR BURGER
ON THERE FIRST.
OKAY, YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE
EVERY CAN IS TOUCHING.
THEN YOU GOT YOURSELF
AN INSTANT COOLER.
NOW YOU JUST LEAVE
HER SET ON HIGH.
AND BY THE TIME THE
BURGER'S HOT AND TASTY,
THE DRINKS'LL
BE COLD AND FROSTY.
[coughing]
WELL, WE'RE ALL
OFF THE GO GO BARS.
SO WE'RE BACK
TO HAVING NO ENERGY,
WHICH MEANS NOTHING'S GOING
TO CHANGE AROUND HERE,
WHICH IS ACTUALLY THE ONLY
APPEAL TO THE WHOLE
POSSUM LAKE AREA
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
A LOT OF THE GUYS HAD TROUBLE
QUITTING THE GO GO BARS
COLD TURKEY,
BUT NOT ME.
SEE, THE DIFFERENCE IS,
I'VE GOT A STRONG MIND.
WELL, I'VE GOT A
PRETTY STRONG MIND.
WELL, I'VE GOT A MIND.
WELL, THAT'S IT, UNCLE RED.
THIS TEST IS OVER.
SO WHAT DID YOU
DO WITH THOSE EXTRA
GO GO BARS I FOUND?
I THREW THEM ALL INTO
MERCURY CREEK, HAROLD.
SEE, THAT'S
WATER POLLUTION.
NOT IN
MERCURY CREEK.
IT CAN HANDLE
A FEW ENERGY BARS.
I'VE SEEN IT DISSOLVE
A SNOWMOBILE.
WELL, EITHER WAY,
I'VE PHONED THE COMPANY.
I TOLD THEM THEIR
PRODUCT IS DANGEROUS.
AND THE LIST OF
INGREDIENTS WAS MISLEADING.
"MAY CONTAIN CAFFEINE"?
IT WAS
PURE CAFFEINE!
REALLY?
YOU GOT A GO GO BAR!
YOU GOT A GO GO BAR.
NO, NO,
THIS IS JUST ONE
FROM THE ORIGINAL BATCH
THAT YOU GAVE ME, HAROLD.
THERE'S NO INGREDIENT
LISTING ON THERE.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
NOT ON THE ONES
THAT WE GAVE YOU.
THIS IS JUST A PLACEBO.
THERE'S NOTHING IN HERE
BUT WATER, FLOUR AND
SOME FLAVOURING.
YOURS WERE ALL FAKE.
YOU MEAN ALL THOSE
CHANGES IN ME
WERE JUST MY BRAIN
AT WORK, HAROLD?
SEE HOW STRONG
MY MIND IS?
[possum squealing]
OH, MEETING TIME!
YEAH, YOU GO
AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING HOME STRAIGHT
AFTER THE MEETING.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD WAIT UP.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE.
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheers and applause]
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
HERE WE GO.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, APPARENTLY WINSTON
HAS SOME KIND OF PUBLIC
SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENT.
YEAH, GUYS, YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO BE CAREFUL
WHEN YOU'RE FISHING
IN MERCURY CREEK.
WITH ALL THE GO GO
BARS IN THERE,
FISH ARE GOING TO BE A LITTLE
MORE TWITCHY FOR A WHILE.