AT ANY OF OUR BIG
FAMILY DINNERS,
IT'S KIND OF LIKE GOING
TO A KARAOKE BAR.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHETHER
YOU'RE GOING TO GET
A TURKEY OR A HAM.
SO I SAY, WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
IF YOU COULD COOK BOTH?
NOW YOU MAY THINK YOU NEED
TO HAVE TWO OVENS TO DO THAT.
MAN, ARE YOU EVER WRONG.
THAT'S BECAUSE YOU DON'T
REALIZE THERE'S A BURNER
IN THE BOTTOM
OF THE DISHWASHER.
NOW, IT'S THERE
TO DRY DISHES,
BUT WE'RE GOING TO USE IT
TO COOK OUR TURKEY.
IN FACT, WE'RE SO CLOSE
TO THE BURNER,
WE CAN ACTUALLY MAKE TOAST
AT THE SAME TIME.
NOW, THE OTHER SHELF
IS FOR THE POTATOES.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
A FULL SLATE OF VEGETABLES.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
AND WE CAN KEEP THEM
COMPLETELY SEPARATE
IN THE SILVERWARE HOLDER.
AND HERE'S A BONUS
THAT NO OVEN COULD EVER DO.
YOU KNOW HOW YOUR DISHWASHER
HAS A PUMP AND A
SPRINKLER SYSTEM,
TO PICK UP THE WATER
FROM THE BOTTOM
AND THEN SQUIRTS IT
ALL OVER THE DISHES?
WELL, IT'LL DO THE
SAME THING WITH GRAVY.
NOW ALL WE DO IS SET
THE CONTROL TO DRY,
WHICH TURNS ON THE ELEMENT.
YOU KNOW, SOME TIMES
I EVEN AMAZE MYSELF.
OKAY, EVERYTHING'S
DONE PERFECTLY.
NOW ALL'S WE DO IS RUN
THE REGULAR DISHWASHING CYCLE.
IT'S NOT JUST AN OVEN,
IT'S SELF-CLEANING.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
NO, NO.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
WE JUST WON THE POSSUM LAKE
FISHING DERBY.
WE'VE NEVER
DONE THAT BEFORE.
USUALLY THE GUYS
AT CARIBOU LODGE BEAT US
WITH SOME
UNDERHANDED TRICK,
BUT THEY DIDN'T DO
SO WELL THIS YEAR
BECAUSE NONE OF
THEIR OUTBOARDS WOULD RUN.
YEAH, I HEARD SOMEBODY POURED
SUGAR INTO THEIR GAS TANKS.
VICTORY IS SWEET.
OH, UNCLE RED,
WAIT UNTIL YOU HEAR THIS!
[ APPLAUSE ]
WHAT HAPPENED?
DID YOU GET A SCHOLARSHIP
TO BALLET SCHOOL?
NO, I DID NOT, NO.
WE'VE BEEN CHALLENGED
TO A FISHING DERBY
BY ANOTHER LODGE.
THE GRAND PRIZE
IS 10,000 DOLLARS.
HOLY COW.
BOY, WE COULD REALLY
FIX THIS PLACE UP WITH
10,000 BUCKS.
YOU COULD JUST TEAR IT
DOWN AND START ALL OVER.
WELL, HAROLD,
AND LOSE THE HISTORY,
THE MEMORIES
AND THE AMBIENCE?
HOPEFULLY.
WELL, WHO'S THIS LODGE
THAT THINKS THEY CAN
TAKE US ON, HAROLD?
IT'S, UM, BADGER LODGE.
NO, NO!
WHAT?
NO. NO, YEAH.
OKAY.
BADGER LODGE,
THEY'RE AMERICANS.
WELL, WHAT DIFFERENCE
DOES THAT MAKE?
WELL, THE AMERICANS
ARE BEST AT EVERYTHING.
SAYS WHO?
THEY DO.
YOU KNOW, UNCLE RED,
THEY SPEND MORE ON
FISHING GEAR
THAN WE DO ON MISSILES.
HAROLD, YOU KNOW,
THEY'RE JUST PEOPLE.
THEY DON'T KNOW
POSSUM LAKE;
CANADIAN FISH;
AND THEY
DON'T KNOW US.
WE CAN'T BEAT THE ODDS.
I MEAN, CALIFORNIA HAS THE
SAME POPULATION AS CANADA.
YEAH, BUT THEY'RE
CALIFORNIANS.
YOU BRING 'EM UP
HERE IN FEBRUARY,
AND IT'S GAME OVER.
NO, UNCLE RED,
AMERICANS ARE THE --
THEY HAVE
10 TIMES EVERYTHING...
10 TIMES THE POPULATION,
10 TIMES THE ECONOMY.
EVERYTHING WE HAVE,
THEY HAVE 10 OF.
WELL, THAT MEANS THEY'VE
GOT 10 HAROLDS.
THEY'RE DEAD
IN THE WATER.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YEAH! YEAH!
WOO-HOO!
TODAY'S WINNER RECEIVES
CARDBOARD BOX SEATS
TO THE PORT ASBESTOS
THEATRE IN THE DARK'S
OUTDOOR PRODUCTION
OF A MIDSUMMER'S NIGHTS
MOSQUITO INFESTATION.
THIS IS JUST THE TICKET
IF YOU'RE ITCHING
FOR A NIGHT OUT.
OKAY, COVER YOUR EARS.
OKAY, MR. GREEN, YOU'VE GOT
30 SECONDS TO GET WINSTON
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH,
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND... GO!
OKAY, WINSTON.
YOU KNOW, WHENEVER WE HAVE
A WING-DING AT THE LODGE
AND THE COPS COME OVER
BECAUSE OF THE NOISE
WE ALWAYS SAY TO THEM
HEY, NOBODY'S...
SOBER.
NO, OKAY, OKAY.
WHEN YOU SEE A WOMAN
AND SHE'S THE ULTIMATE,
SHE'S THE BEST,
THAT MEANS SHE'S...
EXPENSIVE.
NO, OKAY, NO.
WHEN ANYBODY
SEES YOUR PARENTS
THEY ALWAYS THINK THEY'RE
SOMETHING FOR EACH OTHER.
COVERING
FOR EACH OTHER.
NO, BUT YOU KNOW
HOW YOUR MOTHER SAYS
THEY NEVER ARGUE
BECAUSE
EVERYTHING IS...
DAD'S FAULT.
WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
MR. GREEN.
YEAH, I KNOW.
OH, I KNOW.
WINSTON, REMEMBER LAST SUMMER
WE HAD THAT HURRICANE
AND EVERYBODY'S
SEPTICS BACKED UP.
YOU HAD THREE MONTHS
OF WORK OUT OF IT.
WHAT DID YOU CALL THAT?
YEAH,
THE PERFECT STORM.
YEAH! YEAH!
WE'RE HELPING OUT
A LODGE MEMBER, BLAIR COBDEN,
AND HE'S GOT HIS
SNOWMOBILE SHOW
ON THE LOCAL PORT ASBESTOS
T.V. STATION.
I GUESS HE'S RUNNING
A LITTLE BIT LATE.
HE'LL BE HERE THOUGH.
HERE HE IS.
[ CRASH ]
OKAY, BLAIR.
HOW'S THE
SNOW MACHINE RUNNING?
THROTTLE
STICKS A BIT.
YEAH,
I CAN SEE THAT.
I THINK I HIT
YOUR DOGHOUSE.
HE'S LONG GONE
ANYHOW.
SO I THOUGHT WE'D
TALK A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT THE SHOW.
WE GOT SOME CLIPS.
I THOUGHT
WE'D RUN THEM
AND THEN YOU CAN TELL US
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
FIRE IT UP.
ALL RIGHT.
Blair:
I'M REAL EXCITED,
I'M HEADING
TO FISH LAKE LODGE,
A BIG TRIP.
YOU CAN SEE I'M EXCITED.
Red:
YOU LOOK EXCITED
THERE, YEAH.
Blair:
THERE'S BRENDA, MY SLED.
Red?
BRENDA'S A SLED, OKAY.
THAT'S GOOD TO KNOW.
YOU, KIND OF, JAZZED BRENDA
UP A LITTLE BIT, DIDN'T YOU?
Blair: YEAH, YOU SEE,
FISH LAKE LODGE
IS A REAL FANCY PLACE,
AND I SOUPED HER UP A BIT
'CAUSE I DIDN'T WANT TO
PULL IN THERE LOOKING
LIKE A GOOF.
Red:
NOW, WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE?
IS THIS A SETBACK
OF SOME KIND?
Blair:
I FAILED TO NOTICE
THAT THE BROCHURE SAID,
"ON TRANQUIL
FISH LAKE ISLAND."
Red: OH.
SO THE FERRY BOAT WOULDN'T
TAKE THE SNOWMOBILE?
Blair:
NO FERRY, RED.
JUST ME, BRENDA
AND THE OPEN WATER.
Red:
WOW. HOLY COW.
NOW, DID YOU GET ENOUGH
SPEED UP THERE, BLAIR?
Blair:
APPARENTLY NOT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU HEAR A LOT OF TALK
ABOUT GLOBAL WARMING,
WHICH IS MELTING
THE POLAR ICE CAP,
WHICH WILL LEAD TO
WORLD-WIDE FLOODING
AND MASS EXTINCTIONS
AND SO ON.
BUT WHAT REALLY BUGS ME
IS HOW HOT THE SUMMERS
ARE GETTING.
OH SURE, YOU CAN PUT ONE OF
THESE WINDOWS SHAKERS
INTO YOUR HOME
IF THINGS ARE GETTING
TOO HOT IN THE BEDROOM.
NICE PROBLEM.
WHAT IF YOUR CAR DOESN'T
HAVE AIR CONDITIONING?
OKAY, YOU CAN KEEP COOL
THROUGH EVAPORATION,
WHERE YOU OPEN
ALL THE CAR WINDOWS,
GET NAKED AND DOUSE
YOURSELF WITH ALCOHOL.
BUT THE COPS NEVER
BELIEVE THAT STORY.
MIND YOU, YOU DO END UP
IN THE COOLER.
SO TO AVOID JAIL,
I SUGGEST A
DIFFERENT TECHNOLOGY.
YOU WANT TO
PUT OUT THE HEAT,
TRY A FIRE EXTINGUISHER.
MAKE SURE YOU GET THE KIND
THAT SHOOTS OUT Co2,
NOT THE KIND
THAT SHOOTS OUT FOAM.
THEY'RE FOR SHAVING
WHILE YOU'RE WAITING
FOR THE FIRE TRUCK.
THESE Co2 UNITS
PUT OUT STUFF
THAT'S ABOUT
3000 DEGREES BELOW ZERO.
WATCH HOW THIS COOLS
SOMETHING DOWN.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE
HOW THE TEMPERATURE DROPS.
NOW, THE REAL PROBLEM
IN A VEHICLE
IS THE SUN BEATING DOWN
ON THE UPHOLSTERY
UNTIL IT GETS HOT ENOUGH
TO FRY EGGS ON.
AND IF YOU'VE EVER
FRIED YOUR EGGS,
YOU KNOW HOW
PAINFUL THAT IS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO COOL
THE WHOLE CAR,
JUST THE SEATS.
MOUNT ONE FULL
FIRE EXTINGUISHER
ON EACH SIDE
OF THE BACK SEAT.
I'M GUESSING YOU DON'T USE
YOUR BACK SEAT ANYMORE EITHER.
WOW, I'M FINALLY USING
THE SEAT BELTS ON THIS CAR.
OKAY, THAT WENT WELL.
THIS IS THE
EMERGENCY BRAKE --
SORRY, THIS WAS
THE EMERGENCY BRAKE.
NOW, I KNOW THAT'S GOING
TO ALARM A BUNCH OF YOU
NERVOUS NELLIES,
BUT WHEN
I THINK ABOUT IT,
HOW OFTEN DO I USE
MY EMERGENCY BRAKE?
ONCE, MAYBE TWICE A MONTH.
WHEREAS I BURN MYSELF
ON THE UPHOLSTERY
THREE OR FOUR
TIMES A DAY.
YOU TELL ME WHICH
IS THE REAL EMERGENCY.
NOW, WITH MY CUSTOM
CARBON DIOXIDE-POWERED
AIR CONDITIONERS,
I CAN DRIVE ALL DAY WITHOUT
BEING IN THE HOT SEAT.
NOT UNTIL
I GET HOME ANYWAY.
NOW, YOU WANT TO ATTACH
THE OTHER END OF THE CABLE
AROUND THE NOZZLES
OF THE FIRE EXTINGUISHERS.
IF YOUR BRAKE CABLE
IS TOO SHORT,
USE SOME OF THE WIRING
FROM THE TAIL LIGHTS.
IF OTHER DRIVERS CAN SEE
THAT YOUR TAIL LIGHTS
AREN'T WORKING,
HEY, THEY'RE
FOLLOWING TOO CLOSE.
OKAY, AND THE TANKS
ARE ALL HOOKED UP.
NOW LET'S JUST IMAGINE THAT
THE CAR'S JUST SITTING
OUT FOR HOURS,
AND THE UPHOLSTERY'S
HOTTER THAN STINK.
AND STINK CAN BE
VERY, VERY HOT.
BUT WATCH THIS.
OH, BABY.
HOW COOL IS THAT, EH?
I'M GOOD TO GO.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME --
[shivering] THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
FIRE!
F-F-FIRE!
I WANT TO TALK
TO ANY COUPLES
WHO HAVE BEEN MARRIED
FOR A WHILE.
WHEN I WAS A YOUNG MAN,
THERE WERE
THREE KINDS OF CARS.
FIRST, THERE WAS
THE CLUNKER.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE BEATER,
THE PIECE OF CRAP,
THE CAR THAT
LOOKED WORTHLESS
AND PERFORMED DOWN
TO THAT STANDARD.
THEN THERE WAS
THE HOT CAR.
THE CORVETTE, THE MUSTANG,
YOU KNOW,
THE SPORTS CAR.
IT LOOKED GOOD
AND DELIVERED ON THE PROMISE.
THEN THERE
WAS MY FAVOURITE,
THE SLEEPER.
THE CAR THAT LOOKED
LIKE A CLUNKER,
BUT PERFORMED
LIKE A HOT ROD.
NOW, I KNOW THAT
ON YOUR WEDDING DAY,
YOU THOUGHT EACH OTHER
LOOKED LIKE A PRETTY
SPORTY MODEL.
AND WHEN YOU LOOK
AT EACH OTHER NOW,
YOU LOOK LIKE A COUPLE
OF CLUNKERS,
WITH A BAD SHIMMY
IN THE REAR END.
BUT THAT'S ALL ATTITUDE.
MAYBE YOU CAN'T BE
A SPORTS CAR,
BUT YOU DON'T NEED
TO BE A CLUNKER,
YOU CAN BE A SLEEPER.
SURE, YOUR TIRES ARE BALD
AND YOUR FENDERS ARE WRINKLED,
BUT YOU MIGHT STILL HAVE
A SURPRISE OR TWO
UNDER THE HOOD.
'CAUSE WHEN
I SAY SLEEPER,
I'M ONLY TALKING
FIGURATIVELY.
IF YOU'RE A SLEEPER,
LITERALLY,
YOUR MARRIAGE IS
IN SERIOUS TROUBLE.
YOU GOT TO KEEP YOUR END UP,
FIGURATIVELY AND LITERALLY.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
announcer:
YOU'VE SEEN HIM ON THE ROAD.
YOU'VE HAD HIM IN YOUR YARD.
YOU'VE WHIFFED HIM
ON THE BREEZE.
NOW, LET WORLD-RENOWNED SEWAGE
SUCKER, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
INTO YOUR HEART
AND ONTO YOUR TURNTABLE
WITH HIS FIRST EVER
LONG PLAYING ALBUM.
YES, IT'S WINSTON ROTHCHILD'S
THE SOUNDS OF SUCKING.
24 OF THE GREATEST SONGS
EVER WRITTEN
SUNG AND INTERPRETED
AS ONLY A MAN WITH NO
PROFESSIONAL TRAINING CAN.
YOU'LL GET...
THE POPULATION
OF A COUNTRY
DOESN'T MAKE ANY
DIFFERENCE, HAROLD.
YOU ONLY HAVE FIVE GUYS
ON A FISHING TEAM.
IF THEY'VE GOT
300 MILLION MORE,
THEY ALL HAVE TO SIT
ON THE BENCH.
YES, BUT, SEE, WE MAKE UP
OUR TEAM BY PICKING
FIVE OUT OF,
SAY, OH, 100.
THEY MAKE UP
THEIR TEAM BY PICKING
FIVE OUT OF,
SAY, OH, 10,000.
I'M SURE YOU SEE
THE DIFFERENCE.
YEAH, IT'LL TAKE
THEM FOREVER.
HAROLD, WE GOT
THE BEST TEAM.
I DON'T CARE IF THIS
LODGE IS FROM MARS.
WE'RE GOING TO
WIN THIS THING.
YOU SEEM
SO CONFIDENT.
WELL, YOU GOT
TO BE, HAROLD.
FISHING'S A
MENTAL GAME.
IT'S ALL ABOUT
WHAT YOU'VE GOT
IN YOUR NOGGIN.
OKAY, FINE, BUT I STILL
NEED THE CHEQUE TODAY.
WHAT CHEQUE?
THE $5,000 CHEQUE,
THE WAGER.
YOU TOLD ME THERE WAS
A $10,000 PRIZE.
YEAH, YOU PUT UP FIVE,
THEY PUT UP FIVE,
THAT'S 10.
OH, I'M THINKING
OF PUTTING UP FIVE, HAROLD.
WELL, DON'T BLAME ME.
YOU SIGNED THE AGREEMENT.
YOU ACCEPTED
THE CHALLENGE.
HAROLD, HOW COULD YOU
LET THIS HAPPEN?
DON'T YOU READ DOCUMENTS
BEFORE I SIGN THEM?
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red:
SO BILL CAME BY.
WE HEARD HE HAD
A CASE OF SHINGLES.
WE MISUNDERSTOOD.
SO HE AND WALTER HAD PLANNED
TO RE-SHINGLE THE SHED.
AND SO, YEAH, NO PROBLEM.
THE SHINGLES ARE THERE
AND HE BROUGHT A LADDER
CAREFUL, OOH.
AND OH, OH.
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
WE'RE GOOD.
WHOOPS.
OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
AND BILL TAKES THE LADDER
OVER AND SETS UP.
THEY'RE GOING TO ACTUALLY
PUT THE SHINGLES
ON THE LITTLE SHED
ON THE LEFT THERE.
AND BILLS KNOWS HE
SHOULD ALWAYS HOLD THE LADDER,
BUT YOU'RE BETTER TO HOLD IT
FROM THE SIDE, BILL.
AND THEN --
CAREFUL, CAREFUL, CAREFUL.
OH.
AND THEY'RE NOT EVEN
ON THE ROOF YET.
OKAY, THEY FINALLY
GET UP THERE,
AND THEY START NAILING
THE SHINGLES ON.
THE HEAD COMES OFF
THE HAMMER AND --
WELL, YOU GOT TWO WINDOWS
THAT MATCH NOW.
OKAY, NEVER MIND,
NEVER MIND.
SO AWAY THEY GO.
START HAMMERING IN,
AND WALTER SET UP
HIS SHINGLES THERE
AND HE MUST HAVE SET IT UP
OVER A KNOT OR SOMETHING.
IT WAS REAL HARD,
AND HE COULDN'T GET
THE NAIL TO GO IN PROPERLY
BECAUSE IT'S STARTING TO
BEND OVER AND EVERYTHING.
SO HE DID THE
NORMAL MALE RESPONSE,
JUST HIT HER
A LITTLE BIT HARDER.
LIKE THAT.
OKAY, IS HE ALL RIGHT?
UH-H-H...
YEAH, HE'S GOOD.
OKAY, LATER THAT DAY THEY
DECIDED TO WORK TOGETHER
RATHER THAN INDEPENDENTLY,
SO I GET WALTER TO --
YOU KNOW, THIS DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE THE BEST IDEA EVER TO ME.
YOU KNOW, I JUST --
THERE WE GO.
OKAY, THAT'S GOOD.
WOW.
WHY DON'T YOU FALL IN
BACKWARDS THIS TIME?
A LITTLE CHANGE OF PACE.
STILL LATER THAT DAY
THEY'RE FINALLY GETTING
THE THINGS ON THERE,
BUT BILL DECIDES WE'VE GOT
TO UP THE TECHNOLOGY HERE.
WE'VE GOT ONE OF THESE
NAIL GUN UNITS
WITH THE COMPRESSED AIR.
TAKE HER UP
TO 60-70 POUNDS.
THERE... OOPS.
WELL, YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE PARKED THERE.
OKAY, SO BILL SAYS --
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
OKAY, OKAY.
SO WALTER'S GOING
TO JUST NAIL A NAIL IN
WHILE BILL, KIND OF HOLDS
THE SHINGLE IN PLACE.
THIS SHOULD WORK --
THIS SHOULD WORK JUST FINE.
HE'S GOT SOME POWER NOW.
BUT BILL'S SAYING
NO, C'MON ON,
THIS IS NOT NEARLY
THE KIND OF SPEED WE NEED.
SO HE TAKES HER,
AMPS HER UP A LITTLE BIT MORE,
TAKES HER UP TO 100 POUNDS,
WHAT ARE YOU, 110?
THAT'S GETTING PRETTY HIGH
WE'RE ALMOST UP TO --
OH BOY, OH BOY.
SO BILL STARTS --
IT'S GOT SOME REAL KICK
TO HER NOW
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
HE STARTS LOSING IT.
WE'RE LOSING IT.
CAREFUL, BILL, CAREFUL.
OH, DOWN THE HOLE,
HE STARTS FIRING INSIDE
AND SHOOTING SHINGLES
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
SO BILL HEADS DOWN
AND WALTER, GET DOWN!
GET DOWN THE LADDER!
SAVE YOURSELF!
WOW!
IT'S LIKE A WAR MOVIE.
AND DOWN HE COMES.
OKAY, OKAY.
YOU KNOW, YOU GOT TO LOOK
AT THE BRIGHT SIDE.
OKAY, FINE.
THE SHED DIDN'T
GET SHINGLED.
NO, THE SHED --
BUT LOOK AT THE BRIGHT SIDE,
YOUR CAR DID.
LOOK AT THAT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
REMEMBER THESE,
MR. MICROPHONE?
THE ONES YOU
USED TO TALK INTO
THAT MADE YOUR VOICE
COME OUT THE RADIO?
BACK IN THE OLD DAYS,
DUMB SINGLE GUYS
USED TO USE THESE
TO AMPLIFY THEIR VOICES
OVER THEIR CAR STEREO
IN HOPES OF PICKING UP
WOMEN ON THE STREET.
[on the radio ]
HEY, THERE, MAMA.
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD.
IT DIDN'T WORK,
BUT IT DID TEACH ME
THAT OUR TOWN DOES HAVE
PLAINCLOTHES POLICEWOMEN.
ISN'T IT GREAT
WHEN OLD TECHNOLOGY
FINDS A COMPLETELY
NEW APPLICATION?
LIKE STORING YOUR HOCKEY PUCKS
IN A PATTY STACKER
OR CUTTING YOUR HAIR
WITH A FLYMO.
SEE, THERE'S A BIG WRESTLING
SMACKDOWN ON T.V.
THIS AFTERNOON,
BUT BERNICE WANTS ME TO GO
WITH HER TO THE MALL.
I SET UP THE T.V. IN A HIDDEN
CORNER OF THE BASEMENT,
BUT I'LL TELL YOU
I COULD NEVER PULL THIS OFF
WITHOUT THE HELP
OF MR. MICROPHONE.
GOT TO KEEP THE SOUND OFF
FOR THE WRESTLING,
BUT THAT'S OKAY,
I'VE GOT CLOSED CAPTIONING
SO I CAN FOLLOW THE PLOT.
I'VE GOT TO BE QUIET
SO I CAN HEAR
BERNICE CALLING ME.
Bernice: OKAY, COME ON.
LET'S GO.
I CAN'T HONEY.
[ over radio ]
GOT TO FIX THE TRANSMISSION.
COMING DEAR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, THE FISHING DERBY
RESULTS ARE IN.
I DON'T WANT TO GIVE
ANYTHING AWAY.
BUT LET'S JUST SAY
THAT THE THEORY
THAT CANADIANS
ARE SOMEHOW INFERIOR
HAS BEEN BLOWN RIGHT OUT
OF THE WATER.
WHOO! WHOO! WHOO!
IT WAS GREAT!
OH MY GOODNESS!
YEAH! YEAH!
THAT'S RIGHT,
WE TIED.
YEAH! YEAH! YEAH!
OH, I FEEL SO GOOD
ABOUT MYSELF.
YOU KNOW,
ON DAYS LIKE THIS
I THINK I CAN
TIE ANYBODY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
JUST LIKE I
TOLD YOU, HAROLD,
YOU'VE GOT TO BELIEVE
IN YOURSELF.
IT'S ALL ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENS UP HERE.
MALE PATTERN BALDNESS.
NO, NO, NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD
ABOUT TIEING,
WHEN WE WERE TALKING
ABOUT TIEING?
YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD
ABOUT THAT?
YOU DON'T HAVE THE
EMBARRASSMENT OF LOSING.
AND NOBODY'S MAD AT YOU
FOR WINNING,
AND THEY DON'T THREATEN
TO GIVE YOU A WEDGIE
IN FRONT OF
MARY-ELLEN CARMICHAEL.
YOU LIKE EVERYBODY
TO BE HAPPY,
DON'T YOU?
YEAH. YEAH.
I BRUISE EASILY.
OKAY, SO WE DIDN'T WIN
THE 10,000 DOLLARS,
BUT NEITHER DID THEY.
YOU KNOW, SO WE JUST GET
OUR CHEQUE BACK.
WELL, NO, NO, NO.
NOT EXACTLY, NO.
THEY GOT OURS
AND WE GOT THEIRS.
OH, YEAH, WELL,
SAME DIF.
NO, NO, THEIRS
IS IN AMERICAN.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH!
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I'M THINKING OUR
MARRIAGE IS KIND OF A TIE,
BUT WE LIKE TO CALL IT
A WIN-WIN
BECAUSE NEITHER OF US IS
INTERESTED IN A STALEMATE.
HUH? HUH?
AND THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR CHEQUE
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
EVERYBODY
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
COME ON, SIT DOWN,
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
I THINK WE SHOULD ALL BE PROUD
OF OUR PERFORMANCE
IN THE FISHING DERBY.
MAYBE EVERYBODY
COMING OUT EVEN
IS KIND OF A
CANADIAN THING.
OTHERWISE WE GET INTO
A BIG DISCUSSION
ABOUT WINNERS AND LOSERS
AND THE NEXT
THING YOU KNOW
HAROLD'S HAVING
ANOTHER BAD DAY.