YOU KNOW,
AROUND POSSUM LODGE,
MOST GUYS DON'T WORRY TOO MUCH
ABOUT A LITTLE LITTERING.
BUT LATELY PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
LOSING THEIR DOGS
IN THIS STUFF.
SO, OKAY, WE NEED TO
CUT DOWN ON THE LITTERING.
BESIDES, IT'LL GET
YOU INTO TROUBLE
WITH A LOT OF THOSE
SPECIAL INTEREST GROUPS,
LIKE HOMEOWNERS
OR POLICE...
OR SOCIETY.
SO TODAY I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW YOU CAN MAINTAIN
YOUR CIVIL RIGHT
TO HURL GARBAGE
OUT THE WINDOW,
BUT WITHOUT GETTING
INTO TROUBLE.
FIRST THING YOU DO
IS TAKE A MILK CRATE
AND CAREFULLY
REMOVE THE BOTTOM.
OKAY, I'VE ATTACHED
A GARBAGE BAG
TO THE OPEN END OF
THE MILK CRATE HERE.
THAT'S ACTUALLY
GONNA CATCH MY GARBAGE.
AND THANKS TO
THE HIMMELMAN HINGE,
THE WHOLE UNIT TUCKS
AWAY BEHIND THE VAN
SO IT WON'T CUT
INTO THE GAS MILEAGE.
EVEN MORE
ENVIRONMENTALLY FRIENDLY!
I'M PRACTICALLY
SAVING THE PLANET HERE.
AND I CAN BRING THE
CRATE OUT WHEN I NEED IT,
THANKS TO THIS
ROPE AND PULLEY
ATTACHED TO THE
DRIVER'S WINDOW.
BUT TALK IS CHEAP...
IT'S ONLY WHEN YOU TRY
MY IDEAS IT GETS EXPENSIVE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ POLICE SIREN ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
I BOUGHT A PIECE OF LAND
FROM JUNIOR SINGLETON,
AND ALL IT COST ME WAS
TWO PAIR, ACES HIGH.
AND THEN LAST NIGHT
HAROLD AND I WENT UP
TO TAKE A LOOK AT IT,
AND, UH, THAT WAS A SETBACK.
NOW, JUNIOR HAD
TOLD ME THE LAND
HAS A GREAT
VIEW OF THE SWAMP,
AND IT DOES...
ALL YOU DO
IS LOOK STRAIGHT DOWN.
WELL, WELL, WELL,
IF IT ISN'T DONALD CHUMP!
WELL, THAT WOULD MAKE
YOU MY APPRENTICE, THEN,
WOULDN'T IT,
HAROLD?
DO I LOOK NORMAL
TO YOU, UNCLE RED?
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES YOU JUST
MAKE IT TOO EASY FOR ME.
I'M NOT FEELING WELL.
I'M ALL SWEATY AND
ITCHY AND WOOZY.
DON'T FORGET
SLEEP AND DOPEY.
THERE WAS A LOT OF BUGS AND
MOSQUITOES UP AT THAT SWAMP.
AND BASED ON MY SYMPTOMS AND
THIS WEBPAGE I WAS JUST ON,
I MAY HAVE CONTRACTED...
NORTH MILE VIRUS.
CAN YOU TAKE
A PILL FOR THAT?
NO, I GOTTA GET
A SHOT.
WOW!
WELL, YOU MAY TOO.
ARE YOU ALL
ITCHY AND FEVERISH?
NO! NO.
I FEEL --
I THINK WE'RE
BOTH FINE, WE'RE GOOD.
ARE YOU AFRAID
OF NEEDLES?
HAROLD, I'M MARRIED,
I'VE BEEN GETTIN'
THE NEEDLE FOR 38 YEARS.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
I'M JUST GONNA
GO LIE DOWN ON THE
COT IN THE BASEMENT.
FINE, HAROLD,
FINE.
YOU'RE SURE
YOU'RE NOT ITCHY?
I'M NOT ITCHY!
I'M NOT ITCHY.
A-A-ALL RIGHT!
YOU'RE IRRITABLE,
I'M NOT IRRITABLE.
MAYBE NOT,
BUT YOU'RE A CARRIER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY, CHARLIE FARQUHARSON
WILL BE PLAYING FOR THIS COUPON
GOOD FOR ONE OVERCOOKED
QUARTER POUNDER
AT BUTCHER BOB'S
BLACKENED BURGER BAR,
WHERE IF YOU CAN CHEW IT,
WE DIDN'T DO IT.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
EARS THERE, CHARLIE.
RED, YOU'VE 30 SECONDS TO GET
CHARLIE TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
UH, OKAY,
CHARLIE, CHARLIE!
OKAY, THIS IS SOMEBODY
WHO'S SELF-EMPLOYED.
A FARMER.
NO, NO, THIS IS A GUY WHO
TAKES A LOT OF RISKS
IN HIS JOB.
A MARIJUANA FARMER.
OKAY, NO.
THIS IS SOMEBODY WHO SEES AN
OPPORTUNITY AND RUNS WITH IT.
A SHOPLIFTER.
OKAY, NO,
THIS IS A GUY
WHO GETS AN IDEA BUT HE USES
OTHER PEOPLE'S MONEY TO DO IT.
A TEENAGE SON.
NO, THIS IS LIKE --
THIS IS LIKE A GUY WHO RUNS,
SAY, AN ENTERPRISE.
CAPTAIN KIRK!
NO! NO.
OKAY, OKAY, CHARLIE,
IF A GUY MAKES IT BIG
WHAT IS HE?
ON VIAGRA.
R[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
UH, RED, YOU'RE
ALMOST OUTTA TIME.
I KNOW.
CHARLIE, CHARLIE, WHEN YOU
WERE GROWING UP IN
PARRY SOUND,
THERE MUST HAVE BEEN SOMEBODY
WHO MADE A NAME FOR HIMSELF
AT SOMETHING.
WELL, THERE WAS ONE FELLA
SPONTANEOUSLY COMBUST ALL OVER.
MADE A COMPLETE
'ASH' OF HIMSELF.
NICE FRENCH FELLA.
YEAH?
WHAT WAS HIS NAME?
ANDRé PRéNEUR.
YEAH!
announcer: WE HAVE A SURPRISE
FOR YOUNG JIMMY ANDERSON.
TODAY IS CAREER DAY,
AND JIMMY WILL BE SPENDING IT
WITH A GROWN-UP
DOING A VERY
IMPORTANT JOB.
I WANNA BE A FIREMAN!
[ DOORBELL ]
[ INSPIRING MUSIC ]
DO YOU LIKE TRUCKS?
COOL, A FIREMAN!
HEY, MISTER,
YOU SMELL.
[ INSPIRING MUSIC ]
CAN I WORK THE SIREN?
[ PEACEFUL MUSIC ]
YOU KNOW, I AGREED TO DO THIS
BECAUSE I LOVE KIDS.
[ INSPIRING MUSIC ]
I ALSO LOVE
SUCKING SEWAGE,
AND I WANTED TO SHOW
THAT TO A YOUNG CHILD.
SEE, I DON'T HAVE
ANY KIDS OF MY OWN,
SO THIS IS A HUGE
OPPORTUNITY FOR JIMMY.
I POINTED OUT
THE TREMENDOUS AMOUNT
OF SEWAGE IN THIS AREA.
AND I TOLD HIM,
SOME DAY THIS
COULD ALL BE HIS.
[ INSPIRING MUSIC ]
FIRST-TIME JITTERS.
YOU KNOW, I REALLY
ENJOYED THIS EXPERIENCE.
IT GAVE ME A
CHANCE TO CONNECT
WITH SOMEONE YOUNG
AND IMPRESSIONABLE,
AND TO HAVE A LITTLE FUN.
[ PEACEFUL MUSIC ]
Winston: AND YOU KNOW,
WHEN IT CAME TIME TO
SAY GOOD-BYE,
I ACTUALLY HAD
A TEAR IN MY EYE.
SO DID HE.
LAY OFF,
TOILET BOY.
[ INSPIRING MUSIC ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
HAVE YOU SEEN THESE FANCY
EXHAUST PIPES THEY HAVE?
IT'S MADE OF STEEL,
BUT YOU CAN BEND IT
ANY WAY YOU WANT.
IT'S STRONG AND FLEXIBLE.
KIND OF LIKE A
MIDDLE AGED MAN,
EXCEPT FOR THE STRONG
AND FLEXIBLE PART.
WELL, THIS EXHAUST PIPE IS
GOING TO BE THE CENTREPIECE
OF THIS WEEK'S
HANDYMAN CORNER,
BECAUSE WE'RE GOING TO USE IT
TO EXTEND THE TAILPIPE
ON THIS VEHICLE.
OF COURSE, TO DO THAT,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
UNDO THE EXISTING PIPE
AND THEN INSERT THIS ONE
SOMEWHERE NEAR THE MIDDLE.
NOW, THE OLD PIPE MAY BE
RUSTED ON THERE PRETTY GOOD.
SO YOU'RE GONNA
NEED A SPECIAL WRENCH
AND A COUPLE OF CLAMPS.
[ COUGH ]
SAFETY GOGGLES MIGHT
HAVE BEEN A GOOD IDEA.
I'LL JUST SQUINT MORE.
BOY, PRETTY RUSTY
UNDER THERE.
GOOD THING THE
FLOOR IS GONE.
I COULD HAVE SUFFOCATED.
BUT NOW WE'VE GOT OUR
FLEXIBLE PIPE IN PLACE,
AND WE CAN AIM OUR
EXHAUST ANYWHERE WE WANT.
KINDA LIKE WHEN
YOU WERE SINGLE.
NOW ALL WE NEED IS
A WAY TO KEEP THE PIPE UP
AND STEER IT.
SO NOW I HAVE MY AIMING
MECHANISM IN PLACE.
I USED A CLOTHESLINE,
BUT YOU CAN USE THE STEERING
SYSTEM OUT OF YOUR BOAT.
WELL, NOT YOUR BOAT,
BUT SOMEONE'S.
SO NOW WHEN I TURN
THE STEERING WHEEL,
THE TAILPIPE IS PULLED
HORIZONTALLY AND VERTICALLY.
SO THE TECHNOLOGY IS
TWO-DIMENSIONAL IN CHARACTER,
MUCH LIKE MYSELF.
NOW, YOU'LL BE AIMING THROUGH
THE REARVIEW MIRROR,
SO EVERYTHING
WILL BE BACKWARDS.
BUT I PUT THE
HOOD ORNAMENT ON THERE
TO WORK AS A SIGHT.
OKAY...
WE'RE GETTIN' THERE.
NOW ALL WE GOTTA DO IS
ADD A LITTLE FIRE POWER.
AND AT MY AGE THE BEST
PLACE TO LOOK FOR THAT
IS UNDER THE HOOD...
OF THE CAR.
I TOOK ONE OF THE
ENGINE SPARK PLUGS,
MOUNTED IT ON
THE MUFFLER HERE.
HAD TO EXTEND
THE WIRE A BIT,
NOT SURE HOW GOOD THE
CONNECTIONS ARE,
BUT I FIND WITH
REAL HIGH VOLTAGE,
IT'S NOT ALL THAT CRUCIAL.
STUCK A PIECE OF DOWELING
INTO THE SPARK PLUG HOLE.
WANTED TO USE ONE OF THE
CORKS FROM MY WINE BOTTLE,
BUT IT'S THE
WRONG SIZE THREAD.
SEE, THE SPARK PLUG
MOUNTED HERE
ALLOWS THE GAS
TO EXPLODE IN THE MUFFLER
RATHER THAN BACK
IN THE ENGINE.
WHY AM I DOING THIS,
YOU ASK.
WELL, YOU LIKE SKIING,
TOBOGGANING,
SNOWMOBILING,
A WHITE CHRISTMAS?
WELL, THEN YOU
NEED A SNOW CANNON.
NOW YOU CAN HAVE SNOW WHERE
YOU WANT AND WHEN YOU WANT
JUST LIKE AT THOSE
FANCY SKI RESORTS,
BUT AT A FRACTION
OF THE COST,
EXCLUDING LEGAL FEES.
NOW JUST AIM YOUR TAILPIPE
AT WHEREVERYOU WANT YOUR
BLIZZARD DELIVERED.
YOU'LL HAVE LIFT-OFF RIGHT
AFTER IGNITION, BELIEVE ME.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
ACTUALLY, THIS IS ONE SNOW JOB
SHE'LL THANK YOU FOR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I WANT TO TALK
TO YOU GUYS
WHO HAVE PEOPLE
WHO LOOK UP TO YOU
AND ASK FOR YOUR ADVICE.
THEY SEE SOMETHING
IN YOU, DON'T THEY?
AND WE BOTH KNOW
THEY'RE WRONG.
OH, SURE, YEAH,
YOU USED TO KNOW
EVERYTHING.
YOU HAD OPINIONS
ON THE WAY KIDS DRESSED,
UNTIL YOUR KIDS
FOUND THE PICTURES OF YOU
IN THE MADRAS CAPTAIN
WITH LEO SAYER HAIR
AND THE MR T NECKLACES.
YOU THOUGHT YOU KNEW WHAT WAS
WRONG WITH THE GOVERNMENT
UNTIL EVERY GREAT GUY
YOU VOTED INTO OFFICE
TURNED INTO A MORON.
YOU KNEW HOW ANNOYING
AND STUPID CELL PHONES WERE
UNTIL YOUR MOTORHOME
BROKE DOWN IN UTAH.
YOU KNEW KIDS WERE
WASTING TIME ON COMPUTERS
UNTIL YOU BOUGHT
A TRUSS ON E-BAY.
SO NOW
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
WELL, YOU KNOW
THAT YOU KNOW NOTHING.
JUST DON'T ADMIT IT.
IF PEOPLE COME AT YOU
WITH QUESTIONS,
ASK A QUESTION BACK.
QUESTIONS LIKE,
"HOW DID IT FALL?"
OR "DO YOU HAVE
ALL THE PIECES?"
OR "HOW MUCH TIME DO WE HAVE
BEFORE YOUR WIFE GETS HOME?"
YOU NEVER NEED ANSWERS
WHEN YOU HAVE QUESTIONS.
WILL IT WORK?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, THAT NORTH MILE VIRUS
THAT HAROLD AND I PICKED UP
ISN'T GETTING
ANY BETTER.
IT WON'T KILL YOU,
BUT AFTER A FEW NIGHTS YOU
ALMOST WISH THAT IT WOULD.
UNCLE RED, IS THAT
DOCTOR HERE YET?
NOT YET, NO.
HAROLD, YOU'VE GOT TO
GET A DOOR ON YOUR
MICROWAVE.
NO, THIS IS LOTION
FOR THE ITCH.
OH.
HEY, GREAT DANCE, BOYS.
NOW TRY THE WATUSSI.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
WHAT DO YOU WANT,
DALTON?
A CAMERA.
HERE, THEY JUST CAME
PRIORITY POST.
OH, OKAY.
YOU KNOW, THEY SELL
PIMPLE CREAM IN FLESH TONE.
OKAY, IT'S FROM
THE MEDICAL CLINIC.
"DEAR SIRS,
"WE CANNOT COME TO THE LODGE
AS THE VIRUS YOU'VE CONTRACTED
"IS EXTREMELY
CONTAGIOUS."
WHAT DOES IT
REALLY SAY?
HA! THAT'S WHAT IT --
LOOK AT THIS.
OH, THAT'S LOW.
"IN THE MEANTIME,
"PLEASE FIND ENCLOSED
TWO SYRINGES."
HERE YOU GO.
WOW.
WHAT YOU LOOKING
FOR, HAROLD?
A REALLY TINY NURSE.
OH, WE DON'T NEED
A NURSE.
WE'LL JUST DO THIS
OURSELVES.
I CAN'T GIVE MYSELF
A SHOT.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU GIVE ME A SHOT,
I'LL GIVE YOU A SHOT,
ALL RIGHT?
OKAY.
OKAY. OKAY.
ALL RIGHTY.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
I'LL GO FIRST.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
WHY DO I ALWAYS HAVE
TO BE THE MATURE ONE?
I FEEL LIKE I'M IN
A PETER SELLERS MOVIE.
"DR. STRANGELOVE?"
NO, A SHOT
IN THE DORK.
AHHH.
OWWW!
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red: HAROLD AND WALTER HAD
GONE FOR A HIKE IN
THE WOODS, THERE.
AND WALTER HAD KIND OF
A NORMAL-SIZED BACKPACK,
AND HAROLD WENT
THE ULTRA-DELUXE --
FIGURES HE'S GOING
TO GET LOST.
HE CARRIES THE MAP
AND DOESN'T ALWAYS
LOOK WHERE HE'S GOING.
STEPPED RIGHT
ON WALTER'S FOOT, THERE.
COMES BACK THE OTHER WAY
AND REPEATS IT.
AND HE COMES OVER
TO APOLOGIZE.
WALTER'S NOT
THAT INTERESTED.
SO HAROLD TAKES OFF
THE BACKPACK.
IT'S A HEAVY UNIT.
SO THE IDEA IS THAT HE'S
GOING TO HANG IT ON A TREE.
ALL HE NEEDS TO FIND IS
A TREE THAT HAS A NAIL IN IT.
OH, THERE WE GO.
AND OF COURSE, THE WEIGHT
OF THE BACKPACK
PULLS THE TREE
RIGHT OVER.
SO HAROLD'S
A LITTLE CONCERNED.
HE'S WONDERING IF THAT
FELL ON WALTER'S FOOT.
APPARENTLY YES.
SO WALTER GETS
THE BANDAGE ON THERE.
AND HAROLD'S TRYING
TO BE HELPFUL.
BRINGS HIM ONE
OF THESE WALKING STICKS
AND DEMONSTRATES HOW
TO USE A WALKING STICK.
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
SO WALTER TRIES
THE WALKING STICK.
IT DOESN'T GO REAL WELL.
OH!
OKAY, SO WE GOT
TO GO TO PLAN B,
WHICH IS HAROLD
CARRIES BOTH BACKPACKS,
AND WALTER WALKS
IN A WAY THAT WILL NOT
HURT THE INJURED FOOT.
AND HE'S PRETTY
CREATIVE THAT WALTER.
SO THEY'RE
WALKING ALONG.
HAROLD HEARS
A BUZZING NOISE,
AND IT'S NOT JUST COMING
FROM HIS HEAD AS USUAL.
HE LOOKS UP AND THERE'S
A BEEHIVE UP THERE.
SO HAROLD KNOWS
THE SAFEST THING TO DO
WITH A BEEHIVE IS
TO TAP ON IT,
BUT IT SEEMS
PRETTY SOLID.
I GUESS THEY'RE OKAY.
AND THEN WALTER
DOESN'T NOTICE
THAT IT ACTUALLY DROPS
OUT OF THE TREE
AND --
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD.
OH BOY, OH BOY.
OH NO, OH NO.
HOW DOES HE DO THAT?
SO THEN HAROLD --
NO, HAROLD, NO, NO, NO.
NOW HE'S GOING TO
SWING AND HIT IT.
UNFORTUNATELY,
HE HITS THE FOOT.
AND THEN HE GETS -- HE DOES
GET THE PRYBAR IN THERE
AND JUST FLIPS
IT RIGHT OUT.
AND OKAY, WE'RE GOOD.
WE'RE GOOD, WE'RE GOOD.
WHAT HE DOESN'T NOTICE
IS THAT IT DROPPED
INTO HIS BACKPACK.
SO HAROLD PICKS UP
THE BACKPACK.
I THINK WE'LL SEE
HAROLD AGAIN.
HERE HE COMES.
YEAH, YEAH.
HAROLD'S GONE
TO HOLLYWOOD
TO BE IN A BEE MOVIE
BY THE LOOK OF IT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IF YOU'RE LIKE ME,
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET UP
IN THE MORNING.
HECK, MOST DAYS, YOU DON'T
WANT TO EVEN GET UP IN
THE AFTERNOON.
BUT IF THROUGH
SOME MIRACLE,
OR MANAGERIAL OVERSIGHT,
YOU MANAGE TO LAND
YOURSELF A JOB,
CHANCES ARE YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO GET UP EARLY.
THE PROBLEM
WITH ALARM CLOCKS IS
YOU CAN REACH OVER
AND SHUT THEM OFF
OR SMASH THEM TO BITS
WITH YOUR WORK BOOT
AND GO RIGHT
BACK TO SLEEP.
YOU NEED AN ALARM
THAT WILL GET YOU UP,
NOT JUST WAKE YOU UP.
OKAY, SO WHAT YOU
DO IS YOU TAKE THE TWO
OUTSIDE LEGS OF YOUR BED
AND YOU MOVE THEM
TO THE MIDDLE.
OH, SURE,
YOU'VE GOT TO LEARN
TO JUST SLEEP ON YOUR
SIDE OF THE BED,
BUT I'M GUESSING
YOU'RE USED TO THAT.
AND IN THE MORNING WHEN THE
IMMOVABLE OBJECT, YOU,
MEETS THE
UNSTOPPABLE FORCE, GRAVITY,
YOU'RE GOING TO FIND OUT THAT
GRAVITY WINS EVERY TIME.
[ CLOCK TICKING ]
[ ALARM ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, I JUST HAD MY NEEDLE,
AND I FEEL GREAT.
I'M PROUD OF MYSELF.
I TOOK IT LIKE A MAN.
HEY, THAT WASN'T
SO BAD AT ALL.
NO.
OH, YOU GOT
A RED ONE.
C'MON HAROLD,
TRADE ME, WILL YOU?
NO, YOU ALREADY
LICKED YOURS.
OH, OKAY.
NO!
IS IT SAFE?
YEAH, YEAH.
C'MON IN, DALTON.
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
YOU GUYS FINALLY
STOPPED BEING CHICKEN
AND GAVE EACH OTHER
THE SHOT, HUH?
NO, NO, NO.
APPARENTLY, WE'RE NOT
CONTAGIOUS ANYMORE,
SO THE CLINIC JUST
SENT SOMEBODY OVER
TO GIVE US
THE NEEDLE.
OH, I HOPE HE
WAS GENTLE WITH YOU.
OH, YEAH.
SO ANYONE ELSE
FEELING FEVERISH?
ME, ME!
I'M FEVERISH,
ITCHY.
OH, BOY, I BELIEVE
I'M GOING TO BE
REQUIRING
IMMEDIATE MEDICAL
ATTENTION.
I MAY EVEN NEED
TO BE BEDRIDDEN
FOR -- FOR --
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN
FEELING LIKE THIS?
A COUPLE OF DAYS.
I HAVE WHAT
THEY HAVE.
I'M GOING TO NEED
WHAT THEY GOT.
HM, WELL, WHY DON'T
YOU WAIT FOR ME
IN MY CAR?
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO
GIVE HIM THE SHOT
IN YOUR CAR?
OH, NO, NO, NO.
YOU SEE A SHOT
WON'T COVER IT.
PEOPLE WHO CATCH THE VIRUS
THROUGH HUMAN EXPOSURE,
MUCH HARDER TO CURE.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO PUT
HIM IN QUARANTINE FOR WEEKS
AND PUT HIM THROUGH A
BATTERY OF INVASIVE TESTS.
NOT GOING TO BE PRETTY.
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD
TELL THEM DOWN THERE
DALTON'S AFRAID
OF NEEDLES.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO GO
WITH SUPPOSITORIES.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
SOMEONE DOESN'T
SOUND WELL.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
THAT WAS OUR POSSUM SQUEAL.
WE HAVE A MEETING NOW.
WE HAVE TO GO.
OH, OKAY.
WELL, THANKS
FOR EVERYTHING.
HAROLD?
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M HEALTHY AS A HORSE,
STUBBORN AS A MULE
AND HOPING TO BE
HAPPY AS A RABBIT.
AND THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF,
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN, GUYS.
YOU GOT TO SIT DOWN.
HURRY UP AND SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN,
THE DISEASE IS CURED,
THE ITCHINESS IS
COMPLETELY GONE,
EXCEPT FOR DALTON WHO YOU
CAN SEE IS A LATE SCRATCH.