♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: HI THIS IS RED GREEN
IN TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD'S
GOING TO SHOW YOU SOME
BULLY PROOFING,
BILL'S GOING TO
TAKE DOWN A TREE,
AND I'M GOING TO BUILD A
REALLY NEAT INTERCOM SYSTEM.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
♪ ♪ ♪
>>HAROLD: HERE'S THE
MAIN REASON WE CALL THIS
THE RED GREEN SHOW
THE MAN WHO PAYS THE BILLS
AND SOMETIMES THE HAROLD'S.
HERE HE IS THE SMALL/MEDIUM
MR. LODGE, RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
THANKS FOR TUNING US IN,
SMALL/MEDIUM,
WHAT WAS THAT HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: WELL YOU KNOW
DON'T YOU GET IT?
SMALL/MEDIUM LODGE
YOU KNOW IT'S LIKE A
DWARF PSYCHIC AT A RESORT,
OR YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE IT
COULD BE LIKE CLOTHING SIZE
SMALL/MEDIUM, LODGE.
>>RED: YEAH, YOU KNOW I WISH
I HAD AN EXTRA LODGE
I'D SEND YOU INTO IT.
BY GOLLY I'M LOOKING FACE
TO FACE WITH THE OPPORTUNITY
OF A LIFE TIME, HERE THIS WEEK.
BUSTER HADFIELD ABOUT 3 MONTHS
AGO BOUGHT HIMSELF A BRAND NEW
12 PASSENGER VAN,
AND OF COURSE IT GOT REPOED.
NOW BUSTER HAS TAKEN THEM TO
COURT IN THAT ONE HE SAYS
THAT AS FAR AS HE'S CONCERNED
THE ADD WAS VERY CLEAR IT SAID,
NO MONEY DOWN, NO INTEREST
NO PAYMENTS EVER, OKAY.
AND THE JUDGE SAYS YEAH THERE
IS A PLAN LIKE THAT BUT IT'S
CALLED GRAND THEFT AUTO.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED THAT IS
LIKE A REALLY AWESOME VAN TOO.
YOU KNOW IF WE HAD A VAN LIKE
THAT YOU KNOW I COULD DRIVE
ALL THE CHEERLEADERS TO EVERY
FOOTBALL GAME, YOU KNOW AND WHO
KNOWS MAYBE ONE DAY ONE OF THEM
MIGHT ACKNOWLEDGE MY EXISTENCE,
YOU KNOW LIKE IN A POSITIVE WAY.
>>RED: WELL YOU KNOW HAROLD
I THINK I CAN GET OURSELVES
A REAL GOOD DEAL ON THAT UNIT,
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
TAKE OVER THE PAYMENTS.
>>HAROLD: YEAH BUT UNCLE RED,
WHAT IS THERE'S MORE OWING
ON THE VAN THAN IT'S WORTH?
>>RED: OH COME ON NOW HAROLD
YOU THINK A BANK IS GOING TO
LEND SOMEBODY MORE MONEY
THAN THEY CAN PAY BACK?
>>HAROLD: YES, THEY DO IT ALL
THE TIME BUT YOU KNOW IT'S FOR
RICH PEOPLE AND GOVERNMENTS.
>>RED: RIGHT BUT THIS IS BUSTER
OKAY, NOW THE WHOLE THING COMES
DOWN TO THE ART OF NEGOTIATION,
WHICH HAPPENS TO BE MY
SPECIALITY HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OH REALLY?
AND HOW MUCH DID YOU
PAY FOR THE POSSUM VAN?
>>RED: NOTHING HAROLD
THAT WAS A GIFT FROM MY PARENTS
FOR GRADUATING FROM
PUBLIC SCHOOL,
THAT WAY I WOULDN'T HAVE TO
BORROW MY DAD'S CAR TO DRIVE
TO JUNIOR HIGH.
>>HAROLD: BIT OF A SLOW
LEARNER THERE WERE WE?
>>RED: WELL IT WAS A DIFFERENT
WORLD THEN HAROLD YOU KNOW
WE HAD, WE HAD THE CHORES
AND THE HARVEST AND
OF COURSE BILLIARDS.
OF COURSE ALL OF US WERE IN
THE SAME BOAT AT THAT TIME,
YOU KNOW THE YOUNGEST GUY
IN MY HIGH SCHOOL CLASS
WAS ALWAYS THE TEACHER.
>>HAROLD: YOU'RE TRULY AMAZING
UNCLE RED I MEAN THERE YOU STAND
I THIS AGE OF INFORMATION WITH
VIRTUALLY NO EDUCATION
NO INSIGHT,
NO SPECIAL ABILITIES,
CERTAINLY NO PEOPLE SKILLS
BASICALLY AN I.Q. YOU KNOW ABOUT
ROOM TEMPERATURE AND THERE YOU
STAND SIR AND I SAY THIS TO YOU
THAT YOU ARE A TRIBUTE TO
THE TELEVISION STANDARD.
>>RED: WELL THANK YOU HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: YOU'RE WELCOME.
♪ UP AT THE LODGE ♪
♪ WE HAVE A SPECIAL DISH ♪
♪ WE CALL IT NEW BORN CHILLI ♪
♪ IT'S PART RABBIT ♪
♪ SO THERE'S HARE ♪
♪ IN YOUR SOUP ♪
♪ PART TURNIP, PART CABBAGE ♪
♪ PART CHILLI ♪
♪ OH MIX HER ALL UP ♪
♪ WITH A POUND OF CAYENNE ♪
♪ THAT'S NEW BORN CHILLI ♪
♪ ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ WE CALL IT NEWBORN ♪
♪ BECAUSE IT'S LUMPY ♪
♪ ON THE BOTTOM ♪
♪ AND IT MAKES A RACKET ♪
♪ IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT ♪
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
HANDYMAN'S CORNER
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO MODERNIZE YOUR HOME,
TO MAKE IT NOT ONLY MORE
CONVENIENT FOR YOUR FAMILY BUT
ALSO EASIER TO SELL WHEN THAT
DAY COMES WHICH IT WILL,
WHEN YOU CAN NO LONGER MOTIVATE
YOURSELF TO COME UP WITH
THE MORTGAGE PAYMENT.
ALL RIGHT NOW THE FIRST THING
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED IS
ABOUT HALF A DOZEN OF THESE
PREVIOUSLY OWNED PERSONAL
PORCELAIN APPLIANCES,
AND I'LL TELL YOU YOU CAN PRETTY
WELL NAME YOUR OWN PRIZE ON
THESE UNITS BECAUSE THERE IS
VERY LITTLE DEMAND SURPRISINGLY
ENOUGH FOR THE USED TOILET.
NOW YOU'RE ALSO GOING TO NEED
A BUNCH OF THE A.B.S. DRAIN PIPE
AND A WHOLE TRUNK LOAD OF
FITTINGS YOU KNOW THE 'T'S AND
THE ELBOWS AND WHAT HAVE YOU,
SO THAT YOU CAN CONNECT ALL OF
THIS STUFF INTO YOUR EXISTING
DRAIN SYSTEM.
NOW YOU CAN USE THE EPOXY CEMENT
ON THAT OR YOU COULD YOU USE
GUM OR EVEN POP RIVETS.
I PREFER THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
OKAY NOW YOU PUT ONE OF THESE
UNITS IN EACH OF THE ROOMS
YOU USE MOST OFTEN AND YOU
HOOK THEM RIGHT INTO THE DRAIN
SYSTEM LIKE I'VE DONE HERE.
THEY SAY THAT A MAN'S HOME
IS HIS CASTLE WELL NOW YOU CAN
HAVE A THRONE IN EVERY ROOM.
AND PUT THE UNIT RIGHT OUT IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE ROOM LIKE
THIS BECAUSE THIS IS NO LONGER
A TOILET, THIS IS NOW A
CUSTOM MADE ROOM TO ROOM
INTERCOM SYSTEM,
A COMBINATION TRANSISTOR
AND RECEIVER OR A TRANSCEIVER
AS WE CALL IT IN THE BUSINESS.
AND THE DRAIN SYSTEM BECOMES
YOUR DISTRIBUTION GRID,
AND IF YOU HOOK HER INTO THE
ROOF READER AS I'VE DONE HERE
YOU NOW HAVE A TWO WAY
PUBLIC ADDRESS SYSTEM
RIGHT OUT TO YOUR FRONT DOOR.
SO YOU CAN YOU KNOW GREET
YOUR GUESTS OR TELL THE POLICE
THAT YOU'RE NOT HOME OR WHATEVER
NOW WHEN YOU WANT TO SIGNAL
PEOPLE ON THE SECOND FLOOR
INSTEAD OF USING A BUZZER TAKE
ALL THE STUFF OUT OF THE TOILET
AND GET YOURSELF A LITTLE
BELL LIKE THIS.
(BELL RINGS)
AND THEN HOOK THAT RIGHT
ONTO THE FLUSHER HANDLE,
AND THEN WHEN YOU WANT
TO CALL SOMEBODY
(BELL RINGING)
JUST LIKE A PHONE.
NOW I IMAGINE A BUNCH OF YOU
ARE ASKING HEY RED WHAT
ABOUT THE SMELL?
WELL THIS IS A QUESTION
I'VE HAD TO DEAL WITH
THROUGHOUT MY LIFE,
AND I MUST ADMIT YOU GET ONE
OF THESE UNITS INTO THE DINING
THE OCCASIONAL PUFF OF METHANE
CAN PUT YOU OFF FOR DINNER,
AND ONCE SHE HITS THE CANDLES
IT WILL PUT YOU OFF YOUR SEAT.
THE BEST WAY AND EASIEST WAY
TO KEEP YOURSELF AWAY FROM
THE ODOURS OF THE UNDER WORLD
IS JUST TO FIRE A LITTLE BIT
OF WATER IN THERE,
NOT A WHOLE BUNCH JUST
ENOUGH TO FILL THE TRAP.
FUMES? WHAT FUMES?
NOW THE ONLY PROBLEM IS THIS
ALSO BLOCKS THE SOUND CREATING
WHAT WE CALL A BREAKDOWN IN
COMMUNICATION AND WHAT YOU
DO IS YOU GET A GAS SIPHON
LIKE THIS, THIS IS THE KIND
THAT USE AT THE MALL WHILE
YOUR WIFE'S INSIDE SHOPPING
AND YOU STICK THIS DOWN THROUGH
THE WATER BECAUSE YOU WANT TO
GET ALL THE WAY DOWN AND
AROUND AND INTO THE DRAIN PIPE,
AND THEN YOU GET YOURSELF
A FUNNEL LIKE THIS WHICH
MAYBE THE KIND YOU USE SAY AT
A BEER DRINKING CONTEST AND
YOU STICK THAT IN THE END,
AND THIS BECOMES YOUR
SPEAKER MICROPHONE,
LET'S GIVE HER A TRY.
(RINGING BELL)
HAROLD!
(WATER TINKLING)
>>HAROLD: NOT RIGHT NOW
UNCLE RED I'M KIND OF BUSY,
WHEW!
>>RED: WOW SHE'S AS CLEAR
AS A BELL ISN'T SHE?
YOU KNOW WE COULD USE THIS
ACTUALLY TO PUMP MUZAC ALL
THROUGH THE WHOLE LODGE
TRY AND IMAGINE THE BEST OF
BOX CAR WILLY COMING OUT
OF A JOHN.
ANYWAY REMEMBER IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST FIND
YOU HANDY.
I'M JUST GOING TO PUT YOU
ON HOLD THERE HAROLD,
I'LL GET BACK TO YOU.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S THAT
PART OF THE SHOW WHERE WE EXPOSE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS THAT
MEN FIND SO DIFFICULT TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW'.
NOW HERE TO PROVE THAT
POINT ON THE EXPERTS PORTION
OF THE SHOW, IS MY UNCLE RED
AND MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
HERE WE GO WITH OUR LETTER
A VIEWER SENT THIS IN
ACTUALLY FOR YOUR
PROFESSIONAL ANALYSIS,
SO THIS OUGHT TO BE INTERESTING.
IT SAYS, 'DEAR EXPERTS,
I FOUND THIS DO-HICKEY WHILE
CLEANING OUT MY CLOSET
AND I'D LIKE TO KNOW WHAT IT
IS AND HOW IT WORKS, PLEASE GIVE
ME A CLUE,' SIGNED CLUED OUT.
>>RED: IS THERE ANY OTHER
INFORMATION THERE HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: NO OH YEAH, OH YEAH
SORRY THERE IS IT SAYS I BET MY
WIFE $20 THAT YOU GUYS WOULD
GET THIS WRONG.
>>RED: WELL I WOULD SAY
THAT THIS IS A PIECE OF
FARM MACHINERY OF SOME KIND,
IF YOU LOOK AT THE
MARKINGS THERE.
>>HAP: DON'T TOUCH IT RED,
WHAT YOU HAVE THERE IS
A TOP LEVEL, TOP SECRET
EXPLOSIVE DEVICE.
>>HAROLD: ARE YOU SURE
MR. SHAUGHNESSY?
>>HAP: YES HAROLD
THE ISRAELIS USE THESE
AND THE TURKS, IT'S A KIND OF
A KIND OF A PLASTIC EXPLOSIVE
OR PLASTIQUE ONLY THIS ONE
IS METAL, SO IT'S CALLED
IT'S CALLED A METALIQUE.
>>RED: WELL HAP I DON'T
KNOW WHAT THIS IS EITHER,
I'LL TELL YOU ONE THING
WE'RE NOT GOING TO WASTE
ANYMORE TIME WITH IT LET'S
GET ONTO THE NEXT LETTER
(LOUD EXPLOSION)
>>HAP: WELL SOMEBODY OUT THERE
OWES HIS WIFE $20 BUCKS
AND SOMEBODY IN HERE
OWES ME AN APOLOGY.
>>RED: IT DIDN'T EXPLODE HAP
IT LANDED ON AN AEROSOL
PAINT CAN, NOBODY OWES
ANYBODY ANYTHING.
>>HAROLD: SOMEBODY
OWES ME A NEW BIKE.
>>RED: IT IS WINTER
THE FROZEN RAIN TURNS
THE WILLOW TREE INTO A
GIANT SHIMMERING CHANDELIER.
A MILLION DIAMONDS DANCING
IN IT'S BRANCHES OR SO IT SEEMS
AS I LOOK UP THROUGH IT
AND TO THINK I DIDN'T
EVEN NOTICE ALL THIS BEAUTY
UNTIL I SLIPPED AND FELL
FLAT ON MY BACK,
THIS IS MY LUCKY DAY.
♪ ♪ ♪
(LOUD SNORING)
>>RED: GLEN! GLEN!
FOR GOSH SAKES!
(STARTS ENGINE)
>>GLEN: OH, OH, OH RED IT'S YOU
I WAS HAVING THIS DREAM
I THOUGHT SOMEBODY WAS
STEALING MY R.V.
>>RED: NO KIDDIN'?
WHAT WERE YOU DOING UNDER THERE?
>>GLEN: OH I WAS CHECKING
FOR AN OIL LEAK
COULDN'T FIND ANYTHING THOUGH.
>>RED: NO?
HOW LONG WERE YOU
UNDER THERE GLEN?
>>GLEN: OH NOT LONG,
UM, ABOUT, IS TODAY TUESDAY?
>>RED: I DON'T THINK
SHE'S LEAKING TOO BAD BUT
MIGHT BE TIME TO
CHANGE THE FILTER.
>>GLEN: YEAH I WAS GOING TO
GET TO THAT THIS AFTERNOON,
I WAS GOING TO DO THAT TODAY
BUT I GOT THESE COTTAGERS
SQUAWKING AT ME, FIX MY BOAT,
FIX MY BOAT, BUT LIKE WE'RE
NEVER GOING TO HAVE ANOTHER
SUMMER AGAIN YOU KNOW,
(PHONE RINGING)
OH EXCUSE ME RED.
>>RED: YEAH.
(PHONE RINGING)
GLEN AREN'T YOU GOING
TO ANSWER THAT?
>>GLEN: I JUST SAID I'VE GOT TO
PUT AN OIL FILTER IN FIRST RED.
>>RED: OH.
(PHONE RINGING)
>>GLEN: THERE YOU GO RED
THERE'S NO SUCH THING AS
PATIENCE ANYMORE.
>>RED: YOU KNOW GLEN I'M TRYING
TO SAVE A LITTLE BIT OF MONEY
UP AT THE LODGE WE THOUGHT
WE MIGHT START A CAR POOL
YOU KNOW WHERE YOU GET ALL
THE GUYS TRAVELING AROUND
IN JUST THE ONE VEHICLE.
>>GLEN: OH THAT'S
A GREAT IDEA RED.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH.
>>GLEN: YEAH I'VE GOT THE
8 BUCKET RECLINERS IN HERE,
I'VE GOT THE QUEEN SIZE BED
I'VE GOT A FRIDGE FULL OF
TV DINNERS AND BOTH MICROWAVES
ARE FIRED UP.
OH DOLORES AND I CAN GO AT
ANY SECOND WE'RE ON
A 24 HOUR ALERT.
>>RED: WELL NO THAT'S GOOD,
THAT'S GOOD, BUT ACTUALLY
I WAS GOING TO USE
BUSTER HADFIELD'S 12 PASSENGER
VAN AFTER I BUY IT.
>>GLEN: OH WELL
COUNT ME OUT RED.
(PHONE RINGING)
(YELLING) ALL RIGHT!
MAN, THEY BUY A BOAT FROM
ME THEY THINK THEY OWN ME.
>>RED: WELL GLEN YOU KNOW IT
MIGHT BE THE GUY FROM THE
R.V. PLACE.
>>GLEN: THAT'S TRUE.
(PHONE RINGING)
PHONES IN ON THE A TABLE RED,
I APPRECIATE IT.
>>RED: OH FOR GOD'S SAKE!
>>GLEN: IF IT'S THE R.V. GUY
SEE IF HE'S GOT THAT INFLATABLE
SATELLITE DISH FOR ME.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
>>GLEN: IF IT'S NOT HIM
THEN JUST SAY NO PARLEY ANGLAIS
AND HANG UP THE PHONE.
>>RED: WELL AS I SAID
NEGOTIATION IS THE KEY TO MOST
THINGS IN LIFE AND I THINK
I'VE COME UP WITH A LITTLE PLAN
HERE THAT'S GOING TO BE ABLE TO
JUSTIFY ME GETTING THAT BRAND
NEW 12 PASSENGER VAN.
>>HAROLD: WELL I DON'T KNOW
UNCLE RED THAT'S NOT WHAT
I HEARD, YOU KNOW I MEAN IF
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT THAT CAR
POOL THING BECAUSE ALL THE
PEOPLE I TALKED TO THEY SAID
THEY WANT TO DRIVE THEIR
OWN CAR YOU KNOW IT'S LIKE A
CONTROL THING, YOU KNOW MEN CAN
BE AWFULLY FINICKY WHEN IT
COMES TO THEIR RADIO DIALS
GUYS GET PRETTY PICKY WHEN
IT COMES TO VOLUME KNOBS.
>>HAROLD: WELL THANK YOU
MR KNOB.
WHAT HAROLD DOESN'T REALIZE
IS THAT IN MY PLAN ALL THE GUYS
WILL BE IN THEIR OWN CARS
BECAUSE WHAT I'M GOING TO DO
IS DUCT TAPE ALL THE VEHICLES
TOGETHER AND THEN RUN THIS
ROPE UP TO MY 12 PASSENGER
AND TOW THE WHOLE BUNCH OF THEM,
THAT'S GOING TO BE BETTER
FOR THE ENVIRONMENT TOO.
>>HAROLD: EXCUSE ME UNCLE RED
HOW DO YOU FIGURE THAT'S
BETTER FOR THE ENVIRONMENT?
AM I MISSING SOMETHING?
>>RED: WELL YOU'RE MISSING
SO MANY THINGS HAROLD,
BUT WHAT I WAS REFERRING TO
IS THAT WE'VE ONLY GOT ONE
ENGINE RUNNING YOU SEE,
AND THEN I'LL GET ALL THE
GUYS TO CHIP IN FOR GAS SO
WE'LL GET SOME SAVINGS THERE.
I MEAN IT'S A TERRIFIC,
I KNOW THERE'S GOING TO BE
A FEW WRINKLES IN IT BUT WELL
FOR INSTANCE THE GUYS WHO'S
GOT THE BEST BRAKES HE'LL GO
AT THE END, BUT WE'RE GOING
TO WORK IT OUT BECAUSE
I'VE GOT A SMART PLAN,
THIS IS A SMART PLAN,
DON'T YOU THINK THIS
IS A SMART PLAN HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: WELL HAVE YOU ACTUALLY
PAID FOR THE VAN YET?
>>RED: NO, NO, NO.
>>HAROLD: OH AND ARE YOU GOING
TO GET A CHANCE TO ACTUALLY
YOU KNOW TRY THIS CONVOY CARAVAN
OR MOD IDEA OF YOURS BEFORE
YOU DO PAY FOR IT?
>>RED: OH SURE YEAH AH HUH.
>>HAROLD: WELL OKAY THEN
I GUESS I DON'T SEE A PROBLEM.
>>RED: GREAT, GREAT THANK YOU
VERY MUCH HAROLD.
♪  MOWING EVERY HAY FIELD ♪
♪ AND PUTTING THEM IN BALES ♪
♪ PICKING ALL THE PEA PODS ♪
♪ AND PUTTING THEM IN PAILS ♪
♪ IT'S TIME TO REAP ♪
♪ THE HARVEST ♪
♪ WE'RE GOING AS FAST ♪
♪ AS WE CAN ♪
♪ TRYING TO GET THE CROPS IN ♪
♪ BEFORE THE FARMER THAT ♪
♪ OWNS THIS PLACE COMES OUT ♪
♪ AND STARTS SHOOTING ♪
♪ AT US AGAIN ♪
>>RED: WELL BILL HAD SAID
TO ME HE WANTED TO TAKE SOME
TREES DOWN SO I THOUGHT I'D
GET THAT ONE OUT OF THE WAY
JUST AS I WAS ARRIVING.
IT WAS A BEAUTIFUL DAY
A LITTLE BIT OF A BREEZE
THERE AND BILL HAD THE CHAINSAW
HAPPENING AND HE HAD AN AXE
AND HE HAD THE TREE SAW
THERE SO HE'S PRETTY WELL SET
FOR ANYTHING, HE RAN OUT OF GAS
AND YOU'RE ALL SET YOU'RE GOING
TO BE JUST, SO I GUESS HE'S
GOING TO BE, WELL IT LOOKS LIKE
HE'S GOING TO START UP
THE CHAIN SAW AND JUST
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
SOME OF THESE DON'T START RIGHT
ON THE FIRST PULL YOU KNOW,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU HAVEN'T
GOT THEM TURNED ON.
YEAH THAT'S RIGHT BILL EMPTY
(ENGINE REVVING)
UP SHE GOES, YOU GET HER
REVVED UP I HOPE THE CHAIN
IS ON THERE REAL GOOD
AND OH! OH! OH!
(GLASS SHATTERING) OH!
ALL RIGHT PLAN 'B'
I'VE NEVER SEEN ONE OF THESE
BEFORE IT'S KIND OF A SWEDISH
LOOK AT THAT, UNBELIEVABLE!
MUST BE A TINY LITTLE MOTOR
THERE I COULDN'T EVEN SEE
AN ENGINE ON THAT UNIT
NO EXHAUST OR ANYTHING.
NOW THIS TREE APPARENTLY IS
OFFENDING BILL IN SOMEWAY SO
SHE'S GOING TO COME DOWN
AND THAT LITTLE RIG
INCREDIBLE ISN'T IT?
AMAZING WHAT THEY'RE DOING
NOW WITH THE COMPUTER CHIPS
AND SO ON...
SO HE'S GOT HER ALL CUT OUT
THERE NOW HE'S GOT THE AXE
AND HE'S GOT THIS THING SHARP
UNBELIEVABLE, THAT'S A
PROFESSIONAL AXE HE'S GOT
RIGHT THERE.
OH, OH, OH, NOW LUCKILY I HAD
SOME DUCT TAPE IN MY WALLET
ACTUALLY I HAD DUCT TAPE
INSTEAD OF MY WALLET.
NOW HE MARKS A NOTCH HERE
KIND OF A 'V' THING, HE'S
GOING TO CUT THAT OUT WITH
AN AXE AND THEN THAT WILL
DETERMINE WHICH WAY
THE TREE FALLS.
THIS IS PROBABLY GOING TO TAKE
A LITTLE WHILE SO I'LL GET BACK
TO THAT THERE RED,
YEAH OH MAYBE IT'S NOT GOING
TO TAKE AS LONG AS I THOUGHT.
ANYWAY NOW WHAT HE WANTS TO
DO IS GET OUT HIS MAGIC SAW
AMAZING THING, AND CUT THROUGH
FROM THE OTHER SIDE
YOU SEE AND THE WHOLE TREE
WILL FALL OVER TOWARDS THE
NOTCH THERE WHICH IS,
THAT'S ACTUALLY WHERE I HAD
THE VAN, WAS IT NOT,
GIVE HER A BOOT THERE,
YEAH, YEAH, OH BOY!
I HAVE NO EXPLANATION FOR THIS
FOLKS I THINK WE SHOULD GET
OUT OF HERE BILL!
>>RED: AND NOW HERE'S SOMETHING
FOR THE YOUNG PEOPLE,
OR AS WE CALL IT FILLER.
>>HAROLD: OH HI, OKAY WELL
WELCOME TO THE FIRST EVER
EDITION OF 'BULLY PROOFING'.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT SO MAYBE YOU'VE
HAD A SIMILAR HIGH SCHOOL
EXPERIENCE WHERE YOU KNOW
LIKE A BIG KID COMES ALONG,
RIGHT AND HE KNOCKS THE BOOKS
OUT OF YOUR HANDS AND THEN
YOU KNOW PUNCHES YOU,
RIGHT AND HE STANDS IN YOUR LIP
AS HE EATS YOUR LUNCH
YEAH WELL OKAY YEAH IT'S NOT
SO BAD THE FIRST FEW TIMES
BUT EVENTUALLY YOU'RE GOING
TO WANT TO KNOW THE ART
OF BULLY PROOFING.
(GASP OF PAIN)
LOOKS SOFT DIDN'T IT?
BUT THERE'S NUMEROUS PROVEN
TECHNIQUES, I LOOKED SOFT
THERE'S PROVEN TECHNIQUES
THROUGHOUT THE TIMES,
BUT LIKE FOR INSTANCE ONE
OF THE GOOD ONES, RIGHT,
FLEEING QUICKLY OFTEN
TIMES A GOOD ONE.
ANOTHER ONE, THE DEADLY
GARLIC DIET OR PERHAPS
THE FAMOUS AND ORIENTAL
TECHNIQUE OF NAN CHUCK.
THAT'S A GOOD ONE TOO THAT'S
WHERE YOU THROW UP ON A PERSON!
BUT WHATEVER YOU CHOOSE
THE POINT IS YOU'VE GOT TO
STAND UP FOR YOURSELF, SO.
>>RED: (SCREAMING) HAROLD!
>>HAROLD: WHAT IS IT?
UNCLE RED WHAT?
>>RED: STOP FOOLING
AROUND WITH ALL THAT STUFF.
>>HAROLD: OKAY ALL RIGHT,
I DON'T EVEN THINK SO BUDDY.
>>RED: AND CLEAN UP ALL THOSE
BLOCKS YOU KNOCKED OVER.
>>HAROLD: OKAY ALL RIGHTY OKAY.
OKAY...
I SHOULD HAVE VOMITED.
>>RED: WELL I DROPPED IN ON
DOUGIE FRANKLIN BECAUSE HE
WAS SAYING THAT HE SHOULD BE
PULLING THE CARS IN THE CAR
POOL WITH HIS MONSTER TRUCK
INSTEAD OF ME IN THE
12 PASSENGER VAN.
>>DOUGIE: IT'S A MATTER OF
DRIVING SKILLS REALLY,
DRIVING SKILLS.
>>RED: DRIVING SKILLS?
>>DOUGIE: I'M NOT SAYING YOU'RE
A BAD DRIVER I'M JUST SAYING
WELL I'VE BEEN IN EVERY TYPE OF
AUTOMOBILE EMERGENCY IMAGINABLE
AND WELL TO YOU I MEAN YOU KNOW
TO YOU A MULTI VEHICLE SMASH UP
IS SOME KIND OF VAGUE CONCEPT,
TO ME WELL IT'S A FAMILIAR
EXPERIENCE, MY DRIVING RECORD
IS HERE FOR ALL TO SEE.
IT'S NOT SOME SORT OF AIRY
FAIRY TEXT BOOK KNOWLEDGE
YOU'RE LOOKING AT HERE,
THIS IS HANDS ON/HEAD ON
EXPERIENCE I MEAN,
I KNOW EVERYTHING THERE IS
TO KNOW ABOUT WELL HEAD ON
COLLISION THERE, WRONG
WAY UP A ONE WAY STREET,
WHACKING A BIG GUY AT
A CROSS WALK, TRYING TO
PASS ON A CURVE, YOU NAME IT.
>>RED: WELL IT IS QUITE
AN IMPRESSIVE RECORD
YOU GOT HERE DOUG.
>>DOUGIE: SO THAT'S WHY
I'VE GOT TO DRIVE RED
I MEAN TRUTH BE KNOWN I'M
A BIT OF A NERVOUS PASSENGER.
>>RED: WELL DOUGIE ALL OF
A SUDDEN SO AM I.
SORRY BUT THE VAN HAS
GOT TO BE UP FRONT.
>>DOUGIE: WELL SURE OKAY FINE
I CAN SIT THIS ONE OUT
NO HARD FEELINGS I GUESS.
>>RED: OH NO, NO, NO, NO,
NONE BELIEVE ME.
>>RED: WELL THE CAR
POOL IDEA WAS NOT AN
UN-QUALIFYING SUCCESS.
>>HAROLD: QUELL SORT
DE SURPRISE MONSIEUR.
YOU'VE YOURSELF A STRING OF
BARELY ROAD WORTHY VEHICLES
ALL DUCT TAPED TOGETHER UP
TO A 12 PASSENGER VAN
MOOSE THOMPSON UP THERE
ON THE ROOF DOING HAND SIGNALS.
AND I HEARD YOU GOT
4 TRAFFIC TICKETS.
>>RED: WELL YOU'RE DEAD WRONG
HAROLD IT WAS 5 AND IT WOULD
HAVE BEEN 6 BUT LUCKILY
MOOSE WAS LICENSED
FOR AN 18 WHEELER.
>>HAROLD: 18 HOW DO YOU
GET 18 FROM 5 VEHICLES?
>>RED: WELL JUNIOR SINGLETON
HAD HIS MOTORCYCLE IN THERE
SO IT WAS 4 FOURS AND A 2.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
>>RED: WE WERE, WE WERE
ACTUALLY DOING REAL WELL TILL
WE GOT TO THE CENTRE OF TOWN
AND YOU KNOW WHAT IN HINDSIGHT
NOW I THINK WE SHOULD HAVE
DECIDED A HEAD OF TIME WHICH
WAY WE WERE GOING TO TURN
AT THE INTERSECTION.
YOU KNOW THE WORST OF IT
WAS JUNIOR SINGLETON BECAUSE
HE HAD HIS IGNITION KEY TURNED
OFF WHICH LOCKED HIS STEERING.
>>HAROLD: OH OKAY EXPLAIN THIS
TO ME, SO YOU GOT NAILED FOR
LIKE CROSSING A MEDIAN AND
BOTH SHOULDERS, YOU GOT FAILING
TO STOP AT 2 STOP SIGNS AT
THE SAME TIME AND THEN
DRIVING A TRAIN WITHOUT A TRACK,
WHAT WERE THE OTHER 2?
>>RED: AH HAVING A PARADE
WITHOUT A PERMIT,
AND PASSING ON A HILL.
>>HAROLD: SO WHAT HAPPENED
LIKE ARE WE BUYING THE VAN?
>>RED: OH NO I'M NOT
BUYING THE VAN,
NOT AFTER THAT TEST DRIVE
I MEAN JUST LIKE THE SLIGHTEST
LOAD AND THAT TRANSMISSION
OVERHEATS LIKE YOU
WOULDN'T BELIEVE.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH SQUEAL
OF THE POSSUM,
THAT'S MEETING TIME.
>>RED: YEAH YOU GO AHEAD HAROLD
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
>>HAROLD: OKEY DOKE.
>>RED: WELL THAT'S ABOUT IT FOR
THIS SHOW, SO IF MY WIFE IS
WATCHING I'M JUST WONDERING
IF YOUR BROTHER IN LAW IS STILL
WITH THE TRAFFIC VIOLATION
SECTION OF THE POLICE
STATION DOWN THERE?
AND IF HE IS, WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE INVITE HIM AND THAT ZINGO
WIFE OF HIS AND THOSE
4 BRATTY KIDS OVER FOR SAY
A BARBECUE TOMORROW NIGHT,
THAT WOULD BE FUN WOULDN'T IT?
AND FOR THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF HAROLD AND MYSELF
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORITATI.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca