ONE OF THE THINGS MEN
PRIZE ABOVE ALL ELSE
IS THEIR DIGNITY
UNLESS THEY'RE IN A
PARADE OR SOMETHING.
IF YOU'VE EVER SEEN
A GANG OF SHRINERS,
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
WE SEEM TO
ENJOY CEREMONIES.
MAYBE MEN LIKE TO CELEBRATE
IMPORTANT ACHIEVEMENTS OR EVENTS
AS A WAY OF SHARING
IN THE GLORY
OR MAYBE WE JUST LIKE GETTING
DRESSED UP AND ACTING
LIKE WEENIES.
IT'S NOT SMART OR CORRECT
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT MAKES US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red: ON TODAY'S SHOW,
BILL AND I ARE GOING TO DO A
TRIBUTE TO BENJAMIN FRANKLIN,
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU SOME
EXERCISES AND APPLIANCES
YOU CAN WEAR
TO LOOK THINNER,
DOUGIE IS GOING TO DO
SOMETHING WEIRD WITH HIS FACE
AND THEN HAROLD AND I ARE
GOING TO DO A LITTLE BIT
OF STREAM FISHING.
AND NOW HERE'S THE REASON
WE'RE ALL HERE,
AND YOU'RE ALL THERE
AND EVERYONE ELSE IS
EVERYWHERE ELSE,
MY UNCLE... RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THIS WEEK GOT SOME GOOD NEWS,
GOT SOME BAD NEWS.
WHAT'S THE BAD NEWS?
MEET MY NEPHEW
HAROLD.
AND NOW THE GOOD NEWS...
THIS WEEK MARKS A 130th
ANNIVERSARY OF THE CREATION
OF THE SPINCAST
FISHING REEL.
WOW!
AND WHEN YOU STOP
TO THINK ABOUT IT,
EVERY OVER-FISHED LAKE,
RIVER AND STREAM
OWES ITS PRESENT STATE
TO THIS MARVELOUS INVENTION.
SO THE QUESTION IS,
HOW ARE WE GOING TO CELEBRATE
THIS MOMENTOUS OCCASION?
NOW, MOOSE THOMPSON
HAD AN IDEA,
HE SAID WHY DON'T WE PUT
ALL THE GUYS' NAMES INTO A HAT
AND YOU PULL A NAME OUT
AND WHOEVER'S NAME YOU GET,
YOU GO GIVE HIM A WEDGY.
GREAT IDEA.
NOT A LOT TO DO WITH THE
SPINCAST THING BUT I LIKE IT.
UNCLE RED, HOW ABOUT AN
EVENING OF ENTERTAINMENT THEN
WITH THE LOCAL THEATER COMPANY,
THE POSSUM PLAYERS?
NO, HAROLD.
NOT A GOOD IDEA TO GET ACTORS
AND HUNTERS TOGETHER,
ESPECIALLY THOSE ACTORS.
AND THESE HUNTERS.
INSTEAD WE'RE ALL
GOING TO MEET IN THE
CENTRE OF TOWN,
WE'RE GOING TO HOLD UP A
SPINCAST FISHING ROD,
AND BUZZ IS GOING TO
FLY OVER IN HIS PLANE
AND TAKE AN
AERIAL PHOTOGRAPH.
WELL, WHAT IF
SOMEBODY BLINKS?
WELL, WE'LL RETOUCH THE
PHOTOGRAPH, HAROLD,
WE GOT TO AIRBRUSH MOST
OF YOUR TEETH OUT ANYWAY.
IF YOU CAN'T BE WITH THE
PLANE YOU LOVE,
LOVE THE PLANE
YOU'RE WITH.
OH WE HAD AN EARTHQUAKE
LATE LAST NIGHT
IT SHOOK THE LODGE
AND GAVE US ALL A FRIGHT
A FRIGHT
HIT ABOUT NINE ON
THE RICHTER SCALE
THE SCALE
BOUNCED ALL THE CONTENTs
OUT OF THE MINNOW PAIL
PAIL
SO WE WENT OUTSIDE TILL
THE DANGER PASSED
BECAUSE IF LODGE GOES DOWN,
IT'LL GO DOWN FAST
BUT IT WASN'T AN EARTHQUAKE
SHAKING THE GROUND
IT WAS A KID IN A CHEVETTE
WITH THE BASE TURNED UP
WAY BEYOND ANY
SENSIBLE LEVEL.
ALL RIGHT, HERE'S
THE SITUATION...
YOU'VE JUST TAKEN YOUR
WIFE OUT FOR DINNER
AT ONE OF THOSE LOVELY
ALL-YOU-CAN-EAT PLACES.
WHICH OF COURSE IS A
DIRECT CHALLENGE NO REAL
MAN COULD REFUSE.
ABSOLUTELY.
YOU GOT YOURSELF UP,
YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY UP THERE
FOR YOUR NINTH PLATE OF BEEF,
WITHOUT HAVING A LEAF
OF SALAD YET,
YOUR WIFE TURNS
TO YOU AND SAYS,
HEY, ARE YOU
HAVING MORE MEAT?
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YOU SAY TO HER,
HONEY,
I LIKE THE RARE PART,
NOBODY ELSE IS ORDERING
BEEF SO IT HAS FALLEN
ON ME
TO SINGLE-HANDEDLY EAT
MY WAY RIGHT THROUGH INTO
THE MIDDLE OF THAT ROAST.
OR YOU COULD TRY,
PEOPLE ARE STARVING
IN AFRICA.
THAT ONE WILL WORK.
THAT'S GOING
FOR THE JUGULAR.
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
OR YOU COULD SAY,
I'M NOT JUST EATING MEAT,
I'M ALSO HAVING
VEGETABLES.
I MEAN, HORSERADISH IS
A VEGETABLE, RIGHT, RED?
SURE IS.
SO IS GRAVY,
I BELIEVE.
ABSOLUTELY.
AND DON'T
FORGET SALT.
SALT.
THAT'S RIGHT THERE ON
THE VEGETABLE LIST
IN MY BOOK.
OR, YOU KNOW,
WORST-CASE SCENARIO,
SHE'S STILL ON YOUR CASE,
LOOK AT HER AND
GIVE HER THIS FACE.
AND THEN SAY,
IT'S OKAY, HONEY,
I'M NOT HAVING
ANY DESSERT.
"FOR SALE:
ANTIQUE HOPE CHEST,
"HOPE YOU LIKE IT,
HOPE IT'S VALUABLE,
"HOPE TO GET $500."
NOT A HOPE.
YOU KNOW WITH EVERYBODY GETTING
READY FOR THIS AERIAL PHOTO
FOR THE COMMEMORATING THE
INVENTION OF THE SPINCAST REEL,
THE BEAUTY PARLOURS AND
BARBERSHOPS AROUND POSSUM LODGE
ARE JAMMED
TO THE EYEBALLS.
SO I THOUGHT I WOULD TAKE
TODAY'S HANDYMAN CORNER
AND SHOW YOU HOW TO DO A
COMPLETE BEAUTY MAKEOVER
USING STUFF YOU FIND
RIGHT AROUND YOUR HOUSE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S START WITH
SOMETHING FOR THE LADIES,
LIKE DOING YOUR NAILS,
FOR EXAMPLE.
GET YOURSELF A
PIZZA BOX LIKE THIS
AND TRACE YOUR
HAND ON THERE
AND THEN PUNCH OUT ALL THE
FINGERNAIL TIPS THERE,
AND THEN ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS
-- A REAL GREAT TIME SAVER,
IS YOU JUST PUT YOUR
HAND INSIDE THE BOX,
TAKE SOME SPRAY PAINT THERE
AND JUST PUT THAT ALL ON THERE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER,
YOU KNOW, HOW YOU DO IT.
I HOPE THE OTHER LODGE MEMBERS
STILL RESPECT ME WITH,
YOU KNOW,
PAINTED FINGERNAILS.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, WE HAVE TO HAVE THE BACK
OF YOUR HAND AGAINST THE HOLE.
THIS ACTUALLY LOOKS LIKE
I'VE BEEN ARRESTED AND
FINGERPRINTED.
GUYS WILL RESPECT ME
NOW FOR SURE.
BUT FOR YOU LADIES THERE'S
ALL KINDS OF TOOLS RIGHT
IN THE WORKSHOP
YOU CAN USE FOR
BEAUTY TREATMENTS.
YOU COULD TWEEZE YOUR
OWN EYEBROWS,
SHAVE YOUR LEGS,
LAY THE MAKEUP IN THERE.
WANT PIERCED EARS?
TRY A POP RIVETER.
IF YOU'RE HAVING TROUBLE
FITTING INTO THAT DRESS THAT
YOU BOUGHT LAST FALL,
YOU DON'T NEED A GIRDLE,
GET YOURSELF ONE OF THESE
TUBE SOCKS AND CUT THE
TOE OUT OF THAT
AND JUST SLIP THAT
BABY ON THERE.
YOU WILL GET A SHAPE THAT
WILL GET ALL KINDS
OF ATTENTION.
SHE'S COMING.
ALMOST COMING.
COME ON.
THERE WE GO.
AND I'LL TELL YOU,
YOU'RE NOT JUST LOOKING GOOD,
YOU'RE LOSING WEIGHT
BECAUSE THERE'S NO WAY
YOU CAN EAT FOOD
WHEN YOU'RE WEARING
THIS TYPE OF A UNIT.
AND ANOTHER THING IS
YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOUR DIGESTIVE SYSTEM
IS TIGHT AS A DRUM.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
WHAT ABOUT THE MEN?
WHAT CAN THEY DO TO GET
THEMSELVES KIND OF GUSSIED UP
FOR A FANCY OCCASION?
WELL, BASICALLY THEY SHAVE
AND GET A HAIRCUT.
I DON'T EVEN DO THAT.
I DON'T SHAVE MYSELF.
BUT WHEN I HAVE TO GO
SOMEWHERE AND LOOK REAL GOOD
LIKE AT A FUNERAL OF
SOMEBODY WITH MONEY,
WHAT I'LL DO IS COVER UP MY
BEARD WITH THESE FLESH
COLOURED BANDAGES,
AND I JUST
CAMOUFLAGE THE BEARD.
MAN, I LOOK
LIKE JAY LENO.
AS FAR AS THE HAIRCUT GOES,
YOU KNOW THE REASON THAT A
BARBER CAN CHARGE YOU
UP TO SEVEN BUCKS
TO CUT YOUR HAIR IS BECAUSE
HE'S LEARNED HOW TO CUT EVERY
HAIR EXACTLY THE SAME LENGTH.
BUT THERE'S A CHEAP WAY
THAT YOU CAN DO THAT AT HOME
EVEN IF YOUR HEAD
ISN'T BOWL SHAPED.
OKAY, FIRST THING YOU NEED
IS AN OLD LAMP,
TAKE THE
CORD OFF OF IT,
AND THEN GET RID OF THE LAMP
SO YOUR WIFE DOESN'T ASK
ANY STUPID QUESTIONS.
AND THEN YOU WANT TO TAKE
ONE OF THEM LIGHT DIMMERS
AND HOOK THAT INTO
THE MIDDLE OF THE CORD
AND HOOK THAT ALL UP, AND I'LL
SHOW YOU HOW THAT WORKS.
[ ELECTRICITY ZAPPING ]
ALL RIGHT, ONCE YOU GOT
THAT HOOKED UP,
PLUG HER IN AND THEN ATTACH
THE BARE ENDS OF THE WIRES
TO YOUR EARLOBES.
NOW WHEN I TURN ON
THE DIMMER HERE,
THE ELECTRICITY FLOWS INTO
THE HEAD OF THE VICTIM --
I SHOULD SAY THE CUSTOMER,
MAKING HIS HAIR STAND
RIGHT UP ON END,
MAKING IT REAL
EASY TO CUT.
YOU'RE GOING TO END UP WITH
A FELLOW WHO'S NOT ONLY
HANDSOME, BUT HANDY.
WATCH THIS.
NOT QUITE WHAT
I HAD IN MIND,
BUT HE'S NOT GOING TO NEED A
HAIRCUT FOR A WHILE.
Red: STAY TUNED.
COMING UP, BILL HAS ANOTHER
NEGATIVE EXPERIENCE
WITH GRAVITY,
AND THEN BUZZ SHOWS HAROLD
WHAT IT'S LIKE AT BOOT CAMP.
I WANT TO TALK TO ALL
YOU MIDDLE-AGED GUYS
ABOUT HOW YOU FEEL
TIRED ALL THE TIME.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GOING THROUGH.
MANY IS A TIME I SIT IN THE
LIVING ROOM THERE LISTENING
TO MY WIFE TALK,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN MY LEG
WILL FALL ASLEEP,
OR I'LL BE GOING UP
A FLIGHT OF STAIRS
AND HAVE TO PULL OVER
INTO THE SLOW LANE
TO LET THE DOG GO BY,
AND HE'S 17,
WHICH IN DOG YEARS IS...
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK.
IT JUST SEEMS THAT
AS THE YEARS PILE UP,
THE ENERGY LEVEL
GOES DOWN.
NOW, YOUR DOCTOR IS GOING
TO TELL YOU IT'S THE
HOURS YOU KEEP
OR THE FOOD YOU EAT OR HOW
MUCH OF IT OR NOT GETTING
ENOUGH EXERCISE,
PLUS THE FACT THAT YOU'VE
PUT ON 75 POUNDS
SINCE THE LAST TIME
YOU DID ANYTHING,
BUT I SAY IT'S
ALL IN YOUR MIND.
SEE, YOUR MIND HAS JUST SAT
THERE QUIETLY FOR 40 YEARS,
WATCHING YOUR
BODY DO STUFF LIKE...
FLIP OVER THE HANDLEBARS
OF YOUR BIKE;
OR TAKE THE FAST WAY
DOWN FROM THE ROOF;
OR GO [ snap ] FROM PICKING UP
TOO MUCH WALL BOARD.
AND YOUR MIND IS TIRED OF
TAKING IN ALL THAT PAIN.
SO ONE DAY WHEN YOUR
BRAIN IS ASLEEP,
LIKE WHEN YOU'RE WATCHING
RERUNS OF "MATLOCK"
OR SOMETHING,
YOUR MIND QUIETLY TELLS YOUR
MUSCLES TO GO TO SLEEP
OR CRAMP UP OR SOMETHING.
AND THAT EXHAUSTION IS
JUST SELF-PRESERVATION,
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
YOU SHOULD BE HAPPY
THAT YOUR BODY IS TOO TIRED
TO DO THE THINGS
THAT YOU WANT TO DO
BECAUSE THAT TIREDNESS
IS SAVING YOUR LIFE.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, THIS GROUP PHOTOGRAPH
WE'RE PLANNING TO TAKE
IS TURNING INTO A
PORTRAIT OF DISASTER.
SOMETIMES I THINK THE
RESIDENTS AROUND HERE ARE
ONE CHROMOSOME AWAY
FROM DRAGGING THEIR
KNUCKLES ON THE GROUND.
HOW HARD CAN IT BE TO TELL
THEM TO SHOW UP ON TIME
AND JUST STAND IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE STREET?
EXACTLY, ALL THEY GOTTA
DO IS STAND THERE AND
STARE AT THE SKY.
THEY DO IT
FOR AN ECLIPSE.
SOME OF THE GUYS ARE SAYING,
BRING THE PLANE IN LOW
SO YOU CAN'T
SEE MY BALD SPOT,
AND OTHERS WANT US
TO DELAY IT FOR A MONTH
SO THEY CAN GO ON A DIET,
FOR GOSH SAKES.
THE PLANE IS GOING TO BE
1,000 FEET UP,
NO ONE IS EVEN
GOING TO NOTICE.
WHAT A BUNCH
OF VAIN IDIOTS.
SAYS THE GUY WHO SPENT
TEN BUCKS ON ACNE CREAM.
I HAD A FLARE-UP!
SO I JUST TOLD THE FAT ONES
TO STAND UNDER THE GROCERY
STORE AWNING.
THE GROCERY STORE
HAS GOT A NEW AWNING?
WELL, YEAH.
SEE, THE MERCHANTS REALIZE
THEIR SHOPS ARE GOING TO
BE IN THE PICTURE,
SO NOW THEY'RE FIXING
THEIR STORES UP.
OH GREAT.
WELL, IT WAS UNTIL THEY
SAW THE ADVERTISING
POTENTIAL.
NOW THE FUNERAL PARLOUR PUT
A GREAT BIG SIGN ON THE ROOF,
COFFINS,
PRICED TO MOVE.
OH BOY.
THE WORST WAS MURRAY'S
LEISURE WEAR...
10-FOOT LETTERS: MEN'S AND
LADIES' PANTS HALF-OFF.
WELL, WHAT WITH PICTURE
DAY COMING UP,
I THOUGHT WE'D DROP IN
AND SEE OUR RESIDENT
BUSH PILOT/AERIAL
PHOTOGRAPHER BUZZ SHERWOOD.
HEY, BUZZ.
YO, RED MAN,
HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD. GOOD. GOOD.
GOOD TO SEE YOU, EH?
HAROLD!
OH, FOR CRYING
OUT LOUD, HAROLD,
HOW MUCH CAN THAT HURT?
I WAS ASKING HAROLD.
SO, BUZZ, YOU ALL SET FOR
THE PICTURE TAKING THING?
OH, SURE, SURE.
AS SOON AS WE PASS
OUR SAFETY INSPECTION,
WE'RE IN BUSINESS.
WHAT SAFETY INSPECTION?
OH MAN,
THE RULE MAKERS.
THE WHOLE CORRUPT
SYSTEM, MAN,
THEY JUST WANT TO TIE
MY FEET TO THE GROUND.
YOU KNOW, THEY PULL THESE
RANDOM CHECKS, RIGHT,
SO THAT GUYS LIKE ME
MAKE SURE OUR PLANES
ARE SAFE.
SAFE?
I MEAN,
WHAT IS SAFE?
IT'S LIKE, ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO PREDICT WHAT'S GOING
TO FALL OFF OR NOT?
SEE!
SHEESH.
WELL, IF THEY
FIND SOMETHING --
WHAT AM I SAYING?
WHEN THEY FIND SOMETHING
WRONG WITH THE PLANE,
WHAT HAPPENS THEN?
OH, MAN, THE FLIGHT FUZZ
COME DOWN ON YOU
SO HARD, MAN!
WELL, THEN, WHO ARE
WE GOING TO GET
TO FLY OVER POSSUM LAKE
AND TAKE OUR PICTURE?
OH, DON'T -- DON'T PANIC.
DON'T PANIC.
HEY, YOUR BUDDY BUZZ
HAS EVERYTHING UNDER
CONTROL,
'CAUSE I'VE BEEN
WORKING ON BEAUTY HERE.
SHE'S GOING TO
PASS NO PROBLEM.
I EVEN CAULKED UP ALL
THEM BULLET HOLES.
WELL, YOU MISSED A WHOLE
BUNCH RIGHT THERE IN
THE TAIL SECTION.
OH, THOSE ONES.
THAT'S OKAY.
THOSE ARE GOING
IN HOLES.
I CAN SAY THAT WAS LIKE
A HUNTING ACCIDENT
OR SOMETHING.
IT'S THE EXIT HOLES
THAT MAKE THEM NERVOUS.
AND LOOK, LOOK WHAT I FOUND,
LOOK WHAT I FOUND, HUH?
TWO MORE BOLTS TO
HOLD THE PROPELLER ON.
NOW I GOT FOUR OUT
OF FIVE THERE.
AND THESE THINGS,
DID YOU KNOW THESE
WERE CALLED FLAPS,
AND YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO OIL THEM?
I MEAN, I JUST
LEARNED SO MUCH.
THE CONTROL PANEL,
I PUT A BATTERY
BEHIND IT, RIGHT,
AND NOW IT LOOKS LIKE IT
REALLY WORKS WITH LIGHTS
AND EVERYTHING.
IT'S JUST AMAZING.
SO YOU THINK BEAUTY IS
GOING PASS THIS THING?
OH, NO PROBLEM.
I PUMPED OUT THE PONTOONS
AND DUCT TAPED THE HOLES.
THIS IS GOING
TO BE GREAT.
AND THAT WILL FOOL
THE INSPECTORS?
NO SWEAT.
WHAT IF THEY ASK
YOU TO FLY HER?
OH, WELL,
THEY NEVER DO,
BECAUSE THAT WOULD MEAN THEY
WOULD HAVE TO GET IN IT
AND GO UP WITH ME.
UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED,
WHAT'S THIS DEFICIENCY
IN ADULTS
THAT MAKES THEM WANT
TO DRINK ALCOHOL?
WELL, THERE'S NO
DEFICIENCY, HAROLD.
IT'S A TRADITION,
A RITUAL.
ALCOHOL IS A
SIGN OF FRIENDSHIP,
YOU KNOW, LIKE BAPTISM
OR INSTALLING A NEW POPE
OR A PLAYOFF GAME.
WELL, PERSONALLY,
YOU KNOW,
I JUST DON'T THINK
IT'S NECESSARY.
FOR INSTANCE, LIKE,
HOW COME THEY NEED
LIKE ALCOHOL
AT LIKE A WEDDING?
HOW COME?
WELL, HAROLD,
WITHOUT ALCOHOL
A LOT OF WEDDINGS
WOULD NEVER HAPPEN.
IT'S UP TO EACH PERSON
TO KNOW HIS OWN LIMIT,
YOU KNOW, IT'S AN INDIVIDUAL
THAT MAKES THE DECISION,
THAT'S ALL.
WELL, I THINK THAT A LOT
OF THE LODGE MEMBERS
ARE MAKING BAD DECISIONS,
EVERY WEEKEND.
WELL, HAROLD, EITHER
THEY'VE GOT A DISEASE
THAT NEEDS TO BE
LOOKED AFTER
OR MAYBE THEY'RE TRYING
TO ESCAPE AN UNPLEASANT
SITUATION.
I NEVER THOUGHT OF THE
LODGE AS AN UNPLEASANT
SITUATION.
ONLY WHEN YOU'RE
HERE, HAROLD.
WELL, DON'T YOU WORRY,
I'M GOING BACK HOME
IN A FEW MONTHS.
WANT TO GIVE US A
PUSH THERE, HAROLD,
THE BEER STORE
CLOSES IN AN HOUR.
Red: TIME FOR
ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
I'D BEEN READING THE MAIL,
SO I WAS OUT FLYING A KITE,
OF COURSE.
AND BILL DECIDED
TO JOIN ME.
ISN'T THAT BEAUTIFUL?
JUST SUCH A SIMPLE THING UP
THERE, FLYING AWAY,
IT'S KIND OF MAGICAL.
AND BILL IS GOING TO WHIP
OUT A KITE KIT.
YEAH, THESE ARE GREAT.
GOT THE CHILD PROOF LOCK BAG,
WHICH IS SENSIBLE.
YOU DON'T WANT A KID
OPENING UP ONE OF THOSE
AND PLAYING WITH A KITE.
LUCKILY BILL HAS A VASECTOMY
KIT IN HIS OTHER POCKET.
OH WELL,
THANK YOU, BILL.
YEAH, OH-OH IS RIGHT.
NOW WHAT?
YOU GOT ANOTHER ONE OF THOSE
KITS IN YOUR KIT THERE?
WELL, THAT'S FAIR ENOUGH,
HE'S GOING TO GIVE ME HIS.
OH, NO, HE HAS
GOT ANOTHER ONE.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
FAIR ENOUGH.
SO NOW WITH THESE, YOU KNOW,
YOU GOT A LITTLE BIT OF
ASSEMBLY REQUIRED.
AND OF COURSE WE CAN PUT
THESE TOGETHER FASTER
THAN MOST WOMEN CAN
READ THE INSTRUCTIONS.
BILL'S IS KIND OF A WILD
LOOKING THING, ISN'T IT?
MINE IS -- OH BILL.
NOW, THAT'S ODD, THE WILD
LOOKING THING IS --
WOW. UNBELIEVABLE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, TO ME THE
THING ABOUT WILD KITES IS
THEY SHOULDN'T REALLY
BE IN CAPTIVITY.
THERE YOU GO, BE FREE.
GO BE FREE.
FAIR IS FAIR, BILL.
SO WE DECIDED
TO COMBINE OUR EFFORTS
AND MAKE A SUPER, DUPER, TRIPLE,
TRIPLE DECKER THREE STOREY --
YEAH, IT'S A BEAUTY.
IT'S A BEAUTY.
ALL RIGHT, BILL,
THROW 'ER UP.
LET 'ER GO.
OH BOY.
THROW 'ER UP.
LET 'ER GO.
FOR GOSH SAKE.
ALL RIGHT, BILL, BILL,
I'LL TAKE CARE OF
THAT ONE, OKAY?
NOW, HERE IS A KITE KIT.
LOOK AT ALL THIS.
LOOK AT THIS.
HUH, WHAT?
A LITTLE BIT OF
OVERPACKAGING THERE.
OH, I SEE, THE KIT IS ACTUALLY
THE BOX THAT IT COMES IN.
WELL, NOW, THAT'S SMART.
BOY, THIS IS A BEAUTY.
THIS IS A BEAUTY.
THIS THING -- THIS THING IS
REALLY GOING TO FLY.
IT'S GOING TO FLY.
DO YOU THINK THAT STRING
IS HEAVY ENOUGH?
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, BILL, THROW 'ER UP.
THROW 'ER UP.
THERE SHE GOES.
OH, MAN, LOOK AT HER GO.
LOOK AT HER GO.
LOOK OUT, BILL,
IT'S COMING BACK... BILL.
FAIR ENOUGH.
HE'S FINE.
OH, OH, UP SHE GOES,
BIG WIND, BIG WIND.
THERE SHE GOES.
AND THAT'S A 107-FOOT BILL.
AND NOW IT'S,
OH, A 100-FOOT BILL,
90, 80, 70, 60.
OKAY, THAT'S A
SEA LEVEL BILL THERE.
IS HE ALL RIGHT?
CHECKING OVER THE KITE.
OH THERE HE GOES.
HE'S OKAY.
WE'LL CHECK
HIS TAIL LATER.
Red: COMING UP,
WE GOT WINSTON ROTHSCHILD,
THE ULTIMATE HOSER,
AND HAROLD IS
GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW
HE COLOURED HIS PLACEMAT
FROM THE
POSSUM LODGE DINER.
WELL, FOR A WHILE
THERE IT LOOKED LIKE
THAT BIG GROUP AERIAL
PHOTO THING WAS GOING
TO BE CANCELLED.
WE GOT THE DATE AND
THE TIME ALL NAILED
DOWN AND EVERYTHING,
BUT WE GOT FAMILIES
FEUDING WITH OTHER FAMILIES,
AND THEY REFUSED TO POSE
IN THE SAME PICTURE.
I GOT THAT COVERED, UNCLE RED.
I HAVE GOT THAT COVERED.
I'VE COLOUR CODED
THE DOWNTOWN AREA.
LOOK AT THIS, I PUT
THE POTTSONS RIGHT HERE
BECAUSE THEY DON'T
WANT TO BE NEAR THE
RICHARDSONS,
WHO I PLACED STRATEGICALLY
OVER HERE, YOU SEE?
NOW, THEY'RE IN FRONT
OF THE SIMMS UP HERE
BECAUSE YOU KNOW WHY,
THEY HATE THE TYLERS.
RIGHT THERE,
THAT'S THE TYLERS.
BUT THAT'S OKAY,
THAT'S GOING TO BE OKAY,
BECAUSE WHAT I'VE DONE IS
I PUT US, THE GREEN FAMILY,
RIGHT IN THE CENTRE OF TOWN,
RIGHT THERE AT THE CROSSWALK.
AND THE FREDERICKS --
KNOW WHAT I'VE DONE
WITH THE FREDERICKS?
PUT THEM RIGHT THERE
AS A DEFENCE.
ASK ME WHY.
DON'T, BECAUSE
I'LL TELL YOU.
BECAUSE WHAT I'VE
DONE IS I'M PROTECTING
THE SIMMS FROM THE TYLERS
BECAUSE IF THEY TRY TO
SNEAK UP HERE,
YOU KNOW, ON THE FLANK
OF THE SIMMS, CAN'T HAPPEN
BECAUSE OF THOSE FREDERICKS
DEFENCE PEOPLE.
WHAT ABOUT THE
RICHARDSONS, YOU ASK?
I TELL YOU.
THEY'RE RIGHT HERE.
AND IF THEY TRY THE OLD
QUARTERBACK SNEAK PLAY,
WHAT WE DO IS WE
REVERSE OUR OFFENSIVE,
WE MEET DOWN HERE
AT THE MAILBOX
RIGHT DOWNTOWN RIGHT THERE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU CAN JUST
FEEL THE LOVE IN THE
COMMUNITY, CAN'T YOU?
A LOT OF PEOPLE AROUND
POSSUM LAKE THINK THIS
GROUP PHOTO THING
IS A TOTAL WASTE
OF TIME AND MONEY.
SO I THOUGHT WE'D TALK
TO WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE
TO GET SOME OF
THE ENTREPRENEURIAL
ANGLES ON THE PROJECT.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I GOT A
SUGGESTION JUST OFF THE
TOP OF MY HEAD, EH,
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
THE PHOTO, LAMINATE IT
AND MAKE PLACEMATS
OUT OF IT,
YOU KNOW,
LIKE FOR TABLES.
I DON'T KNOW,
WINSTON.
I THINK AN AERIAL SHOT OF
POSSUM LAKE
IS GOING TO MAKE
IT HARD ON DIGESTION.
AND MAYBE TOUGH TO CLEAN.
HOW DO YOU TELL THE
LAKE FROM THE STAIN?
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT
MY BUSINESS GURU
AND SUCCESS MENTOR
ANTHONY ANTHONY
SAYS, EH?
YOU GOT TO SEIZE EVERY
OPPORTUNITY, YOU KNOW,
AND INCREASE BUSINESS.
WELL, ALL RIGHT,
FINE, WELL, TELL EVERYBODY
HOW YOU'RE GOING TO USE
THE TOWN PHOTO OPPORTUNITY
TO INCREASE
YOUR BUSINESS THEN.
WELL, LIKE A LOT OF
FOLKS OWES ME MONEY,
RIGHT?
DINGER LOMBIE
OWES ME 50 BUCKS
FROM A JOB I DONE
FOR HIM LAST SPRING,
AND WELL THE KEELYS
STILL HAVEN'T PAID UP
FROM LAST MONTH.
OH, AND THERE'S THIS BIG
JOB FOR THE ST. GERMANES
THAT I DONE.
I RESCUED A REAL
EXPENSIVE PIECE OF
JEWELLERY FOR THEM.
I MEAN, HOW HUNGOVER
DO YOU HAVE TO BE
TO RALPH YOUR
NECKLACE RIGHT OFF?
WELL, I STILL
DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU'RE GOING TO GET
THE PEOPLE TO PAY UP,
WINSTON.
OH, IT'S SIMPLE,
I'M GOING TO GO
TO THE PHOTO.
DRESSED UP IN MY
WORK CLOTHES, RIGHT,
AND WHEN I SEE SOMEBODY
WHO OWES ME MONEY,
I'M JUST GOING TO GO
OVER THERE AND STAND
NEXT TO THEM.
HO HO HO.
EXACTLY.
AND WHEN THEY PAY UP,
I'M GOING TO GO OVER
TO MY NEXT OUTSTANDING
ACCOUNT, EH.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE
HOW FAST THESE FOLKS
ARE GOING TO COUGH
UP THE CASH.
YEAH, I'M GUESSING YOU'LL
GET PAID IN FULL, HUH?
OH, I MIGHT EVEN DO
BETTER THAN THAT, EH?
PEOPLE DON'T COUNT
MONEY TOO GOOD
WHEN THEIR EYES
ARE WATERING, EH?
AND WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW,
WHERE CLAIMING TO BE AN
EXPERT THIS WEEK WITH
MY UNCLE RED
IS MR. DALTON HUMPHREY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, HERE'S A LETTER,
AND IT'S FROM A VIEWER
IN TRURO, NOVA SCOTIA.
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"HOW CAN I MAKE SURE I HAVE
ENOUGH MONEY SET ASIDE
FOR RETIREMENT?"
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT I'M DOING.
I'M GOING TO
RETIRE AT 65,
SO I'M JUST PUTTING ENOUGH
MONEY AWAY TO LAST ME.
I'M GOING TO BE FINE
AS LONG AS I DIE AT 67.
WELL, MAYBE JUST
NEVER RETIRE,
YEAH, BECAUSE WHAT YOU DO
IS YOU PICK A JOB
WHERE THERE'S NO MANDATORY
RETIREMENT AGE,
YOU KNOW, LIKE, SAY,
A POLITICIAN.
OR A CAR THIEF.
YOU GOT TO SAVE
FOR A RAINY DAY.
YEAH. SURE.
MAYBE THAT'S
A BETTER ROUTE.
YEAH. OKAY.
YOU GOT TO SAVE,
MAKE SACRIFICE,
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE PEOPLE
WANT EVERYTHING.
THEY WANT FOOD AND
THEY WANT SHELTER
AND THEY WANT CLOTHING.
YOU KNOW, THE THING
YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER IS
WHAT MY OLD MAN SAID,
HE SAID, YOU KNOW,
YOU GOT TO TAKE YOUR INCOME,
SET SOME ASIDE,
SOME YOU LIVE ON.
THEN YOU SAVE A
CERTAIN PERCENTAGE.
I KEEP IT TO AROUND
10 PERCENT.
WELL, NOT EVERYBODY CAN
SAVE 10 PERCENT, DALTON.
TO LIVE ON.
YOU SAVE 90 PERCENT
OF YOUR INCOME?
WELL, SURE, YOU KNOW,
YOU HAVE TO GIVE UP
A FEW LUXURIES,
LIKE TOOTHPASTE OR
SOCKS OR STUFF
LIKE THAT.
MY DAUGHTER
SPENDS A BIT.
$400 FOR A BLOUSE.
$400 FOR A BLOUSE
FOR MY DAUGHTER.
YOU HAVE A DAUGHTER?
I DON'T EVEN
HAVE $400.
WELL, WE ALL SHOWED UP
FOR THE AERIAL PHOTO
JUST AS PLANNED,
BUT IT DIDN'T GO QUITE
AS WELL AS WE HOPED
THAT IT WOULD.
WELL, YOU COULDN'T HAVE
ASKED FOR A BETTER DAY.
WE COULD HAVE PUSHED
FOR A BETTER PILOT,
I THINK.
BUZZ'S PLANE IS NOT
REALLY EQUIPPED TO FLY
WITH ALL THAT AERIAL
PHOTOGRAPH EQUIPMENT.
BUZZ'S PLANE REALLY ISN'T
EQUIPPED TO FLY PERIOD.
THAT'S VERY TRUE.
SO HE BORROWED A PLANE
FROM RANGER GORD,
ONE OF THEM WATER
DIVE BOMBERS.
WE'RE ALL STANDING THERE
SQUINTING UP AT THE
SUN SMILING,
BUZZ COMES OVER,
PULLS THE WRONG LEVER
AND SOAKS US WITH
1,200 GALLONS OF WATER.
YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T REALLY
MIND GETTING WET SO MUCH,
IT WAS JUST THAT RED CHEMICAL
THEY ADDED TO THE WATER,
IT REALLY ITCHES.
IT'S FIRE RETARDANT.
YEAH, WE DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT
SPONTANEOUS HUMAN
COMBUSTION ANYWAY.
THAT WAS THE BAD NEWS,
THE WORST NEWS IS
BUZZ HAD HIS FINGER
OVER THE LENS,
A COMPLETE
WASTE OF TIME.
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
DID YOU NOT
SEE THE PHOTO?
IT'S COOL.
IT LOOKS GREAT.
THERE'S LIKE 1,000
ANGRY, SCREAMING PEOPLE,
YOU KNOW, ALL COVERED
IN RED LIQUID, RUNNING
HELTER SKELTER,
BIG PINK FINGER
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE.
IT DOES KIND OF
CAPTURE THE SPIRIT
OF POSSUM LODGE.
YOU KNOW, I FIGURE WHAT WE
CAN DO IS SELL THE PICTURE
TO ONE OF THOSE
TABLOID NEWSPAPERS,
"GIANT DIGIT
ATTACKS TOWNSFOLKS,
"BLEEDS ON
PETRIFIED POPULOUS."
THEY PAY BIG BUCKS
FOR PICTURES LIKE THAT,
YOU KNOW, STRANGE MUTANTS
AND ALIENS AND ELVIS.
WELL, I GUESS YOUR
FAMILY ALBUM MUST BE
WORTH A FORTUNE, HUH?
OH NO, UNCLE RED,
I DON'T HAVE THAT
MANY PICTURES OF YOU.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I WILL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING,
I'M BRINGING YOU A
LITTLE ANNIVERSARY GIFT.
I GOT YOU THAT SPINCAST
FISHING REEL
I'VE HAD MY EYE ON
FOR A MONTH OR SO.
I KNOW HOW MUCH
YOU LIKE NICE THINGS.
THIS ONE IS A REAL BEAUTY.
I TELL YOU WHAT,
YOU WOULDN'T BE EMBARRASSED
TO LEND THIS TO ANYONE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND CAPTAIN HAROLD-LINER,
UNTIL NEXT TIME,
KEEP WATCHING
AND KEEP YOUR
STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.