For those of you who
went to private school,
this is called
an exhaust manifold.
This is called a wrench.
And what I'm doing
here is called work.
See, I'm trying to increase
the horsepower of this engine
and the best way to do that
is to allow the exhaust
to flow more easily
out of the engine.
Regardless of what
your grandfather said,
exhaust flowing more
easily is no joke.
See, the problem is the
exhaust from each cylinder
gets funneled into
this bottleneck,
which restricts the flow.
You older guys know
what I'm talking about.
Now, a lot of guys
go with bigger pipes,
maybe even use one
for each cylinder.
These are called headers.
Not like the header you took
down the basement stairs...
nobody laughs
at these ones.
But I'm thinking,
if size matters...
why stop at pipes?
Why not go up to something
that's way bigger
and used to
handling hot gases?
No, not your grandfather.
That's right,
furnace ducts.
Is it just me or is this not
one of the sharper vehicles
you're likely to see
in your lifetime.
That's what happens when you
get all your ducts in a row.
And talk about performance,
I figure I've raised the
horsepower by around
35,000 BTUs.
Please allow me
to demonstrate...
The heat is on.
[ INAUDIBLE/
ENGINE ROARING ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
All right.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
No, no, I appreciate that.
Big, big week up at
the lodge this week.
Somebody's trying to put
Old Man Sedgwick into a home.
Not their home, nobody
wants him in their home.
I'm against locking up
old guys in homes, you know.
I used to be all for it
but that was back in the day
when it was me against them.
Now I am them.
Oh, Uncle Red.
Uncle Red.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I got this book for
Old Man Sedgwick
and I was hoping maybe
you could drop it at
Shady Acres for him.
It's called, "How to
tell you're having a
medical emergency."
Well, I'll just
file this over
in that area.
Now, see, Harold,
first of all,
Old Man Sedgwick
only likes books from
World War I.
They've got to
have big pictures
and a 36-point font.
And secondly, more
importantly,
he's not going to
Shady Acres, Harold.
If he belongs anywhere
it would be Belly Acres.
But he's not
going to a home.
Oh, yes, he is.
No.
Yeah, I was talking
to his his son
and he said he was going.
And he said it like,
"Oh, he's going!"
So...
Well, that's not right.
How old is he anyway?
He's well
into his 90s.
Well, so what?
Lots of people in their 90s
are living on their own.
Oh no, no, I was
talking about the son.
No, no,
Old Man Sedgwick,
I don't know,
he's -- he's --
He's older than any recorded
history, I don't know.
I don't know how
you could even consider
putting Old Man
Sedgwick into a home.
Well, it's better than
leaving him up there
in that shack
with 4,000 magazines
and a space heater.
You know he
talks to his lamp?
Yeah, well that's because
they're both on a dimmer.
Well, thank goodness his
son doesn't feel that way
because he's putting
him into a home.
I didn't even know
his son could do that.
Oh yeah,
oh yeah, oh yeah!
Any relative can
with just cause.
You know, there
are days when I think
you should go
into a home.
Well, there are days
when I'd gladly go.
Well, seriously,
though, Uncle Red,
if you ever went into
a home I would visit
you every day.
Well, thank you,
Harold,
but that would kind of
defeat the purpose.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Today's winner
receives this coupon
for 300 board feet
of lumber
from the Mercury
Creek Lumber Yard.
Every piece of lumber is a
maximum length of two inches
because at Mercury Creek
Lumber, we saw it first.
Okay, Edgar,
cover your ears.
Oh, never mind.
Okay, Mr. Green,
you've got 30 seconds
to get local explosives
enthusiast, Edgar Montrose,
to say this word...
Okay, Mike.
And Go!
Okay Edgar, you're
going to give advice
to a young person
choosing their career.
You'd say, find your...
First-aid kit.
No, okay, okay, no.
You don't just enjoy
blowing things up,
you have a
something for it.
A permit?
Oh really?
since when?
Uhh... tomorrow.
No, I know.
This is an exotic fruit.
Red, I think the
politically correct term
is "alternate lifestyle."
No, okay, okay.
No, no, no.
Okay, if there are two people
that have a very strong
physical attraction,
they have a lot of...
Laundry.
You're almost out
of time, Mr. Green.
Okay, okay, okay.
Edgar, two people having
a hot love affair,
this is something
they share...
D-N-A.
No, Edgar.
What do you need
to make you happy?
A vacant building,
25 pounds of dynamite
and a noise-abatement
officer with a little...
compassion.
Yes sir!
RED: How come you're
not fishing, Harold?
I ran the numbers of
the of the local
fish population
feeding patterns
into my laptop.
The resultant probability
model made it quite clear
that fishing in this lake
is not an effective
use of my time.
So what?
Spending an
afternoon with you
is not an effective
use of my time, either.
DALTON: What's that you're
reading there, Harold?
Is that a book?
Why, yes, it is.
Yes, it's a book.
Since there's no
fish in the lake,
I thought I'd
expand my mind.
Why? You're already
a fat head.
[ RED AND DALTON
CHUCKLE ]
HAROLD: You know laughing at
that doesn't make it funny.
Just like forcing
your opinion on somebody
doesn't make
it smart.
Harold, have you been
watching PBS again?
You guys are living
in the past.
It's like you're
living in the '50s.
DALTON:
I like the '50s.
HAROLD: As a time era
it's fine,
but as a way of life
it's holding you back.
DALTON:
I like being held back.
Well, you're the past,
I'm the future.
No wonder I find it
so hard to get up
in the morning.
You don't get
it do you?
This book predicts
that science will
create a computer
that thinks faster
and clearer than man.
No, get out of here.
Come on.
Yes, yes it is!
We're on the cutting edge
of a brave new world.
DALTON: If computers
are so smart,
why hasn't science
discovered the cure
for the common cold?
RED:
That's a good question.
No, that doesn't
even make sense.
That's like saying well
because a balloon holds air,
how come we can't turn right
on a red light in Quebec?
Okay, all right.
I don't know what
I was thinking.
Obviously, artificial
intelligence is no match
for natural stupidity.
'Cause there is no way a
computer is ever going
to be able to tell
guys like us what to do!
RED: That's right.
That's our wives' job.
I've never
been in a war,
which is probably why
we've always won,
but I sure like the
military equipment.
Like these cannons on wheels
that you roll up to the target
and then aim and then blow
something to smithereens.
Kind of like mass
destruction to go.
So today on
Handyman Corner,
we're going to build
a fun home version
of that powerful weapon.
I'm going to use this piece
of drain pipe as my gun barrel
and instead of
mortar shells
we'll be
firing off muffins.
If you're like me, you
probably have a wife
that doesn't
want you to die
and you know how
annoying that can be.
She's always watching
your weight
and pushing you to exercise
and eat multi-grain muffins
instead of
cream-filled doughnuts
and high-fibre muffins
aren't that easy to hide.
Oh sure, you could
feed them to the dog
but as soon as your
wife sees the backyard,
she'll know what
you've been up to.
The safest method,
as always
is to just blow them
to kingdom come.
This car is going to be
the mount for my muffin gun.
I've just got to take her
down to Flinty's
and get the front
fenders cut off.
I needed a sight for my gun
so I just used the hood
ornament.
Some ornaments make better
sights than others,
Lincoln and
Mercedes are good
or you could use one of
those Pontiac Aztecs,
the whole car's a sight.
Now, obviously,
to fire the gun
I'm going to use the
master cylinder
from the car's
power brake system.
See, ordinarily when you
stomp on the brake pedal,
this small piston shoots
forward with a lot of juice
and slams on the brakes.
So I'm just going to
biggie-size the piston
with a hockey puck.
You can buy these at one of
those specialty shops
like Pucks 'r' Us
or the Puckatorium
or Puck Depot, Puckers
or Just Pucks
or Pucks 'n' Such.
They got a lot cheaper
during the strike.
Now, when I fire off a muffin,
it won't just be a shot,
it'll be a slapshot.
Okay, got my gun
mounted on the wheel
so I can adjust the
up and down angle
by just edging the
car forward or back
and I can adjust the
side to side angle
by just turning
the steering wheel.
Now all I need is my
automatic muffin motor
and I'm good to go.
Where would we be
without eavestroughs?
Vermont.
Okay, the trick to
the muffin feeder
is to mount the hockey stick/
pushrod/ammo magazine --
hey, wait a minute, that's
two minutes for slashing --
onto the outside wall
of the other front tire
but at a spot
that's 90 degrees
from where the
gun is mounted.
That way when one goes
down the other comes up
like stocks and bonds
or pants and skirts.
And it's just that easy.
Remember, if the women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
This isn't
a healthy diet,
this is war.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
It would've ended up
there anyway.
I want to talk to
you older guys
who arrived at
that point in life
where your income should more
than cover your expenses.
[ LAUGHING ]
Not even close, is it?
Now you have
a choice to make.
Either you work up
the courage to demand
the raise you deserve
or, and this
is more likely,
you win the lottery.
But no matter what you do,
you will always
want more money.
Money is like food.
You can never
have enough.
Actually, it is possible
to have enough food
so money is
more like beer...
or cars...
When I had that
20-year-old Studebaker,
I wanted a
15-year-old Rambler.
When I got the Rambler
I wanted a van.
When I got the van
I wanted an import
or at least a van
that didn't catch fire.
So my advice is instead
of focussing on your
need for more money,
enjoy what you have and
spend it with confidence
on things you want
like, for example,
my book,
which is available at fine
bookstores everywhere.
Remember,
I pulling for you.
We're all
in this together.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Seeing tonight's dinner
steaming in the centre
of your dining room
table is a Kodak moment.
Seeing last week's dinner
steaming in the centre
of your back yard
is a Rothschild's moment.
Looks like
Old Man Sedgwick
won't be going into
Shady Acres after all.
I don't want to go
into the details
but let's just say
that somebody went down,
met with the head nurse
and straightened the
whole thing out.
You know, it's always best
when you just have a quiet
word with people.
Uncle Red?
Yep?
Can I have a quiet
word with you?
Nope.
Well it seems somebody went
down to Shady Acres Rest Home
and said that Old Man Sedgwick
was an unfit resident.
Why did you do that?
Well, he needed somebody
to stick up for him.
Well, what we got was
somebody to stick
it to him.
Uncle Red, he wants
to go to Shady Acres.
Wants to?
Where'd you
hear that one?
From him.
I talked to him.
Did you?
Well, no.
when you try
to talk to him,
you can't get a
word in edgewise.
He goes on and on and on
about everything that's
bothering him
which I don't
want to hear
and then he gets into
this whole other thing
about some car
he had 40 years ago
and that's what
old people are like.
You know that and this is why
he shouldn't be in a home
and why would he want
to be in a home anyway?
Because he's smart!
What?
He's got friends there.
He'll have a life there.
And if there is a problem
he'll have people to
take care of him.
No, Harold, there's got
to be another way.
Well, you could
take care of him.
You know, if he's that
keen on going, you know...
I don't think
I should interfere.
Well, he can't go now
because you did interfere.
You told them that he was
a sleepwalker, a pyromaniac
and a potential murderer?
I may have oversold it.
Uncle Red, you have to go
down to Shady Acres right now
and make this right.
Okay, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
Oh yeah, how?
I'll just tell them I made
a stupid mistake, okay?
Okay, well, I'll
go with you
'cause if you're going
to show them you're an
idiot, I got proof.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Winston and Bill are going
to have a little day
on the beach.
They took some backpacks
and are just going
to enjoy the day.
Bill decided that this
was a good spot
so he dropped --
He took out
some suntan lotion.
It was a high UV that
day and whoa...
You know you want to keep
your knife in another bag
I think, Bill.
And Winston
took his Frisbee --
oh, that's unfortunate.
And Bill doesn't have
the sense of humour
he used to have.
He just fires it
and away she goes.
It picked an
updraft or whatever
and goes all the way
across the lake.
And Bill finds that very funny
but Winston's out of Frisbees
says maybe Bill
should go across
but Bill says why should I
bother, I don't care
about a Frisbee.
So Winston's thinking you need
something to care about
so how about
your backpack?
There we go.
So now he wants Winston to
go across and Winston
says you go
and Winston says why
don't we both go across.
Okay, so Bill
takes off --
He's either dancing or
removing his shoes
and he got his shoes
and socks off
but the water was just
a little cooler than
what Bill expected.
Nope, got to
rethink that.
So then Winston's
got an idea.
He's got something
in his bag.
That's a teddy bear,
Winston.
Oh yeah, this is one of
those self-inflating rafts
so you've got to be
careful with those.
You've got to stop it.
When it gets full, Bill,
you've got to stop it.
Bill!
Okay, now, here's a
little safety message
for any of you
kids with an axe...
About an hour later,
Winston realized that Bill
was actually making stilts.
So he got
Winston up there
and this looks like
trouble to me.
Neither of these guys is
too familiar with the
concept of gravity.
So then they decide
maybe a picnic table
will give them
a little more leverage.
Winston needs Bill to
push him off and then
Bill loses his balance and ends
up jumping right on Winston.
So now, you've got
a passenger
and they're heading
towards the water.
Winston comes right up
to it and decides
he's going to take
a big step to go in.
He raises then hits
Bill right in the face
and it was unfortunate
the way this happened
and then he was
out of balance
and then Winston
falls right --
Oh...
Boy, he thought it was
a pole vaulting exhibition.
But just when they're
about to give up,
along comes
the park ranger
and wouldn't you know it,
he's got everything in there.
There's the backpack.
There's your Frisbee.
There you go, oh!
And there's your backpack.
Everybody's happy.
If a man's home
is his castle
then his back yard is
his trophy room.
It's really a shrine
to a lifetime of tinkering.
Unfortunately, your wife
may not see it that way
or any other way.
In fact, she doesn't want
to see it at all.
As I always say, out
of sight, out of mind
which doesn't mean that
if you need glasses
you're half crazy.
What it does mean that what
your wife doesn't know
won't hurt you.
So I mounted my tarp onto
the rim of my basketball hoop.
Got the whole thing mounted
over the barbeque.
Now, all I have to do
is fire up the grill
and we have ourselves our own
disappearing trophy pile.
Now you just tie off
your tether line and voila,
no crap for your wife to
look at in the back yard.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I had everything under
control, Harold.
I don't think your
comments were appreciated.
Oh, they were appreciated.
They were essential.
Okay, so we go down
to Shady Acres there
and I tell them there's
been a misunderstanding
about Old Man Sedgwick,
that his deficiencies were
a little exaggerated,
you know.
Heck, I even put in
a good word for him.
You said he was the greatest
man that ever lived.
Not ten seconds after
admitting that you had lied
about him being a
murderous pyromaniac.
Don't you find
that incredible?
Harold, you
and I are related,
I find that
incredible.
I'm not the
bad guy here.
I'm not the one who's banned
from Shady Acres for life.
Well, I'm glad
I'm banned.
That means you'll never
be able to stick
me in there.
Well, you handled it poorly.
That's all I'm saying.
Is Old Man Sedgwick
in Shady Acres now?
Yes, but only because I
brought in a complete
application form,
his medical records
and convincing letters
from both him
and his son.
And what did I bring
to the meeting, Harold?
Guilty admissions,
some pathetic pleading
and a few veiled threats.
Really, that's...
No, no, no.
I brought
you, Harold.
You were my
ace in the hole.
Well, thank you.
You're very welcome.
That's the first time
you've ever called me
an ace in the hole.
I've called you
something similar.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Meeting time.
Yeah, you
go ahead, ace.
I'll be down in the
hole in a minute.
Okay.
Okay, if my wife
is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting
and I learned today
that Shady Acres
has refused me
as a resident
so it looks like you're going
to have to take care of me
and I was hoping you could
start practising tonight.
Don't forget, I'm only
as old as you feel.
And to the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of
myself and Ace
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge,
keep your stick
on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Come on in.
Guys!
Sit down.
C'mon, everybody sit down.
Guys, sit down.
All rise.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
Sit down.
All right, bow your heads
for the man's prayer.
I'm a man
but I can change
if I have to
I guess.
All right men, as you know
Old Man Sedgwick
is now living at the
Shady Acres Rest Home
and he wanted
me to tell you
that he appreciates you guys
coming over and visiting.
But he's starting to notice
it's always at mealtime
and the cleaning staff
sent back the gift
basket of prunes
because they
said his bed
is just too far
from the restroom.