ONE OF THE KEY DIFFERENCES
BETWEEN MEN AND WOMEN
IS THEIR PERCEPTION
OF REALITY.
WOMEN LIKE REALITY.
MEN PREFER FAKE THINGS...
CUBIC ZIRCONIUM,
FUN FUR,
PADDED BRAS.
THE FAKE AND ARTIFICIAL
DRAWS MEN LIKE A MAGNET.
I WAS SITTING WITH TWO
GUYS AROUND THE CAMPFIRE
THE OTHER NIGHT AND THEY
WERE TALKING ABOUT
THESE NEW ARTIFICIAL
FIREPLACE LOGS
WITH THE GREEN AND BLUE FLAME
AND HOW FANTASTIC THEY ARE.
YOU SEE, TO MEN
BEING REAL IS EASY.
LOOKING REAL IS
A LOT MORE SPECIAL.
IT'S NOT
SMART OR CORRECT
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT MAKES
US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red Green:
ON TODAY'S SHOW,
DOUGIE FRANKLIN IS GOING
TO TELL ALL YOU GUYS
HOW TO AVOID GOING
TO CHURCH ON SUNDAY,
BILL AND I ARE GOING
TO PLAY CROQUET IF I WIN,
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO MAKE FURNITURE
OUT OF LEAVES
AND UNFORTUNATELY MIKE
BOUGHT A LITTLE TOO
MUCH LUMBER.
AND NOW HERE IS THE MAN
WHO KNOWS ONE END OF
THE HAMMER FROM THE OTHER,
THOUGH HE'S QUITE
HANDY WITH BOTH,
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
AND PLEASE PUT
YOUR HANDS TOGETHER,
PREFERABLY ONE ON EACH
SIDE OF HIS HEAD,
FOR MY NEPHEW, HAROLD.
REAL COLOURFUL WEEK UP AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK,
JUNIOR SINGLETON HAD
ABOUT 200 CANS OF PAINT
EXPLODE OUT OF
HIS PAINT SHOP.
IT SAYS RIGHT ON THE CAN,
DO NOT STORE NEAR HEAT.
YOU THINK HE'D KNOW BETTER
THAN TRY TO PROP UP A
STOVE WITH THEM.
YEAH, BUT JUNIOR IS NOT A
GREAT LOVER OF LITERATURE.
THE ONLY THING HE'S READ
COVER TO COVER IS A MATCHBOOK.
WELL, I BET HE DOES NOW
'CAUSE BOY WHEN THAT SHED BLEW,
THERE WAS PAINT EVERYWHERE,
ALL OVER EVERYTHING.
IT LOOKED LIKE ONE
OF THOSE PSYCHEDELIC
POSTERS FROM THE '60s.
YEAH, I THOUGHT SOMEBODY
HAD BLOWN UP THE SMURFS.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU, DID
YOU SEE THAT PINE TREE
OUT IN THE LANE THERE,
KIND OF A FROSTY PINK?
NICE LOOKING.
LOOKED GOOD.
THERE IS A LOVELY TURQUOISE
OAK IN THE LANEWAY,
THAT'S MY FAVOURITE.
ALTHOUGH THERE'S ALSO
A SLATE METAL CHERRY
RED ELM.
VERY NICE.
WELL UP AT THE LODGE WE
LIKE TO TURN ADVERSITY
INTO PERVERSITY,
SO WHAT WE'RE GOING
TO DO NOW IS PAINT
EVERY TREE
IN THE FOREST
OR I SHOULD SAY AT
LEAST THE LEAVES
AND THAT WAY
WE'LL GET AUTUMN COMING
EARLIER AND ALL THE
TOURISTS WILL COME
UP TO OUR PLACE FIRST
TO SEE THE FALL COLOURS.
TOMORROW IS THE FIRST
DAY OF THE END
OF YOUR LIFE.
OH, DON'T MIND THE FLIES,
JUST CLOSE YOUR EYES
YOU'LL BE IN AND OUT
TOUTE DE SUITE
TO FIND WHERE STUFF
GOES, JUST FOLLOW YOUR NOSE
THERE'S A HOLE AT
THE END OF THE SEAT
NO NEED TO FLUSH,
THERE'S NOTHING TO FLUSH
GRAVITY FEEDS
STRAIGHT TO HELL
BUT JUST BE SURE TO
DOUBLE CHECK THE BROCHURE
BECAUSE THIS
IS DEFINITELY NOT
A FIVE-STAR HOTEL
OKAY, YOU'VE JUST DROPPED
THE WIFE AND THE KIDS
OFF AT SUNDAY SCHOOL
AND THE WIFE TURNS
TO YOU AND SAYS,
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU COME
INTO THE CHURCH WITH US?
AND YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO COME UP
WITH AN EXCUSE.
AMEN. AMEN.
AND IT'S GOING TO
HAVE TO BE A HUMMER,
ONE THAT WORKS THAT ALSO
DOESN'T OFFEND YOUR WIFE.
TALL ORDER THERE.
RIGHT ON.
NOW, HERE'S ONE
I USE ALL THE TIME.
NO, HONEY, WHENEVER THE
MINISTER STARTS TO WAX
ELOQUENT ABOUT SIN,
IT JUST PLANTS BAD
IDEAS IN MY HEAD
THAT WEREN'T THERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
OR YOU COULD
THREATEN TO SING.
THAT WORKS
AROUND MY HOUSE.
OR THERE'S THIS,
THIS IS GREAT,
JUST BAMBOOZLE
THEM WITH SCRIPTURES.
SOMETHING TO THE
EFFECT OF,
HONEY, ROMANS 8:4...
YEA, VERILY,
IT CAME TO PASS,
THE WOMEN AND CHILDREN
SOUGHT REFUGE IN
THE TEMPLE
WHILE THE MEN WENT FORTH
TO HOSE DOWN THEIR
VEHICLES.
YOU KNOW, NO MATTER HOW MUCH
PAINT WE PUT ON THE LEAVES
AROUND POSSUM LODGE,
THEY'RE ALL GOING TO FALL
OUT OF THE TREES ANYWAY
'CAUSE THAT'S ALL PART OF
MOTHER NATURE'S PLAN,
AND WE KNOW HOW
IRRITATING SHE CAN BE.
SO I THOUGHT I WOULD TAKE
HANDYMAN CORNER HER
AND SHOW YOU HOW
YOU CAN SAY GOOD-BYE TO THAT
ROTTEN PILE OF MOLDY LEAVES
AND HELLO BRAND NEW
LIVING ROOM COUCH.
ALL RIGHT, FIRST THING
WE'RE GOING TO NEED IS
A COUPLE OF TABLE --
WHERE THE HECK DID --
DARN LEAVES, MUST HAVE --
PILED IN HERE.
NO.
DARN KIDS.
HERE WE GO.
ONE.
THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT, SO YOU NEED A
COUPLE OF THESE VINYL
TABLE CLOTHES,
WHICH YOU CAN PICK UP AT A
CHURCH PICNIC DURING
THE CLOSING PRAYERS
WHILE EVERYBODY
HAS THEIR EYES SHUT.
OKAY, AND YOU PUT
ONE DOWN ON THERE,
AND YOU PUT THE OTHER ONE,
LIE IT RIGHT DOWN
RIGHT ON TOP.
THAT HAPPENS
A LOT OF PICNICS.
AND THEN YOU WANT TO SEAL UP
THREE OF THE SIDES.
YOU CAN USE A GLUE GUN FOR
THAT OR A SOLDERING IRON,
OR YOU COULD CRIMP
EAVESTROUGHING ALONG THERE.
BUT I PREFER TO USE THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
YOU WANT TO REALLY LAY THE
DUCT TAPE ON THERE
BECAUSE THIS COUCH IS GOING TO
HAVE TO WITHSTAND THOUSANDS
OF POUNDS OF PRESSURE,
ESPECIALLY DURING
THE PLAYOFFS.
ALL RIGHT,
NOW ALL YOU GOT TO DO
IS RAKE UP THE LEAVES OFF
YOUR FRONT LAWN AND
YOUR BACK LAWN
AND START STUFFING
THEM IN THERE.
NOW, IF YOU HAVE
A DOG OR SOMETHING,
YOU MAY WANT TO SIFT THROUGH
THE LEAVES TO AVOID
ANY SURPRISES.
OR I SUPPOSE YOU CAN
WEAR A PAIR OF GLOVES
OR SOMETHING.
HOPE THAT
WAS A PINE CONE.
AND THERE WE ARE,
A COMFY LEAF COUCH.
A COUPLE LITTLE THROW
CUSHIONS FOR ACCENT PIECES.
AND HOW ABOUT A VERY
ATTRACTIVE LEAF FOOTSTOOL?
AND THE BEAUTY OF THIS IS
IN 5 MONTHS IT WILL BE SPRING
AND ALL YOUR FURNITURE
WILL BE FULL OF COMPOST,
SO NOW YOU CAN START GROWING
REAL POTATOES INSTEAD OF
JUST COUCH ONES.
SO ENJOY YOUR
LIVING ROOM SET.
AND REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
ANOTHER BONUS IS WHEN YOU
WANT TO LIE ON THE COUCH,
YOU CAN BE A KID AGAIN
AND JUMP IN THE LEAVES.
Red: STAY TUNED
AS BILL AND I HAVE A
GAME OF FULL CONTACT CROQUET,
AND RANGER GORD TELLS US
EVERYTHING HE KNOWS
ABOUT THE FOREST,
IT ONLY TAKES
A MINUTE.
I WANT TO TALK TO
YOU MIDDLE-AGED GUYS
ABOUT JOB SECURITY.
I'VE HAD A FEW JOBS MYSELF
OVER THE YEARS,
AND I KNOW THE PINK SLIP
WARNING SIGNS.
OKAY, FIRST OF ALL...
TAKE A DAY OFF WORK
AND NOBODY NOTICES.
THAT'S A BAD SIGN, OKAY?
OR YOUR BOSS KEEPS BRINGING
NEW EMPLOYEES INTO YOUR OFFICE
AND SAYING,
"WHAT ABOUT HERE?"
OR YOU GO ON HOLIDAYS
FOR A WEEK
AND THEY REPLACE YOU
WITH A 12-YEAR-OLD KID
WHO DOESN'T SPEAK ENGLISH.
AND THEN WHEN
YOU COME BACK
THEY HAVE A GOING AWAY PARTY
FOR HIM AND EVERYBODY CRIES
AND THE BOSS TAKES DOWN
HIS HOME PHONE NUMBER.
BAD SIGN.
SO IF THIS SOUNDS
FAMILIAR TO YOU,
LUCKILY, THERE ARE A
FEW THINGS YOU CAN DO
TO AVOID THE INEVITABLE.
FIRST ONE, GO OUT RIGHT NOW
AND MARRY SOMEBODY WHO
HAS A JOB.
NEXT THING YOU CAN DO IS
GET ON A FIRST-NAME BASIS
WITH EVERYBODY DOWN AT
THE UNEMPLOYMENT OFFICE.
AND THE THIRD ONE,
MOST IMPORTANT,
DON'T GET
DOWN ON YOURSELF.
TRY TO LOOK AT THE BRIGHT
SIDE OF BEING UNEMPLOYED.
FOR ONE THING,
YOUR TIME IS YOUR OWN, HUH?
NO TRAFFIC PROBLEMS.
YOU WAKE UP IN THE
MORNING, YOU'RE THERE!
I KNOW WHEN I WAS
OUT OF WORK
FROM EARLY JUNE 1982
TO LATE AUGUST... 1989,
I NEVER GOT
DOWN ON MYSELF.
I FIGURED, YOU KNOW, THERE'S
A LOT OF GUYS OUT THERE
MAKING A LOT OF MONEY DOING
SOMETHING THEY HATE: WORK.
WHEREAS HERE
AM I MAKING ZIP
DOING SOMETHING
I LOVE: NOTHING.
SO REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU
BECAUSE WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, THIS IDEA OF PAINTING
ALL THE LEAVES TO BRING
AUTUMN HERE EARLY
HAS GONE OVER THE DAM
IN A BIG WAY.
EVERYBODY IS
PRETTY DARNED EXCITED
ABOUT HAVING THE SEASONS
CHANGING THAT MUCH SOONER.
ESPECIALLY
MOOSE THOMPSON NOW
BECAUSE HIS BOSS TOLD HIM
HE COULD HAVE TWO WEEKS
OFF THIS FALL.
NOW HE GETS TO TAKE THEM WHILE
HE'S STILL GOT THE GOOD
SUMMER WEATHER.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK,
HE LIKES THE IDEA
BECAUSE HE SAYS NOW HE CAN
BRING HIS DOCK IN
WHILE THE WATER
IS STILL WARM.
YEAH, THE ONLY
REAL DOWN SIDE IS
NOW WE'RE HUNTING WHEN
THERE'S MOSQUITOES AND
BLACK FLIES OUT,
SO WE'RE GOING TO DELAY THE
HUNTING SEASON CLOSER
TO CHRISTMAS,
WHICH IS GOING TO
BE IN OCTOBER,
AND EASTER WILL
FALL IN DECEMBER
AND THEN NEXT SUMMER
IS GOING TO START IN FEBRUARY,
WHICH IS GOING TO SAVE
EVERYBODY A TON OF MONEY
IN AIR CONDITIONING.
UNCLE RED, I HOPE YOU'RE
TAKING YOUR TIME
AND CAREFULLY CHOOSING
THESE COLOURS, YOU KNOW.
I GET NERVOUS WHEN PEOPLE
IN PLAID START CHOOSING
COLOUR COORDINATES.
WELL, WE DON'T WANT TO
TAKE A LOT OF TIME
CHOOSING THEM,
SO WE'RE NOT ASKING
THE WOMEN TO HELP.
Audience: OHHHHHHHH!
NOW, WE WERE GOING TO GO
WITH THE GLOSSY,
BUT THAT TAKES
TWO COATS,
SO WE'RE GOING TO GO WITH
THE SATIN FINISH ON THAT.
AND WITH THE SAPLINGS WE'RE
GOING TO GO WITH
THE MULBERRY,
AND THEN EVERY ALTERNATE
LEAF WILL HAVE KIND OF
THE BEIGEY, BROWN, YELLOWY
KIND OF A PUTRID KIND
OF A LOOK HERE
MIXED IN POSSIBLY WITH A
BURGUNDY AND A LIME GREEN.
UNCLE RED, YOU THINK
THIS IDEA OF YOURS
IS GOING TO WORK?
DON'T YOU THINK THAT
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO KNOW
THE TREES ARE JUST PAINTED?
YOU EVER SEEN THE PEOPLE THAT
COME UP AND LOOK AT THE
FALL COLOURS?
THESE ARE
SENIOR CITIZENS.
THE AVERAGE AGE IS
DECEASED, HAROLD.
THEY'RE ABOUT FOUR FEET TALL,
THEY'RE SITTING THERE
IN THE BUS,
THEY CAN HARDLY SEE OVER
THE EDGE OF THE WINDOW THERE,
THEY GOT THE
BIFOCALS HAPPENING,
TINTED GLASS WINDOWS AND THE
FOREST IS GOING BY AT
100 KLICKS AN HOUR.
UNCLE RED, I DON'T THINK
YOU SHOULD TALK LIKE THAT,
YOUR FATHER WILL PROBABLY
BE A PASSENGER IN ONE
OF THOSE BUSES.
NO WAY.
HE'LL BE DRIVING.
Red: WE'RE UP HERE AT
FIRE TOWER 13 WITH RANGER GORD,
A MAN WHO HAS SPENT THE LAST
16 YEARS, DAY AND NIGHT,
UP IN THAT TOWER NOT ABLE
TO HAVE A WIFE,
NOT ABLE TO HAVE
A FAMILY.
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY
IN A WAY HE IS WEDDED
TO THE FOREST.
THAT'S TRUE, RED.
IN FACT WE MADE IT
OFFICIAL LAST WEEK.
HAD A LITTLE CEREMONY
AND EVERYTHING.
HOW DO YOU MEAN,
GORD?
I GOT MARRIED
TO THE FOREST.
MADE IT OFFICIAL.
I MEAN, AFTER 16 YEARS
OF NOT BEING MARRIED,
YOU KNOW,
IT WASN'T FAIR.
YEAH, I ORDERED
A RING AND EVERYTHING.
COST ME TWO
MONTHS' SALARY.
I THINK HE MEANS
TWO MONTHS' SANITY.
ANYWAY, WE'RE ALL PAINTING
LEAVES, AS YOU KNOW,
SO I THOUGHT I'D GET
RANGER GORD TO TEACH US
ALL ABOUT LEAVES THIS WEEK.
I MEAN, I WANTED TO TALK
ABOUT HOW BEARS MATE,
BUT APPARENTLY
RED DIDN'T THINK THAT
WOULD BE A GOOD IDEA.
NO, IT'S NOT A
GOOD IDEA.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK
ABOUT LEAVES, GORD.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT I'M
GOING TO DO WITH ALL
THE BEAR COSTUMES.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK
ABOUT THE LEAVES, GORD.
ALL RIGHT, SO HERE
ARE SOME LEAVES.
HERE IS AN OAK LEAF.
YEAH.
A MAPLE LEAF AND,
OF COURSE,
A BIRCH LEAF.
WHAT SORT OF DIFFERENCES
DO YOU NOTICE,
MR. NO-BEAR-MATING
GREEN?
WELL, THE OAK LEAF IS
CERTAINLY ROUNDER,
AND THE MAPLE LEAF HAS
GOT ALL THE POINTS
GOING THERE
AND THEN THE BIRCH
IS SMALLER WITH THE
SERRATED EDGE ON IT.
SURE.
YEAH.
WHAT ELSE?
WHAT ABOUT
THEIR MOODS?
YEAH.
SEE, THE OAK LEAF
IS HAPPY,
HAPPY AND CONTENTED,
SEE?
AND THE MAPLE LEAF
IS ANGRY,
UPSET ABOUT SOMETHING.
[ GROWLS ]
AND THE BIRCH LEAF
IS TENSE,
HOLDING IT ALL IN.
YEAH.
BUT I MARRIED HER FOR
BETTER OR WORSE.
ALL RIGHT, GORD, WELL,
YOU KNOW, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I APPRECIATE IT.
BUT THE GUYS ARE PAINTING,
AND I REALLY SHOULD GO
HELP THEM, YOU KNOW.
OKAY.
AND MAKE SURE YOU USE
A LATEX PAINT
BECAUSE SOME OF THE OIL
BASED PAINTS HAVE FUMES
THAT COULD DAMAGE
THE BRAIN.
NO KIDDING.
IT'S MAIL CALL.
OKAY, BOB FROM
CALEDONIA WRITES...
"HOW CAN YOU FIGURE
OUT WHETHER A WOMAN
"FINDS YOU HANDSOME
OR JUST HANDY?"
THAT'S A
GOOD QUESTION
BECAUSE THERE'S NOTHING WORSE
THAN THINKING SHE SAID,
YOU KNOW, COME ON UP
FOR A NICE LIGHT DINNER
WHEN SHE ACTUALLY SAID
WAS COME ON UP AND FIX
MY LIGHT DIMMER.
WHOLE FAMILY STANDS AROUND
AND WATCHES YOU ALMOST
ELECTROCUTE YOURSELF.
WELL, THAT WOULD EXPLAIN
A FEW THINGS, HAROLD.
BOB, I WOULD SAY THAT
IT'S THIS WAY...
IF A WOMAN INVITES YOU UP
FOR A NIGHT CAP,
THAT MEANS SHE
FINDS YOU HANDSOME;
WHEREAS, IF SHE INVITES YOU UP
TO BAIT HER MOUSE TRAPS,
WELL, SHE FINDS YOU HANDY.
IF SHE INVITES YOU UP TO
SHOW YOU HER YOUR NEW BEDROOM,
YOU'RE HANDSOME;
WHEREAS, IF SHE INVITES YOU UP
FOR AN ESTIMATE TO FIX
HER NEW BATHROOM,
WELL, YOU'D BE HANDY.
IF SHE SAYS COFFEE,
TEA OR ME,
SHE FINDS YOU HANDSOME.
IF SHE SAYS LATEX,
OIL OR SEMI-GLOSS,
YOU'RE HANDY.
BUT IF YOU CAN FIND A WOMAN
WHO SAYS "I DO,"
YOU'RE IN LUCK,
BECAUSE THAT MEANS SHE
FINDS YOU HANDSOME
ANDHANDY.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
I DO!
THAT'S THE ONE
RIGHT THERE, I DO.
I DO WHAT?
YOU DON'T, HAROLD.
NOT YET.
NOT EVER.
Red: WELL, BILL HAD CALLED ME
OUT TO THE FIELD OUT BEHIND
THE LODGE THERE
BECAUSE HE HAD SET UP
A CROQUET SET
AND APPARENTLY HE HAD
SET UP QUITE AN UNUSUAL --
I DON'T REMEMBER SEEING THAT
MANY STICKS ON THEM BEFORE.
ANYWAY, I TOOK A SHOT.
I ALWAYS LOVE CROQUET.
YEAH, THERE YOU GO.
PERFECT.
THAT'S THE WAY YOU
DO IT, BILL, YEAH.
YOU KNOW I THINK CROQUET
I THINK OF IT AS KIND
OF AN ENGLISH
THE ROYAL FAMILY THING.
ALTHOUGH I GUESS "CROQUET" IS
KIND OF A FRENCH WORD AND A --
A LITTLE BAWDY ENGLISH
FROM BILL THERE.
YOU GOT TO HIT THE BALL AS
PART OF THE GAME THERE, BILL.
OH. OH. OH. OH.
NO. NO. NO. NO. NO.
NO, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE GOING THROUGH --
YOU GOT TO GO THROUGH
THE HOOPS IN A CERTAIN --
BUT I THINK IT WAS PROBABLY A
GAME THAT PROBABLY DATES BACK
TO THE TIME WHEN --
NO. NO --
DATES BACK TO THE TIME -- NO.
LATER THAT WEEK...
PROBABLY DATES BACK TO THE
TIME WHEN I GUESS PEOPLE
HAD A LOT MORE TIME.
BILL, THIS IS NOT --
NOW, EASY, EASY.
OH. OH.
I THINK THAT'S
A DIFFERENT GAME.
WHAT'S THAT?
OH, IT'S ONE OF THOSE
RADIO CONTROLLED --
RADIO CONTROLLED CAR.
THAT'S HAROLD'S RADIO
CONTROLLED CAR THERE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HE'S DRILLING A HOLE.
IS HE TRYING TO
LIGHTEN THE BALL?
HE TOOK THE RADIO CONTROL
UNIT OUT OF THE -- WHAT?
OH THAT'S FROM THE
UNPLUGGED ALBUM.
OH... OH, I SEE.
WE GOT A RADIO CONTROLLED
CROQUET BALL.
LOOK AT THAT THING.
LOOK AT THAT.
OH LOOK AT HIM RACK UP
THE POINTS.
I'M THINKING TO MYSELF,
HEY, YOU GOT A RADIO
CONTROLLED CAR,
WHY CAN'T I HAVE A RADIO
CONTROLLED PLANE?
HEH-HEH-HEH
BOY, I LOVE A CHALLENGE.
WATCH THIS, BILL.
HOW ABOUT THAT, HUH?
STAR TREK.
I GOT MINE DRIFTING THROUGH,
FLOATING IN,
TOUCHING THE POST...
BOINK, THERE WE GO!
ON TO THE NEXT HOOP.
OH FANTASTIC.
THERE GOES BILL.
I'M RIGHT BEHIND HIM.
I'M GOING TO WIN.
YEAH. YEAH. YEAH. YEAH!
GET OUT. GET OUT. GET OUT.
GET OUT. GET OUT.
OUT OF MY HOUSE.
OH.
OH MAN.
NOW, REMEMBER THIS, KIDS,
DON'T BE A SORE WINNER.
IT CAN CAUSE
YOU PROBLEMS.
SEE WHAT I MEAN?
DO YOUR BRAGGING WHEN
NO ONE CAN SEE YOU.
Red: STAY TUNED.
BUZZ SHERWOOD HAS A
WHOLE NEW PERSONALITY,
AND HAROLD AND I HAVE
A WHOLE NEW WARDROBE.
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU, SIR,
WE HAVE NEW RESPECT FOR
MOTHER NATURE
AND HOW SHE CAN WHIP UP
THOSE COLOURS IN THE FOREST,
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK
IS HOLDING US UP?
TAKING THE TIME TO TAKE
THOSE NEWSPAPERS
AND WRAP THEM AROUND
THE TRUNKS OF THE TREES.
NO, HAROLD, IT'S WRESTLING
THE DARN SCAFFOLDING
THROUGH THE FOREST.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE EITHER
SHORING UP ONE END
OR THE OTHER.
I'LL TELL YOU
SOMETHING ELSE,
PUTTING A PRIMER COAT ON
THOSE BIRCH TREES IS A
WASTE OF TIME.
OH, HEY, HEY, UNCLE RED,
HERE'S AN IDEA.
HOW ABOUT GETTING BUZZ TO
DROP A BUNCH OF PAILS OF
PAINT FROM HIS PLANE?
OH, YEAH, HE CAN COVER
MORE ACRES IN A
COUPLE FLYBYS
THAN YOU CAN IN A WEEK.
HAROLD, YOU SHOULD
CIRCLE THIS DATE,
YOU'RE GOING TO
WANT TO REMEMBER IT.
WHY?
BECAUSE RIGHT NOW AND
UNTIL WE TRY THIS IDEA,
YOU ARE A GENIUS.
UP IN THE NORTH MANY PEOPLE
HAVE COME TO RELY ON
THE BUSH PILOT.
IN OUR AREA MANY PEOPLE
HAVE COME TO BLAME THE
BUSH PILOT.
THAT'S BECAUSE IT'S
BUZZ SHERWOOD.
HEY, BUZZ!
BUZZ?
RED GREEN,
MY GOOD FRIEND.
HOW ARE YOU??
DON'T HURT ME.
I'M SO GLAD
YOU'RE HERE.
AND, HAROLD, HOW ARE MY
FELLOW TRAVELLERS TODAY?
WELL, WE'RE FINE.
GOOD. GOOD. GOOD.
WHAT YOU ARE YOUR
DOING HERE, BUZZ?
WELL, I'M ASSESSING THE
CONDITION OF MY AIRCRAFT
AND ITS MAINTENANCE LEVEL
AND I FEAR IT IS
UNFLIGHTWORTHY AND
DANGEROUS.
ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
RED, I'VE NEVER
FELT BETTER.
I'VE MET A WOMAN.
OH, MAN!
SHE BELONGS TO A VERY
SPECIAL CHURCH.
WE TALKED --
WELL, WE DIDN'T
TALK SO MUCH
AS WE SHARED
AN EXPERIENCE.
AND I HAVE DECIDED TO
EMBRACE THEIR WAYS,
AND I'M SO GLAD I DID.
SHE'S TAUGHT ME HOW TO
TAME THE BEAST WITHIN.
WELL, SHE'S NOT
HERE RIGHT NOW
SO MAYBE YOU CAN LET
THE BEAST OUT THE
ONE MORE TIME.
I NEED A BIT OF
A FAVOUR.
CAN YOU FLY
FOR ME BUZZ?
AH, NO MORE
FLYING, RED.
ONLY MY SPIRIT
FLIES NOW.
WOULD YOU BE INTERESTED
IN BUYING SOME OF MY
POSSESSIONS?
ALL MONIES RAISED GO
TO THE GREATER ONENESS.
WELL, I DON'T THINK
YOUR CLOTHES WOULD
FIT ME,
I'M KIND OF A
GREATER ONENESS MYSELF.
MY ALBUMS, YOU'D ENJOY
SOME OF MY ALBUMS.
NO, THEY WOULDN'T
FIT ME EITHER.
NEVER BEEN A BEEN A
BIG MOBY GRAPE FAN.
AH, MOBY GRAPE,
THE OLD BUZZ.
YEAH.
NOW THE NEW
BUZZ HAS FOCUS.
EXCUSE ME, I HAVE TO CLOSE
THE CIRCLE WITHIN NOW
AND BECOME AS
ONE WITH IT.
WELL, IT'S TOO BAD,
BUZZ, YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, I CERTAINLY
RESPECT YOUR DECISION,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
WHAT I WAS PLANNING
ON GETTING YOU TO DO
IS TO GET UP IN THE
PLANE THERE AND TAKE
SOME BUCKETS OF PAINT
AND OPEN THE DOORS -- WELL,
THAT WON'T BE NECESSARY,
AND JUST TAKE THE LIDS
OFF AND THROW THE
PAINT OUT THERE
AND THEY'D CATCH IN THE
WIND AND FALL DOWN
AND PAINT ALL THE LEAVES
ON ALL THE TREES IN THE
FOREST, YOU KNOW.
AND THE COLOURS THAT
WE PICKED THE OLD BUZZ
WOULD HAVE LIKED.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
PURPLE AND YELLOW
AND KIND OF AN ORANGEY,
RUSTY, MAGENTA THING.
PSYCHEDELIC?!
YEAH.
FAR OUT. GREAT!
I'M FREAKY.
I'M IN. I'M IN.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A GREAT IDEA.
THAT ONENESS THING
WE'LL LEAVE TILL LATER?
OH, THIS, YEAH, SURE.
WE CAN DO THIS
ANOTHER DAY.
THIS PAINTING THE
FOREST SOUNDS WAY BETTER.
GREAT, YEAH, GREAT.
I'M IN.
WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT.
DIDN'T YOU SAY THE
PLANE WAS UNSAFE?
OH YEAH, BUT IT'S OKAY
BECAUSE I'M AT ONE
WITH IT.
WELL, I'M NOT.
WE'RE BACK HERE
AGAIN AT OUR DREAM HOME
RENOVATION PROJECT,
AND UNFORTUNATELY WE HAVE
RUN INTO ONE OF THE SNAGS
THAT A LOT OF
RENOVATIONS RUN INTO.
I'M REALLY SORRY,
MR. GREEN.
I'M REALLY,
REALLY SORRY.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
A LOT OF YOU
REMEMBER MIKE.
MIKE OF COURSE,
IT'S NO SECRET,
ESPECIALLY IN THIS
NEIGHBOURHOOD,
MIKE IS A CONVICTED
FELON OUT ON PAROLE.
DID I GET THAT
RIGHT, MIKE?
THAT'S RIGHT,
MR. GREEN.
YEAH.
AND, MIKE, NOW THAT YOU'RE
OUT AND UNSUPERVISED,
TELL THE PEOPLE AT
HOME WHAT IS THE
ONE THING
THAT KEEPS YOU ON THE
STRAIGHT AND NARROW.
OH, URINALYSIS.
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
AS I SAY -- ALL RIGHT.
AS I SAY, WE GOT
INTO A BIT OF A
PROBLEM HERE.
MIKE WENT A
LITTLE OVERBOARD
AND HE WENT OUT AND
BOUGHT WAY TOO MUCH
OF THE PANELING
AND THE 2X4s FOR OUR
REC ROOM RENOVATION.
WAY, WAY,
WAY TOO MUCH.
I'M REALLY SORRY,
MR. GREEN.
WELL, IT'S ALWAYS A
GOOD THING TO HAVE
A LITTLE EXTRA,
BECAUSE YOU GOT TO
ALLOW FOR BREAKAGE
AND MISTAKES
AND THE OCCASIONAL
HOUSE FIRE.
NOW, RATHER THAN TAKE
THESE 2X4s AND BURN THEM
IN A BARREL OVER ON
A PICKET LINE SOMEWHERE
OR TO TAKE THE
PANELING AND SHRED HER
DOWN THROUGH A GARBURATOR,
WHAT I'M GOING TO DO IS I'M
GOING TO TAKE THESE 2X4s
AND THIS EXTRA PANELING
AND SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE
SOMETHING A LOT NICER
THAN THAT
CRAPPY REC ROOM.
I'M REALLY SO SORRY,
MR. GREEN.
I'M SORRY, MR. GREEN.
YEAH,
OKAY, MIKE.
WELL, A LOT OF PEOPLE SAY
THEY LIKE TO HAVE THE CEDAR
SHAKES ON THEIR HOUSE,
BUT THEY'RE JUST NOT
PREPARED TO GO THE
BIG DOLLAR.
WELL, I BET EVERYBODY HAS
ENOUGH MONEY FOR PANEL
SHAKES.
REAL NICE, MR. GREEN.
AND CORRECT ME
IF I'M WRONG
BUT TO ME NOTHING SAYS
MONEY AND TASTE LIKE
AN AWNING.
MAGNIFICENT.
NOW, IF YOU HAVE A DREAM
HOME THAT HAPPENS TO HAVE
A FIREPLACE IN IT,
FOR SURE,
FOR DARN SURE,
YOU'RE GOING TO WANT
TO HAVE ONE OF THESE
BABIES RIGHT HERE.
WELL, I DON'T HAVE A
HOUSE OR EVEN A FIREPLACE,
BUT I WANT ONE
OF THESE ALREADY.
WHAT IS IT??
WELL, MIKE, THIS IS A
CHUTE FOR FIREWOOD.
KIND OF A TIME SAVING
SHORTCUT DEVICE
THAT ALLOWS YOU TO PUT
THE WOOD RIGHT DOWN
INTO THE BASEMENT.
WHAT, LIKE THIS?
WELL, YOU OF COURSE WANT
TO MAKE SURE THAT THE
WINDOW IS OPEN
BEFORE YOU DID
THAT, YOU KNOW.
SO SORRY
ABOUT THAT, SIR.
WELL, THERE YOU
HAVE IT, HUH?
WE HAD A FROWN,
WE TURNED IT
UPSIDE DOWN,
AND NOW...
WE'RE SITTING PRETTY.
YEAH, WISH THEY'D TAUGHT
ME SOMETHING LIKE THIS
IN PRISON.
OH, SURE, MIKE.
I GUESS THIS MUST BE A
BIT OF A LIFE LESSON
FOR YOU, HUH?
YOU MADE A BIG MISTAKE,
BUT WE WORKED IT OUT
AND NOBODY HAD TO
GO BACK TO PRISON.
GUESS NOW WOULD BE A GOOD
TIME TO TELL YOU ABOUT
THE 10 EXTRA BATHTUBS.
I'LL TELL YOU, THERE IS
NOTHING MORE FRUSTRATING
THAN TO SEE A GOOD IDEA
GO RIGHT DOWN THE DRAIN.
LITERALLY, FIGURATIVELY
AND REALLY.
BUZZ DID A GOOD JOB,
HE FLEW OVER IN THE
PLANE THERE,
DROPPED A GREAT BIG HUNK
OF BLUE PAINT
THAT COME DOWN AND MIXED
WITH THE PURPLE HE HAD
ALREADY DROPPED
AND THAT KIND OF BLENDED
IN WITH THE DUSTY SALMON.
BY THE TIME HE WAS DONE,
THE WHOLE AREA AROUND POSSUM
LAKE LOOKED UNBELIEVABLE,
LIKE ONE OF THEM CARNIVALS
FROM RIO "DI JANUARY."
YOU KNOW, BUT WE SHOULD
MENTION AT THIS TIME
THAT WE USED
A WATER BASED PAINT,
THAT WAY NONE OF THE
WILDLIFE WOULD GET HURT.
YEAH, RIGHT,
WATER BASED PAINT,
ISN'T THAT GREAT STUFF?
UNTIL IT RAINS!
WELL, I THINK YOU WERE
ASKING FOR IT.
I MEAN, THAT'S WHY THE
STORM WAS SO BIG, YOU KNOW.
YOU CAN'T GO AROUND
PLAYING TRICKS ON
MOTHER NATURE.
REALLY, HAROLD?
I THINK YOUR PARENTS DID.
SO OUR WHOLE KALEIDOSCOPE
OF PAINT WASHED OFF
ALL THE LEAVES,
DOWN INTO THE RIVERS
AND ALL ENDED UP DOWN
IN POSSUM LAKE.
SO NOW THE FOREST IS
BACK GREEN AS USUAL
AND POSSUM LAKE IS
THE COLOUR OF DIRT.
AS USUAL.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD.
I WILL BE DOWN IN A
LITTLE WHILE, HAROLD.
WELL, THERE'S A LESSON FOR
ALL YOU GUYS OUT THERE,
BE IT MOTHER NATURE OR ANY
WOMAN, FOR THAT MATTER,
DON'T TRY TO IMPROVE ON A
WOMAN'S HANDIWORK,
YOU'LL JUST
GET DUMPED ON.
AND IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I WILL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
IF YOU'RE STILL LOOKING FOR
A COLOUR FOR THE LIVING ROOM,
I HAVE A SIERRA GOLD GOING
DOWN MY LEG WHICH MIGHT
BE JUST PERFECT.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
AND UNTIL NEXT TIME,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RISE. ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
THERE WAS A
THING LAST NIGHT,
THIS METEOR WENT FLYING
THROUGH THE SKY --