Lights, camera
Action. She was a credits roll, the audience
and whatever you're supposed to do do that
and what because it's time for the red green
showing a hundred thousand fingers, just push
the record button and about 20 or 30 just
push the pause button.
But they won't even notice. Take the Marlin
and try and play it back and go, Hey, what's
going on there anyway?
Taking a pause button, here's the man whom I
like to call the man from uncle, because
that's basically what he is to me, but he's
also the star of the show.
Here he is. I'm also confused at this point.
Red. Green.
Harold, thank you and welcome to Possible
Hodge.
Any of you just heard that introduction will
already have guessed that Harold is a
relative and there's a huge favor involved
in his working on the show here.
Well, I don't consider this a favor.
I enjoy like directing and producing and
doing this stuff.
Don't worry, as soon as his salary adds up to
what I owe his father, he's out of here and
kind of an interesting week up at the Lodge
this week.
Something strange going on with helmet our
maintenance man.
I usually helmet spends his days kind of
tinkering around making adjustments to the
water pump to the point where it doesn't
work at all.
This week he hasn't been doing any
maintenance, so actually everything's working
pretty good up at the lodge.
It kind of proves that saying that we always
use on helmet, which is if it ain't broke,
too bad, don't total it off.
I think helmets and L-O-V-E.
I know the signs and not just with his
mother, which you know is good.
We don't actually talk much about love up
here at the lodge.
Sex, yes. Love no.
Love to us is kind of private and
potentially embarrassing, whereas sex is more
or less public domain.
I don't know. I think sex is
Every bit as much private as love is, maybe
even more so.
It certainly isn't something you want to
share with a group.
Well, then you've never been to the large
Christmas party, have you, Harold?
Oh, don't start talking about the Christmas
party to me.
No. Oh ho, ho, ho.
I get that one. Is there anything under the
Christmas tree for me?
Oh hey, it's the wrong size.
Oh la la la.
Shut up, Harold. All righty.
I'll take five.
Do you have a bad hand, do you all little
ones for twos and a three?
Give me two bill. I am fine.
Three. What do you think?
I think Bill should make a decision.
Oh, my corsage made it for my date tonight.
I sent a corsage. That's a duck blind.
Well, you want to get your date out of her
dress.
Pin that on to her. Let gravity do the rest.
Okay, look at Ray's helmet.
You have a date. Yeah, why not?
I just you know who? And who knew a girl
would actually say, You know what?
I was thinking, Oh, second, one time I think
I was thinking, What a lovely corsage you
made. I was thinking that I say that and I
said it to you.
You know what else I was thinking? How
generous.
All right, I'll raise.
So who's the lucky woman?
Let me guess lady wrestler Rita Frommer.
Rita Frommer, the pie lady.
Yeah, oh man.
She's hot. She's about a nine nine.
That's German for no.
She's like Suzanne Somers on Three's
Company.
Only she's brunette and she's shorter, and
she's like the other one on Three's Company.
Yeah, yeah. John Ritter.
Ok, look, he's such a little cutie with a
bakery.
Rita's bun. How is it? That's right.
Oh. You got a date with her.
I've had my eye on her for years.
How did you get her to go out with you?
Yeah. You know, I go in there by Danish from
her just to see her in that little apron
thing.
Did you get her to go out with you?
I asked her. Oh yeah.
She insisted on bringing her twin sister,
though, you know, as a chaperone.
Oh, just in case you accidentally sat on
her, huh?
Ok, look, I call. What have you got?
Mm hmm. Uh huh.. Hey.
Ok, that's mine.
I'm good. I actually just close the store
and become a professional gambler.
What about me? Well, I'll close the store
with you in it.
Oh yeah, the bun lady's got a twin sister,
huh?
Yeah. Leslie. Well, she said they're not
identical twins.
Leslie's blonde. Oh, long lines.
Good. Well, why don't we make this a double
date?
I don't know if Leslie like that.
Well, I I could go as your chaperone.
Yeah. Like, you know, I'll bring the RV.
I'll stop the bank, get some money at the
Drive-Thru, bring a picnic lunch.
Maybe later we'll go to the drive in, watch
a play.
Well, I made dinner reservations at that new
Chinese Italian place there.
Chop Louie's Bamboo Pizzeria.
We got to drive through. Wow.
Look, I think you shouldn't show up with
Glenn now.
I think you should take me there.
Oh man, come on. I can get you a real
corsage just from the store for free.
No charge and I'll get you a nice suit all
set up there in a suit.
Yeah. Well, what's wrong with what I'm
wearing?
Well, nothing. If you plan on taking or
dancing in an open pit mine.
Get your R.V. ready, Glenn.
It is this evening's got to be special.
Clean the tire treads if you have no problem
read can I borrow some of your clothes?
What the cleaning tire treads with no to
work.
How will that know you guys have a great
time on your date?
Don't know anything I do.
All right, you boys. You might be interested
in trying some of these Murray's own
aphrodisiacs. Guaranteed to give you a power
and stamina.
Murray, these are nice girls.
Oh, I don't know.
P e z.
Yeah, that's that's so that's French, you
don't you know, yeah, that's French for
Putin. All right.
Let's roll. Yeah, I thought we'd take a
bullet.
Good idea. Women love to go bowling.
You know, I think they got a drive through
there.
You want to stop it, Mr Huge, and get a
tuxedo.
Oh, maybe good.
The rope that hangs from the old oak tree was
once the noose for Arlo McGee.
He hanged for three days quite a long
duration.
The winds swung them around like a bird
feeding station, and this is one of the songs
they sung for a man who wasn't well groomed
or well-behaved, but certainly well hung.
This week on and in our corner, I'm going to
show you how to turn your home into a castle
by using fancy decorative trim, because
almost every castle that I've ever seen the
pictures, you know, I've always had fancy
trim on the outside, up off the walls and
across the tops and inside as well.
And 90 percent of that fancy trim is made
with plaster, and that's something that
peasants like you and me can do.
What I have here is a bag of plaster of
Paris, but the instructions are in English
to, you know, nothing, any nothing, any
handy man.
I know whatever. Thanks to reading
instructions.
Mix that up and just goes in with water, I
think.
I suppose you could use turps on this if
you're in a hurry.
That seems that seems about right.
Nice and portable.
Ok, now we're going to need something to use
as a mall.
What I want to make here is some sort of a
round decorative flower design or something
like that. Go on either side of the
fireplace, I think look real sharp.
So something maybe here we don't agree on.
I like using hubcaps.
You know, I particularly recommend the big
three mid to late sixties.
You know, there are real, real sharp looking
unit.
Put that down there and we just put our
plaster right in there.
Oh, I guess the pasture, Paris, that's a
little faster than I thought it did, huh?
Well, maybe I'll just take a look at those
instructions and we'll whip up another batch.
Ok, well, according to the box, once you mix
it up like this, it sets in about 10 minutes,
so I better get right on that.
So I'll just put this in right into my
hubcap.
Ok, bye.
Maybe I made a little too much here.
I wish I had all four hubcaps and I would
have it the guy had parked longer.
I don't have much time here.
I can sort all that stuff out later when I
got left about eight, eight minutes, eight
and a half minutes, something like that. All
right.
What else? Just get me.
All right. And I got a garbage can lid here.
I don't know quite what that is.
Oh, that's a goalie's man. That would be
ideal.
Shovel helmet.
Six minutes. Five minutes What?
I got left. Oh, OK.
Mm hmm.
Five minutes, I miss left.
Ok, I think it should be dry, but I'll just
check it.
No, I guess I could use a few more minutes.
Oh oh, oh oh, oh OK.
Just put a little time in there waiting for
the blast.
Oh good. We should be in good shape now.
All right. All right.
Yes.
Well, by golly,
I think we got her look at this.
Look at this. You just take that off there
real easy.
Is that attractive? What does that say to
you?
Does that say money? Does that say Roland
and money to you?
Look that up on, you know, that looks like
it's one of those classic drama things they
have. They have tragedy in all those be and
they got the tragedy his way and the comedy.
And then you get with this one, which would
be shut
Out
Or could make a dandy clock, but the hands
right on the nose?
We got her.
Oh my god.
Oh, take a look at that.
Be still my heart. Isn't that a beauty?
Now that that could also be a clock, I would
put that clock.
I put that clock anywhere. I put that right
on the front of my car.
That is a beautiful, beautiful thing.
And well, here's here's another thing we're
in the kind of a clock motif here.
How about this? That's a sundial.
On the other thing is these here are more of
a I guess they're more of a fun, more of a
training, not really something big enough to
make a clock out of
A
Watch you can make. You can make a watch out
of these, maybe make watches for all your
friends. So this is obviously the perfect
kind of hobby for anybody who cares what time
it is. Remember the next time women to find
a handsome, and he should at least find your
handy line of.
I hate this crap. But
it is autumn harvest time.
Little seeds have grown to bulbous pumpkins,
the tiny flower buds on the apple tree have
ripened into delicious fruit, and the couch
potatoes have grown another gem.
Well, by golly, this double date is turned
into a real big deal.
Glenn asked me to go down to Murray's store
and get a corsage or chocolates, both of
which he'll probably eat on the way there.
And then he and Helmut went off to make
themselves look presentable.
They went down to Glen's marina because he's
got the power tools there that they're going
to need. And now the whole south end of the
lake and the covered with aftershave, Buster
said he hears some chainsaws going, so I
figure they're probably shaving their entire
bodies to make themselves look thinner.
So I think it's excellent
To have taken pride in their appearance
because after all, clothes
Make the man well, then say Hello, Mr.
Doofus,
I dress like this. So the show has a look.
Well, it's not working here. Nobody's
looking.
Can I go change? I'll change if it helps the
show.
Well, yeah, if we could do the show while you
were changing, that would help.
Yeah, you can't.
You're kidding. Go on.
Good. Because actually people think I'm
quite a fashion plate.
Well, I think you're quite a roasting pan.
You got. You get it again.
Let's go to one roast.
That's funny. You're a nut ball.
Shut up, Harold.
Got me again. Good.
Oh, hello, Richard.
What can I do to you today, I read.
How's it going, man? Really slow things are
going great.
Business is booming now.
What can I tell you? I read, We're very busy
here.
Well, I'm just here for Glenn.
I was going to get him some chocolates or
some flowers, you know, for that, for that
big day to his tonight.
Well, we're out of chocolates.
We have plenty of chocolates.
You ate the last box during the all night
Mod Squad reruns.
Well, they were awful.
You know, I find box chocolates are so
inferior.
Luckily, I still have some canned
chocolates.
Can chocolates, can
Chocolates there in the store room, on the
second shelf, in the back?
Ok, Lansdale really go for these.
I mean, they're a little more expensive, but
who can put a price on love?
Well, I imagine you could.
Murray can't find them for the love of Mike.
They're right there on the second shelf, at
the back.
There they are, right in front of your face.
These are baked beans.
Well, they're labeled wrong.
I'll take 30 percent off.
No. 20 percent. 10.
I'll take 10 percent off.
So maybe we should crack them up and make
sure their chocolates
And lose the freshness.
Oh man, that's the whole point behind canned
chocolates.
You know, Murray, I think we're going to just
forget about chocolates and even forget about
flowers. I think that'll do better if he has
had some perfume.
Right? Well, that be Chanel No.
Five or obsession.
And speaking of obsession, it's time for
adventures with Bill.
Bill brought a lot of gear here, he's going
to chop a tree.
I'll take that top bit.
I'll just put the action up.
Oh, not not that long ago, Bill, put it, put
it down in the act.
This could pull it out of there and get that
out of their bill by hand.
It looks a bit loose down.
Oh no, sorry, Bill's got all the gear there.
These are called. I'm not sure what these
are.
Oh, yeah, I know these are called horns,
their horns, they put them on and they dig
into the tree. Bill got all this gear off
one of them telephone trucks parked outside a
doughnut shop. That's some kind of a
protector or something.
I threw that away up here.
Golly, I don't know what those protectors
are on there for.
Anyway, nothing to protect.
Things go point down there, not point in
that area.
Anyway, he's all set up, and now he just
goes, Oh, I see what the protectors are for.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Otherwise, you pick up pieces of driftwood
and any small animals you might step on.
Anyway, he's got the hard hat there, and now
I'm going to put this belt around the tree,
which I thought had to be snug before he
could get it.
I've never done this kind of work before.
You know, I was, I must admit, I was
guessing.
All right, Alison, off. Now we got her, OK?
I see, I see you need a little bit, a little
bit of slack in there and then Poppy goes,
dig down in and then the other and going, I
got to admit I was at this point, I was
pretty impressed because Bill was getting up
the tree there, and a lot of times Bill tries
things and they just don't.
I don't know. I just don't seem to come
together just the way.
But this was this was really how well I met
him.
I was speechless. And he's getting up there.
All done 50, 60, 62 feet.
Way up there. And then the idea is he's
going to just cut the top right off the tree
because I guess she was getting dangerous or
what have you.
I don't know why they do it, actually, but
I, when it happened was lightning had already
hit this tree and the top was completely
done.
Bill hadn't noticed. I'm trying to get his
attention, but he's kind of wiping the bill.
The tops missing up bill, all.
Typekit. Oh, boy.
Ooh! Lightning struck twice the same place.
That he's OK, and he's inviting me to share
his joy.
It shouldn't be a pretty quiet, large
meeting tonight with Glenn and helmet out
painting the town plaid just seen them leave
it in the RV.
Glenn had mapped spread all over the
windshield and helmet was folding the table
down into a bed.
Wow. That'd be a little insensitive thinking,
isn't it?
I mean, I'd be a major turnoff for any woman
to walk right in there and see a bed there.
Oh no, Harold, he's going to turn it back
into the table by the time they get there.
It's just a tux. That helmet rented was only
an extra extra, extra large and it's a tad
snug, so we can't get the pants on unless
he's lying down.
Learn why helmet had no trousers on.
When I saw him, I thought to myself, Well,
he's confident this thing.
Oh no, it's just a pants on.
They're on. They're so darn tight on them,
Harold, that he's afraid that if he creases
them, it'll create a weak spot and then the
pants will rupture and his whole body will
explode outwards. So once he got them on, is
going to open the sunroof so that helmet can
stand up for the trip.
Oh, there's the cry of the wild possum uncle.
Read time for the lodge meeting better.
Get down there.
Yeah, this is probably won't take too long,
and the only business I know of is McGee is
going to try and sell us something.
So we're just going to let them talk for a
minute.
Then we say no, and then that's the end of
it.
So I'll be right back.
Great. Great. Great.
Hey, hey, hey.
All right.
Above all, I will.
On a quiet night tonight, boys.
Ok, the floor recognizes Murray Woolworth.
Yeah, OK.
Well, I just want everyone to know that
Thursday is going to be ladies night down at
the store and the ladies can expect a 10
percent discount.
My life about that difference, this only
applies to single ladies.
Good for me. Well, if that's all this is
tonight, then I'm going to call on.
It goes back a little bit early, aren't you?
Oh, so how'd it go?
How'd it go? A double date.
How did it go? You're on a double date
tonight with you, with each other and how to
go the double date? Fine.
Where's the tax?
I broke it. That was the date.
Double your pleasure. Double your fun, huh?
That's. Oh, did like did you actually look
like I look like Billy Joel from the nickel
junction? No more like Billy the Kid from
Gunsmoke.
Did she have a nice personality?
Oh, wait a minute. Hold the phone, I just
thought of something.
Leslie is a boy's name too, right?
Bingo.
I just assumed that they were identical
twins, and they're not.
Oh, okay.
Leslie was just as disappointed, though,
because he thought that Glenn was a girl.
Oh, really?
Yeah, you know, like Glenn Close.
Wow, I was a real letdown.
You know, Leslie actually thought Glenn was
a good looking girl and I thought I was
desperate. He didn't believe you were a guy.
No, I shouldn't have shaved my whole body.
Oh, no. He asked for proof.
So Glenn whipped out, is what you about?
My driver's license? And Leslie said that a
driver's license could be faked.
So then he grabbed.
Well, forget the details, suffice to say, as
I punch the guy's lights out and we can't go
back to that restaurant again, that's it.
End of story.
Well, maybe, you know, even Leslie can still
be friends, though.
No, no.
That never works out, right?
All right, well, that's it for large
business.
I'm going to call on Bill here.
Supply the evening's entertainment.
This is a great one. Yeah, I love this script
I have.
Okay. Nothing up his sleeve.
Oh, well, there's a dream date they'll
remember for a while, or at least until they
work up the courage to go on another one.
It's amazing to me with so many eligible
bachelors up here.
While they have so much trouble meeting
women, I think it's because the women have
gotten smarter. It's too bad.
Anyway, my wife is watching.
I'll be coming straight home after the
meeting and I'll be bringing a box of
chocolates minus the chocolates because I
know you're on a diet and I should be,
especially now. So until next time, on
behalf of myself and Harold and the whole
gang up here at Possum Lodge.
Keep your stick on the ice.
Oh, oh my God.
Oh, God. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh
oh. So.