AND NOW HERE'S THE MAN WHO
PUTS THE DOWN IN DOWN HOME,
AND TOWN IN DOWNTOWN,
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE,
RED GREEN!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
BY GOLLY,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
LOT OF EXCITEMENT UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
JUNIOR SINGLETON FOUND A NEST
OF RACCOONS UNDER HIS PORCH;
STINKY PETERSON'S GOT A BUNCH
OF SKUNKS UP IN HIS ATTIC --
BEEN THERE TWO,
THREE YEARS PROBABLY;
AND IT LOOKS LIKE OLD MAN
SEDGWICK'S GOT A MESS OF
WEASELS IN HIS BED.
WEASELS IN HIS BED?
NO, BUT IT
LOOKS LIKE IT.
I'M THINKING TWO WORDS:
LAUNDRY DAY.
NOW, YOU KNOW
TO A LOT OF PEOPLE,
ANIMAL INFESTATION
IS A PROBLEM,
BUT FOR LODGE MEMBERS
IT'S AN OPPORTUNITY.
YEAH, AN OPPORTUNITY TO GO
HUNTING OUT OF SEASON.
NO, NO, HAROLD, DOES
THE TERM PETTING ZOO
RING A BELL?
NO, BUT IT DOES
SOUND AN ALARM.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
RED: What yer lookin' at
here is a bunch of segments
from this
particular show,
the main message being,
for gosh sake,
don't even think
about changing the channel.
I'll tell you something,
if you're gonna try and make
sense out of this program,
you've got to give it
your undivided attention.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
WELL, IN ABOUT 20 MINUTES
THE POSSUM LODGE PETTING ZOO
WILL BE OPEN FOR PETTING.
THE GUYS ARE JUST PUTTING
THE FINISHING TOUCHES ON
THE ANIMAL PEN.
BUSTER HADFIELD FOUND
A BUNCH OF SNOW FENCE
JUST STANDING IN
THE MIDDLE OF A FIELD.
AMAZING WHAT PEOPLE LEAVE
LYING AROUND THEIR PROPERTY.
UNCLE RED,
MAYBE IT'S JUST ME,
BUT I DON'T THINK RACCOONS,
WEASELS AND SKUNKS
ARE THE BEST CHOICE
FOR A PETTING ZOO.
WHAT IF SOMEBODY
GETS BITTEN OR SPRAYED?
DOESN'T MATTER,
THEY PAY IN ADVANCE.
OKAY, WELL, YOU REMEMBER WHEN
THE FIRST ACCIDENT HAPPENS,
AND YOU GET YOUR
FIRST LAWSUIT,
YOU REMEMBER
IT WAS ME WHO SAID...
ACCIDENTS HAPPEN.
I BET YOUR PARENTS
TAUGHT YOU THAT ONE,
DIDN'T THEY?
NOBODY WARNED THEM,
DID THEY, HUH?
WELL, I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW
BOTH MY PARENTS ARE
VERY FOND OF ME.
WELL, I'M SURE THEY ARE,
AND THAT'S EXACTLY THE
HUMAN INSTINCT
WE'RE TAPPING INTO
WITH OUR PETTING ZOO.
WELL, NOBODY GETS
TO PET ME.
AH, YOU JUST HAVEN'T
MET THE RIGHT WOMAN,
HAROLD.
OR THE RIGHT SPECIES.
RED: Well, now, later on in
the show, in the Adventures
with Bill deal
we're going to be doing
some bungee jumping,
but this is a little
bit of a preview here.
He told me to
meet him at the cliff,
because --
but he'd already --
no, Bill, come on down,
no, no, no...
I don't want --
Bill, I don't want --
no, you come, you come,
you come, you come.
All right, you know, if the
mountain won't come to --
well, you know.
So I got up there,
this is later that week,
and where the
heck's Bill now?
Bill? Bill?
Probably went for a nap,
went to lie down behind
a tree there.
What? What?
Oh, for gosh sake.
He went -- he went --
you know, communication
is such a big, big, big...
it's a -- it's a --
AHEM!
So Bill got up there,
and all set to go
bungee jumping,
and he notices an
extra lump in his clothes,
which is unusual
for a man of his age.
That's a rock, Bill,
that's a rock!
They tell you
not to look down.
OH, HATS OFF
TO MY SCIENCE TEACHERS
THEY'RE ABSOLUTELY
RIGHT AFTER ALL
COZ I JUST THREW
A FRIDGE OFF MY ROOF
AND COLD AIR
DEFINITELY FALLS
TODAY'S GRAND PRIZE IS SUPPLIED
BY THE LONGSHOT FAMILY
RESTAURANT,
POTATOES, VEGETABLES
AND A LEG OF FISH.
REMEMBER, IF IT'S A GOOD MEAL,
IT'S A LONG SHOT!
OKAY, UNCLE RED,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET BUZZ SHERWOOD
TO SAY THIS WORD...
BUZZ -- OKEY-DOKEY.
THE WORD IS...
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT, BUZZ.
OKAY, THE FIRST
MEAL OF THE DAY IS...
LUNCH!
NO, YOU KNOW, I'M TALKING ABOUT
YOU GET UP IN THE MORNING --
I DON'T GET UP
IN THE MORNING.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
WHEN YOU GET UP
YOU KNOW THE FIRST
THING YOU EAT IS...
CHIP AND DIP!
NO, I'M TALKIN'
BACON AND EGGS...
FOLK SINGERS!
FOLK SINGERS?
YEAH, I WAS IN
A DUO WITH A GIRL,
WE CALLED OURSELVES
BACON'N'EGGS.
I WAS BACON
AND SHE WAS EGGS.
OVER EASY.
TIME'S ALMOST UP!
ALL RIGHT, BUZZ,
ON YOUR BIRTHDAY,
YOUR GIRLFRIEND BRINGS YOU
SOMETHING IN BED...
YOU WANT ME
TO SAY THAT?
NO! NO! NO!
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
UM, UM...
CLEAR YOU MIND.
THINK MOVIES.
SOMETHING AT TIFFANY'S.
DRUG BUST!
YEAH, IT WAS GRADE 10
GRADUATION, RIGHT,
AND THERE WAS
THIS GREAT PARTY,
WENT ALL NIGHT LONG,
AND THEN WE SAID, HEY,
LET'S SIT DOWN AND HAVE
SOME BREAKFAST,
AND THEN THE COPS
CAME IN AND --
[ BELL RINGING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
THIS WEEK
ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
YOU CAN PUT A SKYLIGHT
IN YOUR VAN.
IT'S GONNA BEAUTIFY THE THING;
IT'S GONNA INCREASE THE VALUE;
AND MAKE IT A
LOT MORE FUN TO DRIVE.
HECK, IT'S SUCH
A GREAT IDEA,
I'M ALMOST TEMPTED
TO TRY IT ON MY OWN VAN.
BUT WHO AM I KIDDING?
LET'S GET THE BUGS OUT FIRST
BY DOING IT ON BUSTER
HADFIELD'S VAN.
OKAY, YOU'RE GONNA NEED A
VARIETY OF TOOLS HERE.
AND A PANE OF... GLASS.
NEED ANOTHER PANE,
HAROLD.
OKAY, WE GOT OUR TOOLS,
AND WE GOT OUR GLASS,
LET'S GET TO WORK.
[ GLASS BREAKING ]
NEED ANOTHER PANE,
HAROLD.
ALL RIGHT, GOT MYSELF
A STRONG WINDOW HERE
THAT WILL DO JUST FINE.
WHAT WE GOTTA DO IS GET
THE PUTTY OUTTA THERE
TO GET THE --
AW, C'MON, JUNIOR!
WINTER'S FIVE MONTHS AWAY.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, WE WON'T
WORRY ABOUT THE GLASS
RIGHT NOW.
WE'LL PUNCH A HOLE
FOR OUR SKYLIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, I WOULD PUT THE
SKYLIGHT RIGHT HERE OVER
THE DRIVER'S SEAT.
AND, OF COURSE,
BEFORE WE CAN USE THE SAW,
WE'RE GONNA NEED
A PILOT HOLE EYE.
PUT IT RIGHT ABOUT THERE.
OR THERE.
JUST DOUBLE CHECKING,
MAKE SURE I'M WORKING
ON THE RIGHT VAN.
YEAH, IT'S NOT MINE.
ALL RIGHT, THERE'S
THE HOLE FOR OUR SKYLIGHT.
I'M JUST LAYING IN
A BEAD OF CAULKING THERE.
DON'T WANT RAIN DRIPPING
DOWN THE BACK OF YOUR NECK.
'COURSE, I GUESS IT
WOULDN'T BOTHER YOU SO MUCH
IF YOU FIRST HAD CAULKING
DRIPPED DOWN THE BACK
OF YOUR NECK.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GET THE GLASS.
ALL RIGHT, THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A HANDYMAN
AND A HOBBYIST
IS THE -- WHOA!
THE ABILITY TO
TAKE SOMEONE'S HOBBY
AND TURN IT
INTO SOMETHING HANDY.
THE HANDY THING
IS A VAN SKYLIGHT.
THE HOBBY THING
IS AN AQUARIUM.
SO FIND YOURSELF
AN EMPTY AQUARIUM.
OR EMPTY YOURSELF
A FOUND AQUARIUM.
AND YOU KNOW, THESE AQUARIUMS
COME IN A BUNCH OF
DIFFERENT SIZES,
SO IF YOU'VE
GOT A REAL FAT HEAD,
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
STEP UP TO A 45-GALLON.
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT.
SURE THE INSIDE OF THE VAN
MIGHT SMELL A LITTLE FISHY,
BUT JUST GOES
WITH THE UPHOLSTERY.
AND THE BEAUTY OF
HAVING A UNIT LIKE THIS
IS YOU KNOW IF YOU
GET LOST OR SOMETHING,
YOU CAN JUST POP
RIGHT UP HERE, LOOK AROUND,
OR WHEN YOU GO TO THE DRIVE-IN,
YOU'RE GONNA BE UP ABOVE
EVERYBODY ELSE.
BALCONY SEATING.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU ALWAYS HAVE
A KID IN THE BACK SAYING,
"GEEZ, ARE WE THERE YET?
ARE WE THERE YET?"
WELL, HECK, WHY NOT PUT IN
A SKYLIGHT FOR HIM TOO?
THEN HE CAN SEE FOR
HIMSELF IF HE'S THERE YET.
CAN'T WAIT
TO SHOW THIS TO BUSTER.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
RED:
Stay tuned and relaxed.
Whatever this is,
we've got a lot more of it.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
I WANNA TALK TO YOU KIDS
ABOUT SOMETHING I WAS THINKING
ABOUT THE OTHER DAY.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU'RE ALWAYS
GETTING YOUR PARENTS TO GET
YOU THIS OR GET YOU THAT?
BUY YOU SOMETHING,
PAY FOR A BROKEN WINDOW,
PUT UP BAIL,
THAT KIND OF THING?
YOU KNOW THAT MONEY YOU'RE
GETTING THEM TO SPEND
IS NOT REALLY THEIRS,
IT'S YOURS.
OR AT LEAST IT
WILL BE ONE DAY.
IT'S A LITTLE WORD
CALLED "INHERITANCE."
DO YOU KNOW THAT WORD?
THAT MEANS THAT SOME DAY
WHEN YOUR PARENTS ARE GONE,
YOU'RE GONNA GET
EVERYTHING THEY GOT...
THE HOUSE, THE CAR,
THE MONEY.
NOW, HERE'S THE WAY IT WORKS,
IT'S ANOTHER LITTLE PHRASE
THAT'S CALLED
COMPOUNDED ANNUALLY.
THEY THAT WORKS IS
THE BANK ACTUALLY PAYS
YOUR PARENTS NOT TO
SPEND THEIR MONEY.
SO THINK ABOUT THAT ONE.
THAT WAY THE MONEY CAN JUST
SIT THERE AND GROW AND
EVERYTHING.
HOW OLD ARE YOUR PARENTS?
I'M GUESSIN' THEY'RE OLD, EH?
45, 50?
SEE, THAT'S OLD!
WHAT I'M SUGGESTING IS YOU
KINDA PICK UP THE SLACK NOW,
PAY FOR SOME
THINGS YOURSELF,
AND LET THAT THING
GROW AND GROW AND GROW,
AND THEN WHEN
YOUR PARENTS GO,
YOU'RE GONNA BE
UP TO YOUR NECK IN CASH.
THEN NEXT TIME,
MAYBE I'LL TALK TO YOU
ABOUT A MAGIC PIECE OF PAPER
THAT EXPLAINS WHY YOU SHOULD
BE NICE TO YOUR PARENTS.
IT'S CALLED A WILL.
[ HAROLD GIGGLES ]
SO, UNCLE RED, HOW'S
THE PETTING ZOO GOING?
GOOD. FINE.
LEARNED A LOT.
WHAT SORT OF THINGS,
FOR EXAMPLE?
YOU KNOW, COZ YOU'RE NEVER TOO
OLD TO LEARN... OBVIOUSLY.
AND WHAT WAS
TODAY'S LESSON LEARNED
IN THE TWILIGHT YEARS
OF YOUR PRODUCTIVE ERA?
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
LET'S FIRST RECOGNIZE
HOW DIFFICULT IT IS
TO BE AN ENTREPRENEUR
WHEN YOU'VE GOT THINGS
TO DEAL WITH LIKE AN
INFORMED CONSUMER,
AND WILD ANIMALS
WITH ATTITUDE.
UNCLE RED, YOU KNOW, REALLY,
YOU SHOULD HAVE THAT HAND
LOOKED AT,
COZ WILD ANIMAL BITES
CAN LEAD TO ALL SORTS
OF COMPLICATIONS.
NAW, IT'S NOT A BITE,
I SLAMMED IT INTO THE VAN.
I WAS BEING CHASED
BY ONE OF THE ANIMALS.
I SAW THAT,
I DID!
IT WAS A SQUIRREL,
WAS IT NOT?
A LITTLE TINY ONE.
JUUUUUST A BABY.
IT HAD A LOT
OF SPUNK!
I WAS AFRAID IT WAS
GONNA GRAB PART OF
MY ANATOMY
AND THEN BURY IT
FOR THE WINTER.
I WARNED YOU, I WARNED YOU,
I WARNED YOU.
BUT YOU GUYS NEVER
TAKE ME SERIOUSLY.
NO, WE DON'T,
AND IT'S SAVING YOUR LIFE.
ANYWAY, WE'VE HAD
A RETHINK ON THIS.
WE LET ALL THE ANIMALS GO,
SINCE THEY'D ESCAPED THROUGH
THE HOLE IN THE FENCE.
SO NOW WE'VE GOT
A WHOLE NEW STRATEGY.
THE WORLD'S FIRST
DRIVE-THRU PETTING ZOO.
D-D-DRIVE-THRU?
SET UP A
ROW OF MAILBOXES,
GOT A DOG IN EACH ONE,
YOU DRIVE UP,
PUT THE LID UP,
PET 'EM...
JUST LIKE THAT.
AND -- AND YOU BELIEVE
THIS IS GOING TO BE
A HUGE SUCCESS?
WELL, IT'LL
GIVE THE MAILMAN
AN INTERESTING DAY.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
OH, LORDY.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE FINE NOW.
WELCOME TO AUTO BIOGRAPHY,
WHERE POSSUM LODGE
MEMBERS GET TO TALK ABOUT
A VERY SIGNIFICANT
AUTOMOBILE IN THEIR LIFE.
AND DALTON HUMPHREY IS HERE
AND IS GONNA TALK ABOUT
HIS VERY FIRST CAR.
DALTON?
YEAH, IT WAS A
CHEVY II, RED.
BLUE.
OH, BEAUTIFUL.
THE NEW BLUE THAT
SMARTIES COME IN.
OH FANTASTIC.
YEAH, AND BOY IT
WAS LOADED, HAD
THE A.M. RADIO,
THE HEATER,
THE SPARE TIRE,
WHOA-HO, MAN!
STILL SMELL THAT
LEATHERETTE DASHBOARD.
THAT WAS BEFORE THEY
HAD THE AIRBAGS, RED.
YEAH.
YOU HIT SOMETHING,
BANG!
YOUR HEAD WOULD HIT THAT
DASHBOARD LIKE A MELON.
DAD GOT THAT CAR USED,
YOU KNOW.
OH YEAH?
YEAH. YEAH.
THEN WHEN WE GOT THE NEW USED
CAR, THE STRADA, CHEAP.
HE LET ME HAVE
THE CHEVY II.
GOT IT AT A GOOD PRICE.
EXCELLENT.
YEAH. YEAH.
NICE OF HIM NOT TO
CHARGE YOU TOO
MUCH ON THAT.
SO YOU'RE AN
ANTIQUE DEALER,
I GUESS YOU
WOULD SAY THE CAR WAS
'PREVIOUSLY ENJOYED' THEN.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, THAT CAR WAS USED.
NO, DAD DIDN'T BELIEVE IN
ENJOYING ANYTHING.
HE FIGURED IF
YOU ENJOYED IT,
THEN IT WOULD PROBABLY
HAVE A BETTER CHANCE
OF GETTING DAMAGED
OR GETTING WORN OUT,
AND THAT WOULD DECREASE
ITS RE-SALE VALUE.
YEAH, DAD WOULD --
GEEZ, DAD WOULD
SELL ANYTHING.
OH, IT WAS FUN,
YOU KNOW?
WE WOULD COME HOME FROM
SCHOOL AND THE FRIDGE
WOULD BE GONE,
OR THE COUCH
OR OUR CLOTHES,
OR, HA! MY TOYS
WOULD BE ALL GONE.
OH BOY, HE SOLD
YOUR CLOTHES?
YEAH, YEAH,
SURE.
HE SOLD YOUR TOYS?
YEAH, WELL, IT WAS A GOOD
WAY OF TEACHING KIDS
TO LOOK AFTER STUFF,
BECAUSE DAD WOULD
SELL THE SHIRT
OFF YOUR BACK.
AND IT TAUGHT ME
THAT THINGS ARE
JUST THINGS.
YOU GET TOO ATTACHED
TO THEM, BY GOSH,
YOU'D BE CRYING YOUR ENTIRE
CHILDHOOD, WOULDN'T YA?
YEAH, WELL, THAT'S A
GOOD TAKE YOU'RE
TAKING ON THAT.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT,
IT TAUGHT ME NOT TO
BE MATERIALISTIC,
NOT TO GET ATTACHED
TO FURNITURE,
AND BOOKS AND FAMILY
PHOTOGRAPHS,
[ LAUGHTER ]
THINGS JUST AREN'T
THAT IMPORTANT, RED.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
ABSOLUTELY.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
IT'S THE MONEY YOU
MAKE SELLIN' THINGS
THAT'S IMPORTANT.
RED: Well, meanwhile,
back at the bungee hill...
it's time for
Adventures with Bill.
Well, it, uh --
interesting.
A lot of people carry frying
pans in their coveralls
apparently.
Hence the gas shortage,
I guess.
And he had one
of those eggs that --
oh, I see, yeah,
I remember those.
Yeah, they've got
the pantyhose in 'em.
He's got unusual
hobbies, Bill has.
He carries pantyhose in eggs
right next to the frying pan.
That is something for you
young people to stay away from,
I would say,
on a regular basis.
Anyway, what he lacks in brains
he makes up for in quantity.
He's got quite a few
of those units in there,
and they just
seem to keep on --
yeah, yeah,
they keep on comin'.
Oh boy, he may be into his
personal collection
at this point.
I guess you're startin'
to get the idea here.
And you're sayin',
What the heck?
I thought they
were bungee jumping.
But this is the deal.
See, what he's got here,
rather than spending $100
on a bungee cord,
Bill would rather buy 100
pairs of $2 pantyhose, see?
That's the kind of logic --
'course he's using my money.
Gonna tie them
all together.
One knot, a real
good test of your knots.
That's a reef knot
for you young folks.
So he's tied about
150 pairs or so,
100 pairs or
something together,
and now I've -- he wants me
to tie that around the ankles.
That's a very
important part.
This is where you really
need a decent knot here.
I was a little bit worried,
but not nearly as much
as I would have been
if it had been
me goin' over the edge.
Yeah, we see you,
Bill, yeah.
I hope they're rated
about 180-pound test.
You know, one size
jumps all, kinda deal.
So while I'm goin' back
to tie that thing to a tree,
Bill, he's kinda
hyperactive,
he's gotta move himself
closer to the edge.
Be careful there, Bill.
It's not completely level.
It's kinda --
there's an angle.
Yeah, that's an angle.
You might fall.
I didn't notice
this right off.
I thought it's odd
that the cord's goin' out,
but I'm not gonna
pay that much --
all of a sudden, boy,
she really started
flyin' out there.
Then I grab it, coz I gotta
stop it coz I know
what's goin' on.
Oh my gosh,
he's a heavy fella,
and something's
gotta stop me.
There we go.
Then he bounces back up
and I get a bit of a break,
but of course
what I didn't realise,
he goes back down on that.
And I mean, I try to
be a patient person,
but you know, you can tire
of a hobby in a big hurry.
And I'm thinkin' I'll
just start pullin' him up.
So I start and a
little bit of this,
There's a lot of weight on that,
and then you've got the leverage
and the mechanical
advantage and all.
And finally my anger
really kicks in,
and boy I really get one,
up you go!
That's a reverse bungee,
that feels good.
Oh! Well, that
didn't feel good.
Well, that's pretty much
how the end of the day --
Maybe one more jump,
hey, Bill, what do you say?
One more, c'mon, pal!
RED: Special thanks to a
lady in Madison, Wisconsin,
who sent us this
Red Green Teddy Bear.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
WELL, THAT DRIVE-THRU PETTING
ZOO ATTRACTED A HUGE CROWD.
WE WERE AMAZED.
OH YEAH, HUGE CROWD!
TELL THEM WHAT KIND
OF CROWD, UNCLE RED,
TELL THEM!
I DID, IT WAS HUGE.
HUGE CROWD.
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE,
VERY EXCITED.
YEAH, RIGHT!
THERE WAS ANGRY DOG OWNERS,
ANGRY POSTAL WORKERS,
THE HUMANE SOCIETY
AND ANIMAL RIGHTS GROUPS.
ALL RIGHT,
HAROLD!
THE POINT IS IT
PROVED WE WERE RIGHT...
PEOPLE LOVE ANIMALS.
SO WE'RE GONNA GIVE THIS
PETTING ZOO ONE LAST SHOT.
WE'RE SWITCHING TO HORSES.
FARMER NASH HAS ALREADY
THROWN IN HIS HORSES.
WE'RE GONNA LET PEOPLE
INTO THE CORRAL
WHERE THEY CAN MINGLE
WITH THE HERD.
HA! THE HERD?
HE ONLY HAS TWO HORSES.
I KNOW THAT,
BUT BUSTER HADFIELD GOT
A BUNCH OF HORSE COSTUMES,
FROM THE POSSUM LAKE
LITTLE THEATRE GROUP.
REMEMBER LAST SUMMER
THEY STAGED
A HORSE CALLED MANNY?
SO WE'RE GONNA JUST
ALL DRESS UP AS HORSES
AND KINDA FILL
OUT THE RANKS.
HAHA! RIGHT!
MAKING FOOLS OF
YOURSELVES AGAIN.
I GET TO BE
THE FRONT HALF.
HAROLD, STICK TO
WHAT YOU KNOW.
POEM BY T.S. ELIOT
AND R.S. GREEN.
"LET US GO THEN,
YOU AND I,
"WHEN THE EVENING IS
SPREAD OUT AGAINST THE SKY,
"LIKE A PATIENT
ETHERIZED UPON A TABLE,
"LET US GO THROUGH CERTAIN
HALF-DESERTED STREETS,
"BECAUSE, MY FRIEND,
LIFE IS SHORT,
"AND HOW MANY TIMES DO YOU GET
TO DRIVE A SNOWMOBILE
THROUGH A MALL?"
OKAY, IT'S THAT TIME OF
THE SHOW WHERE WE EXAMINE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
Audience:
I DON'T KNOW!
AHA, EXCELLENT.
OKAY, THIS WEEK JOINING
US ON THE EXPERT PART
OF THE SHOW
IS MY UNCLE RED,
AND OF COURSE HIS BEST
FRIEND, MR HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS, MY HUSBAND
IS A NICE ENOUGH GUY,
IN HIS OWN WAY.
"UNFORTUNATELY, IT DOESN'T
SEEM TO BE IN ANYONE
ELSE'S WAY.
"NOW HE'S JUST
IN THE WAY.
"WHEN I LOOK AT
MY CHILDREN I WONDER...
"HOW MUCH OF A PERSON'S
APPEARANCE, PERSONALITY
AND DESTINY
"IS INHERITED IN
THEIR GENES?"
NONE.
NO WAY.
NONE WHATSOEVER.
IT'S A MYTH,
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
SURE, YOU CAN
INHERIT APPEARANCE,
BUT NOT YOUR DESTINY.
IF THAT WERE INHERITED,
WHY AREN'T I THE
KING OF RUSSIA?
[ LAUGHTER ]
ABSOLUTELY.
I MEAN, THIS LETTER,
IT'S NOT WRITTEN BY YOUR
WIFE, IS IT, MR SHAUGHNESSY?
NO, I'M TALKING ABOUT
INHERITING MY FAMILY BUSINESS
AS CZAR OF RUSSIA.
C'MON, RED!
YOU MET MY MOTHER.
YEAH, I MET HER ONCE.
SHE WAS RUNNING
A CHIP WAGON IN
PORT ASBESTOS.
BEFORE THAT,
SHE WAS...
SOLE SURVIVING DAUGHTER
OF THE ROMANOV FAMILY.
HER NAME WAS ANN,
ANN, SHORT FOR ANASTASIA.
WE LEARNED ABOUT
THIS IN SCHOOL!
WHEN THE RUSSIANS CAME IN,
THE COMMUNISTS,
THEY JUST TOOK OVER AND THEY
KILLED THE RUSSIAN FAMILY,
THE ROYAL FAMILY
AND EVERYTHING,
AND THEY SAID THERE IS EVEN
ONE DAUGHTER STILL SURVIVING.
THAT'S RIGHT,
CZAR NIKOLAUS --
OR AS I USED TO CALL HIM,
GRANDPA NIK,
HE HID MY MOM IN
A LARGE FABERGé EGG.
[ LAUGHTER ]
AND A GOOD MEMBER --
A GOOD FRIEND OF THE
FAMILY, RASPUTIN,
HE MAILED HER
TO FRANCE.
ALL RIGHT?
AND SHE WAS BROUGHT
UP IN PARIS.
SHE EVEN HAD A SHORT
FLING WITH ERNEST
HEMINGWAY.
THE WRITER
ERNEST HEMINGWAY?
SO... PREGNANT WITH ME,
SHE EMIGRATED TO CANADA,
AND SHE STARTED UP
A CHIP WAGON IN
PORT ASBESTOS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
AND UNTIL THE DAY SHE
DIED SHE COULDN'T STAND
TO HAVE RUSSIAN
DRESSING ON HER SALAD.
BROUGHT BACK TOO
MANY PAINFUL MEMORIES.
YOUR MOTHER TELL YOU
THAT STORY, DID SHE, HAP?
YEAH, EVERY
WORD OF IT.
WELL, THERE YOU ARE,
HAROLD.
SOME PERSONALITY
TRAITS ARE INHERITED.
WELL, I'LL TELL YA,
THIS POSSUM LODGE PETTING ZOO
IS A REAL LEARNING
EXPERIENCE FOR US.
WE LEARNED FIRST OF ALL,
DON'T EVER START A
PETTING ZOO.
AND SECONDLY, DON'T
EVER HAVE GUYS DRESSED
UP AS HORSES
IN WITH REAL HORSES.
OR IF YOU DO, MAKE
SURE THEY'RE GELDINGS.
THE HORSES
OR THE GUYS?
EITHER ONE, HAROLD.
BY GOLLY, THAT ONE CHESTNUT
STALLION WAS FRISKY, EH?
I DON'T KNOW WHY THEY
CALL THIS "FUN FUR."
I THOUGHT YOU
LIKED PETTING ZOOS.
I DO, BUT NOT
HEAVY PETTING ZOOS!
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
GET OFF!
GET AWAY FROM ME!
HAROLD, HAROLD, HAROLD!
IT'S JUST THE
POSSUM SQUEAL.
IT'S TIME FOR
THE MEETING.
OH, OKAY.
YOU GO AHEAD.
YEAH.
JOIN THE OTHER
HORSEMEN OF THE
APOCALYPSE.
I'LL BE DOWN
IN A MINUTE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
I'LL BE COMIN' STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETIN'
AND IF I YELL
OUT 'BLACK BEAUTY'
IN MY SLEEP TONIGHT,
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK!
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
NORTHERN DANCER OVER THERE
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR HOOF
ON THE ICE.
[ APPLAUSE AND CHEERS ]
closed captioning performed
by INTERCAPTION CANADA
www.intercaption.com
ALL RISE! ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
I WAS JUST DOWN AT THE POSSUM
LAKE MOVIE THEATRE THERE,
AND THERE'S A LITTLE DIFFERENCE
ON THEIR ADMISSION PRICE.
THEY'RE GOING UP TO 3,000 BUCKS
NOW TO SEE A MOVIE.