Economists have a whole bunch of theories to
explain the high cost of living, but I'll
tell you what it is. Vehicle inspections see
this little stone chip on the windshield
here. Well, they'll make me fix that.
Is that crazy or what?
I mean, what is the point of being able to
negotiate an automobile purchase a twenty
five dollars if I then got to spend one
hundred bucks putting a new windshield into
work? That's a recipe for disaster.
While I have a different recipe.
At one large egg to windshield using
hand-held convection oven, cook eggs until no
longer running. And to really fault the
inspector stick, one of
these magnetic signs on the side of the
vehicle.
Yeah. No, actually, I can really use that,
I'm a little bit upset.
Look it up in my mailbox here.
I haven't been this mad since that lap
dancer offered me the seniors discount card.
Yeah. See, you can use this.
You just to replace your mailbox.
Well, that's your hamster cage.
Yeah. Yeah, it's OK. He's safe.
I took him out and I put him in your sock
drawer.
You know, I wondered why that one pair was so
hard to unroll.
Actually, that's not going to work as a
mailbox here, because the less Iranian and
then anybody walking by can see my mail.
Oh yeah, all those hemorrhoid pamphlets and
stuff.
Look, they got me, too.
Oh, man, you know what it is, it's a darn
teenagers say they hang out the car window
there. They've got a baseball bat and they
grand slam their mailboxes into the next
county and they think that's fun.
Hey. Ok, well, it is fun, but not for us.
You don't know his teenage years.
It can be anybody. You know it could be.
Could he could be Roy the mailman?
Yeah, maybe Roy went nuts and he did it.
Whoever heard of a postal worker going nuts,
why is it the today's teens are have to wreck
everything, whatever happened to sex and
drinking?
Why would you be asking him?
It's time for the
Possum Lodge word game.
Today's prize is a coupon for a free pony
from the Screaming Pony Breeding Center.
Where every pony is a little horse.
Ok. Edgar, cover your ears and your cup.
Forget it. You got 30 seconds to get Edgar
to say this word.
Pool pool.
All right, Mr and go.
Ok. Edgar Edgar.
This is a game where you try to put the
balls into the pockets.
I don't play those kinds of games.
Ok. Ok. You can swim at a fancy hotel if it
has one of these
A flooded basement.
I got an idea. Say loop.
Backwards loop.
All right. Ok, look. Ok.
When a man and a woman decide to have
children, their genes
End up on the floor.
Almost out of time, right? No, I know, I
know.
Ok, OK, I know when you have a bunch of
talented people together, what's that called?
Certainly not this show.
Well, that, Gary, you're on it, you know?
Well, one person doesn't make a talent pool,
right?
There we go.
Can you smell me now?
Yeah. Good.
Can you still smell good?
Can you smell me now?
Good. Can you smell me now?
Good Rothchild sewage and septic sucking
services.
Can you still smell me? Could we smell bad?
So you don't have to.
No, I'm a guy who likes to eat a lot of hot
dogs.
You can probably tell I'm cooking myself on
one of these barbecue grill units here.
And I always cooked way too many, but
there's never any left over.
So my wife got me this bike hoping that if I
ride this thing, I would drop a few pounds,
plus I'd be farther from the food.
I'm thinking there's a way to ride this bike
that will actually enhance the hot dog
barbecue and experience.
Ok, first thing you want to do is remove the
rear wheel.
Next, you want to get the rim off of the
wheel.
Now, I don't mean the tire.
I meant the tire. I would have said the
tire, wouldn't I?
And there's lots of ways of getting that off
there.
You could cut that with a torch.
You could hack it off with an axe.
You could just wail the whole thing on a big
rock a few hundred times.
But the smart way is to take a pair of side
cutters and cut this bolt right where it
meets the rim.
They. Now you just bend the spokes away from
the sprocket side of the wheel.
They're easy to bend. Bikes are generally
soft spoken.
And these aren't just folks anymore.
They're skewers. I mean, hot dogs taste at
any time, but they're even better after
they've got a few miles on them.
To me, nothing says class like rotisserie
sounds French like Brasier.
And to make rotisserie turn, this is the
part the furnace is going to love because
I'll be riding the bike and down the chain
and brake cable.
But she's all going to pay off because I'm
not just getting exercise.
I'm peddling my wares.
Remember, women don't find you handsome.
They should at least find your handy.
Now, at this point, I like to add a little
barbecue sauce.
No problem.
Getting some claim action, I want to throw a
little water on the fire again.
No problem. Ok, if the water doesn't put out
the
fire, all we got to do is pick up the pace a
little.
Don't forget this is a 10 speed.
Ok. They were to go.
I have a little advice for all you guys out
there with beards.
If you've had your beard for five years or
more.
That's a commitment.
Do not under any circumstances, shave it
off.
You may think that has time has passed.
You've changed from Walter Matthau into Cary
Grant, but I doubt it.
It's a beard, it's not a cocoon.
You're not a butterfly now.
You're just an old caterpillar.
As time has gone by, the part of your face
is under that beard has become a lost world
sags, bags, crags, wrinkles, crinkles,
waddles and warts.
Much better for you and your wife to
remember you the way you were then, rather
than to see the way you are now.
It's like watching an old TV series on cable
and then catching the reunion show and seeing
how rough the old actors look today.
It's bad enough to watch that on TV, you
don't want to see it in your own mirror, so
toss that razor back into the drawer.
You're way too old to survive a close shave.
Remember, I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
How do you guys feel about the way leading
men are presented in today's movies?
Well, I haven't seen any of them, but I'm
sure they're all crap.
Well, there's a problem there.
You know, women get one look at these
Hollywood fancy boys and all of a sudden,
their own husbands and somehow lacking.
I agree with that.
You know, guys like Brad Pitt and Leonardo
DiCaprio make it very hard for middle age
career criminals to get that all important
second date.
You know, I've been wondering a lot lately if
Anne-Marie still finds me attractive.
Well, that's crazy talk.
She never found you attractive.
I'm serious,
I got into bed last night, it was feeling
amorous.
She completely ignored me.
Well, that might help if you slept in the
same room.
You know, maybe we should work on our
appearances.
What if we worked out?
I tried the Stairmaster once they were, you
know, started it for half an hour.
You don't want the whole. We're missing a big
detail here.
See the leading Hollywood man.
You know who they hang out with the leading
Hollywood women.
They're not cruising up here to possibly to
try to steal our wives.
Yeah. You know what it's like.
It's like my business.
I might not have the best store in the
country, but I got the best store in Possum
Lake.
You got the only. Let's not nitpick Mike.
Like, OK, but that's a good point here.
See, the easiest way to be the best man in a
woman's life is to be the only man in their
life. Exactly.
Exactly.
Ok, here's the deal I need to be the only man
in Anne-Marie's life, so I want you to to
promise. But you won't steal Ann Marie away
from me.
You got my word on that one.
I have a way to catch a mailbox vandal.
You know what, these are iron filings.
What?
You've been grinding your teeth.
Iron filings, I put them inside the mailbox,
right, and then whoever smashes it, all I got
to do is take my handy dandy metal detector
here, right?
Then I guess
We're trying to catch a criminal.
Ok, if I want a science lesson, I'll clean
out the fridge.
Well, we just can't keep buying new
mailboxes.
I know, you know, Dalton's store is almost
sold out of them.
That's why I made this baby.
Grab that baseball bat. I want to show you
something.
Ok. Yeah.
Get that over here and just pretend you're
the vandal.
Smash my new mailbox, huh?
But what if it goes flying off and smashes
something beautiful like?
Just. Ok.
Harold Samat.
Yeah, so it's the mailbox.
Well, the plan was we're going to have a
little fishing trip in a canoe, and Winston
loves to fish more than he loves to help.
So he just goes out at the end of the night.
We get all the stuff there and I had the
cooler and then Walter kind of show off the
way he does the launch. A canoe be more
brown than brainy, forgot to actually put a
rope on the canoe. So, you know, I have
really just the one question.
What were you thinking?
So I got the anchor rope there and I figure
if I could maybe just hook into that thing, I
say it's a it's a metal canoe shouldn't be.
It shouldn't be a problem. That's a nice
shot.
And then just start pulling her in.
But there is a kind of a sandbar there, and
it had some foliage on it.
Next thing you know, the canoe is all wedged
on there.
Real good and ask, Do you mind Winston, do
you mind?
I hate to interrupt your fishing, but you
could just help us.
Well, then you know, it's whenever you get
two or more men doing something.
A lot of them are helping, but there's
always going to be one guy who, how can I put
this? Well, he's faking it, really.
So I figure I'll switch from manpower to
horsepower, hook up to the possam van, and I
was just going to just haul her away there,
but I thought if the guys could get some
waves going, so I'm saying to them, you
know, jump up and down to the floating dock,
jump up and down, just get a few ripples,
something going on.
There we go. That's that's it.
That's the idea. And it was about three 18
eight a.m.
Got a lot of jam. So I probably was a little
over aggressive and then a lot of loose rocks
and stones and what have you and.
But we got our way.
And I watch your hand.
Ok, so I figure I could see Walter swimming
over to the dock, and I wasn't quite sure
where Winston was and I got water up there,
but we so far, we got no Winston, we got no
canoe. But he pointed out that Winston was
fishing.
The experts portion of the show, this is
where we examine those three little words
that men find so hard to say.
Well, it's still true in that.
Ok. Today's letter goes as follows Dear
Experts.
La La last night I dreamt I was driving my
car up a steep hill when the engine died and
it started to roll backwards faster and
faster until I woke up in a cold sweat.
What does this mean?
Well, it sounds like he popped the clutch too
fast.
No, no, actually, I think this man wants us
to help interpret what the hidden meaning of
his dream. You're going to need to go into
the world of the unconscious mind.
You're going to need to come out of it.
No, I think this dream is all about anxiety.
Oh, OK. Ok, OK, I get it.
This guy is afraid of hills.
No, no, wait, wait, no. This guy has a fear
of failure.
That's why you can't climb the hill.
He's afraid if he stops, he'll slide
backwards.
And you also have to keep moving forward and
moving on.
Well, if he's afraid of hills, he should move
to Saskatchewan.
I had this really weird dream once, and I was
I was in my jail cell, right?
And and there was this dwarf in the corner.
He was singing that Folsom Prison Blues.
And my mother was sitting in the shower next
to mine.
That is so spooky.
I haven't got to the part where I fell
asleep yet.
You know what, I think I think it's
Important, thanks. Do you know what else is
quite good?
What else is got those dreams where where
you can fly?
Good. I have super powers allow me to do
things that I can't do in real life.
Well, you know how getting a date is not
technically a super.
And what kind of games do you have, Mr.
Green? Oh, I don't have dreams.
You don't dream.
Well, no, because I mean, it sounds like if
you have to, if you want to have dreams, it
must be because you're afraid of something
or you want something you can't have.
So.
Wow, that's really enlightened, Uncle Ralph.
You know, it takes a lot of character to be
happy with where you are and what you have.
Why? Especially considering your
circumstances.
You really know what almost makes me think.
Maybe I should just hang around here with
you forever.
Oh, no,
I didn't say I don't have nightmares.
Ever notice how when a man makes his bed,
his wife will usually come back in and make
the whole darn thing all over again?
I've seen Bernice come back in here and tuck
this thing in tighter than Joan Rivers face.
So it's not really worth it for a man to put
a lot of effort into making the bed and when
it comes to the business of not making an
effort.
I'm the president and CEO.
What we have here is a bed that makes itself
see the string got this attached to all four
corners in my bed close.
And then they run down through these
eyeballs that are attached to all four
corners of the bed.
And they all meet up here.
This is one of these retractable dog
leashes.
So at Night Knight let her out a few feet so
that Bernice and I have enough lead to roam
around a little. And then in the morning, I
just pressed the button.
He'll.
Mailbox still a little too heavy for me.
I figure as the cement cures, it'll get
later Uncle Red.
We just got a phone call from Junior
Singleton.
They think they caught the guy who's been
smashing the mailboxes.
Mike and Dalton are bringing them over right
now so I can scan them.
You know, Harold, I don't understand what
you're saying, and I wish I cared.
You know,
The iron filings that put him in Junior's
mailbox.
So whoever smashes covered in the filings,
no filings that can be picked up by this
metal detector.
Oh gee, it works just like this.
The can that's the Cannes, we got it, Mr.
Green, who he's hanging around downtown,
outside the recreation center, and he was
carrying a baseball bat.
Well, that's good enough for me right there.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
No, no. We need more proof than that.
I got to scan them for
Maybe the metal detector is not working here.
Oh yeah. All right, meeting
time. Well, what do we do now?
Well, you guys might as well go to the
meeting and the young fella here is obviously
not the bad guy. You can either stay or go
whatever you want.
I should go.
I'm on deck.
Dalton, hang on, man, there we.
Yeah, sure. What is it that's curious about
something?
Pretty good year for mailbox sales.
All right, man, has to make a living, you
know, and you know, I was kind of hoping we
could keep this our little secret, you know?
Well, what say you pay everybody's lounge
dues for this year?
We'll let it go at that.
Well, everybody's lunch dues.
That's not fair.
Man's got to make a living Dalton.
Right. I'll see you at the meeting.
If my wife is watching, I'll be coming
straight home after the meet, and I'm hoping
to put the mail back in mail, man.
Might even have a package just for you.
Rasha, thanks for watching on behalf of
myself and Harold and the whole gang up here
in Paris Plage, keep your stick on ice.
Sit down, sit down, sit down.
All right.
Now. By your heads from a man's prayer, I'm a
man that I can change if I have to.
I yes, yes. All right, man, and I have some
good news.
Dalton Humphrey has offered to cover
everybody's dues for the whole year.
That would probably mean more if any of you
were actually planning on paying your dues.