LET'S FACE IT,
MEN AND PAINT DON'T MIX.
YOU GUYS PROMISE
TO DO THE PAINTING.
YOU EVEN GO OUT
AND BUY THE PAINT,
BUT BY THE TIME YOU'RE ACTUALLY
UP THE LADDER WITH
A BRUSH IN HAND,
EVERYTHING SETTLES TO
THE BOTTOM OF THE CAN.
AND SAME WITH THE PAINT.
NOW, STIRRING PAINT IS MESSY
AND SLOW AND... WORK.
SO HERE'S A HANDY TIP.
LET YOUR CAR DO THE MIXING.
DUCT TAPE A CAN TO THE CENTRE OF
THE WHEEL AND THEN DRIVE AROUND.
IN TWO MINUTES THAT BABY'LL POUR
LIKE THE DAY IT LEFT THE STORE.
JUST MAKE SURE IT'S TAPED ON
THERE NICE AND TIGHT.
AND MAKE SURE THE LID IS ON
THE CAN NICE AND TIGHT, TOO.
IT'S  THE RED GREEN SHOW!
AND NOW HERE'S THE MAN WHO MAKES
IT ALL LOOK SO EASY.
AND SO CHEAP... AND SO MESSY.
YOUR HOST AND HERO, MY UNCLE...
RED GREEN!!!
THANK-YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG, BIG, BIG, BIG WEEK
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
HAROLD, YOU'RE GONNA BE
SO PROUD OF ME.
I WOULD WELCOME THAT.
ACTUALLY WHAT WE'RE DOING IS...
WE'RE BUILDING A LITTLE
RACE TRACK, UP HERE,
FOR OUR 4X4s AND RIDING MOWERS
AND WHATEVER EQUIPMENT THE GUYS
CAN SNEAK HOME FROM WORK.
STINKY PETERSON HAS A FORKLIFT
THAT CAN DO 70 CLICKS.
BUT NOW, THERE'S AN OLD BUILDING
RIGHT WHERE WE WANT
TO PUT THE CHICANE.
THAT'S THE ORIGINAL
POSSUM LODGE.
OH, THAT'S AN
EXCELLENT EXAMPLE
OF EARLY PIONEER
BOARD AND BATTEN.
NOW ORDINARILY, WE WOULD JUST
FLATTEN THAT WITH A BACKHOE
OR A WRECKING BALL
OR MOOSE THOMPSON,
BUT THIS TIME, WE'RE GONNA DO
THE POLITICALLY CORRECT THING.
AS A FAVOUR TO THE LOCAL
HISTORICAL SOCIETY,
WE'RE GONNA ACTUALLY MOVE
THE BUILDING TO A SAFER SPOT.
THAT IS GREAT NEWS.
THAT'S FANTASTIC!!!
WOULD YOU LIKE THE NAME
OF A COMPANY THAT DOES
THAT SORT OF THING?
THAT MOVES OLD
PIONEER BUILDINGS
AND THINGS?
BECAUSE THEY HAVE
COMPANIES THAT DO
THAT SORT OF THING.
THEY HAVE
THE PROPER EQUIPMENT
AND THE EXPERIENCE...
WHY DO I
EVEN BOTHER?
YOU THINK WE'RE GONNA SPEND
FIVE HUNDRED BUCKS TO MOVE
A TWO-DOLLAR BUILDING?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
YOU'RE GONNA SPEND
A LOT MORE THAN THAT
IF YOU INCLUDE
THE MEDICAL BILLS.
YOU SEE, THAT'S
THE THING, EH.
YOU YOUNG GUYS TRY
TO SOLVE ALL YOUR PROBLEMS
BY WRITING A CHEQUE.
WHEREAS, THE MEN
OF POSSUM LODGE
TAKE ACTION WITH
OUR OWN HANDS.
AH, THAT EXPLAINS
THE MISSING FINGERS.
WELL HAROLD,
SOMETIMES ONE
IS ENOUGH.
IT'S TIME FOR
"THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME."
AND THIS WEEK,
MR. MIKE HAMAR'S
PLAYING FOR A TRULY
FABULOUS PRIZE
SUPPLIED BY
THE POSSUM LAKE
CREDIT UNION.
THE CREDIT UNION WILL
TEAR UP YOUR MORTGAGE
FREE OF CHARGE.
REPOSSESSION HAS
NEVER BEEN SO EASY.
NO FEES, NO FUSS,
NO HOUSE.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE
30 SECONDS, OR SO,
TO GET MR. MIKE HAMAR
TO SAY THIS WORD:
GO!
MIKE, WHEN YOU
HAVE A BEER,
THAT'S CALLED...?
BREAKFAST?
[laughter]
OKAY, LET'S SAY
YOU'RE THIRSTY,
YOU GO DOWN TO THE 7-11
FOR SOMETHING COLD,
THAT'S CALLED...?
SHOPLIFTING?
[laughter]
NO, NO, I'M SAYING, LIKE,
WHAT WOULD YOU CALL THE DRINK!
EVIDENCE.
[laughter]
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT
JUST A TERM FOR
A DRINK.
WHISKEY!
NO, A GENERIC WORD
FOR A DRINK?
POTATO SKIN WINE.
[laughter]
DO YOU KNOW WHAT GENERIC MEANS?
CHEAP.
OKAY, FORGET
THE ALCOHOL.
WHAT DO YOU CALL
A SOFT DRINK?
MIX.
[laughter]
ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
UNCLE RED.
ALL RIGHT MIKE,
IN PRISON, WHEN YOU GET A MEAL
IT ALWAYS COMES WITH A...?
HAIR IN IT.
[loud laughter]
OH YEAH,
OH YEAH.
AT LEAST WITH THE FOOD
YOU CAN SEE WHAT IT IS,
BUT WHO KNOWS WHAT'S FLOATIN'
AROUND IN THE BEVERAGE.
[ring! ring! ring!]
[applause and cheering]
YOU CAN'T TEAR
THAT BUILDING DOWN.
IT'LL DISINTEGRATE.
IF YOU'RE GONNA MOVE IT,
YOU HAVE TO MOVE IT INTACT.
YOU KNOW, ONE BIG PIECE.
PLEASE CALL A
PROFESSIONAL.
THEY HAVE
THE PROPER JACKS
AND THEY GOT A VEHICLE
WITH ABOUT FORTY
WHEELS ON IT.
OH, REALLY?
WELL, GUESS WHAT
MR. FLAKY SPECKS
ON HIS LENSES?
[laughter]
WE HAVE A VEHICLE
WITH 52 WHEELS.
YOU HAVE A VEHICLE
WITH 52 WHEELS?
YES, SIR.
YOU DO NOT!
OH NO, LEMME GUESS.
YOU GOT
THE DELIVERY TRUCK
FROM THE TIRE COMPANY?
NO, NO, NO.
GO TAKE A LOOK
IN THE PARKING LOT.
52 WHEELS?
WHAT KIND OF VEHICLE
HAS 52 WHEELS ON IT?
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING
WITH 52 WHEELS ON IT.
YEAH...
DO YOU SEE
13 PICKUP TRUCKS?
[laughter]
OH NO!!!
YES, YES!
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO
IS WE'RE GONNA JACK
THE OLD BUILDING UP.
WITH ABOUT 100
CAR JACKS,
GET 'ER UP HIGHER
THAN THE BEDS ON
THE PICKUP TRUCKS.
THEN, WE'LL BACK
SEVEN TRUCKS INTO
THE FRONT END,
WE'LL BACK
SIX MORE TRUCKS
INTO THE BACK END.
WE'LL DROP THE BUILDING
RIGHT DOWN, SO THAT SHE
SITS ON THE BEDS.
AND THEN AWAY YOU GO.
THESE GUYS IN FRONT JUST STEER
AND THE GUYS IN THE BACK
ARE IN REVERSE.
[laughter]
WE'RE PROBABLY GONNA
HAVE TO CO-ORDINATE
THE DRIVERS.
YOUR IDEAS... DO THEY
COME TO YOU IN DREAMS?
HAROLD, IT'S SO SIMPLE.
YOU GOT THE PICKUPS,
YOU GOT 52 WHEELS.
AND IT'S LIKE A...
IT'S LIKE A...
LIKE A GAME OF
52 PICK UP?
YOU KNOW, A FELLA
WROTE ME A LETTER
COMPLAINING THAT
WE ONLY DO PROJECTS
WITH CHEAP, CRAPPY CARS,
AND THAT'S UNFAIR TO
OUR AFFLUENT VIEWERS
WHO MAY HAVE A LUXURY VEHICLE
THAT THEY'D LOVE TO RECYCLE,
BUT THEY JUST DON'T
GET ANY SUGGESTIONS.
WELL, LET ME MAKE
ONE THING CLEAR.
JUST BECAUSE I MAY TAKE A K-CAR
AND TURN IT INTO A ZAMBONI,
OR A FORD FAIRLANE
INTO A LAWN TRACTOR,
DOESN'T MEAN THAT YOU CAN'T DO
THE SAME THING WITH A BEAMER
OR AN AUDI, TOO.
DON'T LET MY REALITY
HINDER YOUR IMAGINATION.
SO, THIS WEEK WE'RE GOING
TO DO A PROJECT USING
THIS LUXURY VEHICLE
FULLY EQUIPED WITH ALL
THE BELLS AND WHISTLES.
RIGHT HERE ON "HANDYMAN CORNER."
[crash, bang!]
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO IS BUILD
SOMETHING WITH THIS VEHICLE
THAT EVERY LUXURY CAR OWNER
ONLY DREAMS ABOUT...
A BACKHOE.
OR IN THIS CASE, A FRONT HOE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
YOU BETTER LISTEN UP.
'CAUSE I KNOW A LOT OF YOU
RICH PEOPLE JUST HIRE SOMEBODY
WHEN YOU HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
THAT'S DIFFICULT OR CREATIVE.
WHAT WE NEED TO DO IS REMOVE
THE CROSSPIECE THINGEE...
THE DOOHICKEY.
THE THING THERE THAT STOPS
THE LADDER FROM DOING
THE SPLITS.
NOW, YOU COULD TAKE
THE RIVETS OUT OF THERE,
BUT HEY, TO AFFLUENT PEOPLE...
TIME IS MONEY.
[whoosh]
[bang]
[bang, crash]
ALL RIGHT, THERE WE GO.
NOW, THOSE LEGS ARE FREE
TO OPEN AND CLOSE,
BUT WE NEED A WAY
TO KEEP THEM OPEN.
IN MY EXPERIENCE, THERE ARE ONLY
TWO THINGS THAT KEEP LEGS OPEN -
CHILDBIRTH AND A THIGHMASTER.
YOU RICH GUYS MAY KNOW
OF ANOTHER THING.
BUT, I'M GOING WITH
THE THIGHMASTER.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S OUR BASIC
BACKHOE UNIT PUT TOGETHER.
AND I'VE ATTACHED 'ER
TO THE FRONT BUMPER.
NOW COMES THE FUN PART.
WE NEED THIS THING
TO MOVE IN THREE WAYS.
FIRST OF ALL, WE NEED
THIS SECTION TO MOVE
SO THAT THE SCOOP CAN GO
RIGHT UP AND OVER THE DIRT.
NEXT, WE NEED THE LADDER ITSELF
TO SQUEEZE TOGETHER AGAINST
THE THIGHMASTER.
SO, THAT THE SCOOP CAN
ACTUALLY PICK UP THE DIRT.
AND LASTLY, WE NEED THE SCOOP
TO BE ABLE TO PIVOT.
SO WE CAN LOAD
AND UNLOAD THE DIRT.
ALL RIGHT, TO DO ALL THAT...
I'M GONNA USE THESE CLOTHESLINES
AND CLOTHESLINE PULLEYS.
I GOT THESE FREE
FROM A NEIGHBOUR
WHO NOW HAS TO BUY A DRYER.
I'LL HOOK ALL THIS UP, AND THEN,
WE CAN GET TO THAT FUN PART
I SPOKE OF EARLIER.
NOW, YOU FIND OUT WHY
WE HAD TO USE A LUXURY CAR.
BECAUSE MANY OF THE HIGH-END
POWER OPERATED OPTIONS ARE GOING
TO BE USED TO RUN OUR BACKHOE.
FOR EXAMPLE, THE HEIGHT AND
THE DRAG OF THE UNIT
ARE GOING TO BE RUN
BY THESE CABLES
WHICH ARE ATTACHED
TO THE POWER WINDOWS,
AND THE ANGLE OF THE BUCKET IS
CONTROLLED BY THE POWER SUNROOF.
HERE, LET ME SHOW YOU.
LET'S SAY YOU GOTTA GET
A PILE OF DIRT OFF
YOUR FRONT LAWN
BECAUSE YOUR IN-LAWS
ARE COMING OVER
AND THEY ALWAYS STEAL YOUR DIRT.
[laughter]
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
WE JUST WANNA LOWER THE HEIGHT
WITH THE HEIGHT CONTROL,
OR IN THIS CASE,
THE DRIVER'S WINDOW.
NEXT, WE JUST GOTTA DROP
THE BUCKET WITH OUR
SUNROOF CONTROL.
THEN, WE JUST PULL IT IN
WITH THE DRAG CONTROL OR
THE PASSENGER WINDOW.
AND THEN, JUST RAISE 'ER UP.
AND THEN, WE CAN TAKE 'ER OVER
TO WHERE WE WANT TO DUMP 'ER.
[applause and laughter]
IS THAT LUXURY, OR WHAT?
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OH YEAH, WE GOTTA DUMP
THE DIRT, TOO.
WHAT WE HAVE HERE IS
THE CADILLAC OF BACKHOES.
NO ACTUALLY, IT'S
THE BACKHOE'S OF CADILLACS.
YOU KNOW, GETTIN' OLDER
HAS ITS UPSIDE.
AND I DON'T MEAN JUST
THE SENIORS' DISCOUNT
ON THE LAXATIVES.
FOR EXAMPLE, OLD CODGERS CAN SAY
ANYTHING THEY WANT, TO ANYBODY.
THEY CAN TELL A PERSON THE TRUTH
RIGHT TO THEIR FACE
AND THAT PERSON WILL SMILE
AND PAT THEM ON THE BACK
AND CONGRATULATE THEM ON BEING
SPUNKY AND FULL OF LIFE.
WHEN YOU REACH
YOUR GOLDEN YEARS,
YOU CAN STOP LYING.
YOU'VE SPENT YOUR WHOLE LIFE
PUTTING A GOOD SPIN ON THINGS
BECAUSE YOU WANTED PEOPLE
TO CUT YOU SOME SLACK.
SO YOU LIED.
FIRST TO YOUR PARENTS,
THEN TO YOUR WIFE,
THEN TO YOUR KIDS.
AND THEY KINDA GOT USED TO IT.
YOUR PARENTS DIDN'T REALLY WANT
TO KNOW WHAT YOU WERE DOING
'TIL ALL HOURS OF THE NIGHT.
YOUR WIFE DOESN'T WANT TO KNOW
HOW SLIMMING THAT DRESS
REALLY IS.
AND YOUR KIDS DON'T WANT TO HEAR
HOW MUCH MONEY IS REALLY IN
THEIR COLLEGE FUND.
SO, YOU JUST BE PATIENT, EH?
JUST HANG ON FOR A FEW YEARS
AND THEN, YOU CAN START
TELLING THE TRUTH, HUH.
PEOPLE WILL THINK YOU'RE
CHARMING OR AMUSING
OR MAYBE, THEY'LL JUST
BLAME YOUR MEDICATION.
NOW, WHEN ACTUALLY YOU START
BEING HONEST IS YOUR DECISION.
BY THE WAY, YOU LOOK GREAT.
HAVE YOU LOST WEIGHT?
REMEMBER, I'M PULLIN' FOR YA.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL WE DID IT!
WE GOT THAT BUILDING
ALL JACKED UP, YES SIR!
HA! HA! HA!
WE GOT 'ER TOTALLY JACKED UP
AND IT WAS ROUGH, TOO.
BECAUSE THE ONE CORNER WAS
AWFUL SPONGY, THERE.
THE JACK DIDN'T EVEN CATCH UNTIL
IT BIT INTO THE EAVESTROUGH.
WE ALSO GOT THE BUILDING SITTING
RIGHT DOWN ON THE TRUCKS, THERE.
SEVEN TRUCKS IN THE FRONT END -
SIX TRUCKS IN THE BACK.
THEN, OLD MAN SEDGEWICK BROUGHT
HIS GREMLIN IN RIGHT UNDER
THE MIDDLE OF THE UNIT.
WELL, IT WAS A GREMLIN.
IT'S MORE OF A DOLLY
AT THIS POINT.
BUT, SHE'S ALL LOADED ON THERE
AND SHE'S BALANCED.
SO, C'MON HAROLD,
LET'S GET THAT
BABY INTO TOWN.
I'M NOT GOING!
I'M NOT DRIVING
NO TRUCK FOR THAT.
FORGET ME, NOOO!!!
UH-UH, UH-UH,
NO WAY JOSE, UH-UH!!
HAROLD,
WE DON'T NEED
DRIVERS, OKAY?
WE NEED SOMEBODY
TO BE IN CHARGE.
SOMEONE TO SUPERVISE.
SOMEONE TO YELL
OUT DIRECTIONS.
YOU KNOW, FORWARD, BACKWARD,
RIGHT, LEFT, AND SO ON.
WE NEED A CO-ORDINATOR.
WE NEED YOU TO
SUPERVISE, HAROLD.
AAH! YEAH!
I SUPPOSE IT WOULDN'T HURT
TO HAVE SOMEBODY INVOLVED
WITH BRAINS, WOULD IT?
YOU DON'T MIND ME
RUNNING THE SHOW,
UNCLE RED?
BECAUSE USUALLY YOU RESERVE
THESE CUSHY MANAGEMENT JOBS
FOR YOURSELF.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
I JUST DON'T LIKE
THE HEIGHTS.
[laughter]
...HEIGHTS?
YEAH, WELL...
IT'S ONLY A ONE
STORY BUILDING,
BUT SITTING UP THERE,
STRADDLING THE PEAK,
HANGING ON TO
THE CHIMNEY,
THAT'S A JOB FOR
A YOUNGER MAN.
THIS LITTLE CONTEST THAT WE HAVE
AT THE LODGE TO GET THE FIRST
TROUT OF THE SEASON.
I BELIEVE THE SIZE OF THE LURE
REALLY MAKES A DIFFERENCE.
AND, YOU KNOW, ONE CAST
IS WORTH THREE...
I GOT SOMETHING THERE
ON MY VERY FIRST CAST.
WHAT HAVE I GOT THERE?
IT LOOKS LIKE A GOOD ONE.
WHAT IS IT?
OH, IT'S A PAIR OF BOXER SHORTS.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE HARD TO CATCH
BECAUSE THEY'RE BOTTOM FEEDERS.
[laughter]
OH, BY GOLLY!
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
HI BILL, YEAH.
YOU'RE NOT USING MY ROD, NO!
THERE'S ALL KINDS OF WAYS
TO FISH, BILL.
FIGURE OUT ANOTHER WAY TO GO
FISHING, IT'S YOUR PROBLEM.
HUH? WHAT?
WHAT'S HE DOING?
LOOKS LIKE THE MEDICATION
HAS KICKED IN.
[laughter]
WHY IT'S A BEAUTIFUL DAY, THERE
AND IT'S SOMETHING TO SIT ON
IF I GET TIRED.
I GUESS THIS IS
THE BEAR TECHNIQUE.
NOW, FOR A LITTLE LUNCH BREAK.
DO YOU WANT ANY OF THIS, BILL?
BILL, YOU WANT ANY...
STILL NO FISH...
I THINK BILL MAY BE HAVING
AN EFFECT ON THAT.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH! OH! OH MY GOSH!!!
OH MY GOSH! OH! OH!!!
NO, NO, NO!!!
YOU GOTTA CATCH IT.
YOU CAN'T JUST
SURROUND IT, BILL.
HE'S GOT 'ER!
LOOK OUT, BILL.
LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT!!!
WHERE IS IT?
OH BOY! OH BOY! OH BOY!
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
HERE'S WHY IT'S GOOD TO
ALWAYS HAVE A FRIEND AROUND.
THERE WE GO! THERE WE GO!
BILL, STAND STILL.
I KNOW WHERE IT IS.
STAND STILL!
HERE IT IS.
OH, THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT, BILL,
GOT GET 'EM.
BILL, BILL, BILL!!!
NO BILL, THAT'S MY GEAR!
NO, NO, BILL!
HEY, I BORROWED THAT STUFF!
GET 'EM, BILL, GET 'EM!
BILL, GET 'EM.
BILL, HE'S IN THE CANOE.
HE'S BEHIND YOU,
BEHIND YOU, BEHIND YOU.
BILL, TURN AROUND.
TURN AROUND, TURN AROUND!
NO, NO, HE'S BEHIND YOU.
HE'S IN THE CANOE.
THERE HE IS, THERE HE IS!
THERE YOU GO, THERE YOU GO!
NOT THE AXE, BILL.
NOT THE AXE, NOT THE AXE!
READ MY LIPS: NOT THE AXE!!!
OH NO, OH NO!
OH NO! OH NO!
OH BOY! OH BOY!
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA,
GO OUT INTO THE DEEP STUFF.
BILL? BILL?
DO YOU FEEL WET AT ALL?
IT'S A GOOD NEWS,
BAD NEWS THING.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I STILL SENSE AN OPPORTUNITY.
AAH! THERE WE GO!
BY GOLLY, THAT BIG LURE
SURE IS PAYING OFF.
C'MON, C'MON, C'MON IN.
HEY! HEY! HEY!
HEY, LOOK, BILL!
I GOT US THE TROUT, BUDDY!!!
[amazing!]
"IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
JOINING ME TODAY
IS EDGAR MONTROSE.
EDGAR IS THE ONLY
DYNAMITE EXPERT IN
THE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
THE ONLY ONE
LIVING, ANYWAY.
NO SIR, RED,
THEY CERTAINLY DON'T.
[laughter]
IF YOU CALL
THAT LIVING.
SO, WHAT HAVE YOU
GOT TODAY, EDGAR?
OH, A VERY LOUD
RINGING IN MY HEAD.
KINDA LIKE THAT...
...ONLY LOUDER.
ALL RIGHT, I GUESS
THE UMBRELLA IS WHAT
YOU WANT ME TO FIX.
WELL, THAT'S TOTALLED, EDGAR.
WHAT I COULD DO, IS MAYBE
FIX THE HOLES IN YOUR HAT.
I'M HOT?
YOUR HAT, EDGAR.
YOU CAN FIX HOLES
IN YOUR CLOTHING,
BY THE WAY,
IF YOU'RE NOT GOOD WITH
A NEEDLE AND THREAD.
YOU CAN USE
THE FASHION DESIGNER'S
SECRET WEAPON:
DUCT TAPE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE UMBRELLA?
OH... UH,
THE UMBRELLA
GOT WRECKED
WHEN I PULLED
FLINTY MCCLINTOCK'S
TRACTOR OUT OF THE MUD.
APPARENTLY, HE THOUGHT
I HAD A TRUCK WITH
A WINCH.
I DON'T HAVE
A TRUCK WITH
A WINCH.
I HAVE DYNAMITE!
SO, I BLEW HER UP
OUT OF THERE!!!
YOU KNOW, RED.
THESE NEW TRACTORS THAT
THEY'RE BUILDING NOWADAYS,
THEY'RE VERY BRITTLE.
ALL RIGHT, EDGAR.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GONNA RETHINK HERE.
I'M NOT GONNA PLUG UP
THE HOLES IN YOUR HAT.
I THINK YOUR BRAIN
NEEDS ALL THE AIR
IT CAN GET.
[applause]
[laughter and cheering]
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU?
SHINGLES.
[loud laughter]
THE GOOD NEWS IS...
THAT OLD BUILDING
IS OUT OF THE WAY,
FOREVER.
BEAUTIFUL, OLD,
PIONEER LOG CABIN.
[pfffht!]
THOUGHT YOU GUYS
WERE GOING TO
SAVE HISTORY,
NOT MAKE IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DIDN'T CALL
THE PHONE COMPANY.
WHEN YOU MOVE A BUILDING
DOWN THE STREET
WITH TELEPHONE POLES
ON BOTH SIDES,
YOU GOTTA CALL
THE PHONE COMPANY.
WHAT THEY DO IS THEY
TAKE DOWN THE LINES
AND ONCE YOU PASS,
THEY PUT THE LINES
BACK UP!!!
WELL, WE DID HALF THEIR
JOB FOR THEM, DIDN'T WE?
WELL, I'M GLAD THAT
I HAD THAT CHIMNEY
TO HOLD ON TO.
I GOT TELEPHONE LINE
BURNS ON MY THIGHS!!
AND THAT'S ANOTHER
THING TOO...
YOU'VE GOTTA CALL
THE POWER COMPANY.
WHAT ABOUT
THE POWER LINES?
YEAH, THAT WAS BAD.
THAT WAS REAL BAD!!!
I SUGGEST THAT YOU SHOULD
PRE-MEASURE ALL BRIDGES
ALONG THE ROUTE
TO MAKE SURE THAT
THEY'RE WIDE ENOUGH.
YEAH, YEAH.
ESPECIALLY THAT
COVERED BRIDGE.
[laughter]
YEAH, THAT POOR OLD
COVERED BRIDGE...
THAT THE HISTORCAL
SOCIETY WORKED SO
HARD TO PRESERVE.
WELL, IT'S NOT
A COVERED BRIDGE
ANYMORE, IS IT?
JUST A BRIDGE, NOW.
SURROUNDED BY LUMBER.
YEAH, YEAH.
YOU SHOULD'VE
PRE-MEASURED.
I KNOW THAT.
OR, AT LEAST,
SLOWED DOWN.
[loud laughter]
C'MON HAROLD,
WE COULDN'T
SLOW DOWN.
ONCE THE POWER LINES
SET FIRE TO THE CABIN,
WE HAD TO, PRETTY MUCH,
HAUL IT, YOU KNOW.
THE IRONY THERE
WAS THAT WE COULDN'T
CALL IN AN EMERGENCY
'CAUSE THE PHONE
LINES WERE DOWN.
SO, WE HAD TO
DRIVE THE FIRE TO
THE FIRE STATION.
YEAH, POOR OLD FIRE STATION...
THAT THE HISTORICAL
SOCIETY WORKED SO
HARD TO PRESERVE.
THE ONE THAT HAD STOOD
THERE FOR 100 YEARS,
TAKING EVERYTHING
THAT MOTHER NATURE
COULD THROW AT HER.
NOT INCLUDING
A FLAMING LOG CABIN
TRAVELLING AT TWICE
THE SPEED LIMIT.
BUT, IN FAIRNESS,
FOR A FIRE STATION,
IT WAS PRETTY DARN FLAMMABLE.
AND YOU KNOW,
FULL MARKS TO
BUZZ SHERWOOD
WHO REALIZED THAT
THE FIRETRUCKS
WERE ACTUALLY
TRAPPED INSIDE
THE BURNING STATION.
SO, HE FILLED UP HIS
WATER BOMBER PLANE
AND DROPPED WATER
RIGHT ON THE FIRE.
WELL, HE TRIED.
HE TRIED.
HE GOT THE BAPTIST CHURCH.
POOR OLD BAPTIST CHURCH...
THAT THE HISTORICAL
SOCIETY WORKED SO
HARD TO PRESERVE.
THAT CHURCH DIDN'T
HAVE A PRAYER.
DID YOU LEARN ANYTHING?
ANY LITTLE THING
FROM ALL THIS?
WELL, I DID HAROLD, YEAH.
I THINK LEARNED
WHAT IRONIC MEANS.
I NEVER REALLY
GOT IT BEFORE,
BUT I THINK
I'M THERE, NOW.
[sound of the squeal]
SQUEAL OF THE POSSUM -
IT'S MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
WHAT IS IT?
A LITTLE BIT
OF HISTORY.
EASY NOW, EASY.
[applause]
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I KNOW I WAS SUPPOSED TO CALL,
BUT I GOT A DANDY EXCUSE.
AND TO THE REST OF YA,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF, AND HAROLD,
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE:
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND...
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RISE.
( LODGE MEMBERS ):
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
JUST A QUICK ANNOUNCEMENT FROM
THE HISTORICAL SOCIETY.
DUE TO THE RECENT LOSS
OF HISTORICAL BUILDINGS
IN THE AREA,
IT SEEMS THE HISTORICAL SOCIETY
WILL NO LONGER BE DECLARING
BUILDINGS AS HISTORICAL SITES.
THEY'LL BE LABELLING THEM
AS TARGETS, AS OPPOSED
TO BUILDINGS.