♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN IN
TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD SALUTES
HIS TEACHERS,
BILL GETS STUCK IN THE MUD,
AND I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU
THE LOWDOWN ON HOW TO
FIX YOUR LAWN CHAIR.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S TIME
FOR THE SHOW ABOUT THE GREATEST
CANADIAN FOLK HERO SINCE
UNCLE JOE ON PETTICOAT JUNCTION
WELL YOU KNOW OF COURSE
HE WASN'T CANADIAN SO
THAT'S NOT FAIR, OF COURSE
THE ONLY THING FAIR ABOUT
MY UNCLE IS HIS COMPLEXION
SO HERE HE IS MY UNCLE,
MR. RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
THANK YOU AND PLEASE TAKE
ANYTHING THAT HAROLD SAYS
WITH A GRAIN OF ASPIRIN
AND A JAR OF GRAVOL.
THINGS HAVE BEEN KIND OF SLOW
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK
SO I ENDED UP WITH SOME TIME
ON MY HANDS SO I THOUGHT
WELL MAYBE I'LL CLEAN OUT
THE BOATHOUSE OR MAYBE DRAG
SOME OF THE OLD CAR BATTERIES
OUT OF THE FRONT HALL
I DECIDED INSTEAD TO TAKE
A LOOK AT THIS MONTH'S MAIL.
>>HAROLD: OH GREAT OH THAT'S
A GREAT CHOICE BECAUSE MAYBE
MY STAR TREK STUFF CAME DID
IT COME MY STAR TREK STUFF COME?
>>RED: NO MISTER SPOCK
IT DID NOT, HOWEVER
YOUR REPORT CARD DID.
>>HAROLD: NO OH GOOD
YOU DIDN'T READ IT BY
CHANCE DID YOU UNCLE RED
YOU DIDN'T?
>>RED: YOU KNOW I THOUGHT
IT WAS KIND OF ODD THAT
MY NEPHEW'S REPORT CARD WOULD
COME HERE TO POSSUM LODGE
RATHER THAN HIS HOME
WHERE HIS PARENTS ARE
DOESN'T THAT SEEM UNUSUAL
TO YOU HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: NOPE.
CAN I HAVE IT PLEASE?
>>RED: OH WE'LL TALK ABOUT
IT LATER I GUESS.
BUT ON A HAPPIER NOTE GOT THIS
APPLICATION FORM FROM THE
GOVERNMENT WHERE THEY SAY IF
WE GET OURSELVES CLASSIFIED
AS A RECREATIONAL TOURIST
ATTRACTION THEY WILL GIVE
US A GRANT FOR UPGRADING
AND PROMOTION.
>>HAROLD: GOVERNMENT MONEY?
HAW! HAW!
YOU'LL LOSE YOUR INDEPENDENCE!
YOU'RE TURNING YOUR BACK
ON THE FREE MARKET CAPITALIST
SYSTEM THAT WE HAVE CREATED
FOR EACH AND EVERY INDIVIDUAL
IN THIS FINE GREAT OUTSTANDING
COUNTRY OF OURS SIR!
>>RED: IT'S $50,000 HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: WELL I'M IN THERE
LIKE A DIRTY SHIRT
DON'T GET ME WRONG.
IT'S NOT ME IT'S THE OTHERS
I'M THINKING ABOUT.
>>RED: THEY'RE THERE WE SHOULD
BE THERE.
OF COURSE WE DON'T NEED THAT
MUCH MONEY THE WHOLE LODGE
IS ONLY WORTH 20...
BUT I FIGURE GOSH IF I CAN GET
EVEN $300 BUCKS GET MYSELF
HALF A DOZEN REPOED BOATS
OR WHAT HAVE YOU THAT'D
BE FINE AND THEN I THOUGHT
TO MYSELF GEE I'M NOT SURE
THAT POSSUM LODGDGULD QUALIFY
BUT THEN I THOUGHT BY GOLLY
IT WOULD ACTUALLY MAKE THE LODGE
MORE CANADIAN IF THE BUSINESS
WAS SUBSIDIZED BY THE GOVERNMENT
DON'T TOUCH THAT REPORT
CARD HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: NO.
♪ OH WHEN I WAS A LAD ♪
♪ MY DAD WOULD TAKE ME DOWN ♪
♪ TO POSSUM LAKE ♪
♪ WE'D BUILD A RAFT ♪
♪ OUT OF LOGS ♪
♪ AND EMPTIES THEN WE'D ♪
♪ LIE IN THE SUN AND BAKE ♪
♪ WE'D PADDLE OUT ♪
♪ A MILE OR MORE ♪
♪ TILL THE SHORE ♪
♪ WAS STARTING TO DIM ♪
♪ THEN GOOD OLD DAD ♪
♪ WOULD SET ON FIRE ♪
♪ AND THAT'S HOW ♪
♪ HE TAUGHT ME HOW TO SWIM ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER'
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU
SOME PINE FURNITURE RESTORATION
THAT WILL NOT ONLY ENHANCE
THE BEAUTY BUT WILL ALSO ADD
TO THE VALUE OF THIS BEAUTIFUL
OLD ANTIQUE ALUMINUM LAWN CHAIR.
NOW WHAT HAPPENS WITH THESE
UNITS IS UNLESS YOU'RE ONE
OF THOSE PURISTS THAT BRINGS
THEM IN FOR THE WINTER
IS THAT THEY SIT OUT THERE
IN THE SUN AND THE SLEET AND
THE RAIN AND THE HAIL AND
THE ICICLES AND THE TORNADOES
AND THE THUNDERSTORMS
AND THE MONSOONS,
IF YOU LIVE NEAR THE COAST.
AND WHAT HAPPENS IS YOU GET
A CHEMICAL CHANGE IN THE
WEBBING HERE WHERE THIS SOFT
PLIABLE PLASTIC DURABLE STUFF
TURNS INTO A KIND OF
CRYSTALLIZED CRUNCHY
GRAHAM WAFER TYPE SUBSTANCE
AND THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW
YOUR BARBECUE GUESTS
SIT DOWN AND..
(LOUD TEARING OF FABRIC)
SPILL THEIR HOT DOGS
AND BEER ALL OVER THEIR
LEISURE SUITS NOT TO MENTION
THE 4 INCH SLIVER FROM THE
DECK THAT GOES UP THROUGH
THE SEAT OF THEIR PANTS
IN SEARCH OF A NEW HOME,
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT YOUR
DINNER PARTY GOES FROM YOUR
BACKYARD TO SMALL CLAIMS COURT.
NOW THIS MIGHT LOOK FUNNY
AND IT IS BUT NOT IF IT
HAPPENS TO YOU.
BUT INSTEAD OF THROWING
THE CHAIR OUT IN THE GARBAGE
OR I SHOULD SAY THROWING IT
IN THE GARAGE WITH THE IDEA
THAT YOU'RE GOING TO FIX IT
SOMEDAY FOR 9 YEARS OR
10 YEARS OR A 100 YEARS
AND THEN THROWING IT OUT
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
A WAY TO RESTORE THIS ANTIQUE
BEAUTY BACK TO AS GOOD AS NEW.
(GRUNTING & GROANING)
OH BOY GLAD I WAXED THE FLOOR.
(JIGSAW BUZZING)
ALL RIGHT ONCE YOU GOT THE
STRAPS CUT THROUGH THERE
YOU JUST GOT TO POP THOSE
METAL CLIPS OFF THE TOP.
(CLANKING & BANGING)
THOSE THINGS ARE REALLY
ON THERE!
(LOUD CRASHING & BANGING)
OH BOY! (HACKING & COUGHING)
ALL RIGHT THAT'S GOT HER.
WELL NOW WHAT WE HAVE TO DO
IS PUT THE NEW WEBBING ON THERE
IT'S EXPENSIVE STUFF I'LL
TELL YOU, $15 BUCKS A ROLL
SEEMS A LITTLE STEEP
TO FIX A $2 LAWN CHAIR
DON'T YOU THINK?
BUT LUCKILY I MAY NOT HAVE
MONEY BUT I HAVE IMAGINATION,
OF COURSE I'D RATHER HAVE MONEY.
SO I'D SUGGEST YOU USE SOMETHING
ELSE LIKE MAYBE RIBBON ALTHOUGH
NOW THE SIDES OF THAT ARE PRETTY
SHARP YOU KNOW YOU THINK A
PAPER CUT'S BAD TRY SLIDING
YOUR BACKSIDE OVER THAT IN
YOUR SPEEDO THAT'LL GET
YOUR ATTENTION
HAVE YOUR OWN CHECKERBOARD
ON THERE OR YOU COULD USE
LAMP CORD THAT'LL WORK GOOD
THAT'S NOT SHARP ON THE EDGE
AT ALL COMES IN THE BROWN
COMES IN THE WHITE COULD
BE KIND OF ATTRACTIVE.
OF COURSE I HAVE A TON
OF THIS LEFTOVER FROM
THAT ELECTRIC WEAVER'S LOOM
I MADE LAST YEAR.
OR A CAR SEATBELT THAT WOULD
WORK WELL YOU'RE SITTING ON
THEM ANYWAY MIGHT AS WELL
MAKE IT OFFICIAL.
OR YOU CAN EVEN USE I GUESS
A KID'S SKIPPING ROPE
WHILE THEY'RE AT SCHOOL
THEY DON'T MIND YOU DOING
STUFF LIKE THAT.
WHATEVER YOU USE YOU WANT TO
ATTACH IT ALL ON THERE WITH
THE HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON
DUCT TAPE.
NOW YOU CAN DO IT THAT WAY
I GOT A BETTER IDEA
LOOK AT THAT, SHINY SILVER FRAME
SHINY SILVER WEBBING KIND
OF LOOKS LIKE THE LONE RANGER'S
LAWN CHAIR DOESN'T IT?
AND THAT SHINY CHROME JUST
SCREAMS MONEY AS FAR
AS I'M CONCERNED OR MAYBE
IT JUST SCREAMS IMAGINATION
AND SHE IS STRONG.
I'LL TELL YOU YOUR AUNT ORCA
COULD SIT IN THIS BABY.
LET'S TRY HER OUT,
OH YEAH, OH YEAH.
OH THAT'S SOLID YOU GOT ROOM
FOR ME IN HERE AND A FULLY
STOCKED COOLER AND YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU COULD DO IS YOU COULD
SAY MAKE A PATIO UMBRELLA
AND A HAMMOCK AND EVEN A GARDEN
TRELLIS COVER THEM ALL WITH
THE DUCT TAPE AND YOU GOT KIND
OF A COORDINATED LOOK
CAN'T BEAT THAT.
SO REMEMBER IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OH WELL, NOW HERE'S AN ADDED
BONUS YOU CAN USE THE
CHAIR AS A LINT REMOVER
OR A HAIR REMOVER
FORGOT ABOUT THE RIP
IN THOSE PANTS.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>HAROLD: THIS IS THE PART
OF THE SHOW THAT I LOVE BECAUSE
WE EXPOSE THOSE 3 LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO DIFFICULT
TO SAY, 'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT
ONCE AGAIN IS MY UNCLE RED
AND HIS BEST FRIEND IN THE
WHOLE WIDE WORLD TODAY
IT'S MISTER DOUGIE FRANKLIN.
HERE'S THE LETTER,
'DEAR EXPERTS I AM THINKING
OF TAKING THE FAMILY ON
A VACATION THIS WINTER
ARE THERE ANY PLACES
YOU WOULD RECOMMEND?'
>>RED: WELL GOLLY THERE ARE
JUST SO MANY OF THEM YOU KNOW
BEAUTIFUL SPOTS MOOSE LAKE,
MOOSEJAW, MOOSE FACTORY IS NICE
MOOSONEE THIS TIME OF YEAR.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED I THINK
THE VIEWER WOULD LIKE
LESS MOOSE AND MORE FUN.
>>RED: OH ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
>>DOUGIE: YOU KNOW YOU GOT
YOUR BAHAMAS YOU KNOW
YOU GOT THE BARBIDOS
YOU GOT YOUR BIMINI ISLAND
YOUR BIKINI ATOLL, PUETY ARTY
YOU KNOW BUT I WOULD RECOMMEND
TO ANYBODY IF YOU'RE LOOKING
INTO A TROPICAL PARADISE
REMEMBER THESE 3 WORDS
FOLKS 3 WORDS FOOD, WEATHER,
MEDICAL CARE YOU CAN'T TELL ME
THE BEST DOCTORS IN THE WORLD
ARE WORKIN' THAT RESORT CIRCUIT.
>>HAROLD: WELL IS THERE A PLACE
THAT YOU WOULD RECOMMEND
MISTER FRANKLIN?
>>DOUGIE: WELL SIR I WOULD
THINK BEFORE I'D SIGN ON
THE DOTTED LINE FOR ANY
ONE OF THOSE TROPICAL TOURS
I'D TAKE A GOOD HARD LOOK AT
A '65 OR A '66 MUSTANG HAROLD.
>>RED: DOUGIE I DON'T THINK
THAT IS TECHNICALLY A RESORT
EVEN IF YOU TURN THE HEATER
UP FULL ON THAT ONE.
>>DOUGIE: WELL THAT'S THE POINT
THOUGH RED I MEAN YOU KNOW WHY
BLOW YOUR BRAINS OUT ON 2 WEEKS
OF SUNSTROKE AND DIARRHEA
YOU KNOW WHEN FOR THE SAME PRICE
YOU COULD INVEST OKAY IN A
MINT BOSS 3O2 CONVERTIBLE
INSTEAD OF FUN IN THE SUN
YOU COULD HAVE IT
MADE IN THE SHADE.
>>HAROLD: YEAH BUT I STILL
DON'T THINK YOU COULD REALLY
EQUATE YOU KNOW SEEING
ANOTHER COUNTRY, ANOTHER CULTURE
EVEN WITH BUYING A USED CAR.
>>DOUGIE: HAROLD THE AMOUNT
OF MONEY I'VE SPENT ON MY
MONSTER TRUCK I COULD'VE
BEEN AROUND THE WORLD 3,
MAYBE 4 TIMES AND WHAT
WOULD I HAVE TO SHOW FOR IT?
>>HAROLD: WELL ADVENTURE,
KNOWLEDGE, MEMORIES.
>>DOUGIE: OH YOU CANNOT
CRUSH CARS WITH MEMORIES.
>>RED: GOT YOU THERE HAROLD.
IT IS SUMMER
A SHOTGUN, A BIG HUNTING KNIFE,
LEG HOLD TRAPS, TRIP WIRES,
PISTOLS...
YOU'RE ARMED AND YOU'RE READY
AND GOD HELP THE NEIGHBOUR
WHO TRIES TO USE YOUR POOL.
>>RED: I TOOK THE APPLICATION
FORM TO RANGER GORD BUT HE
WAS ALL EXCITED ABOUT
SOMETHING ELSE.
>>GORD: OH I WANT TO SHOW
YOU SOMETHING COME HERE,
LOOK OUT THERE
YOU NOTICE ANYTHING?
>>RED: FOREST?
>>GORD: NO A TREE,
A NEW LITTLE TREE.
>>RED: WHAT COLOUR IS IT?
>>GORD: IT'S GREEN
IT'S A GREEN ONE, CUTE HUH?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING
TO CALL HIM YET
OH NO IT'S A HER.
>>RED: 3100 DAYS FOLKS.
>>GORD: YUP BEST ATTENDANCE
RECORD IN THE PROVINCE
MR RELIABLE THEY CALL ME,
THAT'S WHY H.Q. SENT ME
TO THIS TOWER
THIS IS THE TOUGHEST TOWER
THEY GOT I'M THE TOUGHEST
RANGER THEY GOT.
>>RED: IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT,
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT GORD
GORD ONE THING THAT YOU
COULD HELP ME WITH HERE.
I'VE GOT THIS GRANT APPLICATION
FOR THE GOVERNMENT,
I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU COULD
POINT OUT ANY PROBLEMS
YOU THINK IT MIGHT HAVE
OR WHATEVER.
>>GORD: SURE I'M GOOD WITH
THE CLERICAL SIDE OF THINGS TOO
SO IF H.Q. HAS A CUSHY DESK
JOB AVAILABLE I'M READY.
>>RED: YEAH WELL WE'RE TRYING
TO UPGRADE POSSUM LODGE.
>>GORD: OH YEAH YOU'LL BE
FINE AS LONG AS YOU DON'T
HAVE POLLUTION PROBLEMS.
>>RED: YEAH?
>>GORD: IT SAYS YOU'LL
HAVE TO CLEAN UP ANY
ENVIRONMENTAL INFRACTIONS.
>>RED: OH YEAH, ALL RIGHT
WE CAN DO THAT, WE'VE GOT
THE SEPTIC SYSTEM NOW.
>>GORD: OH YEAH, YEAH BUT YOU
KNOW YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO HOOK IT UP HUH?
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
WELL THANK YOU GORD THAT WAS
TERRIFIC THANKS.
>>GORD: DON'T GO!
DON'T GO! DON'T GO!
>>RED: I GOTTA...
>>GORD: NO PLEASE LOOK
I MADE A HUGE SALAD.
>>RED: WELL WE'RE GETTING
THERE WITH THE CLEAN UP
STINKY PETERSON SAYS THAT
HE CAN FIND THE LID
TO THE SEPTIC TANK
BECAUSE HE KNOWS WHAT PART OF
THE LAKE IT DROPPED INTO
WHEN IT BLEW OFF DURING
MEXICAN NIGHT.
AND NOW BUSTER HADFIELD
IS OUT WITH A SNOW SHOVEL
SKIMMING THE SCUM OFF OF
POSSUM BAY AND MOOSE THOMPSON
IS CONVERTING THE BARBECUE TO
RUN OFF PROPANE INSTEAD
OF OLD FURNITURE.
>>HAROLD: THAT'S WONDERFUL
UNCLE RED BUT YOU KNOW ALL THIS
CLEAN UP AND CONVERSION
IT COSTS MONEY AND WHO'S
GOING TO PAY FOR THAT?
>>RED: OH THE LODGE IS HAROLD
OUT OF THE GRANT MONEY.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH THAT'S ALL
WELL AND GOOD BUT
WHAT IF IT DOESN'T ADD UP?
WHAT IF THE EXPENSES WHEN
SUBTRACTED FROM THE GRANT
ACTUALLY EQUAL A DEBIT
WHICH IS OFTENTIMES YOU KNOW
CREATED AND SYMBOLIZED BY
THAT OF A NEGATIVE INTEGER.
>>RED: INTERESTING CONCEPT
FROM A GUY WHO GOT 43 IN MATH.
>>HAROLD: DON'T THAT'S PERSONAL
AND PRIVATE PROPERTY
YOU SHOULDN'T BE LOOKING
OR NOTHIN' AT IT.
>>RED: I DON'T THINK HAROLD HAS
THE STRENGTH OR COORDINATION
TO TAKE THIS OFF ME IF HIS GYM
MARK IS ANY INDICATION.
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ OH THERE ONCE WAS A GUY ♪
♪ FROM THE CITY NAMED DAVE ♪
♪ WHO CAME UP HERE TO CAMP ♪
♪ WELL DAVE NEVER WORE PYJAMAS ♪
♪ AND HE SAID THAT WAS ♪
♪ REALLY CAMP ♪
♪ WHEN IT CAME TIME ♪
♪ TO GO TO BED ♪
♪ ♪ WE HEARD A HORRIBLE YIP ♪
♪ WHILE ZIPPING UP HIS BEDROLL ♪
♪ DAVE HAD MADE A PAINFUL SLIP ♪
♪ WELL WE ALL HAD A ♪
♪ REAL GOOD LAUGH ♪
♪ WITH THE EXCEPTION OF DAVE ♪
♪ WHO NOW WEARS PYJAMAS ♪
♪ TO COVER A SCAR ♪
♪ THAT LOOKS LIKE A LITTLE ♪
♪ WEE WINDBREAKER ♪
♪ WHICH IS WHAT IT IS ♪
>>RED: IT'S TIME NOW FOR NEVER
LEND YOUR VAN TO AN IDIOT
OR AS WE CALL IT
'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'.
BILL HAD BORROWED THE VAN
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
WE KNOW BILL AND HE GOT HER
DEEP INTO A PUDDLE THERE
FULL OF WET MUD AND GOO
SO HE WANTS ME TO PUSH AND
HE'S GONNA, I'M NOT SURE IF
I SHOULD HAVE DONE THIS AND
HE GETS HER AND JUST GUNS HER.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU BILL
I'M SOAKED RIGHT THROUGH
AS FAR AS YOU CAN GO
WITH A PERMIT.
BILL THAT'S ENOUGH NOW
MAYBE YEAH, GOOD PLAN
I'LL DO THE DRIVING.
BILL'S GOING TO TAKE THESE
I THINK THEY'RE LIKE POTATO BAGS
BURLAP OR SOMETHING ONE BEHIND
I DON'T KNOW WHY PUT ONE
IN FRONT, I'M TRYING TO
GO FORWARD AREN'T I?
OH WELL ANYWAY IT'S HIS IDEA
NOW I'M GOING TO SPIN THE WHEELS
AND A WAY WE GO....
AND THEY JUST TOOK OFF
OH, OH, OH, OH BILL
STEPHEN KING LIVES!
NOW HE IS GOING TO TRY
SOMETHING ELSE,
HE'S GOT A BIT OF STRAW THERE
ON A SHOVEL AND HE WANTS
ME TO GET THE WHEELS TURNING
AND HE'S GOING TO PUT THE STRAW
IN THERE AND THAT'S GOING TO
YOU KNOW I GUESS THE WHEEL
IS GOING TO BITE ON THE STRAW
BUT ACTUALLY IT KIND OF BIT
ON THE SHOVEL, OH BOY!
WOW, HOLY SMOKE THAT COULD
BE A NEW OLYMPIC EVENT EH BILL?
AND NOW ANOTHER STROKE OF
BRILLIANCE HE'S GOING TO
ROCK THE VAN,
HE'LL PUSH AND I GO FORWARD
THEN HE PULLS BACK
AND I GO BACK
WE CAN FEEL IT WE'RE
GETTING SOMEWHERE YEAH, YEAH,
SHE'S COMING SHE'S COMING!
OH, OH! WELL I CAN GET LONGER
STUFF IN THE VAN NOW.
>>RED: AND NOW FOR ALL YOU
YOUNG KIDS WHO DON'T MIND
WASTING TIME, HERE'S HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: GET READY BECAUSE
HERE'S THE PART OF THE SHOW
FOR ANYONE WHO'S IN SCHOOL
OH WAIT A SEC, I DON'T MEAN
ANYONE WHO'S IN SCHOOL RIGHT NOW
'CAUSE IF YOU'RE IN SCHOOL RIGHT
NOW HOW ARE YOU WATCHING
THE SHOW? GOT YOU!
OKAY SO WE SHOULD CALL
THIS ANYONE WHO ATTENDS SCHOOL
ALL RIGHTY, ANYWAY THIS WEEK'S
SEGMENT IS CALLED
SEE THE WAY I MADE THE
ROMAN NUMERAL 11, TRES COOL!
ALMOST A METAPHOR.
CREATES THE SUGGESTION OF
A SEQUEL IMPLYING PREVIOUS
SUCCESS, ALWAYS THINKING.
OKAY ALL RIGHT THE
BOTTOM LINE IS RESPECT,
I MEAN RESPECT MY FRIENDLIES
IS A 2 WAY STREET, ALL RIGHT?
YOU HAVE TO RESPECT THE TEACHER
AND THE TEACHER HAS TO RESPECT
YOU ONLY YOU KNOW YOU
GOT TO GO FIRST.
AND THE BEST WAY I FOUND TO
EARN THEIR RESPECT IS ONCE
A MONTH YOU WASH, WAX AND
VACUUM THEIR CAR.
THIS CREATES A SPIRIT OF
COOPERATION YES ALTHOUGH IT
MAY NOT NECESSARILY INCREASE
YOUR MARKS ANY...
BUT YOU KNOW OKAY SAY LIKE
IN MATH YOU GOT LIKE 43
AND YOU JUST NEED THOSE
9 MORE MARKS TO GET THAT 55
OH YOU KNOW YOU'RE BEGGING AND
YOU'RE PLEADING AND EVERYTHING
AND THE TEACHER SAYS WELL
I'LL GET BACK TO YOU WON'T I?
RIGHT THERE YOU SEE THAT'S
BETTER THAN A FLAT
NO LIKE LAST TIME.
YOU KNOW YOU MAY HAVE TO WAIT
A WHILE YOU KNOW LIKE UP TO
A MONTH SAY YOU KNOW FOR SOME
KIND OF AN IOTA OF AN IDEA
THAT THEY'RE GOING TO GET
BACK TO YOU JUST SAY...
>>RED: HAROLD YOUR MATH
TEACHER'S ON THE PHONE.
>>HAROLD: OH THIS IS SO COOL!
'CAUSE I ONLY NEED 9 MORE
MATH MARKS, WOO!
(LOUD CRASHING)
>>RED: OR 9 MORE
FEET OF CABLE.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: I KNOW YOU TEENAGERS
ARE MAINLY INTERESTED IN
ONE THING, SEX AND VIOLENCE
SO I THINK WHAT THE SCHOOLS
SHOULD DO IS KIND OF STRESS
SAY THE SEX PART OF SOMETHING
LIKE SHAKESPEARE,
YOU GOT HAMLET THERE
HE'S ALWAYS TALKING ABOUT HIS
BARE BODKIN AND HE SAYS OPHELIA
RIGHT TO HIS GIRLFRIEND AND HOW
PERVERTED WOULD YOU HAVE TO
BE TO BE CALLED KING LEAR?
AND YOU GOT OTHELLO
YOU GOT INTERRACIAL SEX
AND MURDER AND SUICIDE
AND IF YOU'RE REALLY INTO
THE KINKY STUFF YOU GOT
THE 2 GENTLEMEN OF VERONA
AND AS YOU LIKE IT.
SO I SUGGEST YOU TEENAGERS
DROP THE RAP MUSIC AND
THE MADONNA VIDEOS AND
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS
SHAKESPEARE STUFF
JUST DON'T TELL YOUR PARENTS.
>>RED: HAP CAN YOU TAKE THIS
LETTER INTO TOWN AND MAIL IT
FOR ME IT'S IMPORTANT.
>>HAP: CAN'T DO IT RED
CAN'T ACCEPT BONDED MATERIALS
I MADE A PROMISE TO THE
WITNESS RELOCATION PEOPLE
BUT IF YOU LIKE I'LL
TAKE YOU TO TOWN AND
YOU CAN MAIL IT.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT LET'S GO.
>>HAP: IF YOU'RE REALLY IN
A HURRY I CAN START HER UP
WITHOUT TURNING ON THE BLOWERS
THAT'D GET YOU MOVING IN A REAL
BIG HURRY BUT I CAN'T GUARANTEE
YOU'LL BE HEADING TOWARDS TOWN.
>>RED: NO, NO, NO,
GO DO THE BLOWER THING
AND I'LL UNTIE HER.
>>HAP: NO, NO WAIT, HANG ON
THERE'S ONLY ROOM FOR ONE
CAPTAIN ON ANY SHIP RED
I LEARNED THAT ON THE BISMARCK.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT
STANDING BY TO CAST OFF CAPTAIN.
>>HAP: AREN'T YOU GOING
TO ASK ME ABOUT THE BISMARCK?
>>RED: NOT UNTIL
AFTER WE GET BACK.
>>HAP: CAST OFF.
WHAT IS IT WE'RE MAILING TODAY?
>>RED: AN APPLICATION FORM
FOR A GOVERNMENT GRANT
FOR THE LODGE.
>>HAP: WELL WHY DIDN'T YOU
TELL ME, MY CONNECTIONS
GO ALL THE WAY UP
INCLUDING REAGAN.
>>RED: WELL REAGAN'S NOT
PRESIDENT ANYMORE HAP.
>>HAP: YOU JUST DON'T
GET IT DO YOU RED?
THEY WANT YOU TO BELIEVE
HE'S NOT PRESIDENT
BUT I THINK I WOULD KNOW.
>>RED: WELL IT WOULDN'T MATTER
ANYWAY BECAUSE THIS APPLICATION
IS FOR THE CANADIAN GOVERNMENT.
>>HAP: BOY ARE YOU NAÏVE.
>>RED: JUST GET ME TO THE POST
OFFICE WOULD YOU PLEASE HAP.
>>HAP: IT'S A TOUGH
OLD JOB BEING PRESIDENT
ALL THOSE PRESS CONFERENCES
AND THE SUMMIT TALKS AND
THE ASSASSINATIONS,
I FOUND IT REAL HARD TO
RELAX WHEN I WAS IN OFFICE.
>>RED: YOU WERE PRESIDENT HAP?
>>HAP: OH JUST A COUPLE OF
WEEKS SUBBED IN FOR NIXON
SO HE COULD TAKE THE
FAMILY TO A CLUB MED.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT HAP
THAT'S CLOSE ENOUGH
I THINK I CAN SWIM FROM HERE.
(LOUD SPLASH)
>>RED: WELL BY GOLLY YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO BELIEVE THIS
BUT WE GOT OUR GOVERNMENT
CHEQUE BY RETURN MAIL
THEY MUST BE MORE DISORGANIZED
THAN EVER DOWN THERE.
>>HAROLD: THIS IS EXCELLENT!
THAT MEANS WE'RE GOING
TO BE STINKING RICH!
ARE WE GOING TO BE
STINKING RICH UNCLE RED?
>>RED: WELL I DON'T KNOW HAROLD
I HAVEN'T OPENED IT YET
FIGURED I'D SAVE THAT
FOR TONIGHT'S MEETING.
>>HAROLD: WOW THIS IS EXCITING!
THIS IS HISTORY IN THE MAKING.
>>RED: WELL LET'S JUST SEE IF
YOU'RE AN AUTHORITY ON HISTORY
38, NO I DON'T BELIEVE
THAT QUALIFIES.
>>HAROLD: WELL EVERYTHING
IS RELATIVE ISN'T IT UNCLE RED?
38 OF COURSE WOULDN'T BE BAD
CONSIDERING SOME PEOPLE GOT 12
LITTLE TROUBLE IN SCHOOL
THERE WAS THERE UNCLE RED?
>>RED: WHERE DID
YOU GET THAT HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: GRAMMA GREEN
SHE'S GOT A WHOLE STACK OF THESE
SHE'S SAVING THEM UP FOR
THE GUINNESS PEOPLE.
I NEVER MET ANYBODY WHO FAILED
ART CLASS BEFORE OH BOY!
OH HELLO LOOK AT THIS
IT'S GOT YOUR REAL NAME
RIGHT AT THE TOP RIGHT THERE
I CAN SEE WHY YOU'D WANT
TO BE CALLED RED,
THAT'S WAY MORE BETTER
THAN THIS ONE.
EXPLAINS THE TEACHER'S
COMMENTS ABOUT WHY YOU
GOT IN SO MANY FIGHTS.
OH THIS IS GOING TO BE
GREAT AT THE POSSUM MEETING
TONIGHT THE GUYS ARE GOING
TO LOVE TO FIND OUT THAT
RED GREEN'S TRUE NAME IS...
>>RED: HAROLD! HAROLD!
>>HAROLD: OH, PERHAPS WE COULD
WORK OUT SOME KIND OF TRADE?
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH THAT'S THE
CRY OF THE POSSUM
I'VE GOT TO GET DOWN THERE.
HURRY UP UNCLE RED
AND DON'T FORGET
THE CHEQUE OKAY?
>>RED: YEAH ALL RIGHT HAROLD.
WELL EXCITING!
THAT'S KIND OF OUR SHOW
FOR THIS TIME SO IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING I'LL BE COMING HOME
STRAIGHT AFTER THE MEETING
I'LL BE BRINGING A BIG WAD
OF CASH SO WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE GO NUTS?
RENT A MOVIE
ORDER IN A PIZZA
MAYBE EVEN TIP THE GUY
WEALTH MEANS NOTHING
WITHOUT STYLE.
AND FOR THE REST OF YOU ON
BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE THANKS
FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
♪ ♪ ♪
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>ALL: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>HAROLD: OKAY SIT DOWN.
♪ ♪ ♪
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca