Get ready for spine tingling adventure for
the greatest outdoorsman show since Larry of
the Jungle. I saw with with songs and films,
nudity and offensive language.
I show even young people will like.
And here he is, the star of our show and my
uncle through some bizarre
Case of mistaken identity, which happened to
lead to a hasty wedding.
But that's a long story.
Here he is, the most average man in the
world.
The round knob on the bell for real life.
The game show Mr.
Red Green.
Carol, thank you.
Welcome to Possum Lodge.
I'd like to apologize for Harold's intro,
the only nudity we have here are bald spots,
and there's nothing wrong with our language.
It's the people that use it that are
offensive.
I'm just trying to add some edge, you know,
some controversy like I do with my special
effects unit. No harm in that.
You know, young people like to make more of
things than they really are.
You know, it's something I guess they have
to do in order to help them find their way in
life and everything. I guess it's natural,
but bugs that crap out of me anyway.
Even in our annual report from our lodge
treasurer, Douglas and I thought it was a
pretty well received considering nobody had
read it and nobody listened.
What are you doing, Douglas, the large box?
Oh, you're busy.
Yes, I am.
I know that's hard
For a government employee to relate
To. Was there something else?
Oh, yeah. Would you like to play a game of
golf?
Huh? For flak, huh?
Well, let's see.
I'm very busy wrapping up the large accounts
by the end of the month.
I have to pay the bills and write the checks.
And I hate golf.
So no, I guess not.
Oh, how about you, Harold?
I feel like 18.
I am 18. Come on, guys.
The Sun is shining.
It's nice weather.
Doesn't that just show dimpled balls and
mushy nipples?
Ok. How about a little game of golf?
A mini game. A game of mini golf?
Thank you very much. So enjoy yourself,
though.
Well, I can't wait all day for you guys to
decide.
Oh yeah, by the way, mail came letters for
you.
Well, I'm off to see if anybody else is
interested in a foursome.
Boy, I thought he'd never leave those tramps
hanging in the hallway there.
Oh my God. Who were being audited?
The largest being audited?
Harold, the Blue Lodge is being audited.
Oh boy. Oh, what does that mean?
Are you going to get hurt at all?
This is the end. This is it.
So who the government is against this?
You know how many people they have working
for them who are outnumbered?
Oh, we're done for. Well, I'm going to go
over.
I'm going to count and find out.
We didn't pay enough tax.
Well, how much tax did we pay that this?
None. Oh, that doesn't sound like enough.
Well, now don't worry, fellas, I've been
through this kind of thing before.
All right, everybody, come on over here.
Bill Douglas Harold, grab a seat at the
table.
Ooh, what's this all about, Doug?
I don't like this. You scare me.
I don't get your knickers in or not.
Douglas, grab a seat now read I'm going to
need about a dozen ballpoint pens and a big
wad of paper and hot water lots and lots of
hot water.
No, that's something entirely different.
It could make some coffee.
Yeah. Get the hot water.
Read Well.
Oh yeah, I'll get right on that doc.
Take notes. Oh, Harold, remember that pair of
rubber boots you bought last year so you
could help retrieve old man Sedgwick's teeth
from the swamp?
Oh, vaguely, that was a business expense.
All right. Now, now what are those puppies
set you back?
Fourteen, ninety nine.
My mother still complains about that.
All right. Well rounded off an even hundred.
He doesn't have a receipt.
Well, he will suit his red gets back with
the pens and paper.
Now remember fellows, you got to print real
nice.
So they look official. All right.
That's it. Leap.
No, no.
He's right. You're right.
Douglas, he's right.
So does only the Lodge Treasurer go to jail
or can read be charged two for not keeping
track of your financial misdeeds.
What about haircuts?
I got one for every lodge meeting.
That's another five hundred right there.
Need the Herald zit cream?
How about no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't want to go to court and have to
testify that I have zits.
I don't want Judge Wapner knowing that, oh
yeah.
Bills, medical expenses, they're the stuff.
Stuffy damages. So let's a couple hundred in
a week anyway.
No repairs to the lodge.
You know, renovations, upgrading, cleaning
expenses.
Maintenance costs can't push that one
through thinking about this place?
Ah, yeah, I'm sure, but probably.
Movie rentals for the VCR.
That's why I push it up.
Oh, wait a minute, we don't have a VCR.
There's a bit of a loophole. Yeah. Dig, dig,
dig,
boy, that's a nice ring shuttle, boys that
pick ax ring again four times.
Oh, dig, dig, dig boys work hard to say
because
We got to get the sceptics in and operational
before the men finish lunch.
And you. This week in my corner, we're going
to do a little bit of concentrating on
safety. You've all heard the expression
safety first.
Actually, at the Lodge, it's more like
But you know what's with the decay of moral
values in society?
The members all feel they now have something
to live for.
So there's a whole new focus there on the
idea of safety, and this gave me an idea.
You know, the new cars now have these have
these airbags that are in front of you there.
And now I'm not talking about like the
little bags they have in front of you on the
airplane. I was thinking, what if you had a
personal airbag, something you could wear on
your body at all times for any kind of a
front end collision or whatever somebody?
I went design one of those. And of course,
the first thing you're going to need is an
undershirt. An undershirt is usually just
holding your own stomach, but this time it's
going to be having something of value.
So you want a sealer off real good.
You go across the bottom with some staples.
You might want to make two or three rows of
staples on there.
And then once you've got the staples all in
place, you want to just cover that up with
the handyman secret weapon duct tape.
This is just a safety precaution, really to
cover up the staples because any of you
who've ever been to the outhouse with a
magazine know the damage the stables can do.
I'll finish that off later.
What I want to show you right now is the
most important part of the airbag, which is
the airbag. Nothing runs like a deer.
What do you like a lawn bag?
But this is going to save your life.
What you do is open up your shirt or open up
your blouse or well, that's to stick with the
shirt now and. Right, pack the bag in there,
just like packing a parachute or there was a
movie one time where I think they said, Are
you packing a parachute or are you just glad
to see me? Chuck Lane with this parachute.
All right. What's that's in place, you need
something that's going to fill the bag up,
something to inflate the bag.
And when you think about safety, what do you
think of?
Fire extinguisher and fill that thing up in
two seconds flat.
Now make sure you get the CO2 kind.
Otherwise, you'll be picking fire retardant
out of your shorts for the next twenty four
years and a natural and unobtrusive looking,
isn't it?
And the beauty of it is like, just be
walking down the street and if anything,
should start coming towards me.
I have a full frontal nature, grabs a
speeding truck and what have you.
I just reach
Calmly up over my back quickly, but
Call me up over my back and pull a safety pin
and and just release my personal air bag.
It's that simple. I remember women don't
find it handsome, they should at least find
it handy. I'm freezing and I
Bought my bag. Twist Oh, twist.
Plenty of those big bags
Spot over there, but.
It is autumn Thanksgiving weekend.
Friends and family gather around the TV
Friday night, a basketball game Saturday,
three college football games, hockey at
night, so I'm ready for football games.
Some stock car races in a basketball game
Monday, five football games, the Belgian
Grand Prix and two hockey games.
We really do have so much to give.
Thanks for this year.
So unfortunately, money problems tend to
ruin friendships or whatever it is we have
going for us up here at the Lodge and things
are kind of deteriorated to the point that
people are starting to point fingers at each
other and asking questions like what color a
shoe polish were you drinking when you
bought that?
Well, you know, I'm glad there were some
questionable purchases of late.
You know, I'm talking like the the eight
slot car race track sets, you know, minus the
transformer in cars, the lava lamps, the
wind power
Typewriter, all the backhoe.
What's wrong with the back, Harold?
Nothing, absolutely nothing.
Because I forgot that you purchased that,
didn't you?
It doesn't matter who bought it, Harold.
I mean, backhoe was either a smart purchase
or it wasn't.
I say it was.
Oh, yes, yes. Yes. Yes, yes.
Yes. Oh, it was. I'm just saying that, you
know, you could always rent one.
Yeah. Yeah. Rent one, but if you're renting
one, often enough, it's cheaper to buy a back
home.
Exactly. Yes, yes it is.
It's just the only difference is that the
rental one it runs.
Yes. And the one that I bought will run to
hell as soon as those carburetor parts come
in. Now, don't forget that.
That's how I got such a great price on.
Oh yes, indeed he do.
You got an excellent price on it.
You know, I'm just I'm just some skeptics,
some skeptics, they might ask themselves
like, Well, why did they buy a backhoe that
doesn't run yet?
They continue to rent one that does
something.
Well, Harold, you're just you're just not
going to understand this.
Ok, that's that's that simple.
It's the difference between capital
expenditure in daily operating costs.
You know, you're never going to figure this
out here.
No, no, it's beyond me.
Hi, Bob. Oh, hi.
How are you doing?
Well, I go. Go, figure.
Sorry.
Not bad. I guess I'm doing a little bit of
ministry work.
Oh, don't worry about it.
All right. It's not important.
What are you doing here?
It's the ministry work.
Does land survey.
You do that with the golf ball.
Well, it's the fastest way to, you know,
check which way the green breaks.
Oh yeah, the land breaks.
The land slopes.
Oh, oh yeah.
Oh, yeah, definitely a problem.
Yeah, yeah, definitely some lateral movement
in the sub strata.
Yeah. See, the ball
Didn't go where you wanted it to go.
No, right? Well, a bomb.
But you know, I guess you heard we're being
audited up at the lodging site.
Maybe you could kind of help.
Not that we want to cook the books, you
know, but we were thinking, You know what?
The way you keep your golf score,
You could just just wait here.
I'll listen to me read. I mean, you can
check my golf scorecards all the way back to
nineteen seventy three and you won't find
one discrepancy
And those are signed cards to sign them
myself.
That's good enough for me, Bob.
You probably didn't affect the leaderboard
anyway, right?
You're wondering about my scoring is that is
how I score is that is
Oh, you all been talking about I'll tell you
what, I will put all my work aside, and you
and I'll play a game of golf. I'll start
from zero right now.
How about that, huh? No, no, no, no.
Sure, that's fine. That's fine.
What I was thinking, though, is you're the
only lodge member who is with the government,
and I thought you could kind of explain what
this auditing process is and also maybe give
us some insight tips, you know, and so on.
And what's expected?
Well, I'm with the natural resources.
I'm not with revenue, so I really don't know
much about tax deductibles and you know, that
kind of stuff, you know, I don't know
anything about that.
Oh boy.
Yeah, definitely some
Bad movement there, though the whole
continent is in trouble, you know, that
Offer our our adventure.
This week, bill pulled something out of his
pants, which I thought originally was, some
of them a fishnet pantyhose that he wears a
party sometimes.
And actually, it was. It was a hammock for
today's adventure.
And the first thing you got to do is kind of
unwind it.
And I think we should have just discussed,
you know, whether we're going to go clockwise
or counterclockwise.
And then he started. He got lots of
patients.
That's your kind of surgery right there
anyway.
Yeah. Look, look, look.
Look out. Oh no.
Wait, my only kind of.
Oh, there we switch names. Maybe that's what.
Let's look. All right.
Okay. All right. All right.
I see what you mean. Anyway, we got her.
I got her and then we the trees were just
going.
I think just a little too bit a bit further,
a little too.
Maybe not quite close enough together,
though, I'm trying to say.
But on the other hand, you know, if you do
use trees that are just that little bit
extra, a bit of hard, you get a real good, a
real good tension on the
On the unit. Maybe a little too much.
I don't know.
Well, she's not in shape, but bills, bills,
game, you know, and try hammocks.
There's a lot to the hammock, you know, and
I wonder how people are sleeping when they're
so darn tired from getting into the darn
thing, you know?
So then we decided to tie all four corners
off in this way.
She wouldn't pivot on it still had a bit of
spring to her, but it wouldn't flip over.
So we had a whole other.
Oh, oh, he's
50, 60 feet out there, so I figure, well,
heck, we're done with a hammock and he'll
probably just climb down, come on down,
Bill, come on down, come on down.
Not that way, though. Not that way, Bill.
Oh boy. Anyway, he's OK.
Hammocks are sure are relaxing, are they?
No, no, no, no, no.
See, I'm not saying anything about you walk
around.
I'm just saying that most men your age have
monstrous beer guts.
That's a major concern. Here is Harold.
Well, I'm just saying you don't understand it
because in this day and age, we're more
health conscious, certainly.
And and people are watching what they're
eating and what they're drinking.
How does that plus that equal monstrous beer
gut?
That's a sign of maturity maturity.
No, no. A giant sea turtle lived to be one
hundred and fifty.
You don't see a monstrous beer gut on him.
No, it's not a sign of maturity.
It's a sign of a twenty five year chugging
log contest.
Oh, you're not such great physical.
Shape yourself there, Harold.
I don't have a beer gut.
You have a pizza face.
It's cool. You started it
All. Probably just the beer talking.
Wow, we're all done making up our phony
receipts.
We got receipts for food, entertainment,
ammo, airplanes.
I'll tell you, there isn't a scrap of paper
within 40 miles of the lodge, which has
created a bit of a problem in the eyes
Of the rat. Have you seen Douglas yet today?
You know, he spent the entire day downtown
with a
Really strict looking guy from the
government.
Oh, right.
All right. Ok, well, I suppose Douglas will
explain that at tonight's lodge meeting.
Anyway, the guy has had so darn much fun
making up all the receipts that they've kind
of decided to do that as a as a business,
you know, for other service clubs or whoever
needs phony receipts, they're going to call
it fraud r us.
So they've asked the government to give them
a list of everybody was being audited and
then they'll just start making calls.
You know, I suppose there's a there's a flaw
and the reasoning somewhere would, by golly,
I can't spot it.
Typekit uncle read the squeal of the possum.
The meeting is about to begin.
I'll be downstairs. I'll wait for you down
there.
But you got to hurry, though, OK?
Ok, I'll I'll be right down.
I'll just zip down there and straighten out
the financial situation.
It shouldn't take very long. And maybe if
any of you have financial problems for your
own out there, you want some phony receipts.
Just drop us a line that's for some bogus
stuff.
Or we can also sell you a backroom.
Never get to sit out.
We're to start now. Right now, we're
starting right up.
Now, all right, first thing on the agenda is
who forgot to take the garbage out?
Oh, recognize the doc.
Render. Thank you, everybody.
Thank you, Douglas. Now these these bags
contain nine million dollars worth of
receipts. I've got a few here that I don't
think the government will accept.
I was here. This one here is for us having
our colors done.
No go, Bill Currier.
Maybe I can get a job in the prison laundry.
Earn five cents a day.
Ben, they don't.
But you'll come and see me in prison, won't
you?
It'll be in the next cell.
Well, didn't you tell the tax guys?
We have receipts? I even showed him.
All he did was laugh at me.
Just like that. You should.
You better start praying.
That's it. Pray it will declare ourselves a
religion.
God. Yeah. Yeah, those guys don't pay any
tax.
The Church of the Possum.
I like that. Right?
No, no. I mean, this place is a little bit
of heaven for all of us, isn't it?
Hey, guys. Well, I don't know.
I don't think taking the Lord's name in vain
a lot necessarily makes us a religion.
Ok, why don't we declare ourselves a charity
medal?
Ok. All right. Sounds great.
How about charitable golf game, huh?
But he said it ain't the least it's a in
your actions, we should declare ourselves a
disaster area.
Vijender, another claimed on Oh oh, I know,
I know this is what my mom does, right?
She's got like credit cards. When they get
all full up, she just gets like new credit
cards. Oh no, the government doesn't take
American Express.
That's when we we borrow against our credit
cards.
Ten thousand divided by 50 guys, it's three
hundred dollars.
That's right. All right.
We're safe now.
First thing tomorrow, we all hit the bank
and borrowed $300 to hundred.
Make great. I love you.
I love you. We're sorry.
Wow. There's no other business built up in
there.
I see whoever feels
I got to get up and entertain us.
Oh, the guy from red to show some butter?
You know, I'm going to tell some jokes and
then I'll go, OK.
This guy walks into a bar.
Yeah, which is strange because, OK, we say,
OK, two guys.
Two guys walk into this bar.
Oh, you can fool some of the people some of
the time.
But government isn't people.
No, I think our biggest mistake was
announcing our plans on national television
because a lot of civil servants watch this
show.
Actually, they take the show so they can
watch it at work.
And that way it doesn't cut into their
quality time.
But I suppose honesty is the best policy if
you have to have a policy.
So we'll settle our debt with the government
by just borrowing more money.
Hell, that's what they do.
Anyway, my wife is watching, I'll be coming
straight home after the meeting, and I'm
going to have to stay up late and go through
that shoebox full of receipts in the back of
the junk drawer. And that way, we'll be
ready for the guy guys coming over tomorrow.
So until next time, on behalf of myself and
Harold and all gang up here at large.
Keep your stick on the ice.
I got a million of them.
I got them. Ok.
What do you get when you cross a mink with a
kangaroo?
Nakuru No, a fur coat with one pocket when
you got jet?
Ok. All right.
What's signs of a species?
What's worse? A centipede with a sinus cold
or an elephant with athlete's feet?
Uh, the elephant?