IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE MAN'S MAN,
A LADIES' MAN,
THE MAN OF THE PEOPLE,
MAN, OH, MAN!
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
(Whistling)
THANK YOU!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT -- THANK YOU.
WELCOME TO POSSUM LODGE,
WHERE CIVILIZATION MEETS NATURE
AND NATURE LOSES.
HEY, HAROLD.
GUESS WHAT WE'RE UP TO TONIGHT.
HERE'S A HINT.
(Audience laughing)
GONNA BE FILLING THE CRACKS
IN THE WALLS?
DEMONSTRATE HOW SPIDERS
BUILD THEIR HOMES?
NO.
GONNA BE ACTING STUPID
AND IMMATURE?
YEAH, HE GOT IT.
ABOUT A MONTH AGO,
JUNIOR SINGLETON
GOT ENGAGED -- WE WERE SHOCKED
'CAUSE SHE'S NICE.
THEY'VE DONE THE SHOPPING
FOR GIFTS
AND ALL THE FITTINGS
AND ALL THAT CRAP.
FINALLY, TONIGHT,
IT ALL PAYS OFF
IN THE BIG CELEBRATION
EVERY MAN LOOKS FORWARD TO.
NO, UNCLE RED, THE WEDDING'S
NOT TILL
TOMORROW.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE STAG PARTY, HAROLD.
STAG PARTY'S TONIGHT, OK?
MOOSE THOMPSON'S ORGANIZING
THE FOOD FIGHT.
BUSTER HADFIELD'S DOING
THE DIRTY TRICKS.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S
MARKING THE CARDS.
HOW ARE YOU CONTRIBUTING?
I'M NOT GOING.
PERFECT!
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE OUT OF THIS,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
(Laughing)
WELL, JUST A FEW HOURS TO GO
TILL JUNIOR'S STAG PARTY.
I GOT ALL MY SUPPLIES HERE.
HAND BUZZER, PLASTER BANDAGES,
BALL AND CHAIN...
LAXATIVES THAT LOOK
LIKE CHOCOLATE...
(Laughing)
HOT GUM...
MOLASSES...
ANIMAL TRANQUILLIZER...
INDELIBLE INK...
WHOOPEE CUSHION,
WHOOPEE PILLOW,
WHOOPEE MATTRESS -- WHOOPEE!
UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED!
I GOT GOOD NEWS AND BAD NEWS.
JUNIOR ASKED ME TO GO
TO THE STAG AND I SAID YES.
WHAT'S THE GOOD NEWS?
HE ASKED ME TO GET THE MOVIES.
HE SAID, "THE MOVIES."
I SAID, "O-KAY".
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT HE'S TALKING ABOUT.
SURE YOU DO -- HE'S TALKING
ABOUT "THE MOVIES".
OHHHHH!
I DON'T KNOW.
I WENT TO ALL THE PLACES.
THE CONVENIENCE STORE, GAS BAR,
COFFEE SHOP, LAUNDROMAT...
THE GOOD MOVIES ARE GONE.
DID YOU TRY THE VIDEO STORE?
(Audience laughing)
OK.
YEAH.
WAHAHH, UNCLE RED!
HAVE I GOT SOME HOT MOVIES!
FORGET IT --
NONE OF THAT STUFF.
I HAVE TOO MUCH RESPECT
FOR WOMEN.
WE WON'T BE WATCHING
FILTHY MOVIES.
FILTHY MOVIES?! NO, NO, NO!
THESE ARE WAR MOVIES!
OH, RIGHT!
"THE DESERT FOX"...
"THE BIG RED ONE"...
"BUCK PRIVATES"...
WHO ARE YOU KIDDIN', HAROLD?
IF YOU LIKE UKULELE MUSIC,
CHANGE THE CHANNEL RIGHT NOW!
THIS IS A PREVIEW OF
THE "ADVENTURES WITH BILL".
KIND OF A HAWAIIAN THEME AND...
THOSE LEIS --
YOU CAN'T JUST HAVE ONE.
THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
THAT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE
"WELCOME TO HAWAII".
IT'S LIKE "WELCOME
TO FIRE ISLAND".
OHHH! OH! OHHH!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
I'LL GET MY OWN LEIS,
THANK YOU.
THAT'S SOMETHING TO LIVE BY,
RIGHT THERE.
WHAT BILL WILL ALSO DO
ALL THROUGH THE SHOW,
HE'LL COOK A TURKEY
IN THE LUAU STYLE,
WHERE THEY DIG THE HOLE.
IT'S A TRADITIONAL,
RITUAL THING,
KIND OF A POLYNESIAN THING.
THIS IS PART OF THE DANCE.
THE HANDS TELL THE STORY.
YEAH... OHHH!
THE DIRT TELLS THE STORY.
OHHHH!
AND THE SHOVEL USUALLY
ENDS THE STORY.
UH... YEAH, ANYWAY,
WE LIKE TO DO
SOME OF THE TRADITIONAL
COOKING AT THE LODGE.
THIS IS THE HAWAIIAN,
THE POLYNESIAN, THE FIJI...
HAVE THEY "FIJI"d YOU YET?
NO, THEY HAVEN'T COOKED...
NEVER MIND.
BILL'S DIGGING WITH-- NO, BILL,
THAT'S A UKULELE.
YOU DON'T USE THAT.
I USE THAT --
YOU USE THE SHOVEL.
BILL'S VERY CREATIVE.
AWAY YOU GO --
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES.
OHHHHH
I KNOW A GUY
WITH A CAR NAMED SUE
HE WAS THE BUTT
OF MANY JOKES
HE HAD NAMED HIS CAR
AFTER HIS WIFE
'CAUSE IT'S HARD TO START
AND IT SMOKES
THIS IS THE BIG ONE!
FOR THE GRAND PRIZE OF KEYS
TO A BRAND-NEW BUNGALOW
WORTH OVER $200,000!
OH, BABY!
WHO DONATED
THAT, HAROLD?
THE GUY WHO BOUGHT
THE BUNGALOW.
HE GOT NEW LOCKS,
SO HE DIDN'T WANT THESE KEYS.
THAT'S A GOOD KEYCHAIN.
YOU CAN USE THE KEYCHAIN.
UNCLE RED,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON HUMPHREY
TO SAY THIS WORD.
"DISCUSS."
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT,
DALTON.
WHEN YOU AND YOUR WIFE
DISAGREE ABOUT SOMETHING,
YOU AND SHE...
... ARGUE.
NO, NO YELLING, NO YELLING.
NO, YOU SAID MY WIFE.
ALL RIGHT, OK,
COULD BE ANYBODY'S WIFE
OR GIRLFRIEND, OR BOTH --
RIGHT, HAROLD?
OR, IN YOUR CASE, NEITHER!
OK, UH...
ANOTHER WORD
FOR "TALK".
NAG.
DIALOGUE.
DIATRIBE.
SHARE IDEAS.
COMPLAIN.
ALMOST OUT OF TIME, UNCLE RED.
YOU WANT TO COMMUNICATE
IN A FRIENDLY WAY.
TO GIVE IN.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
IF YOUR WIFE WANTS TO NAG,
ARGUE, OR COMPLAIN,
SHE'LL SAY, "HONEY,
"THERE'S SOMETHING
WE HAVE TO..."
... BUY.
(Audience laughing)
NO, AND BEFORE
YOU BUY ANYTHING,
FIRST,
YOU WOULD...
... KEEL OVER STONE-DEAD!
I'M NOT PUTTING ONE MORE DIME
INTO THAT LIVING ROOM!
PEOPLE EXPECT MOTH-HOLES
IN PLAID DRAPES.
THE CASE IS CLOSED.
I DON'T WANT TO DISCUSS IT!
HEY!
WHAT?
THAT WAS THE WORD.
DISCUSS!
(Applause)
(Grunting)
WHAT IS WITH
THESE CAR COMPANIES?
WHAT'S THE POINT
IN HAVING A GAS GAUGE
IF IT'S NOT ACCURATE?
WHEN IT SAYS "FULL",
IT IS FULL.
I GOT THE WET PANTS
TO PROVE IT.
WHEN IT SAYS "EMPTY",
YOU MIGHT HAVE ANOTHER
50 MILES IN THERE,
OR, AS IN THE CASE TODAY,
YOU MIGHT IN FACT BE EMPTY.
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
I’M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE A
COST-EFFECTIVE HOT TUB.
WHAT DOES A HOT TUB HAVE TO DO
WITH FUEL TANKS? SHHH!
I'M GONNA MAKE MY HOT TUB
OUT OF AN OLD FREEZER.
FREEZERS ARE MEANT
TO KEEP THINGS COLD.
SINCE THIS ONE DOESN'T
ANY MORE,
I FIGURE, WHY NOT USE IT
TO KEEP THINGS WARM?
LET'S START
AND FIND OUT WHY NOT.
(Grunting)
THIS WON'T MAKE A BIG HOT TUB,
BUT WITH ALL THE S.T.D.'s
AND G.S.T.'s AND I.O.U.'s
GOIN' AROUND,
MAYBE IT'S TIME TO GET BACK
TO THOSE INNOCENT TIMES
WHEN YOU JUST PLAYED
WITH YOURSELF IN THE BATHTUB.
SOME OF YOU ARE SAYING, "WHY
NOT USE THE BATHTUB ITSELF?"
FIRST, DON'T CONFUSE
ME STOPPING FOR BREATH
WITH A REQUEST FOR SUGGESTIONS.
AND SECONDLY,
WITH THE LID ON, YOU CAN KEEP
HEAT IN AND BIRD-TREATS OUT.
WE GOT A LITTLE LIGHT,
WHICH MAKES IT NICE FOR
THE ROMANTIC LATE-NIGHT DIPS,
AND MAYBE CAN HELP YOU
FIND YOUR TOUPEE.
TO TURN THIS INTO A HOT TUB,
YOU NEED A PUMP
WITH SOME HOSES ON 'ER.
I KNOW, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO ADD WATER.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
PUT BLEACH IN
TO PURIFY THE WATER.
YOU NEED TO ADD AIR TO IT.
THAT'S IF YOU'RE BUILDING
A REAL HOT TUB... I'M NOT.
THIS HERE IS A FAKE,
JUST A DECOY.
I'M JUST SOLVING
THE GAS-GAUGE PROBLEM
WITH THE POSSUM VAN.
WE WANT IT TO LOOK
LIKE A HOT TUB
SO THAT VISITORS WILL PARK
NEARBY WITHOUT WORRYING.
WHAT IT REALLY IS
IS OUR PERSONAL GAS STATION.
WHAT WE DO,
WHEN NOBODY'S LOOKING,
TAKE ONE END OF THE HOSE,
STICK THAT INTO THEIR GAS TANK.
YOU GRAB YOUR REVERSIBLE
PUMP CONTROL, PRESS "SUCK",
AND IT PUTS ALL THEIR GAS--
WELL, NOT ALL THEIR GAS.
YOU WANT TO LEAVE SOME
SO THEY CAN GET
A FEW MILES DOWN THE ROAD.
THEY WON'T SUSPECT ANYTHING.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
CLOSE THE LID.
YOU DON'T WANT GAS FUMES
TO GIVE YOU AWAY.
WE'VE BEEN THERE, HAVEN'T WE?
WE'LL JUST CUT THAT OFF.
THEN YOU BRING
YOUR OWN VEHICLE NEARBY...
AND PUT THE END OF THE HOSE
INTO YOUR VEHICLE
AND THEN YOU PRESS THE PUMP
TO "BLOW"
AND YOU ACTUALLY FILL UP
YOUR OWN TANK WITH THEIR GAS.
ISN'T THAT BEAUTIFUL?
BY GOLLY! NO ONE'S
ANY THE WISER.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
ONE MORE FILL-UP AND
I GET A SET OF DINNERWARE.
(Electricity sparking)
BY GOLLY, I'M WRONG.
THIS IS A HOT TUB.
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
SOME OF YOU TEENAGERS
ARE WORKIN' HARD AT SCHOOL,
SWEATING OUT SOME SLAVE-LABOUR
JOB ON WEEKENDS,
ONLY TO HAVE YOUR PARENTS SAY,
"CLEAN UP YOUR ROOM!
"NO, YOU CAN'T HAVE
A MOTORCYCLE.
"THE POLICE WANT TO TALK
TO YOU -- HIDE THAT STEREO."
YOU'RE THINKING,
"WHEN DOES THE FUN START?
"WHEN DOES LIFE TURN INTO
A BEER COMMERCIAL?"
WHERE EVERYBODY'S LAUGHING
AND EATING
AND NOT WORKING
AND NOT GETTING FAT.
YOU'RE THINKING YOU'RE
THE ONLY PERSON NOT HAVING FUN.
THE TRUTH IS,
FOR THE MOST PART,
EVERYBODY'S FAKING IT...
EVEN IN THE BEER COMMERCIAL.
THE LAUGHING AND EATING
IS JUST THOSE PEOPLE WORKING.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING.
IN MY LIFE, I'VE ONLY FOUND
THREE THINGS
THAT WERE PURE FUN.
FISHING, BELONGING
TO POSSUM LODGE,
AND PANTS
WITH AN ELASTIC WAISTBAND.
WELL, BY GOLLY,
THAT WAS SOME STAG LAST NIGHT!
AND THE WOMEN
MISSED THE WHOLE THING.
THEY WERE AT SOME STUPID SHOWER
FOR THE BRIDE.
IT WAS A LECTURE ON COOKING.
THEY HAD SOME GUY
NAMED MR. SUPER-BUNS.
(Laughing)
UNBELIEVABLE.
BERNICE SAID IT WAS
A REAL EYE-OPENER.
BUT, BY GOLLY,
WE HAD OURSELVES--
HAROLD, I DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
I LEFT WHEN
THE PRACTICAL JOKES STARTED.
I CAN ONLY TAKE
SO MANY WEDGIES.
BETTER TO GIVE THAN RECEIVE.
YOU KNOW,
ORIGINALLY,
WE WERE GONNA PLAY TRICKS
ON JUNIOR,
'CAUSE HE WAS THE GROOM.
THEN SOME SMART-ALEC YELLED,
"GET THE HEAD USHER!"
THAT WAS YOU --
YOU YELLED THAT.
(Laughing)
I HAD THE MOLASSES
AND THE FEATHERS.
WASTE NOT, WANT NOT.
WE DID THE USHERS
AND FATHER OF THE BRIDE.
THEN WE STARTED WORKING OUR WAY
THROUGH THE CROWD.
A PARTY LIKE THAT
MAKES YOU SEE IT'S WORTHWHILE
GETTING MARRIED.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
IF THE GROOM ISN'T THERE?
WE TAPED IT
TO STINKY'S PANT-LEG.
NOT THE BROOM, THE GROOM --
JUNIOR'S STILL MISSING.
NO, WE STRIPPED HIM.
WE CHAINED HIM TO THE DOCK.
I HEARD HE WAS GETTING
SOME DECENT NIBBLES.
NO, THAT
WASN'T JUNIOR.
YOU DID THAT
TO FLINTY McCLINTOCK.
NO, HAROLD, FLINTY,
WE PUT INTO A BODY CAST.
WE PUT HIM ON
A ONE-WAY TRAIN TO...
THAT MIGHT HAVE BEEN JUNIOR.
WAY TO GO, UNCLE RED,
WAY TO GO!
WEDDING'S IN LESS THAN
TWO HOURS AND THERE'S NO GROOM.
WAY TO GO!
SHE'LL HAVE TO MARRY FLINTY.
FLINTY'S WIFE WILL BE HAPPY
TO LET SOMEBODY ELSE TAKE OVER.
YEAH, I SUPPOSE.
(Red): MEANWHILE, BACK WITH
DON HO'S EVIL TWIN BROTHER,
GUNG HO...
OHHHH!
GOLLY, THERE'S THE TURKEY...
AND IT'S A BOY!
BY GOLLY... ALL RIGHT.
WE'VE DUG THE HOLE.
WE HAD A FIRE GOING.
OK, OK, BILL, BILL!
ALL RIGHT, WE GOT
THE ROCKS ALL HEATED.
WOW, THAT'S HOT, THAT'S HOT.
YOU GET THE ROCKS,
THE HOT ROCKS,
AND YOU PUT THEM
INTO THE TURKEY.
FIRE ONE IN, BILL.
HERE WE GO... OH, BOY, AND...
THERE WE ARE -- BY GOLLY.
IF YOU DON'T THINK THAT'S
PAINFUL, YOU ASK A TURKEY.
YOU DROP 'ER INTO THE HOLE
AND PUT THE HOT ROCKS
ALL AROUND THE TURKEY.
FIRE 'EM IN, FIRE 'EM IN.
GET 'EM IN THERE!
YOU COVER THAT UNIT WITH DIRT.
YOU WANT TO SEAL THAT IN,
LIKE A PRESSURE COOKER,
IN THE HAWAIIAN, POLYNESIAN,
FIJI STYLE OF LIFE.
OH, BILL'S GOT
THE UKULELE TO HELP.
OK, THAT'S GOOD --
WE COVER UP WITH DIRT.
YOU WANT IT COMPLETELY COVERED
WITH THE DIRT OF THE AREA.
HE'S BRINGING IN
THE VARIOUS LEAVES.
THIS GIVES IT
KIND OF THE FLAVOURING.
IT CHANGES THE TASTE,
APPARENTLY.
WHAT HAVE WE GOT NEXT, BILL?
OH... AH! CAR MATS
OUT OF A K-CAR.
AND NOW, WE'LL BE BACK
WHEN DINNER'S READY.
AWAY YOU GO -- OH, MAN!
SO I'VE DEVISED
A 12-STEP PROGRAMME
TO HELP YOU OVERCOME
THIS BIOLOGICAL IMPERATIVE.
NO MORE EXCUSES,
NO MORE SAYING...
(Imitating Red):
"SORRY, IT'S A GUY THING."
I'LL THROW OPEN THE FLOOR
TO MY UNCLE RED
TO START THE MEETING.
MAN!
ALL RIGHT, I'M RED
AND I'M A MAN.
(All): HI, RED.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO
THE "MEN ANONYMOUS" PLEDGE.
I'M A MALE...
BUT I CAN CHANGE...
IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
THANKS.
(Laughing and applause)
LET'S GET STARTED
BY SHARING OUR EMOTIONS.
WHO WOULD LIKE TO START
BY SHARING EMOTIONS?
WOULD SOMEONE LIKE
TO STATE THEIR OPINION?
OH, I THOUGHT SO.
OK, HOW ABOUT... DOUGIE?
OHHHH!
THANK YOU.
GENTLEMEN, MY NAME IS DOUGIE.
I'M A MAN.
(All): HI, DOUGIE.
GENTLEMEN, LAST WEEK
WAS A DIFFICULT ONE FOR ME.
I WAS TEMPTED
TO FALL OFF THE WAGON
AND GO RIGHT BACK
INTO SOME OLD BAD HABITS.
THE TEMPTATION OCCURRED RIGHT
IN FRONT OF THE HARDWARE STORE.
THERE WAS A FELLA THERE
CHANGING A FLAT TIRE
ON HIS PICKUP TRUCK AND...
HE WAS DOIN' IT WRONG!
HE DIDN'T PUT HIS WHEEL NUTS
IN THE HUBCAP!
(Red): OH, FOR
GOSH SAKES!
I BIT MY TONGUE,
AND THEN IT OCCURRED TO ME.
UNE PIECE DE RESISTANCE
AU DOUGIE.
I GOT MY TRUCK.
I PARKED BESIDE HIM
WHERE HE WAS CHANGING HIS TIRE
AND I STARTED CHANGING
ONE OF MY TIRES,
EVEN THOUGH IT WASN'T FLAT.
I CHANGED THAT SUCKER
THE RIGHT WAY
SO THAT SORRY EXCUSE FOR A MAN
WOULD LEARN!
WAY TO GO,
DOUGIE!
THAT'S THE WAY
TO DO IT!
THAT'S
THE STUFF!
(Red): DINNER HAD TAKEN
QUITE A WHILE.
I DOZED OFF IN THE SUN,
BUT, LUCKILY,
I HAD LEFT A WAKE-UP CALL.
THERE WE GO, AND NOW
WE'RE SET TO CHECK OUT--
DIG UP OUR TURKEY.
SHOULD BE COOKED TO PERFECTION.
BILL'S DIGGING WITH...
SOMETHING I HADN'T NOTICED,
AND MAYBE WE GOT LUCKY.
WE DON'T GET LUCKY OFTEN.
YOU'RE NOT WORRIED -- HE THINKS
WE'LL GET LUCKY TWICE
AND THAT NEVER HAPPENS.
YOU ALL RIGHT, BILL?
YOU MAY HAVE HIT A BURIED--
YOU HIT A WIRE, BILL.
WE'LL BE BACK
WHEN THIS ROCK CONCERT'S OVER.
OH, BOY.
HERE'S A GIFT FROM OUR FRIENDS
AT THE OUTBACK PUB IN OTTAWA.
IT'S A BRIEFCASE.
BACK AT THE "OH, WOW" LUAU,
WE'RE DIGGING UP THE TURKEY.
YOU GOT THE TURKEY? IS IT DONE?
VEGETABLES?!
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
IT IS A FARMER'S FIELD.
MAYBE... HE MUST HAVE
PLANTED SOMETHING.
THAT'S THE BEAUTY OF THE LUAU.
THIS WILL HELP ME SEE AT NIGHT,
WHICH IS WHEN WE'LL FIND
THE DARN THING.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
OH, MY GOSH! OH, MY GOSH!
THAT'S A TREASURE--
THERE'S A--
THAT'S GOT--
THERE'S VALUE THERE!
THERE'S CAPTAIN HOOK!
WHAT?
OH, THE HOOKS.
OH, MAN!
STILL NO TURKEY, HUH?
CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
OH, YEAH, THERE'S ONE.
FLINTY DECLINED
THE OPPORTUNITY
TO MARRY JUNIOR'S FIANCEE.
I SUGGEST THAT JUNIOR SHOW UP
FOR THIS WEDDING SOON.
I GOT A FAX OVER MY FAX-MODEM.
JUNIOR'S ON HIS WAY --
HE'S UP NEAR KENORA.
WHY DIDN'T HE FAX HIMSELF
RATHER THAN THE NOTE?
(Laughing)
FAX A PERSON
OVER A FAX MACHINE -- WHOO!
(Laughing)
YOU JUST DON'T GET
THIS MODERN TECHNOLOGY.
THE DUMBEST THING
I'VE EVER HEARD!
WHOO! FAX A PERSON!
HELLO!
DUMB, EH, HAROLD?
'CAUSE THEY DO IT
ON "STAR TREK".
(Audience laughing)
NEVER THOUGHT I'D HEAR HAROLD
SAY "STAR TREK" IS DUMB.
NO, NO! I DIDN'T!
CAPTAIN PICARD, YOU HEARD ME
NOT SAY THAT, RIGHT?
HELLO, KLINGONS!
OH, MAN!
(Audience laughing)
PUT THAT AWAY!
WE GOTTA GET
TO THE CHURCH.
THE WEDDING'S
IN HALF AN HOUR.
BUT JUNIOR'S, LIKE,
FIVE HOURS AWAY.
DON'T GET YOUR JOCKEYS
INTO A JAM.
GETTING THE GROOM TO CHURCH
IS THE BEST MAN'S JOB.
YOU'RE
THE BEST MAN.
OH, MAN, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
WHY? WHAT?
NOBODY SAYS THE GROOM
HAS TO BE JUNIOR.
OH, NO!!
HAROLD, IT'S JUST
A PROXY THING, THAT'S ALL.
YOU JUST SAY THE VOWS
ON JUNIOR'S BEHALF.
JUST PROXY --
IT'S JUST WORDS.
JUST WORDS.
YOU TAKE HIS PLACE
FOR THE WEDDING.
LET'S HOPE HE SHOWS UP
BEFORE THE HONEYMOON.
OH, NO!!
COME ON!
COME ON.
WE ALL BEEN THERE ON THIS ONE.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO WALK IN
THE HOUSE
AND THEN IT HITS YOU.
"WASN'T I SUPPOSED TO
DO SOMETHING ON THE WAY HOME?"
YOU CAN'T REMEMBER WHAT IT WAS.
CAN'T TELL HER --
YOU KNOW HOW SHE GETS.
YOU GOTTA JOG YOUR MEMORY.
SLIP IN
THE HOUSE...
COUNT
THE KIDS.
IF YOU'RE SHORT ONE OR TWO,
MAYBE YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO
PICK THEM UP.
COUNT THE CARS IN THE DRIVEWAY.
IF ONE'S MISSING, MAYBE YOU
WERE SUPPOSED TO PICK 'ER UP
AT A SERVICE STATION
OR ON THE HIGHWAY.
IF THERE'S TOO MANY CARS,
YOU HAVE COMPANY.
MAYBE YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO
PICK UP GROCERIES.
CHECK FOR A LIST
SHE MIGHT HAVE SLIPPED YOU.
IF YOU COME UP EMPTY,
WALK INTO THE HOUSE,
SAY, "HONEY, I'M HOME",
GIVE HER THE BIG HUG.
WHILE HER BACK'S TURNED
TO THE CALENDAR,
SEE IF THERE'S A BIRTHDAY
OR ANNIVERSARY WRITTEN IN.
IF YOU DON'T SEE ANYTHING,
MAYBE YOU FORGOT
TO GET BREAD OR MILK.
SHE'LL CALL YOU "STUPID"
AND LAUGH AT YOU.
CONSIDER YOURSELF LUCKY --
YOU GOT OFF EASY...
... THIS TIME!
(Red): THIS IS IT --
WE'RE GETTING CLOSE,
'CAUSE BILL FOUND A ROCK.
GET RID OF THE ROCK.
I DIDN'T MEAN THAT WAY.
HE'S GOT THE TURKEY, THOUGH.
BY GOSH, CAN YOU SMELL THAT?
ISN'T THAT BEAUTIFUL!
WOW! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, BILL'S AUDITIONING
FOR HIS PUPPET SHOW FOR KIDS.
OH, MAN! GET AWAY FROM ME.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK AT THAT --
LOOK AT THE TABLE SETTING.
THE PRESENTATION IS...
ALMOST NOTHING.
WE NEED DRINKS, BILL.
CAN YOU HANDLE THAT?
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
OH, A WATER PIPE.
CHEERS!
OH, MAN! FRIGHTENING, ISN'T IT?
(Audience laughing)
JUNIOR DID MAKE IT
TO THE CHURCH ON TIME
'CAUSE THE CEREMONY WAS LATE.
THE GUYS WERE HURTIN'
FROM THE STAG PARTY.
TOOK 'EM FOREVER
TO GET INTO THE PEWS.
IT WAS NICE, HAVING OLD MAN
SEDGWICK AS THE RING-BOY.
HE'S GOT RINGS -- HE'S LIKE A
TREE, WITHOUT THE INTELLIGENCE.
TOOK JUNIOR A LONG TIME
TO GET THE RING
ON THE BRIDE'S FINGER
'CAUSE HE WAS COVERED
IN MOLASSES AND FEATHERS.
I THOUGHT YOU'D HAVE
WASHED HIM A BIT.
WE THOUGHT OF HOSING HIM DOWN
BUT THEN HE'D GET MARRIED
IN HIS UNDERWEAR.
THE BRIDE THOUGHT
SHE WAS MARRYING
BIG BIRD.
SHE WON'T SAY THAT
AFTER THE HONEYMOON.
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
REMIND THE GUYS, WE GOT
A BRIDAL SUITE TO SABOTAGE.
OK!
I TAKE MY RESPONSIBILITIES
SERIOUSLY.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
WITH THE WEDDING AND ROMANCE
AND YOUNG LOVE AND EVERYTHING,
I WAS HOPING MAYBE LATER,
WE COULD HAVE SOME FUN.
THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
THANKS FOR WATCHING
AND KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): HE'S HERE, HE'S HERE!
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN... HAROLD?
(Harold): SOMEONE RAN OVER
MY FAVOURITE HAT
ON THE HIGHWAY.
WOULD YOU PLEASE WAIT
UNTIL I'M OUT OF IT NEXT TIME?
(Laughing)
MUST HAVE BEEN STINKY'S CAR --
THERE'S NO TREAD-MARKS.