And now it's time to prove that men do not
lead lives of quiet desperation.
No way they're loud.
And when you think of loud men, don't you
think of the men of Possum Lodge?
Generally, I know my uncle in particular
because he's the leader of the Possum Lodge,
and that's the only because, you know,
discouraging lack of turnout on Election Day.
But anyway, here's the star of the Red Green
Show, and that's due mainly to the fact that,
you know, he has the same name.
Anyway, here he is. Mr.
Red. Green.
Thank you, Harold. Thank you and welcome to
Possum Lodge.
Please don't judge the show by anything
Harold ever says or does.
He's only my producer and director because
first of all, he's my nephew.
And secondly, this is black fly country,
which really teaches you to put up with just
about anything.
And I'm here to put juice into the show like
this.
We have to watch a half hour of that.
Things are really hopping up at the Lodge
this week.
Eddie made a special stew, tasted like a
Hungarian goulash.
You know what? I think the problem is I think
Eddie doesn't concentrate on when he cooks.
Well, that's it in a nutshell, Harold.
And from a nutshell, know Eddie's mind is
somewhere else.
Yeah. Broadway. He wants to sing on Broadway.
Well, no, no. I think it's more like
off-Broadway, isn't he?
I mean it when he sings, it sounds off.
I mean, it's way off Broadway.
Like, maybe the Yukon.
I think we just get on to the next segment.
I'll remember that pacing thing we talked
about at the last production meeting.
Yeah. Ok. So anyway, a bunch of the guys, you
know, managed to have a word with Eddie, you
know, once the Cale Peck had kicked in.
You're kind of rough on especially Moose
Thompson, because Moose said he'd had a whole
bag full of stew and the thing was moose.
He said he eats it darn fast.
He really doesn't taste anything until he's
into the third plateful.
We're going,
Yeah, so once Mohsin finished, you know,
talking to Eddie about his physical
appearance, his religious preference and his
ethnic background, and he has decided to
really back off on the cooking and focus his
full attention onto his showbiz career.
We're going, yeah, I'm I'm done here.
Go ahead.
Oh, oh, oh, OK.
All right. All right. Then do nothing.
Ok, what is that? Larry, Larry is my man.
Well, up there in the booth. Whoa, that's
loud.
Loud.
Ariel. Ok, attach air
Raid siren to truck alternator, check, let's
see oh, and then plug unit in.
All right, Bill. You plug it in and I'll
pump up the volume.
Air raid siren What?
What is this thing, Andy? This is a karaoke
machine, Harold.
You see, you put the the tape with just the
music on it in here and then you sing along.
Very big in Japan.
Wow, that's surprising.
You mean the Japanese workers are singing
songs in the factories and they're making all
those camcorders? The Japanese are very
powerful in the business and there's no
business like show business, and that's my
business.
And now I've got a machine that's going to
hone my skills.
Oh, you can cook on it.
I'm going to be on Broadway, Harold, and you
are not going to rain on my parade.
I'm going to be the next Bobby.
Then I just think I stay here ready.
I got a real deal for Murray, so he makes
them in his basement.
Wait, do you hear the sound on this thing?
Red? Ok, bill, there's a plug over there
behind the stove.
You want to get it?
There's a light show to
Doc Render Thank Eddie took a big jolt there.
Why was he standing in water?
No, but I am. Hey, Eddie, we got that song
book list for you.
What's the matter with him singing falsetto?
No way. He just got some feedback from your
kamikaze machine there.
We brought you the soundtracks to funny girl
Annie, Get your gun and South Pacific.
Except for, I'm going to wash that man right
out of my hair.
Mary and I didn't think you wanted that one
anyway.
Well, you don't have to decide right now.
Better coming from the rain might be a
goner.
Or This is version of Silent Night.
Silent Night. Well, those shoes on.
I guess I'll discharge them.
Bill, you want a ground that on the stove?
You know, a touch more wire, we could use
them to jumpstart the lawn tractor out back.
All right. Let her rip cry for me,
Argentina.
You carry OK me.
Hey, big spender.
I'm standing right there and all of a
sudden.
Seventy six trombones led the big parade.
I got this incredible shot, huh?
Well, maybe you hooked it up wrong?
I didn't hook it up from you.
How heard you solve a problem like Maria?
You built it wrong, and you are just darn
lucky that I wasn't hurt.
Or when you reject you, reject and suffered
permanent damage.
Are you feeling OK, Eddie?
Yes, right? I'm fine name.
Very unusual read.
Entertaining as hell, though.
I'm just lucky there wasn't the polka tape
on that damn machine.
Well, Mary, I think you better give Eddie his
money back here.
Hey, no, no way.
I and I could have danced all night, but I
don't want my money back.
I just I just want this machine fixed.
I need it for my career.
I think cash refund is enough of a long shot.
Well, see, it wasn't my money.
Give it to the soul to make money.
I kind of borrowed it from the The Lodge
Entertainment Fund.
You guys better work this out between you.
But whatever you come up with, it's got to
be entertaining or profitable or kill one of
you.
You know, with that electric shock thing
there, Eddie, I thought it was really
entertaining. You know what? Maybe we could
just like, sell this to Alice Cooper?
Well, well, maybe so.
But she better not touch it till it's fixed.
Chicago, Chicago.
It's my go to town.
It's my kind of town.
What?
Don't stick your face in
A hollow log.
Don't squat on your haunches and a toxic
ball, go by face up in a cattle field.
And don't ever date a woman named Crusher.
This week, handyman gardener, when I show you
how to do some proof on your car.
You know, these days with the government
putting so much salt on the roads, you know,
they end up retaining water and your car
rests out on you.
So you end up having to do some body work or
some some sort of a defensive mechanism.
A lot of people use a fiberglass, but the
fiberglass on the car, but that's hard to do,
and it's expensive. Smells funny, and you
can't even put a fridge magnet and leave a
message for anybody on your car after that.
Now, most Thompson, what he done was he
completely encased his truck in cement, which
was a kind of a novel approach that really
cut into his gas mileage.
But if he's ever in an accident, he wins.
I want to take kind of a kind of a new
approach.
I want you to think about this.
Linoleum put some linoleum spray on your
car.
It's fairly inexpensive, it's lightweight,
it's durable, and if you get into a fender
bender, you know, if you've got a decent
cushion floor on there could save your life.
What you do is take her out and cut her out
and roughly the shape of the car.
Stick it on with the handyman secret weapon
duct tape that doesn't take care three or
four hours on a on a Saturday or or really
any any day.
I mean, that part's up to you, but I think
you'd be quite surprised and to a certain
extent, amazed at how it turns out.
I'm kind of on a limited budget, so I did
this all with with the samples.
But I suppose if the money is in Heidrich,
you would get, you know, the whole roll of
linoleum in nine by 12 or whatever comes in
and do it all.
Actually, I kind of like this look, and I'm
sure there's people out there, maybe yuppies
or what have you that would that would want
to do it all in parquet or teraz or tile of
some kind. But this is just fine for me.
It's easy as heck to keep clean too, because
it's a no wax finish it just a damp mop that
down, especially if there's eggs or what
have you on.
It comes right up. Let's grab it myself.
First thing I'm going to I'm going to polish
this up, but that's just a that's a pride
thing. That's just something that I have.
But if you want to do this with anything,
it's the same technique.
As long as you got the duct tape in the
time, you can have something that looks like
this sitting in your driveway.
So until next time, remember the women don't
find you handsome, they should at least find
a handy, beautiful, beautiful thing.
Is it not?
It is autumn. One last ride in the boat.
One last day at the cottage.
One last drive in the car through the hills
and then the repo man takes it all away.
So anyway, Eddie, the Cook wants us to keep
that karaoke machine since it was bought with
large money, but you know, it's awful hard
to follow the argument when he keeps breaking
into Rodgers and Hammerstein.
I can understand. Good value for the money,
but I am 16, going on 17.
Anyway, the bunch of us went down to Murray
Star to try to get a refund.
We don't know whether to use brute force or
perhaps something more subtle like, say,
closing all the windows and getting stinky.
Peterson negotiate a settlement,
Getting off the red Duane and Murray to both
lodge members.
You know, I really can't see
Them intentionally ripping other members off.
Well, no, no, I agree with that.
But you know, just to be on the safe side.
Mouse and helmet took down a couple of
pickaxes in a Zamboni delegate.
Murray's attention, you know,
All a minute, that's violence normal.
That's using violence as a tool, and I
cannot adhere to violence in any form.
Well, hang on, if I had your personality, I'd
be against violence myself.
Yeah, exactly.
And I'll bet you that violence didn't get you
anywhere, either, did it?
Well, sort of did. Well, Murray gave you your
money back.
Not yet, but I'll tell you, we got an
unbelievable price on work socks.
Oh, OK.
Oh, OK. All right. Oh yeah.
Good deal. Way to go. Good work there, Uncle
Ray.
Oh hey, babe.
We may have to go to binding arbitration to
settle this thing.
What's that?
Well, that's where we tie Murray and Dwayne
into a chair and take their teeth out.
That's fair. Now, Doc, I really appreciate
what you did for
Eddie, there took a heck of a jolt, didn't
he?
Huh? I bet that shows up on this month
electric bill.
Well, I've seen my share of vacations read
really?
I'd say he didn't say he took a peak voltage
at 12 million amps of R C Wow.
Not a curly hair left on his body.
See, that seems like a lot of power.
It seems a little high to me.
12 million something would not kill a man.
Well, no, no, no, not if you got both feet on
dry ground, right?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
As long as the the party are touching, the
ground is larger than the surface area of
your own forehead. You're OK.
Yeah, yeah. I've run that when I was working
at the generating station.
Oh yeah, like electricity generating the
station.
Well, that's the only kind I ever heard of.
Of course, I don't know everything.
I'm kidding. Yeah, we were the biggest
generating station in the hemisphere.
Yeah. Eighty six megawatts per day.
Wow. Yep. Wow.
You know, I remember at lunch time some of
the fellows and I we'd bungee jump off the
transformer tower. Oh, w, OK, hey, you know,
so you got close to the ground.
Then there'd be this flash of lightning arc
across from your sinus cavities right into
the metal tool shed. Oh yeah, then it would
ring.
And this week builds on make right in the
woods.
We're going to talk about first aid.
I look after injuries, which is which is a
good thing, and now he's got a boat.
I'd be an 80 90 pound bag of first aid
medical equipment there, so he's really well
equipped. This is a surgical tape
And all all my research
Reports that all the pain, you know, the pain
goes right up, right up, your leg goes right
into your back there, gets into your central
nervous system.
But luckily, Bill had the surgical tape
right out there on a wrapper up and the kind
of a nice job, a little bit, a little bit of
a handy man secret weapon sneak into another
another part of the show here.
It did a nice job. The unfortunate part is,
of course, you know it was the wrong foot.
Yeah, yeah. No, it's not.
It's that. Oh, and that not only up to the
backbone with the pain gets right up into
your brain, your S.O.S.
Anyway, you got the you got the red, the
foot, correct foot all all wrapped up.
Everything was, Oh guy, and now just get me
up into the standing position.
You know, we were going to pretend, Oh,
You know, the arms pump there? Oh, oh,
Oh, sorry, I'm sorry, I didn't mean any of
that, you know?
But I was darn glad it happened.
Oh God, don't stand
On my foot bill. Anyway, if you can get me up
into now, this is kind of the cantilever
seesaw kind of what I came up with.
Unfortunately, Bill Bill went down, but I
really couldn't put any weight, any weight at
all on the ankle. So Bill says to me, What
do you need?
Is some sort of a crutch there, you know,
and I didn't have a crutch in his bag, but
it's going to take us in an economy he's
going to cut, you know, he's going to try and
cut something out of it and we get a big get
a branch.
What have you? And maybe, no, and that's
well, Bill, that's a little that's too.
That's not going to make it.
That's a there's no that's too it's heavy
and it's too big.
And no, it's not going to work.
No bill.
Oh oh.
All right, so now this required a little more
surgical tape.
Now the pain was running from my brain down
into my foot.
So off he comes back with an olive branch,
he's going to make into a crutch because it
had a little dark thing. And that's what you
need there.
And a little high, though.
I don't think many Boyle has a screening.
Now, bill, you don't watch us bill.
Don't, don't look at the camera bill, you
know?
All right. Well, OK.
So now I'm using the surgical tape on his
hand and.
Now he's got the crutch. You think I'm going
to try this?
I don't think so. I don't think so.
Show us how it works, bill.
So now there's a whole sorry, I'm just
taking that up.
That was a sling again out of the out of the
bag, and he's got a hand in a kind of a
busted up arm and I got the head and the
foot thing, and now we'll get them up here,
just get them up standing now.
You know, Bill doesn't look all that heavy,
but when he starts to run.
Oh oh, oh, sorry, sorry, bill.
So I got a little more of the surgical tape
and this was turning into quite a day.
Really, we haven't felt this bad since New
Year's Day, so I've become now a bit woozy.
So I thought, I, you know, this is the
fireman's lift, but you know, gravity is a
funny thing that can stick and shift.
Oh oh. Back, oh, golly.
So this is something I found this darned
interesting, if you get a couple of polls and
you get a couple of little shirts out of
your laundry hamper and you can, what you do
is you put the sleeves of the poles over the
sleeves of their shirts.
All have a head injury there and over the
poles.
And what you can make is you make a
stretcher because once you get the sleeves on
there, you do up the buttons and you got
yourself, you got yourself a stretcher.
But I'll tell you at this point, I've had
enough of Bill.
I'm hurting. I'm tired.
I'm hungry. Things happen now.
It's time to go, bill and try some first aid
on himself.
I'm out of here and over.
Well, by golly, it's been it's been quite a
day, you know, after after a few trips to
Murray's store, we had about as many work
socks as we were ever going to need at that
price, who could say no even if they were
singles.
So you're pretty much given up on this refund
for the karaoke thing.
Is that what you're doing?
Well, you're getting a little ahead of me
here, Harold.
Well, that's not too hard to do.
Think you can see why nepotism is the main
cause of heart attacks?
So Murray told Dwayne to fix the machine a
problem there being that Dwayne is not
exactly a rocket scientist.
He's more of a nose cone.
So mainly Dwayne fixed a machine and he
plugged it in, and he ended up getting zapped
worse than any worse.
Like, what is he singing like Broadway show
tunes, too?
Well, no, Harold Dwayne had a different tape
in there.
It was Lorne Green reading Robert Service
poetry.
It was a nice change, you know, but I think
we're going to be able to straighten up this
refund situation at tonight's Lodge meeting
or
Oh, there it is. That's the call of the
meeting.
I'll go ahead. Come on. We got to go.
Well, if you'll just excuse me for a few
minutes here, I just got to go down to the
meet and straighten the whole deal up and
won't take too long while I'm gone.
Why don't you just sit quietly and discuss
the favorite part of the show so far?
Great. Great.
Oh boy, oh boy.
Oh boy.
No. Sounds all right.
All right. He
recognizes Murray Woolworth.
Thank you, red. Well, as you know, we at
Murray's pride ourselves on having the lowest
prices around.
But that also means that refunds and
exchanges are a long shot at best.
Well, even so, even so, we have done
everything in our power to satisfy Eddie
here, which led to an unfortunate injury
sustained by my assistant, Duane.
Now there may even be brain damage, but who
can tell?
Don't worry about me, I'm fine now.
Those three things done Neath the midnight
sun by the men who moil for gold.
Duane has nothing to do with this.
I want my feet to keep talking.
Happy talk money back.
Don't you listen?
Are you hard of hearing?
Aren't you listening?
Don't you listen? Can you not hear me?
You are not going to get your finger on the
marge of Lake Laborde.
I cremated Sam McGee.
Money back.
Oh, is that I enjoy being our girl.
So look, if you think that you can.
Sam McGee came from Tennessee, where the
cotton.
Tell me what to do.
Well, then let me tell you.
Well, Glenn, well, hi, sorry.
Sorry, I'm late.
Well, you to have anything else to say then.
No, no, me neither.
No thoughts.
What? No, that's from Dwayne.
Well, this day is full of surprises, isn't
it?
What do you suppose? Just happen there, doc?
Well, read Levi there created what's called a
spark capacitor and this charge dye on the
bottom as it charges, which neutralizes the
electrical imbalances of the brain.
Or or it's real love.
It's too soon to tell.
Really?
Wow, hope for the best on that any other
large business bill?
Ok, I'm going to call on Doc to give us the
evening's entertainment.
Hey, fellas.
Hell no. I don't think I've told all you
guys about the time the meeting Maury
Amsterdam were fly fishing on the Dead Sea.
Yeah.
Well, as we say up the lodge, we don't care
how it ends.
As long as it does, we can get our money
back.
But any machine that can electrocute our
cook has to be worth something.
And you don't see an Eddie and Wayne perform
together.
You get a sense of why vaudeville died.
If my wife is watching, I'll be coming
straight home after the meeting and I'm in
the mood for something dangerous, so you
might want to invite your folks over until
next time. On behalf of myself and Harold
and the whole gang up here at Possum Lodge.
Keep your stick on the ice.
It was quite an act, one of the
Times to bring it down there, I was down
there for about 40 feet.
Google on the bottom water crystal clear.
As far as you can see way up ahead of me, I
know there's no fish.
If there is some kind of a weird kind of
human shape thing and it's paddling and
kicking to beat the band, I look straight at
me as well.
He's got boats, came on there with download.
A good story, but a word of it a lot.