[quirky music plays]
[a gun shoots, a bird cries, a bugle plays]
Welcome welcome, ladies and gentlemen, boys
and girls, senior citizens, viewers
everywhere and all ships at sea and dry dock
boats and boats sitting on concrete blocks
Marine Museum. It's time again for the most
exciting outdoor show since Coniferous Kali's
forest crawling, bringing you the fashion
and entertainment show involving trees.
It's the one and the lonely Red Green show
starring the man who brought you like acting
to the woods and wood to his acting career a
bubbly, bubbly and irreparable Red Green.
Thank you, Harold. Thank you, and welcome to
Possum Lodge, the place that proves the
nature hates a vacuum.
We never use one. And speaking of vacuums,
Harold here is our producer and director and
all around button pusher and not just any
buttons.
This is my vertical flange,
And this is my reverse pinwheel.
Well, it's called an 80 year old machine,
A deal that spells a do, as in much ado about
nothing.
Anyway, it's been kind of a typical week up
at the Lodge.
Oh man, Sedgwick woke up the other day only
to find out that his pants had been stolen
while he was sleeping. So anyway, he crawled
up out of the ditch, dusted himself off,
started hitchhiking back to the lodge.
But by golly, he was having a tough time
getting a ride because people just are
hesitant to stop for a guy who's got no
pants on.
It's just the kind of world that we live in
now, you know, people are so darn suspicious.
And then when a car would stop and the old
man, Sedgwick was a little suspicious.
I mean, who would stop with a guy with no
pants on?
Plus the fact that he was a little bit
confused and he'd forgotten which finger he
used to hitchhike with? Luckily, stinky
Peterson was coming by and he he picked him
up and drove him up to the lodger.
But by golly, old man Sedgwick was pretty
upset about the loss of his favorite Red
pants. You know, I think I might be a little
bit more upset about waking up in a ditch and
not having any idea as to how I got there.
Well, I'm sure he was, too.
The first time it happened, anyway.
Old man, Sedgwick says, we got to, you know,
tighten up large security now.
Well, I agree with him on that, you know,
because this terrible around here,
I'm afraid to leave my valuable TV equipment.
There's no locks in the doors, there's no
doorknobs on the doors.
In some places, there's no doors where
they're supposed to be doors.
Well, Harold, I'm here.
We we have an expression.
If it ain't broke, don't fix it.
And if it is broke, don't fix it anyway.
Yeah, no. Christmas is is our head of
security and it's all, man.
Sedgwick has put a bug in his ear, so he's
going to be tightening everything up, but
hopefully it won't get in the way of the
great, great, fabulous super duper
extravaganza show we got for you this week.
Take it away, Harold.
You're talking about this show, OK?
Oh oh.
Is he dead? If he's dead, I'm in big
trouble.
Oh, boy's life, OK?
All right. All right, he's alive.
Oh, oh no, he's alive.
How come he was not sleeping in his cabin?
He's unconscious.
Oh, OK then. Yeah, it seems somebody bash
them over the head with this club from that
bag. Oh boy, with you.
What's it all?
In my opinion, all that was an error in
judgment.
When he wakes up, he's going to grab you by
the ankles and make a wish.
It was his fault. Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, use a password.
Sure. Doesn't anybody get my memo?
Oh yeah, we get your memo.
We just don't read them. You know, maybe
what you should do is send out memos saying,
Hey, read my memo.
Well, that's not going to work.
So no shooting other large member here.
He brained helmet with a golf club.
Oh, for God's sake, what is par for helmets
head?
It was his fault that he didn't use the
password.
You know, I'm just going to go get some ice
because when he wakes up, he's gonna be sore.
Woof, woof. Yeah, he's right.
If I was, you know, I'd be out of here.
When he wakes up
Starship entry to to to book a flight to Rio
India and to book a hospital room, remember
to cancel one of them. Uh-huh.
Oh, what happened? Someone forgot to yell
for
Oh, no helmet. Forgot the password.
Oh, password. There's a fun game, really.
It's fun. It's golf, though. Well, I'm out
of here.
Well, that's odd. My bag feels one club
later.
The putter is missing by the sound of it.
Oh, no, oh no.
He's our punter is missing his own putter.
Oh, I'm lucky, autograph.
Of these other pass through stolen.
Oh no, lucky autograph.
Zeller putter has been stolen in broad
daylight.
No, nothing. You're ahead of security.
Do something quick. I did.
I implemented a system of passwords.
Oh good god. No.
Oh, good old door. Good.
You find them all right. When you find them,
let me just have one minute with them alone.
That's all I need. I will tear a divot out
of their hide the size of a throw rug.
Five hundred bucks for that club.
Who knows what it's worth now?
Well, Bob, you'd be surprised.
[strumming guitar] Sometimes when I'm
sleeping outdoors at night,
Sometimes sometimes
I count all the stars and I can see there, you
know, inside.
It takes a long, long, long, long, long time
and it's pretty hard.
And I start thinking, Hey, if I'm not the one
that started the argument, why am I sleeping out
in the yard?
This week on the back burner, we're going to
show you what you can do with an old fridge,
you know, fridge is kind of like a kid, even
when they don't work.
I hate to throw them out, end up sitting out
on the back porch full of beer, and the same
thing happens to fridges.
So I say to myself, What do you do with an
old fridge?
Can't you make something out of that?
How about another appliance?
How about making it into a dishwasher?
Ok, so the first thing you need to do is to
create a hole for your water coming in so you
up to your fridge and you measure down about
an arm.
Ok, now you don't believe that you have a
standard size arm, you can use half a leg.
All right. You want to just drill a hole in
there.
Time is kind of the essence here.
All right. Our water supply will go in
there.
Now, as far as the water goes, just a normal
garden hose hooked up to your normal garden
hose outlet.
We don't get fancy here. We just get
effective.
We don't think that brings back memories.
All right, now you want to disperse the
water inside the fridge.
You know, dishwashers have a lot of jets and
so forth.
It sprinkles water around.
How about staying with our garden motif here
and installing a sprinkler to just leave him
out with this up in here and maybe put this
one down on the bottom?
It's very well wide open.
I don't like that style.
I like to be a little more creative.
Take your hose, put a real good knot in
there
And
Then you want a water.
Seal everything up. So use duct tape on the
end of the hose, and I would even wrap duct
tape around where the hose goes actually
into the unit.
Now, when you turn the water on, the water's
got nowhere to go.
So what you do is to grab a small pointy
screwdriver, maybe just sharp knife in the
middle and just punch a few holes right into
the hose.
And now you're ready to throw the dishes in
there and they're covering it nicely into the
door. If you are upset about this ugly
looking thing on the side, you can put this
side of the bridge against the wall, and I
will just put our detergent in there.
Throw that into the butter, right?
Ok. Those are up what I'm going to do.
I'm going just a little chunk of duct tape
on there.
You know me, Mr.
Safety, OK?
During the hose on, we can start washing
dishes.
It should be done now, I guess.
Oh, boy. Isn't that something?
Ok, but this just seem to have melted here.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
All right. Maybe we made it not just just a
tad too hefty on this.
We might have. Maybe, maybe this was it was
a better way to go, but it works.
I'm amazed. So remember, the women don't
find a handsome.
They should at least find a handy.
It's probably better for washing tools to
get to
Point in time. So that's a pretty heavy.
No, no, no.
It is autumn sitting in a duck blind shotgun
raised siting down the barrel, a duck floats
closer and closer.
Boom, I blow its plastic head off.
A few had been squatting here in the cold
dampness and 6:00 this morning.
You'd be bored enough to shoot your decoys
to.
Errol, what's the password?
Well, dissect well, what time is it to 30 to
30 to 30?
Ok, that's between two and three.
So that's that's this is tomorrow's list.
Ok. All right. Hold on.
Hold on. Assassination.
Ok, assassination.
Well, it's OK, I'm the red nose, not even
here hiding from Bob and Helmut.
Oh, OK, good.
Well, Helmut is up and about, but he can't
remember his name or what he should have been
wearing, which is the same thing.
Helmut. Kind of an unusual name.
And, you know, I used to think his parents
were German, but it turns out they were in a
motorcycle gang. Anyway, Bob Stuyvesant is
making everybody's life a living hell around
here. Looking for this, looking for this
putter, and it was a big deal.
It's only a putter. I mean, it's not like
it's a lucky hat anyway.
Between helmets, head and bobs, one track
mine nose caught between a rock and a hard
place.
I sure hate to be Noel right around now.
Well, Harold, I'd hate to be you any time.
So, Bob, is it turning the whole of upside
down and looking for this putter?
Why is it the men get so emotional about
their possessions and cars and yet they treat
their loved ones with such indifference?
Oh, here I'll give it a rest. Will you take
some of the next segment?
Yeah. Ok, I'll go read though, before we.
I was just wondering, you know, I didn't
want to ask you in front of the guys because
I didn't want to seem like sexually naive or
something, you know?
But I was wondering what, what, what is a
fuzzy Zeller?
I'd say it's one of those cover things that
golfers use on their clubs to protect them.
Oh, oh yeah.
Well, they sell those in the Washington
school.
How's it going, Douglas? What can I do for
you?
No, no, no. It's rad.
Well, go jump in the water.
It'll cool down. I'll read you.
Call me Douglas. No, I didn't, Glenn.
All right. All right. Well, helmet, do you
have any idea who or what hit you on the head
this morning?
Well, I don't have time for your head now.
I got a pump here and need
Servicing, young lady. Oh, wow.
Well, that's good because you're one guy who
can fix things helmet.
You know, my mom used to hit me like that.
Help me sleep, you know, a cup of warm milk
and a two by four.
Oh, well, how long do you think you think you
could?
You could straighten up this putter?
I have no idea how this happened.
Do you have a mother going,
Yeah, yeah, oh yeah, I have one of those.
You're not going to call me, Harold, are
you?
Do you call your mother?
Oh, no. A lot is a funny expression helmet.
If you mean more than once a year, then no.
But, you know, if I called her more often, I
don't think we'd be as close.
All right. I don't call my mom as often as I
should, either.
You know, you have a helmet.
You live with your mother.
Well, that's no excuse I could call.
I could make the time difference.
You look like Mamie Eisenhower.
All right.
Yeah. Do you think you could you could
straighten that out, and Bob would really
appreciate it, Alvin?
Well, I don't know.
Maybe you don't want them had the chef might
just snap.
When I try to straighten it out, that'll
happen.
You know, mental fatigue.
If it happens, it happens.
We got nothing to lose at this point.
Helmet?
Ok? I was afraid that it happened.
They just don't make them like they used to,
huh?
I think that's one sturdy pump.
You got there, though.
Thanks. Do you mind if I go call my mother?
Oh, you go ahead. I'll see you later.
Ok. Jay, how to ride for me?
Yeah, right. And and you say hello to your
mother, right?
Hey, mom, dad says hello.
Bell told me to meet him at the top of the
cliff there.
He was going to do a little rappelling, so I
thought he would be climbing up, but he was
come up, got scared that fell and really
scared me, you know?
Anyway, Bill had all the ropes, and this is
a real interesting kind of sport.
It's I'm not sure how old this is.
What you do is you take a piece of rope and
there's a technique, of course, a roll out,
you know? And it's a way you wind the rope
around your body.
It's got one OK under both legs, you know,
and it goes around under and then up and
threw up and threw up.
And you pull that title.
Oh, he's all right.
He's all right. Ok, you got to tell you.
Communication is a big part of the big part
of the game, as it is, as it is as it is.
Oh, I am. So you got many minds that around
and now you drop there.
Now he's ready to go, but you know, they'll
start to think there's something.
He thought there was something he hadn't
done and good.
But what it was is he'd forgotten to tie the
end to the tree,
Which is unfortunate. Oh, I didn't know about
down there a little faster,
And then he wanted to want me to throw him
some kind of a grappling hook so that you
could hook it on to the rope and then throw
the rope back up and we could sort of start
over. So I didn't have a grappling hook.
All I had to ask was, was an anchor.
Oh, I
Can't believe I missed him. So he he picked
up the anchor.
Anything what he can do is tie that onto the
rope and then this way he can throw me the
rope back up. And then I'd have and I have
the, you know, I'd have the rope.
And then so I was a little wandering about
throwing this up.
But you know, Billy's, he's confident, you
know, with no reason to be for any.
They've been given another trial.
She goes on this time he's going to really
be there we go all all, all, all old.
So, you know, that's enough that he asked me
to throw him down another rope, which which
course I did. But here again, I I hadn't
really tied it to a tree, but I was going to
hold it and kind of balance them out.
But one way or another, we were going to get
going to get build back up the cliff.
Once he started with the bouncing and so on,
it started to go a little better and he
started to really make some progress.
And pretty soon he was right up, right up,
on top.
And. And one thing about Bill.
He doesn't get it right the first time.
He just he just doesn't have the brains to
quit.
So anyway, Alfie comes and got a little bit
of foliage there, and I just something to
start a conversation on a priority, really?
Another wrote. Now here we go.
Now we're going first step on a bill.
Tired of the tree. I'm not going to make
that mistake twice.
Bill never makes the same mistake twice.
He's only been married the one time and he
comes back and he's got the right.
He's even got it wound around correctly, and
I take that off.
I didn't figure he'd want to bring in any
television stations on the way now know that
over the nine year bill and he's all set.
He's all set. Got her tied to the tree and
it's everything.
And you know, of course, now he's sensitive.
He's got a real, real good tree there.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, oh, looks good, looks good
and away.
But you know, the thing with trees is you
can you can never tell by looking at a tree
just exactly how and
Over this was.
Oh boy, oh oh.
Oh, boy, that one, that one that was
unfortunate, wasn't it, but he's OK, and one
thing about Bill, he lives to repel one more
day.
The sugar
And turf.
Man, what is with these violent passwords
here?
Decapitation bazooka before that, it was
napalm ignite.
Well, I think it's all in nulls vocabulary
reflects his personality.
You can tell a lot about a person by their
by their vocabulary, you know,
Oh, hey, I don't be such a, you know, a guy
who knows stuff.
Smart guy. Anyway, this golf club situation
is coming to a head, an aluminum head sculpt
around all day with Bob's putter between his
legs.
But he said he's going to have everything
straightened out before tonight's meeting.
Well, you should just tell the truth and let
the chips fall where they may.
Yeah, but these chips may be bits of Noel.
It's meeting time off the rack.
That's the call of the wild possum.
Let's get down there because maybe like Noel
is going to be dragged off to jail or maybe
beaten up or something like that, you know?
You know, I don't want that to happen, but
you know, if it does, I don't want to miss
it.
You know, every once in a while, I get a
glimpse that there may be hope for that boy.
Excuse me, Mac.
Ray Ray Ray
Rice on
The floor recognizes Bob Stuyvesant
Like the robe. Someone someone here that's
taken my putter
and done. God knows what was that something
sick?
I'm sure. So I've asked for help, and no one
has helped me.
No one except Noel when I needed them.
He was there. That's right.
Set up security checks and passwords.
No. Unfortunately, no one cares the way Noel
does.
So I've decided to offer a four hundred
dollar reward for the name of the criminal
who swiped my lucky putter.
No, no, no.
It's fine art.
Don't go out.
Hey, Noel says he can explain it.
Sure. No problem.
I get it for Bob's own good buddy.
Well, here I have some score cards from golf
games you played last week and this was not a
lucky putter. This this is a curse putter,
and that's that autograph was not fuzzy.
It was forged.
I checked it, forged by Satan.
Oh, wow.
Just like a Metallica VIDEO So I'm just
helping out there.
You just take your reward money and buy
yourself a real lucky putter.
I'd like that other one, you know, fun on a
lighter moment.
I would just like to, you know, I went to
smash that thing against the Wall and it was
so inaccurate it missed and hit the helmet
right in the head.
What? But what did I
come over here for Douglas Douglas?
Oh, Helmut, you were just going to do your
impression of Mamie Eisenhower?
And I was,
Yeah, yeah. And you were going to dedicate it
to your mom.
Oh, mom. Yeah, right?
Yeah. Yeah. So there's no no further business
bill.
Ok, then I'm going to have now turned over
to helmet to supply the evening's
entertainment.
Thank you. The first, I would like to
dedicate this to my mom, and I would like to
do my rendition of Mamie Eisenhower
welcoming Dwight back from the war.
Hi, it's me, Mamie.
I'm glad to see Noel standing up and taking
responsibility for his lies.
I certainly hope it's not a precedent for
the rest of us, though.
Anyway, my wife is watching.
I'll be coming straight home after the
meeting and I'll be bringing your anniversary
gift depending on, you know, which stores
are open.
I know the twenty fifth is silver and the
50th is gold.
This is our twenty ninth, which I believe is
donuts, so I'll be bringing twenty nine honey
glazed donuts or thereabouts, depending on
traffic.
Until next time.
On behalf of myself and Harold and the whole
gang up here at Possum Lodge.
Keep your putter in your bag and oh yeah,
keep your stick on the ice.
Ooh, where did you get those medals?
They look very impressive.
What is that one for?
Oh, really, you're courageous, man.
And what's that one for? Oh, you did single
handedly.
Oh, very nice.