♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN
IN TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD DOES
SOME MUSIC REVIEWS,
BILL TRIES DUCK HUNTING
AND I MAKE A SATELLITE DISH
OUT OF A PATIO UMBRELLA.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: AND NOW HERE'S
A MAN WHOSE NAME IS AS
COLOURFUL AS HIS WARDROBE
A REAL FASHION PLATE
WITH A SIDE ORDER OF FLANNEL
A MAN WHO ALWAYS MAKES THE
IT'S BEST IF HE'S DRESSED LIST
HERE HE IS THE STAR OF
OUR SHOW MR. RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
AND THANK YOU FOR TUNING US IN.
WE HAVE A EXCITING AND ENJOYABLE
SHOW AND WE ALSO HAVE
MY NEPHEW HAROLD.
OKAY AND BACK TO
THE ENJOYABLE STUFF.
ALRIGHT HAROLD LET'S
GET ON WITH THE SHOW.
>>HAROLD: WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
TELL THEM ABOUT THE BIG BOAT
RACE WE'RE HAVING, TELL THEM.
>>RED: OH ALRIGHT.
YEAH WE'RE HAVING A BIG BOAT
RACE YOU KNOW ACROSS
POSSUM LAKE.
>>HAROLD: GO ON AND GO ON!
>>RED: THAT'S ABOUT ALL THERE
IS HAROLD, LET'S GET ON
WITH THE SHOW HERE.
>>HAROLD: NO, WE'RE HAVING
A BIG BOAT RACE ACROSS
POSSUM LAKE AND THE WINNER GETS
TO BE THE FERRY BOAT CAPTAIN
BECAUSE THE FERRY BOAT CAPTAIN
IS RETIRING SO HE GETS
THE NEW JOB,
WHOEVER WINS THE RACE.
TELL THEM WHY PEOPLE WANT
THE JOB THOUGH, TELL THEM THAT.
>>RED: WELL HAROLD PEOPLE
LIKE TO BE GAINFULLY EMPLOYED,
NOT EVERYBODY WANTS YOUR JOB.
>>HAROLD: NO EVERYBODY WANTS
TO BE IN THE RACE BECAUSE
EVERY DAY THE FERRY BOAT IT
GOES OVER TO SUNSHINE ISLAND
AND OVER THERE THERE'S
A NUDIST CAMP,
NUDISTS THAT ARE NUDE, YES!
>>RED: THEY'RE SUN WORSHIPPERS
HAROLD THAT'S ALL WE KNOW.
>>HAROLD: OH PLEASE!
COME ON THEY'RE NAKED NUDISTS
OVER THERE UNCLE RED
THE OLD FERRY BOAT CAPTAIN
ONLY RETIRED BECAUSE
HE HAD A HEART ATTACK,
HE'S 27 THERE'S SOME KIND
OF CLUE IN THERE I FIGURE.
>>RED: WELL EVERYBODY'S JUST
KIND OF GUESSING ON THIS
YOU COULD SIT OUT IN A
FISHING BOAT OUTSIDE THAT
NUDIST CAMP AND JUST PRETEND
YOU WERE, I MEAN THE SUN
WORSHIPPER PLACE AND YOU
COULD PRETEND YOU WERE
FISHING AND YOU COULD STARE
IN THERE ALL DAY I DON'T CARE
HOW MANY TIMES YOU PEEK
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO SEE ONE
NAKED BODY AND APPARENTLY
THERE'S SOME KIND OF A ROAD
THAT GOES IN THERE WHERE
YOU CAN SEE THEM BUT
BY GOLLY I'VE NEVER
BEEN ABLE TO FIND IT.
>>HAROLD: I AGREE
IT'S TOTALLY DISGUSTING
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
>>RED: WELL THEN WHY DID
YOU BRING IT UP HAROLD
I DIDN'T?
>>HAROLD: WELL BECAUSE THE
PEOPLE AT HOME WANT TO KNOW
AND IT WOULD PROBABLY BOOST
OUR RATINGS YOU KNOW BUT
IN MY OWN PERSONAL OPINION
I THINK IT WOULD BE
IMMORAL AND EXPLOITIVE.
>>RED: BUT YOU DON'T MIND
MAKING A BUCK OFF SOMETHING
THAT YOU THINK IS A
DISGUSTING SPECTACLE.
>>HAROLD: YO BABE THIS IS TV
THAT'S THE MARK OF
A PROFESSIONAL.
♪ SKIING IN THE SUMMER ♪
♪ OUT BEHIND THE LODGE ♪
♪ DOWNHILL, TRICK AND SLALOM ♪
♪ LANDING IN THE BOG ♪
♪ IT'S ALMOST PERFECT ♪
♪ SKIING THOUGH ♪
♪ IT'S 93 DEGREES ♪
♪ IT'S ALWAYS ♪
♪ EXTREMELY SLIPPERY ♪
♪ SINCE THE GOVERNMENT ♪
♪ DECLARED GEESE AN ♪
♪ ENDANGERED SPECIES ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE GOING
TO SHOW YOU HOW TO GET
BETTER TV RECEPTION.
ONE WAY IS JUST TO
SWITCH TO A DIFFERENT
CHANNEL BUT WE'RE THINKING
MORE OF ONE OF THEM FANCY
SATELLITE DISH/BOWL THINGS
THAT LET'S YOU GET A MILLION
STATIONS ALL CARRYING
YOU KNOW STUFF LIKE 'CHEERS'
AND 'MASH' AND 'LUCY'
THAT KIND OF THING.
WE WERE ACTUALLY THINKING
OF BUYING OURSELVES A DISH
AT THE LODGE AND WE WENT DOWN
AND LOOKED AT THEM AND THESE
THINGS ARE A $1000.
A $1000! THAT'S WHAT
WE PAY FOR HOUSES
BUT I TOOK A CLOSE LOOK AT IT
AND I FIGURE GOLLY I CAN
BUILD ONE OF THOSE.
SO WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
IS ONE OF THESE PATIO TABLES
INCLUDING THE UMBRELLA
AND ABOUT 160 BAGS OF CHIPS
POTATO CHIPS THAT IS,
MAKE SURE YOU GET THE KIND
IN THE FOIL BAG.
STEP ONE EMPTY THE BAGS.
(LOUD CHOMPING & CRUNCHING)
42... NOW MAYBE WHAT WE SHOULD
DO IS JUST MAYBE POUR THESE
INTO A PAIL AND THEN WE CAN
YOU KNOW EAT THEM LATER
WHILE WE'RE WATCHING TV
(COUGHS) I WISH I HAD THOUGHT
OF THAT A LITTLE EARLIER.
MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE CLEANED
THE PAIL OUT FIRST,
WELL I'LL TELL THE GUYS
THESE CHIPS ARE SOUR CREAM
AND ONION...
43 OR IS THAT 44?
OH I'LL DO AN EXTRA.
OH GEEZ THAT WAS MY SPLEEN,
THAT'S A 100
OH THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH.
BOY THIS PLACE IS STARTING
TO SMELL LIKE MR POTATOHEAD'S
HONEYMOON SUITE.
ALRIGHT THAT WILL GIVE US
THE REFLECTIVE SURFACE
FOR THE SATELLITE DISH
NOW WE NEED THE ACTUAL DISH
FORM AND THIS IS WHERE
THE PATIO UMBRELLA COMES IN.
ALRIGHT FIRST WHAT WE'VE GOT
TO DO IS TO GENTLY REMOVE
THE UMBRELLA FROM THE STAND.
THERE WE GO NOW WE'VE GOT
TO INVERT HER, FLIP HER OVER
AND POINT HER BACK
OUT INTO SPACE,
I'LL JUST AIM HER UP THROUGH
THE HOLE IN THE LODGE ROOF.
THERE, NOW WE'LL SECURE IT
ON THERE USING THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
NO PROBLEM, I GUESS YOU WOULDN'T
WANT TO GIVE ME A HAND
EH HAROLD?
MY HANDS ARE ALL GREASY
FROM SOMETHING.
OKAY NOW I'VE REALLY LAID
THE DUCT TAPE IN THERE
BECAUSE YOU'VE GOT TO ALLOW
FOR WIND ESPECIALLY AFTER
44 BAGS OF CHIPS
AND WHAT WE'VE GOT HERE NOW
IS A CONCAVE REFLECTIVE SURFACE
AT LEAST WE WILL HAVE ONCE
WE ADD THE FOIL BAGS TO HER
AND WHAT THAT DOES IS IT
FOCUSES ALL THE ELECTRO-MAGNETIC
WAVES FROM WAY OUT IN SPACE
AND RIGHT UP HERE INTO
OUR RECEIVER.
IT'S STICKING THERE NOW,
NOW WHAT I HAVE TO DO IS
I HAVE TO OPEN UP ALL THE BAGS
LIKE THIS AND ATTACH THEM
INSIDE THE DISH AND I
CAN DO THAT WITH DUCT TAPE
BUT IT'LL TAKE A WHACK OF
DUCT TAPE AND THAT'S GOING
TO COST YOU A FAIR COIN SO
I'VE GOT AN IDEA THAT'S FREE,
YOU KNOW ALL OF THEM PAINT
CANS THAT YOU'VE KEEPING
IN THE GARAGE OR DOWN IN THE
BASEMENT YOU KNOW FOR YEARS
AND YEARS BECAUSE THEY GOT
A HALF INCH OF PAINT IN THEM
OR SOMETHING AND THEY'RE STILL
GOOD SO YOU DON'T THROW THEM
OUT YOU JUST STORE THEM FOR
A WHILE UNTIL THEY SMELL
LIKE OLD FISH AND THEN
YOU THROW THEM OUT.
WELL YOU DON'T NEED TO THROW
THEM OUT WE CAN USE THEM
HERE AS AN ADHESIVE TO
STICK THE FOIL BAGS
RIGHT ONTO THE UMBRELLA.
OH THERE WE ARE 39,
YOU KNOW I'M USING THE
PAINT LIKE WALLPAPER PASTE
ACTUALLY I DO HAVE SOME
WALLPAPER, OH IT DOESN'T
MATTER THIS IS GOING TO TAKE
A LITTLE BIT LONGER THAN
I THOUGHT SO WHY DON'T WE
JUST GET ON WITH THE SHOW
AND WHEN I GET HER ALL DONE
I'LL BRING YOU RIGHT BACK
HOOK HER UP AND MAKE HER WORK,
WELL THAT'S 39.
>>HAROLD: AND NOW HERE'S
THE PART OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE EXPOSE THOSE
3 LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN
FIND SO DIFFICULT TO SAY
'I DON'T KNOW'
AND HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT
ONCE AGAIN ON THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW
IS MY UNCLE RED AND
MR. DOUGIE FRANKLIN.
>>HAROLD: OKAY HERE WE GO
'DEAR EXPERTS, THERE IS
A WOMAN AT OUR OFFICE WHO
I FIND VERY INTERESTING AND
I WOULD LIKE VERY MUCH TO
MARRY HER AND BEAR HER CHILDREN
HOWEVER BEFORE MAKING
A LIFE LONG COMMITMENT
I THINK WE SHOULD MEET FIRST.
SO FAR SHE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW
THAT I'M ALIVE, ANY IDEAS?'
>>RED: WELL I'M KIND OF
WITH HER ON THIS ONE HAROLD
I DON'T THINK THE GUY'S
ALIVE EITHER.
>>HAROLD: WELL UNCLE RED
I DON'T THINK SARCASM HELPS
A SHY PERSON, BELIEVE ME.
>>RED: WELL HAROLD WITH ME
YOU'VE EITHER GOT SARCASM
OR TOTAL SILENCE.
>>DOUGIE: HAS HE GOT
A STOCK EXHAUST SYSTEM?
>>HAROLD: I DON'T KNOW
IT'S KIND OF HARD TO TELL
FROM THIS PICTURE
OF HIM HE SENT.
>>DOUGIE: I JUST WAS WONDERING
MAYBE HE MIGHT WANT TO UPGRADE
TO A THRUSH YOU KNOW OR GET
A LITTLE BODY WORK DONE
CHOP THE FRONT END DOWN
JACK THE BACK END UP
A LITTLE YOU KNOW.
>>HAROLD: WELL YEAH NO
THAT'S A GOOD POINT MY MOM
HAD THAT DONE AFTER SHE
STOPPED HAVING KIDS.
>>RED: WELL DOUGIE'S
TALKING ABOUT
THE GUY'S CAR HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: PARDON ME BUT
HOW WOULD AN ENGINE REBUILD
GET THIS FELLOW CLOSER TO
THE GIRL OF HIS DREAMS?
>>DOUGIE: HAROLD YOUR FIRST
RULE IF YOU WANT TO BE
NOTICED IS YOU GOT TO MAKE
SURE YOUR CAR MAKES A LOT OF
NOISE YOU KNOW BIG THUNDERING
EXHAUST SYSTEM AND PEEL SOME
RUBBER OUT IN THE PARKING LOT.
>>HAROLD: WELL I WOULD AGREE
WITH YOU IF THIS FELLOW
WANTED TO MEET SAY YOU
KNOW A POLICE WOMAN.
>>DOUGIE: I WAS JUST THINKING
YOU KNOW MAYBE HE MIGHT WANT
TO DROP A RACING CAN IN HER
AND GET A HOLLY CARB
MAYBE SOME MOPAR HEADERS
GET THAT ENGINE SO SHE'S
JUST IDLING REAL ROUGH
AND TOUGH YOU KNOW
KIND OF LIKE
(RUMBLES LIKE A LOUD ENGINE)
>>RED: YEAH YOU KNOW LIKE
(DEEP THROATED RUMBLE)
>>DOUGIE: YEAH.
(BOTH MAKING ENGINE NOISES)
>>HAROLD: FOR THOSE OF YOU
WHO JUST TUNED IN THIS
IS NOT THE GERMAN VERSION
OF THE SHOW.
>RED: IT IS AUTUMN
THE LEAVES ARE BURNING
BUT NOT FROM THE MAPLE
NOT THE LEAVES FROM THE OAK
OR THE OLD SYCAMORE
THESE ARE THE LEAVES FROM
THE DINING ROOM TABLE
THE LAST TIME WE HAVE
FONDUE IN THIS HOUSE.
>>RED: 99, THERE SHOULD
BE ONE MORE, I THOUGHT
I HAD A 100,
OH WELL THAT SHOULD DO IT.
SO THERE YOU ARE YOU'RE
ALL TIED RIGHT IN NOW TO
THE INTERNATIONAL SATELLITE
SYSTEM PART OF THE GREAT
VIDEO INFORMATION NETWORK
YOU'VE GOT A 1,000 CHANNELS
AT YOUR FINGERTIPS
NOW LET'S CRANK HER UP
AND SEE WHAT WE CAN
PULL IN HERE.
(THE RED GREEN SHOW PLAYS ON)
(ON ALL TV CHANNELS)
OH MAN THERE'S NOTHING ON...
OH WELL IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY,
OH THERE WE GO.
>>RED: GLEN BRAXTON HAD A MAJOR
PROBLEM KEEPING THE BUGS
ON THE FRONT OF HIS R.V.
WELL MAYBE YOU COULD PUT
SOME KIND OF A WAX OR
A TEFLON COATING ON
THE FRONT OF THERE.
>>GLEN: OH I TRIED THAT
LAST SUMMER RED, I PUT LARD
ALL OVER THE FRONT OF IT
BUT I THOUGHT THEY'D SKIP
OFF IT, IT ATTRACTED THEM.
OH MAN AND IT REALLY GUMMED
UP THE WINDSHIELD
YOU KNOW I HAD TO REPLACE
THE WIPERS EVERY
COUPLE OF HOURS.
>>RED: OH BOY.
>>GLEN: AND THEN IT GOT REAL
HOT AND IT STARTED TO COOK
THE BUGS ON THERE AND KIDS
CAME RUNNING THEY THOUGHT
IT WAS A CHIP WAGON.
>>RED: OH.
>>GLEN: JUST ONCE I'D LIKE
TO GO TO FLORIDA DOWN AND
BACK WITHOUT A BILLION
LITTLE BUG PARTS ALL
OVER THE FRONT END.
>>RED: WELL MAYBE YOU
COULD BACK IT ALL THE WAY.
>>GLEN: YOU KNOW THAT'S NOT
BAD I NEED BIGGER MIRRORS
BUT NO COULDN'T DO IT RED.
>>RED: NO?
>>GLEN: AS I'M GOING BACK
ALL THE TOLL BOOTHS WOULD
BE ON THE WRONG SIDE.
>>RED: OH NO.
>>GLEN: I'LL TELL YOU YOU'RE
ONTO SOMETHING THERE RED
THAT WAS CLOSE.
>>RED: YEAH.
WELL GLEN I WAS WONDERING IF
YOU COULD MAYBE TUNE UP MY
V-8 MARINE ENGINE FOR ME.
>>GLEN: OH I DON'T THINK
SO RED I'M AWFUL BUSY YOU KNOW
YOU COULD DO IT YOURSELF
I MEAN JUST ADJUST THE
NEEDLE VALVE ON THE CARB
IT'LL TAKE YOU TEN MINUTES.
>>RED: AND YOU HAVEN'T GOT
TEN MINUTES TO SPARE GLEN?
>>GLEN: WELL I'M AWFUL BUSY
HERE RED I HAVEN'T GOT ENOUGH
PAPERWORK WITH ME YOU KNOW
PLUS I'VE GOT THIS BUG THING
ON MY MIND RED AND I DON'T
THINK I COULD DEVOTE MY FULL
ATTENTION TO YOU SO IT
WOULDN'T BE FAIR TO YOU.
>>RED: MAN HOW DO YOU
STAY IN BUSINESS GLEN?
>>GLEN: I'M THE ONLY
MARINA ON THE LAKE RED.
>>RED: RIGHT.
>>RED: WELL THINGS ARE GETTING
PRETTY COMPETITIVE FOR THIS
RACE ACROSS POSSUM LAKE
AND IT'S KIND OF DISAPPOINTING
TO SEE THE MEN TRYING SO HARD
TO BEAT EACH OTHER, YOU KNOW
AS IF THEY HAVE ANY CHANCE
AGAINST MY SKIFF.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED ARE YOU
SURE THAT YOU JUST DON'T WANT
TO SNEAK A PEEK AT THOSE
NAKED SUNBATHERS?
>>RED: NO IT DOESN'T INTEREST
ME IN THE SLIGHTEST HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OH WELL I SHOULD
HOPE NOT, NOT AT YOUR AGE.
>>RED: NOT REALLY AN AGE
THING HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: WELL IT SHOULD BE.
>>RED: WELL IT'S NOT,
I HAVE MY REPUTATION AS
LODGE LEADER TO THINK OF
AND I HAVE TO WIN THAT RACE
EVEN IF IT MEANS DROPPING
A 427 SUPER CHARGED HEMI
INTO A 12 FOOT CANOE.
>>HAROLD: I THINK THAT'S
GOING TO MAKE THE CANOE
RATHER HARD TO NAVIGATE
HAVING A 700 HORSEPOWER
ENGINE IN THERE INSTEAD
OF A PADDLE YOU KNOW.
>>RED: WELL I DON'T HAVE TO
STEER IT HAROLD I GOT FORWARD
AND REVERSE, STRAIGHT OVER
STRAIGHT BACK.
>>HAROLD: HO HO YEAH
YOU'RE CERTAINLY GOING TO
BE MORE ENTERTAINING THAN
THOSE NUDISTS.
>>RED: SUN WORSHIPPERS
HAROLD SUN WORSHIPPERS.
>>HAROLD: OKAY, YOU HAVE
INSURANCE UNCLE RED?
>>RED: WELL WHY WOULD
I NEED INSURANCE?
>>HAROLD: YOU'LL SEE.
>>RED: DO YOU HAVE
INSURANCE HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: YES I DO.
>>RED: THAT'S VERY WISE.
>>HAROLD: THANK YOU,
OH I SEE, OH DEAR.
♪ SHE HAD BIG BROWN EYES ♪
♪ AND A NICE PERSONALITY ♪
♪ 4 GREAT LEGS ♪
♪ AND AN ATTRACTIVE HIDE ♪
♪ I REMEMBER HOW ♪
♪ VERY, VERY SAD WE WERE ♪
♪ ON THE DAY SHE DIED ♪
>>HAROLD: BOO HOO!
♪ BUT BY GOLLY ♪
♪ THE BURGERS SURE WERE GOOD ♪
>>RED: WELL THIS WEEK ON
'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'
BILL TOLD ME TO MEET HIM
OUT BEHIND THE LODGE AND
TRY A LITTLE DUCK HUNTING.
WHOA! WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
BILL DOES EVERYTHING POSSIBLY
WRONG WITH A GUN AND LOOK IT
HE'S GOT ONE OF THE OLD
DAVY CROCKETT RACCOON
WELL THAT'S NOT THE
DAVY CROCKETT STYLE
THAT BY GOLLY THAT ACTUALLY
IS A RACCOON, WOW!
BILL LET THAT THING GO,
LET HIM GO, LET HIM GO!
NO, NO, BILL NO, NO, NO, NO BOY
DUCK HUNTING BILL, DUCK.
ALRIGHT HE BROUGHT HIS LAUNDRY
HAMPER OH NO, NO, OH I SEE
BOY HE'S GOT A LOT OF DECOYS
WOW HE MUST BE JUST
MADE OF MONEY...
ANYWAY THE IDEA HE TOLD ME
HERE IS JUST SPREAD THE DECOYS
OUT IN SOME KIND OF A FORMATION
THAT DUCKS FLYING OVER FROM
THE AIR CAN SEE THESE AND BE
ATTRACTED TO THEM IN SOME
WAY BUT I DON'T THINK
HI DUCKS IS GOING TO WORK
ALL THAT WELL,
THEN HIS PLAN WAS JUST TO
NOW TO ME I MEAN AREN'T
WE A LITTLE SORT OF OUT
IN THE OPEN.
OKAY OH DON'T WE NEED TO BE
IN SOME SORT OF A DUCK BLIND
I WAS ACTUALLY ALMOST BLIND
MYSELF AT THIS POINT BUT DON'T
WORRY ANY OF YOU OUT THERE
DON'T WORRY ABOUT DUCKS
OR ANYTHING BEING SHOT,
THEY'RE REAL SAFE
SEE WHAT I MEAN?
THE ONLY PEOPLE THAT ARE IN
DANGER WHEN WE GO HUNTING
IS THE 2 OF US.
ANYWAY BILL BROUGHT SOME
BRANCHES IN
OH, OH, OH, OH MAN,
WATCH WHERE YOUR BACKING
THERE BILL.
NOW HE'S GOING TO BUILD US
A LITTLE BLIND.
>>BILL: OH!
>>RED: SORRY BILL BUT IT
SEEMS FAIR, AND HE'S GOING
TO BUILD US A BLIND OUT
OF THE BRANCHES.
OW! OH ALRIGHT ANYWAY WE'RE
GOING TO BUILD A BLIND UP THERE
SO THAT YOU HAVE SOME SORT
OF COVER, YEAH THAT'S
HOW IT WORKS.
NOW WE JUST SIT BACK DOWN
AND JUST WAIT FOR THE DUCKS
TO COME BY AND OH NOT ONE OF
THE BETTER DUCK BLINDS ANYWAY
BUT WE'RE NOT GOING
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT,
BILL'S GOT A DUCK CALLER
MAYBE THAT WILL DO IT YOU KNOW
THE OLD DUCK HONKER THING,
I'M NOT GOING TO EVEN SPECULATE
AS TO WHAT THAT WAS
BUT HERE WE GO HERE'S
THE DUCK CALLER HERE WE GO.
(LOUD EXPLOSION)
>>RED: OH NO, NO, NO, NO
HERE AGAIN THAT WOULD BE
A SHOTGUN SHELL WELL THE
3RD TIME LUCKY RIGHT BILL?
YEAH OH THIS IS CHECK IT OUT
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, OH THE RIGHT
END ALRIGHT I SEE
OKAY YEAH ALL SET.
(BILL QUACKING)
>>RED: BILL YOU SWALLOWED IT,
BILL OH THEY DON'T WORK THAT
WAY OH YES THEY DO YEAH
YEAH AND THE DUCKS ARE STARTING
TO COME IN WELL NOW THIS IS
NOW I'M STARTING TO HAVE FUN.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
>>RED: NOW I DON'T ACTUALLY WOW!
WE'RE NOT GETTING ANYTHING
BUT BOY WE'RE MAKING A LOT
OF NOISE, YEAH GIVE
ANOTHER CALL.
(THUD OF KICK)
(BILL QUACKING)
>>RED: AND SUDDENLY I STARTED
TO ENJOY DUCK HUNTING MORE
THAN I THOUGHT I EVER COULD.
>>RED: AND NOW SOMETHING FOR
THE YOUNG PEOPLE THAT
COMPLETELY DEFIES EXPLANATION
HERE'S HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: WELCOME TO A BRAND NEW
FEATURE OF THE RED GREEN SHOW
AND IT'S GOING TO BE OF
INTEREST TO ANYONE WHOSE
UNDER YOU KNOW THE AGE OF
60 IT'S H.T.V. AND I'M YOUR
EMCEE, HAROLD COUNTING DOWN
THE VIDEO HITS.
OKAY HERE WE GO NUMBER 60
'SQUEEZE THE BEEF' BY
MOON ME SIDEWAYS.
NUMBER 59 IS DEBBIE AND
THE DEEP FISHERS WITH
'A RIVER RUNS THROUGH ME'.
HOLDING AT 58 'CHOKE ON THIS'
BY MEAT CLEAVER,
THAT'S A LOVE SONG ISN'T IT?
57 IS A BRAND NEW ONE
BY AIR SICKNESS BAG AND IT'S
CALLED 'BE MY THERMOMETER'.
A LOT OF WEDDINGS USING THAT
SONG IT'S A GOOD ONE AND
OF COURSE 56 IS WENDY BAFFIN
WITH 'JUST CUZ'.
JUST CUZ AND WE'VE GOT 55
CHECK IT IN IT'S A GOOD ONE
TOO IT'S 'LIFE SUCKS' BY
HELSINKI JONES AND LOOFAH LIPS.
YEAH YOU'VE GOT TO CHECK
THAT ONE OUT AND OF COURSE
CHECKING IN AT 54
'GRUNT' BY GROAN.
>>RED: AND CHECKING OUT
AND 86ED IT'S HAROLD
AND WHO CARES.
>>RED: I WOKE UP IN THE
PARK LAST SUNDAY MORNING
AND ONCE I GOT THE NEWSPAPERS
OFF ME THERE I COULDN'T HELP
BUT NOTICE HOW MANY TEENAGERS
WERE DOWN THERE THROWING
A BALL AROUND OR HANGING OUT
OR STRIPPING CARS OR
WHAT HAVE YOU.
I THOUGHT TO MYSELF WELL WHY
AREN'T THESE KIDS IN CHURCH
LIKE I WAS AT THEIR AGE
YOU KNOW SITTING IN MY
SUNDAY SCHOOL CLASS IN THE
CIRCLE THERE WEARING THEM
GREY FLANNEL HAND ME DOWNS
WATCHING MRS. PENNINGTON'S
FALSE TEETH DEFY GRAVITY
ALONG WITH THE REST
OF HER BODY.
I LEARNED SO MANY THINGS THERE
THAT THE TEENS OF TODAY
JUST AREN'T GETTING EXPOSED
TO LIKE HOW TO PRETEND
YOU'RE LISTENING, HOW TO
SLEEP WITH YOUR EYES OPEN,
HOW TO MAKE JOKES WITH YOUR
HANDS AND HOW TO SING HYMN
435 WHILE EVERYBODY ELSE IS
DOING 342 BUT THE TEENS OF
TODAY THEY'RE JUST NOT
GETTING IN ON THAT AT ALL,
I DID THAT UNTIL I WAS 16
YEARS OLD AND I NEVER WENT
BACK BUT THAT'S NOT THE POINT
THE YOUNG PEOPLE OF TODAY
HAVEN'T EARNED THEIR RIGHT
NOT TO GO TO CHURCH.
>>RED: WELL WE'RE ALL GETTING
READY FOR THE BOAT RACE
HERE SO I THOUGHT I'D COME
OUT AND VISIT ONE OF MY BEST
FRIENDS OF ALL TIME
BUZZ SHERWOOD, BUZZ.
>>BUZZ: HEY!
>>RED: HOW'S MY FAVOURITE
PILOT OF THE DAY HUH?
>>BUZZ: HEY RED MAN
GIVE ME 5.
>>RED: ALRIGHT, ALRIGHT, OH.
>>BUZZ: OH YEAH.
>>RED: BUZZ, BUZZ, YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH, OH, OH, OH.
>>BUZZ: HEY MY MAN
HOW ARE YOU?
COME HERE I HUG YA!
>>RED: THAT'S FUNNY HAROLD
THAT'S FUNNY.
BUZZ HOW IS YOUR BEAUTIFUL
PLANE RUNNING TODAY?
>>BUZZ: OH NOT YOU TOO MAN
LISTEN I'M NOT TAKING ANYBODY
ON ANY FLIGHTS OVER
THAT NUDIST CAMP
JUST FORGET IT MAN.
>>RED: I NEVER SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT A NUDIST CAMP.
>>BUZZ: OH COME ON MAN
LIKE HAVE NONE OF THE GUYS
AROUND HERE SEEN A NAKED WOMAN
BEFORE I MEAN LIKE WAS I
THE ONLY ONE AT WOODSTOCK?
ALL DAY LONG IT'S BEEN HEY BUZZ
I WANT TO GO UP AND TEST
MY HOME VIDEO VIDEO CAMERA,
HEY BUZZ HOW LOW AND SLOW
CAN YOUR PLANE FLY?
HEY BUZZ I WANT TO OVERCOME MY
FEAR OF HEIGHTS AND BREAK IN
MY TELEPHOTO LENS,
NO WAY MAN, FORGET IT!
>>RED: HAROLD I DON'T LIKE
LOW ANGLE SHOTS GET UP.
>>BUZZ: LOOK I'M REALLY
SORRY TO BUM YOU OUT MAN
BUT RIGHT NOW I'VE GOT TO
GET HER READY FOR THE BIG
BOAT RACE YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M SAYING?
>>RED: YOU'RE ENTERING
YOUR SEA PLANE?
>>BUZZ: NO I'M ENTERING
MY AIR BOAT.
>>RED: OH NO, NO, NO,
BUZZ THAT THING DOES
NOT QUALIFY AS A BOAT.
>>BUZZ: THIS THING DOES
NOT QUALIFY AS AN AIRPLANE.
HEY YOU KNOW WHAT I WAS JUST
GOING TO TAKE MY FERRY OUT
FOR A SHAKE DOWN CRUISE
AND SEE IF IT'S SHIP SHAPE,
WHY DON'T YOU COME ALONG WITH
ME YOU CAN BE LIKE THE ENSIGN
OR THE PURSER OR SOMETHING.
>>RED: WELL.
>>BUZZ: COME ON, COME ON
STEP ONTO MY BRIDGE
GO ON, GO ON, HUH?
>>RED: THIS MIGHT BE AS
CLOSE AS I GET TO THE
LOVE BOAT HUH?
>>BUZZ: YOU SCARE ME
SOMETIMES RED,
ALRIGHT HERE WE GO.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>BUZZ: IT'S TIME TO CAST OFF,
YEAH ALRIGHT WHAT DO THEY
DO ENGINES ON 1/3RD.
>>RED: ALRIGHT.
>>BUZZ: OKAY COME ON
YEAH ALRIGHT WE NEED
A LITTLE CRUISE MUSIC.
(RADIO BLARING)
OH GOOD ONE!
ALRIGHT BATTEN DOWN ALL
HATCHES AND PORT HOLES.
>>RED: I THINK WE NEED
TO ABANDON SHIP SIR.
>>BUZZ: WELL APPARENTLY
THEY HAVE
ALRIGHT LET'S ROCK AND ROLL!
>>RED: WELL I'M SORRY TO
SAY I DIDN'T WIN THE BIG
BOAT RACE, MOOSE THOMPSON
LUCKED OUT.
>>HAROLD: I CANNOT BELIEVE
THAT MOOSE THOMPSON BEAT
THAT CANOE OF YOURS.
>>RED: THE WHOLE THING WAS
RIGGED HAROLD, I TOOK HIS
GAS CAN AND I POURED ABOUT
5 POUNDS OF SUGAR IN THERE
THEN JUST BEFORE THE RACE
HE CHEATED AND SWITCHED
CANS WITH ME.
WELL I THINK I'M GOING
TO PUT IN A GRIEVANCE
IT SURE IS EXPENSIVE.
>>HAROLD: SO WHAT YOU'RE
TELLING ME IS LIKE
MOOSE THOMPSON IS THE
NEW FERRY BOAT CAPTAIN?
>>RED: YEAH HE REPORTED
FOR WORK RIGHT AFTER THE RACE.
>>HAROLD: BOY WHAT'S
THE PAY SITUATION?
>>RED: I BELIEVE IT'S
$15 A TRIP PLUS EXPENSES
BUT I THINK MOOSE WOULD
HAVE PAID TWICE THAT MUCH
UNTIL HE FOUND OUT THE
SUN WORSHIPPERS REALLY
ARE SUN WORSHIPPERS.
A BUNCH OF OLD FAT GUYS
SITTING AROUND IN ROBES CHANTING
UP AT THE SUN LIKE THEY'RE
MAYANS OR AZTECS OR SOMETHING.
>>HAROLD: WELL THERE YOU GO
I HOPE YOU LEARNED A LESSON
THAT'S A LESSON
JUST FOR YOU.
>>RED: SHUT UP HAROLD!
>>HAROLD: AND THAT'S
A LESSON JUST FOR ME.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH THERE'S
THE POSSUM,
TIME FOR ANOTHER MEETING.
>>RED: YEAH YOU GO AHEAD
HAROLD I'LL BE DOWN
IN A SECOND.
YOU KNOW I ALWAYS LIKE A SHOW
WITH A POINT TO IT AND I THINK
THE POINT HERE IS MIND YOUR
OWN BUSINESS AND HOPEFULLY
THAT HASN'T BEEN LOST IN
ANYBODY WHOSE BEEN WATCHING
LIKE SAY FOR EXAMPLE
MY WIFE'S PARENTS,
JUST KIDDING! JUST KIDDING!
AND IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
I'M GOING TO BE COMING HOME
THE LONG WAY 'CAUSE I KNOW
I NEED SOME TIME TO FIGURE OUT
HOW I GOT INVOLVED WITH THIS
WHOLE THING BUT I'M PRETTY SURE
I'VE COME UP WITH A WAY
OF BLAMING HAROLD.
AND EVERYBODY ELSE ON BEHALF
OF HAROLD AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE
AND OF COURSE MYSELF
THANKS FOR WATCHING
AND KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>ALL: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORITATI.
>>RED: ALRIGHT I'VE GOT
ONE ANNOUNCEMENT BEFORE
WE GET STARTED HERE,
THE SENIOR CITIZENS ARE
HAVING A DANCE AT THE
END OF THE LAKE ON
SATURDAY NIGHT.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca