[quirky upbeat music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> AND NOW IT'S TIME FOR THE
RED GREEN SHOW STARRING
RED GREEN.
WHAT, MORE?
UM, RED GREEN SHOW: ALL ABOUT
NATURE AND WILDLIFE AND HOW
THEY CAN BE, UH, KILLED.
STARRING MY UNCLE--
CAN'T THE CAMERA MOVE
FASTER OR SOMETHING, COME ON,
HURRY UP--STARRING THE MAN OF
THE HOUR, THE HOST WITH THE
MOST, THE WOODSMAN'S WOODSMAN,
OR I'D LIKE TO SAY THE
WOODS PERSON BECAUSE I'M TRYING
TO MAKE THIS SHOW NON-SEXIST.
YOU KNOW, THESE GUYS AROUND
HERE, THEY DON'T CARE.
THEY'D HAVE IT AS OFFENSIVE AS
CAN POSSIBLY BE.
IT'S A FULL-TIME JOB FOR ME
TRYING TO BE--
>> THANK YOU, HAROLD.
>> SURE.
>> THANK YOU, AND WELCOME TO THE
SHOW.
I GOT A HECK OF A SHOW FOR YOU
THIS WEEK.
WE HAD A--WE HAD A TREASURE HUNT
UP AT THE LODGE HERE, AND, BUT
I'M LOOKING FOR GOLD,
BUT ALL WE FOUND WAS
FOOL'S GOLD.
SPEAKING OF WHICH, HAROLD, COME
ON OVER HERE A SEC.
HAROLD IS MY NEPHEW AND
PRODUCER/DIRECTOR OF THE SHOW,
AND HE HIS THIS FANCY LITTLE
WHIZMO RIGHT HERE.
>> YEAH, IT ALLOWS ME TO DO
THINGS LIKE THIS.
AND THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR
NOTICING.
>> WELL, HAROLD, YOU'RE NOT
GONNA NEED THAT LITTLE WHIZMO
FOR A WHILE THIS WEEK, BECAUSE I
GOT A HECK OF A STORY FOR THE
FANS HERE.
WE WERE ALL UP IN THE ATTIC AT
THE LODGE LOOKING FOR OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK, AND WE FOUND AN OLD
TRUNK, AND IT HAD A PADLOCK ON
IT, AND WE GOT THE CROWBAR, BUT
IT JUST WOULDN'T COME LOOSE, SO
WE GOT THREE OR FOUR 10-POUND
SLEDGES AND WE JUST CREAMED
THOSE IRON THINGS, YOU KNOW, AND
WHEN WE GOT INSIDE IT, THERE WAS
SOMETHING, I GUESS, THAT HAD
BEEN MADE OF GLASS.
IT WAS NOW JUST IN PIECES AND
SHARDS AND SO ON, GOT BROKE
SOMEHOW, I GUESS, PROBABLY
VALUABLE AT SOME POINT, BUT THE
INTERESTING THING HERE IS WE
FOUND A MAP, AND THE MAP HAD AN
"X" ON IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT AN "X" IS FOR?
>> YES.
CUE UP THE NEXT SEGMENT.
>> HAROLD, "X" IS FOR BURIED
TREASURE.
>> WELL, IT'S BURIED NOW.
[folksy guitar and spoons music plays]
>> WHO IS THAT HIDING
IN MY BEDROLL?
IS IT YOU, MARY BROWN?
WAY DOWN WHERE I CAN'T
SEE YOU
WANTING TO GO TO TOWN
WHO'S THAT HIDING
IN MY BEDROLL?
IS IT SOMEONE ON A FLIRT?
I REACH IN
AND GRAB YOU DOWN THERE
OH FOR GOSH SAKES
IT'S JUST MY OLD SHIRT
[strums acoustic guitar]
THIS WEEK, HANDYMAN CORNER, I'D
LIKE TO SHOW YOU THAT A TOILET
IS AN ASSET.
YOU KNOW, THERE WAS A TIME WHEN
WE'D HAVE AN OLD BABY LIKE THIS,
AND WE JUST WOULD THROW IT IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE LAKE, BUT NOW
IT'S GETTING TO A POINT, WE GOT
SO MANY FIXTURES AND APPLIANCES
AND WHATNOT OUT THERE THAT IT'S
JUST YOU'RE RISKING YOUR PROP
EVERY TIME YOU DO A POWER TURN
AROUND THE CANOE CLUB.
SO IT'S A LOT BETTER IF WE COME
UP WITH SOME OTHER USE FOR THESE
THINGS, AND I'VE DONE JUST THAT.
NOW THE--
[grunting]
THE FIRST STEP ON THIS,
AFTER THE HERNIA--
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS TO GET IT
APART IS TO LOOSEN THE BOLTS A
BIT ON THERE.
YOU GOT TO EXPECT A CERTAIN
AMOUNT OF BREAKAGE ON THESE,
BUT IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER
'CAUSE ALL WE'RE GONNA USE IS
THE TANK ON THE BACK.
SO AS YOU CAN SEE, I'VE GOT THE
BACK OF THE TANK SEPARATED HERE,
AND I'VE ATTACHED THESE CAR
SEAT BELTS.
I WAS ONLY SITTING ON THEM
ANYWAY.
I'VE USED A HANDYMAN'S SECRET
WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
SO NOW WHAT WE HAVE IS YOUR
PORTABLE CERAMIC BEVERAGE
COOLER.
WHAT YOU DO IS PUT SOME ICE IN
THERE, THROW IN SOME OF YOUR
FAVORITE BEVERAGES, POP THE LID
ON HERE, AND ON A DAY WHEN YOU
KNOW YOU'RE GOING WITH THIS, YOU
MIGHT WANT TO HAVE A COUPLE OF
STEROIDS FOR BREAKFAST.
EASE IT UP ONTO YOUR SHOULDER.
AND YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY.
NOW A LOT OF GUYS SAY YOU SHOULD
USE BEER FOR THIS 'CAUSE IT
ENDS UP IN THE TOILET ANYWAY, IT
MIGHT AS WELL START THERE.
YOU KNOW, WHEN THE ICE MELTS
WITH THIS BABY, AND YOU WANT TO
GET RID OF THE EXCESS WATER, NO
PROBLEM.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME, REMEMBER,
IF WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH THE
REST OF THE TREASURE HUNT STORY.
>> BE STILL MY TREMBLING HEART.
>> THAT COULD BE ARRANGED.
>> YOU KNOW, HAROLD, ONE OF THE
THINGS I ENJOY MOST ABOUT THE
LODGE IS COOKING OVER A LOG
FIRE, YOU KNOW, JUST RIGHT OUT
IN THE OUTDOORS THERE, AND
DOESN'T THAT MAKE THE FOOD TASTE
SPECIAL?
>> SPECIAL'S A STRONG WORD.
IT MAKES IT TASTE BURNT.
>> WELL, OKAY, THERE'S A LITTLE
BIT OF--THERE MIGHT BE SOME
CARBONIZATION ON THERE, BUT
THAT'S HEALTHY FOR YOU.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
IT GETS IN YOUR SYSTEM, AND IT
MAKES YOUR STOMACH WALL BLACK.
THAT'S WHY YOU SHOULD COOK IN A
STOVE.
>> NO, NO, NO, THAT'S CARBON.
THAT'S WHAT PLANTS EAT, CARBON.
>> BURNT HOT DOGS?
THINK AGAIN.
THERE'S NO WAY THAT A PLANT'S
GONNA TAKE THE TIME TO PUT A HOT
DOG ON A STICK.
THEY'D HAVE TO TEAR ITS OWN STEM
OFF TO DO THAT.
IT JUST WOULDN'T HAPPEN.
THAT'S WHY THEY HAVE STOVES, FOR
PLANTS TO EAT PROPERLY.
>> NO, NO, NO, THEY DON'T HAVE
STOVES FOR PLANTS.
>> YES, THEY DO.
IT'S A HOT HOUSE.
>> THAT'S NOT A STOVE FOR A
PLANT.
>> HAVE YOU EVER BEEN IN ONE?
>> WELL, AS A STAG, I WAS.
WHAT DID YOU SAY AGAIN?
>> A HOT HOUSE.
>> OH, NO, NO, I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY, MY MISTAKE.
"IT IS WINTER.
CHILDREN RUSH PAST PULLING SLEDS
AND TOBOGGANS, SHOPPERS HURRY
BY, HEADS BOWED AGAINST THE
WIND, AND TO EACH YOU CALL OUT A
FAMILIAR REFRAIN,
'CALL 9-1-1, I'VE SLIPPED AND
BROKEN MY BACK.'"
ANYWAY, JUST TO GET BACK
TO THIS BURIED TREASURE THING,
THIS WAS KIND OF EXCITING.
WE'RE ALL UP THERE IN THE ATTIC,
AND THEY GOT THE TREASURE MAP
OUT, AND WE POURED OVER IT,
AND WE POURED AROUND IT;
WE EVEN POURED SOME RIGHT ON IT,
YOU KNOW, AND TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT EXACTLY WHERE THE "X" WAS,
AND WE FIGURED OUT THAT IT WAS
PROBABLY HALFWAY BETWEEN THE
LODGE AND THE OLD MILL DOWN THE
ROAD, BUT NOW THE OLD MILL, OF
COURSE, DIDN'T SHOW UP ON THE
MAP, BECAUSE IT'S LESS THAN 400
YEARS OLD, BUT THE LODGE WAS
THERE.
SO ANYWAY, OFF WE GO.
WE TOOK COMPASSES AND MAPS AND
ROPES AND PICKAXES AND A
BACKHOE, AND WE GOT THERE ABOUT
2:00 IN THE AFTERNOON.
WE FIGURED WE WERE RIGHT IN THE
PERFECT SPOT WHERE A PIRATE WITH
BURIED TREASURE,
WENT RIGHT ON TOP OF A HILL
UNDER SOME TREES, EASY TO SPOT,
AND ONLY ABOUT 500 MILES FROM
THE SEA.
>> EXCUSE ME, UNCLE RED, THERE'S
BEEN SOMETHING I HAVE BEEN
WANTING TO DO EVER SINCE YOU
STARTED TALKING.
>> WELL, WHERE ARE WE NOW,
HAROLD?
>> I'LL DRAW YOU A MAP.
[laughter]
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S NOTHING MORE FUN THAN
FISHING WITH YOUR BEST FRIEND.
>> WELL, THIS COMES CLOSE, RED.
>> IT'S A GREAT DAY--
NOT TOO SUNNY, NOT TOO WINDY.
>> WELL, THE WIND IS GONNA COME
UP LATER FROM THE SOUTHWEST.
OUGHT TO GET TO ABOUT 30, 35,
TAPER OFF AROUND SUNDOWN.
SCATTERED SHOWERS OVERNIGHT.
SUN WOULD RISE AT 6:37 TOMORROW.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW ALL THAT
STUFF?
>> YOU GOT TO KNOW HOW TO READ
THE WEATHER WHEN YOU'RE A
FARMER.
>> FARMER, HUH?
YOU WERE A FARMER?
>> OH, SURE, BACK IN MY 20s.
BOUGHT ME A LITTLE SPREAD OUT
WEST, STARTED A FARM.
>> WHAT DID YOU GROW, WHEAT?
>> NO, RUBBER.
ANYBODY CAN GROW WHEAT.
HOW MANY RUBBER FARMERS DO YOU
KNOW, RED?
>> JUST YOU.
>> WELL, I BOUGHT ME THIS LITTLE
PIECE OF LAND AND 240 RUBBER
TREES FROM--WHERE'S THAT COUNTRY
WITH THE THINGS?
>> MALAYSIA?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
ANYWAY, I PLANTED THESE RUBBER
TREES RIGHT IN THE PRAIRIES.
>> I ALWAYS THOUGHT RUBBER TREES
WOULD ONLY GROW IN A TROPICAL
RAIN FOREST.
>> WE HAD THEM IN GREENHOUSES,
BIG GREENHOUSES, ATTACHED TO THE
BACK OF A TIRE FACTORY.
A BLOB OF RUBBER OOZES IN ONE
END, AND STEEL-BELTED,
WHITEWALL, RADIAL, BIAS-PLY
SNOW TIRES POP OUT THE OTHER.
I WAS ALL SET TO MAKE MY FIRST
TIRE AND TURN A LITTLE PROFIT
WHEN ALL MY CREDITORS CLOSED IN
ALL AT ONCE.
THE ONLY RUBBER THAT FACTORY
EVER PRODUCED WAS MY OWN CHECKS.
>> YEAH.
CREDITORS ARE LIKE THAT
SOMETIMES.
>> BUT WAIT, IT GETS TO ME WHEN
YOU CAN'T BELIEVE A WORD THEY
SAY.
>> YEAH, I KNOW THE FEELING.
[folksy guitar and spoons music plays]
OH, SHE'S FULL OF RUST
AND THE BRAKES ARE SHOT
THE TIRES ARE BALD
AND SHE SHAKES A LOT
SHE BURNS A LOT OF OIL
AND SHE'S HARD ON GAS
BUT I GOT 37 MORE PAYMENTS
SO I'LL BE KEEPING HER
>> OH, UNCLE RED, THIS IS SO
GREAT.
WE GOT SUCH AN EXCELLENT LETTER
TODAY.
IT'S FROM THE YUKON.
YEAH, I PUT THE STAMP IN MY TIME
CAPSULE.
>> THE YUKON, EH, HAROLD?
>> YEAH.
>> LAND OF THE MIDNIGHT SUN,
HUH?
DOGSLEDS, IGLOOS, SIX MONTHS OF
DAYLIGHT UP THERE, YOU KNOW?
THEY GOT THE GOLD RUSH UP THERE
AND POLAR BEARS, PENGUINS.
IT'S QUITE A PLACE.
>> WOW.
SOUNDS GREAT.
WHOO, WHOA, OKAY.
"DEAR RED, LIVING UP HERE IN THE
YUKON IS GREAT.
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS THAT PEOPLE
FROM THE SOUTH WHO STEREOTYPE US
NORTHERNERS.
THEY THINK OF THE YUKON AS THE
LAND OF THE MIDNIGHT SUN WITH
EVERYONE ON DOGSLEDS LIVING IN
IGLOOS AND HUNTING SEALS FOR SIX
MONTHS OF DAYLIGHT.
TOURISTS ASK US WHERE THE GOLD
RUSH IS AND WHERE THEY CAN FIND
POLAR BEARS AND PENGUINS.
WHAT KIND OF IDIOT DOESN'T KNOW
THAT PENGUINS ARE ONLY IN THE
SOUTH POLE?"
>> I THINK THE MAIN PROBLEM
THERE IS WITH THE FOREIGNERS.
YOU KNOW, THEY GO UP NORTH, AND
THEY'RE EXPECTING TO SEE
SNOWMOBILES AND MOUNTIES, YOU
KNOW, AND WHEN'S THE LAST TIME
YOU SAW A MOUNTIE, HAROLD?
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER SEEN A
MOUNTIE, YOU KNOW?
I DON'T THINK MOUNTIES EVEN
EXIST.
HOW ABOUT THIS VIEWER?
WHEN'S THE LAST TIME HE SAW A
MOUNTIE, MR.--UH, DOES HE GIVE
HIS NAME THERE?
>> YEAH, IN FACT, IT'S, UM,
"CORPORAL H. BENSON OF THE
ROYAL CANADIAN MOUNTED POLICE
WHITE HORSE DETACHMENT."
>> UH, OKAY, SORRY, UH, SORRY,
CORPORATE BENSON, UH, NO
OFFENSE, SIR, YOU GUYS ARE DOING
A GREAT JOB AND, UH, IT'S A
GREAT CANADIAN TRADITION THAT
YOU'RE CARRYING ON THERE, YOU
FELLAS UP--I'LL TELL YOU--I'LL
TELL YOU ONE THING, CORPORAL H.
BENSON, IF WE HAVE TO HAVE ONE
STEREOTYPE, THEN LET IT BE THE
CANADIAN MOUNTIE IN HIS BRIGHT
RED UNIFORM.
I SALUTE YOU, SIR.
>> RED, THE "H" STANDS FOR
HELEN.
>> WE GOT ANOTHER WINTER
ACTIVITY WE'RE FEATURING ON OUR
ADVENTURES WITH BILL SEGMENT
THIS WEEK.
THIS, OF COURSE, IS, AS YOU CAN
TELL, A SNOWSHOE.
NOW THE FIRST THING YOU NEED TO
DO IS TO MEASURE THE SNOWSHOES.
THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO BE--
GOD, THAT HURT.
I REMEMBER THAT, YEAH.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH YOUR HEIGHT.
ANYWAY, BILL IS AN ABSOLUTE
EXPERT ON SNOWSHOEING.
I THINK HE'S BEEN SNOWSHOEING
EVER SINCE HE WAS, UH, SMALLER.
SO I WAS JUST GUESSING HOW TO
PUT THEM ON.
I DIDN'T REALIZE THERE WAS A--
THERE WAS A, YOU KNOW,
A BETTER TECHNIQUE.
BUT THEN AGAIN, LIKE, BILL'S
BEEN DOING IT, UH,
DOING IT FOR QUITE A WHILE, AND,
UH, I PROBABLY SHOULD HAVE PAID
MORE ATTENTION TO HIM.
MIND YOU, HE DID GET MY
ATTENTION THERE, BUT I THINK
WHAT HAPPENED THERE, BILL JUST
GOT FED UP WITH ME NOT DOING IT
THE RIGHT WAY AND JUST DECIDED
HE JUST WOULDN'T DO IT.
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW, HE'S GOOD
THAT WAY.
YOU KNOW, HE'S NOT PUSHY.
GOLLY, THOSE ARE KIND OF CROSSED
OVER EACH OTHER.
WELL, AS THEY SAY, HE KNOWS WHAT
HE--YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES, PEOPLE
ARE BETTER TEACHERS THAN THEY
ARE AT ACTUALLY, UH--ACTUALLY
DOING THE ACTIVITY, AND I THINK,
YEAH, I THINK BILL KIND OF FALLS
INTO THAT CATEGORY WHEN YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT SNOWSHOEING,
UNLESS THIS IS A TECHNIQUE
THAT'S DESIGNED FOR SOME
SPECIFIC LEARNER.
NO, I THINK THAT'S JUST PLAIN
WRONG.
ONE OF THE MOST DIFFICULT THINGS
WITH SNOWSHOEING IS TURNING
AROUND, BECAUSE THEY'RE A LOT
BIGGER THAN A REGULAR SOLE,
BUT I JUST--AGAIN, I WAS
GUESSING HERE, BUT, UH, BILL HAS
A REALLY INTERESTING TECHNIQUE.
AND YOU KNOW, IF YOU HAVE A LOT
OF TIME ON YOUR HANDS, I THINK
THIS IS THE RIGHT TECHNIQUE TO
USE.
CERTAINLY INTERESTING TO WATCH.
AND IT DOES SCARE ALL THE
WILDLIFE AWAY.
THERE'S THAT ASPECT.
NOW BILL'S GONNA SHOW YOU
SEVERAL TECHNIQUES OF TURNING
AROUND.
THIS ONE, I THOUGHT, WAS
PARTICULARLY, UH, I GUESS,
CREATIVE, FOR LACK OF A BETTER
WORD.
AND THERE HE GOES.
YEAH, THAT WORKED REAL WELL.
NOW HERE'S ONE, TOO, THAT, YOU
KNOW, AGAIN, A WHOLE DIFFERENT
TECHNIQUE, BUT, UH, YOU KNOW, IF
YOU'RE CREATIVE AND IF YOU HAVE
A 6-FOOT STAFF, THERE YOU
GO, AND HE'S RIGHT AROUND, AND,
UH, AND AWAY WE GO.
YOU KNOW, AS THEY SAY, FOR ME, I
WOULD JUST TURN ON THE
SNOWSHOES, BUT HE LOVED THIS
ONE.
HE WANTED TO TRY THIS A FEW
TIMES.
OH, BOY.
NOW HERE'S SOMETHING REAL
INTERESTING.
YOU CAN MAKE YOUR OWN SNOWSHOES
OUT OF A SET OF TIRES.
THIS WAS KIND OF--
UH, WE ALWAYS KID BILL;
HE'S KIND OF A PULL START.
WELL, ANYWAY, YEAH, YOU CAN
MAKE IT.
YOU PUT YOUR FOOT IN THE TIRE,
IT DOESN'T EVEN HAVE TO BE SNOW
TIRES, YOU KNOW, AND THEN USE
ROPE TO MAKE THE WEBBING FOR IT,
SO WE GOT BILL'S ONE LEG IN
THERE, AND THEN WE GOT KIND OF
KIBITZING AROUND, WELL, I DID.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
YEAH, HE REACHED FOR THE OTHER
TIRE AND HE KIND OF FELL DOWN,
AND YOU KNOW, WHAT I DID WAS I
THOUGHT I'D HAVE SOME FUN WITH
HIM, SO I GOT THE TIRES UP, AND
I THOUGHT I JUST WOULD JUST PUSH
HIM DOWN THE HILL, YOU KNOW?
BILL LOVES THIS.
HE REALLY ENJOYED THIS.
WHEN HE SPOKE TO ME FROM THE
HOSPITAL, HE SAID, "YOU KNOW,
RED, THAT WAS REALLY DIFFERENT."
THEN HE LOST CONSCIOUSNESS
AGAIN.
I THINK THE BEST WAY TO TALK TO
THE TEENAGERS OF TODAY IS TO
JUST BE HONEST WITH THEM.
AND BELIEVE ME, I DON'T LIKE
DOING THAT ANY MORE THAN YOU DO.
NOW I WANT TO TALK ABOUT GUNS.
NOW I KNOW THIS IS A HUNTING
LODGE AND YOU SEE LOTS OF GUNS
AND ANIMAL SKINS AROUND, BUT THE
TRUTH IS IS THAT ALL OF THAT
STUFF WAS HERE WHEN WE TOOK OVER
THE LODGE 25 YEARS AGO.
TO MY KNOWLEDGE, NONE OF OUR
MEMBERS HAS EVER KILLED AN
ANIMAL WITH ANYTHING OTHER THAN
A STEEL-BELTED RADIAL.
OH, YEAH, WE GO HUNTING, BUT WE
DON'T TAKE ANY AMMO, AND WE SURE
AS HECK DON'T KILL ANYTHING.
AND IT'S NOT JUST BECAUSE NOBODY
WANTS TO CLEAN A BEAR.
THE TRUTH IS, WE TALK A LOT
ABOUT GUNS, BUT WE DON'T REALLY
USE THEM.
SEE, THAT'S THE WAY MEN ARE--A
LOT OF TALK, NOT MUCH ACTION.
JUST ASK OUR WIVES.
NOW THE TRUTH HURTS, BUT--BUT
THIS IS IMPORTANT, OR AT LEAST I
THOUGHT IT WAS A MINUTE AGO.
WELL, WE WON'T AIR THIS ONE.
"IT IS WINTER.
THE SNOW IS ON THE ROOFTOPS.
THE SNOW IS ON THE TREE.
THE WIND BLEW DOWN MY CABLE.
NOW THERE'S SNOW ON MY TV."
HEY, YOU KNOW, UH, WE GET THE
ODD COMMENT THAT PEOPLE ARE
GETTING TIRED OF HEARING ME
TALK, SO WE WANTED TO DO
SOMETHING THAT WOULD REVERSE
THAT PROCESS.
>> OKAY, UM, BIG QUESTIONS,
RIGHT?
OKAY, WE GET SO CAUGHT UP IN
DAY-TO-DAY EVENTS, LIKE, YOU
KNOW, EATING AND SLEEPING AND
ROLLER DERBY AND STUFF, THAT WE
FORGET ABOUT THE BIG QUESTIONS,
RIGHT?
LIKE, BIG QUESTIONS LIKE, WHY?
OH, OH.
THAT REMINDS ME OF ANOTHER
BIG QUESTION.
WHO?
BIG QUESTIONS, RIGHT?
WELL, LIKE, NOT PHYSICALLY BIG
QUESTIONS, RIGHT, LIKE, HEY, I'M
NOT PHYSICALLY BIG, BUT I'M BIG
PHILOSOPHICALLY.
YEAH.
AND MY LARGE INTESTINE IS OVER
10 FEET LONG.
SO YOU FIGURE OUT WHY IT TAKES
SO LONG TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
OKAY, THESE ARE BIG QUESTIONS.
AND BIG QUESTIONS NEED BIG
ANSWERS, RIGHT?
I GOT THEM.
I GOT THE BIG ANSWER.
ALIENS.
ALIENS--WE'RE NOT ALONE. NO WAY.
BUT YOU KNOW, I'D REALLY PREFER
TO TALK ABOUT THIS LATER,
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO MISS
STAR TREK.
OKAY? OKAY.
THANK YOU.
>> STAY TUNED TO FIND OUT HOW
THE TREASURE HUNT TURNED OUT.
>> BIG HINT--WE'RE STILL DOING
THE SHOW.
>> IMAGINE IF SUPERMAN EVER GOT
INTO A FIGHT WITH ANYBODY, HUH?
HE'S QUITE A GUY.
>> HE CAN TAKE ANYBODY ALMOST.
>> ANYBODY--NOT ALMOST, ANYBODY.
>> NO, ALMOST.
BATMAN COULD TAKE SUPERMAN IN AN
INSTANT.
>> OH, GET OUT OF MY FACE.
>> I DON'T EVEN HAVE TO, BECAUSE
IT'S TRUE.
>> BATMAN IS LIKE PHIL DONAHUE
WITH AN ATTITUDE.
>> DON'T SAY THAT.
THAT'S NOT EVEN TRUE.
BATMAN IS WAY BETTER THAN
SUPERMAN.
>> HE HAS NO SUPER POWER.
>> YES, HE DOES.
>> I DON'T THINK HE DOES.
>> HE'S GOT PSYCHOLOGICAL POWERS
OVER SUPERMAN.
>> OH, WELL, HOW DOES THAT
COMPARE WITH X-RAY VISION?
>> EASY, BECAUSE HE CAN JUST
THINK ABOUT STUFF,
AND WHILE SUPERMAN'S LOOKING
AROUND THROUGH WALLS, HE CAN
SNEAK UP ON HIM WITH BRAIN
ATTACK.
>> OH, YEAH, HOW ABOUT BEING
ABLE TO STOP BULLETS?
YOU KNOW, FASTER THAN A SPEEDING
LOCOMOTIVE?
GIVE ME SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
ALL RIGHT?
ABLE TO JUMP TALL BUILDINGS WITH
A SINGLE BOUND.
>> HE'S A BAT.
HE CAN HANG UPSIDE DOWN.
ALL THE BLOOD WOULD RUSH TO
SUPERMAN'S HEAD, AND HE'D GET
FOGGY, AND HIS X-RAY VISION
WOULD GET ALL SCREWED UP.
>> SUPERMAN WOULDN'T HANG UPSIDE
DOWN.
HE JUST WOULD FLOAT BESIDE HIM
AND STING LIKE A BEE.
>> HE DOESN'T HAVE HOVER
ABILITIES.
>> HE DOESN'T NEED HOVER
>> YEAH, BUT HE CAN'T FLOAT
BESIDE HIM, THEN, SEE?
AND WHEN HE'S GOING SO FAST--
>> HE HAS HOVER. HE HAS HOVER.
HE HAS A HOVER SETTING.
>> HE DOESN'T. NO, HE DOESN'T.
>> YOU'VE NEVER SEEN HIS
TRANSMISSION THE WAY I HAVE.
>> NO, YOU'RE THINKING OF MR.
AMERICA.
HE HAS HOVER ABILITY.
>> HELICOPTER MAN.
>> THAT'S THE GUY.
>> YEAH.
NOW WE'RE OUT HERE ON LOCATION
WITH MY GOOD BUDDY DOUGIE
FRANKLIN, AND, DOUGIE, THIS IS A
NICE SET OF WHEELS YOU GOT HERE.
>> WELL, RED, IT OUGHT TO BE.
COST ME ABOUT $18,000.
>> WELL, STILL, THAT'S REALLY
NOT THAT, NOT THAT BAD FOR A
TRUCK THIS BIG.
>> NO, NO, THAT WAS FOR THE
WHEELS, RED.
THE TRUCK COST A LOT MORE.
I MEAN, IT'S A LOT OF TRUCK
THERE, AND IT'S A BIG ONE, AND
THAT'S WHY YOU GOT TO PAY MORE,
AND THAT KIND OF MAKES IT ALL
WORTHWHILE.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
ACTUALLY, HOW TALL IS THIS
VEHICLE?
>> WELL, I'LL TELL YOU, I
COULDN'T REALLY GIVE YOU THE
EXACT HEIGHT OF HER, BUT I WAS
OUT THERE ON YOUR BASELINE ROAD
GOING UNDER THAT UNDERPASS THERE
AND DOING ABOUT 80 MILES AN
HOUR.
>> OH, SO SHE'S OBVIOUSLY NOT
ANY TALLER THAN THE BRIDGE ON
THE BASELINE ROAD.
>> NOT ANYMORE.
I LOST A WHOLE RACK OF LIGHTS--
SPOTLIGHTS I HAD UP AT THE TOP
AND MY GOOD WHIRLY LIGHT
FOR ACCIDENTS.
I LOST THAT SUCKER AS WELL.
>> OH.
>> BUT SHE IS BIG, AND SHE HAS
TO BE BIG FOR COMPETITION.
>> YEAH.
>> AND, UH--
>> YOU TAKE THIS DOWN TO
CARTERVILLE, DON'T YOU?
>> WE DONE REAL WELL AT
CARTERVILLE THE LAST YEAR.
WE TOOK THE MOST CARS JUMPED BY
A TRUCK--BY A MONSTER TRUCK.
WE TOOK MOST CARS CRUSHED BY A
MONSTER TRUCK.
WE ALSO WON THE MOST SEVERE
WHIPLASH TO THE DRIVER AWARD.
WE ALSO GOT THE, UH, THIS ONE, I
WAS PROUD OF, THE HIGHEST FLAME
SHOOTING OUT OF AN EXHAUST
STACK.
>> REALLY?
>> THAT ONE MEANT SOMETHING
TO ME.
AND THE BIG TROPHY, WE TOOK THE
BIG TROPHY OF THE DAY, OF
COURSE, WHICH WAS THE LARGEST
AUTOMOTIVE FIRE AT AN INDOOR
VENUE.
I'LL TELL YOU, TO TAKE THAT
TROPHY AND WALK AWAY FROM IT,
YOU KNOW, VERY FEW PEOPLE DO
THAT.
WE'RE QUITE PROUD.
>> WELL, I THINK THE IMPORTANT
THING HERE IS THERE IS AN AWFUL
LOT MORE TO THIS SPORT THAN
PEOPLE REALIZE.
>> WELL, THAT'S TRUE, YOU KNOW,
AND, RED, WE'RE HOPING TO
COMPETE AT THE COMMONWEALTH
MONSTER TRUCK GAMES.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO THE
COMMONWEALTH GAMES WITH THIS?
>> WELL, WE'RE HOPING TO
REPRESENT CANADA THERE, AND, UH,
OF COURSE, THERE'LL BE MONSTER
TRUCKS FROM, UH, AUSTRALIA,
NIGERIA.
THEY GOT THE BIG MONSTER TRUCKS
COMING FROM THE BAHAMAS,
PAKISTAN.
UH, WE'RE REAL PLEASED.
I'M HOPING WE'RE GONNA DO WELL.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, THEY SAY THAT, UH,
THIS YEAR AT THE COMMONWEALTH
TRUCK PULL AND MONSTER TRUCK
GAMES, THEY'RE HOPING TO HAVE
NELSON MANDELA THERE AS KIND OF
YOUR GRAND MARSHAL OF THE WHOLE
EVENT.
>> WELL, GOLLY, DOUGIE--
>> YES, IT'S A BIG PRESENCE.
>> HEY, WELL, GOOD LUCK TO YOU,
YOU KNOW.
>> I APPRECIATE THAT.
THANK YOU.
>> I'LL LET YOU GET BACK TO, YOU
KNOW, WHATEVER THE HECK IT IS
YOU DO HERE, AND WE'LL SEE--
HEY, MAYBE, UH, DOWN AT THE
COMMONWEALTH GAMES, WE'LL SEE
YOU ON THE PODIUM SINGING THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
>> WELL, I'LL TELL YOU, I GUESS
I BETTER LEARN THE WORDS.
[laughter]
IF NOT, I'LL NEED TO GET MY HORN
TO PLAY IT.
OKAY, RED.
>> OKAY, DOUG.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD, GET US OUT OF
HERE.
>> EE-I-EE-I-O
>> IT'S "OUR HOME AND NATIVE
LAND," I BELIEVE.
>> SORRY, I WAS JUST, I'LL GET
THAT DOWN, DON'T YOU WORRY
ABOUT IT.
I WILL GET IT DOWN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WATCH THAT WHEEL THERE.
I JUST DUSTED HER OFF.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO ANYWAY, THE BUNCH OF US HAD,
YOU KNOW, KIND OF DECIDED WHERE
THE BURIED TREASURE WAS,
AND WE STARTED DIGGING, AND WE
DUG AND WE DUG AND WE DUG AND WE
DUG AND WE DUG AND THEN WE
DUG, YOU KNOW, AND THEN, UH, WE
ALL KIND OF SPLIT UP AND JUST
STARTED JUST DIGGING ANYWHERE,
YOU KNOW, AND DOING A LOT MORE
DIGGING AND STILL NOTHING, AND
UNFORTUNATELY, WHAT HAPPENS WITH
MEN SOMETIMES IS THE
FRUSTRATION, YOU KNOW, STARTS TO
SET IN, AND PRETTY SOON, WE'RE
JUST GOING AROUND AND WHACKING
TREES WITH OUR SHOVELS, YOU
KNOW, AND THROWING BIG CLUMPS OF
DIRT AT EACH OTHER AND TRYING TO
DRIVE OVER PEOPLE'S FEET WITH A
BACKHOE.
AND THEN, OF COURSE, THE OWNER
OF THE GOLF COURSE CALLED THE
COPS.
ANYWAY, YOU KNOW, UH, WE'RE NO
RICHER, BUT WE'RE A LITTLE
WISER.
LIKE, FOR INSTANCE, WE KNOW NOW
NOT TO DIG FOR BURIED TREASURE
AT A GOLF COURSE WHILE IT'S
OPEN.
SO, UH, ANYWAY, MY WIFE IS
WATCHING.
I'M GONNA BE A BIT LATE TONIGHT
'CAUSE A BUNCH OF US ARE GOING
DOWN TO THE LIBRARY, AND IF YOU
NOTICE THE SHOVEL'S MISSING,
DON'T WORRY, I'VE GOT IT.
ALL RIGHT, ANYWAY, THANK YOU SO
MUCH FOR WATCHING, AND ON BEHALF
OF MYSELF AND, UH, HAROLD...
>> HAROLD, YOUR NEPHEW.
>> HAROLD, MY NEPHEW, ALL RIGHT,
CLOSE ENOUGH, UH, AND THE REST
OF THE GANG UP HERE AT THE
LODGE, YOU KEEP YOUR STICK ON
THE ICE.
[applause]