HAVE YOU EVER WONDERED WHY A
GOLF BALL GOES SO FAR?
THEY TELL ME IT'S
ALL THE DIMPLES.
OH, YEAH, THESE LITTLE
DENTS IN THE GOLF BALL
MAKE IT AERODYNAMIC.
ACTUALLY, THERE ARE 336
DIMPLES IN A GOLF BALL.
I KNOW.
I COUNTED THEM ONE DAY WHEN I
WAS WITH BERNICE AT THE MALL.
SO I'M THINKIN' IF DIMPLES MAKE
THE GOLF BALL GO FARTHER,
THEY SHOULD HAVE THE SAME
EFFECT ON THIS VEHICLE.
THAT'S WHERE THIS BALL-PEEN
HAMMER COMES IN.
WE'RE GONNA TAKE THE
TECHNOLOGY OF THE GOLF BALL
AND APPLY IT TO THE POOR
DESIGN OF THIS FORD
336 TIMES.
ONE.
TWO.
THREE.
334,
335,
336.
IF HENRY FORD HAD OF
THOUGHT OF THIS,
HE WOULD'VE MADE A FORTUNE.
THIS SHOULD WORK GREAT 'CAUSE
WE'VE GOT AN OVERSIZED DRIVER.
FORE! DUH!
(play on Ford)
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HEY, BY GOLLY.
THAT'S GREAT.
YEAH, APPRECIATE THAT.
BIG, BIG, BIG WEEK UP AT THE
LODGE THIS WEEK.
THE ROCK REEF BREWERY IS
UPGRADING ALL THEIR EQUIPMENT
'CAUSE THEY'VE BEEN GETTIN'
A LOT OF DEAD MICE IN
THEIR BEER BOTTLES.
NOW, PERSONALLY, I THINK
IT'S A CULT SUICIDE THING.
AND IF YOU EVER TASTED THE BEER,
I THINK YOU'D AGREE WITH ME.
NOW, THEIR SLOGAN IS,
"THE BEER THAT GOES DOWN FAST."
BUT LATELY, THEIR STOCK HAS
ACTUALLY BEEN GOIN' DOWN A
LITTLE BIT FASTER.
SO THEY'RE UPGRADING
THE WHOLE PLANT,
AND THE BIG NEWS IS
THEY'RE GIVING AWAY ALL THEIR
OLD BEER BARRELS,
AND EVERY GUY IN
THE LODGE GETS ONE.
UNBELIEVABLE.
HEY, RED, YOU GET
YOUR BEER BARREL YET?
YEAH. YEAH.
YEAH?
YEAH, 'CAUSE I'M PUTTING
FIREWOOD IN MINE.
WHY NOT?
YOU KNOW, IT EVEN SAYS
LAGER (logger) RIGHT ON IT!
OH, MAN.
WHAT ABOUT YOU,
WINSTON?
YOU DOIN' SOMETHING
WITH YOURS?
WELL, I FIGURE IF I USE MINE
AS A SEPTIC HOLDING TANK,
IT'LL SORT OF TAKE ON THAT
HOMECOMING FEEL TO IT.
I LIKE THAT
ONE, YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT OLD MAN SEDGWICK?
WHAT'S HE GONNA DO
WITH HIS BARREL?
HE SAYS HE'S GONNA
USE HIS AS A BARREL.
SOUNDS LIKE HE'S OFF THE
MEDICATION AGAIN.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, RED?
GOT ANYTHING IN MIND?
WELL, I DO, AND
YOU KNEW I WOULD.
HERE'S A HINT.
WHAT DO WE HAVE
AT ROCK REEF POINT?
UH, REEFS, ROCK,
AND A SMOLDERING CHIP WAGON.
NO, NO, NO.
WHAT DO WE HAVE THAT
COMES UP OVER
THE POINT
AND DROPS DOWN
INTO MERCURY CREEK?
OH, THE RUN-OFF FROM THE
RENDERING PLANT.
NO, NO, NO.
WATER.
ROCK REEF FALLS.
JUST LIKE NIAGARA FALLS.
THINK ABOUT IT.
WHAT DO PEOPLE DO IN
BARRELS AT NIAGARA FALLS?
WELL, IT IS THE
HONEYMOON CAPITAL.
NO, NO, NO.
THEY GO OVER THE
FALLS IN A BARREL.
THAT'S WHAT I'M GONNA
DO WITH MY BARREL.
MAN, ARE YOU GUYS
REALLY THAT DUMB?
I DUNNO.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME TO PLAY THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
IF YOU'VE EVER WANTED TO PACK UP
AND TRAVEL TO ANYWHERE IN THE
WORLD AT THE DROP OF A HAT,
WELL, TODAY'S PRIZE IS THE
PERFECT HAT FOR DROPPING.
OH!
SORRY, RED.
AND TODAY, PLAYING FOR
THAT HAT, IS MIKE HAMAR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET MIKE TO SAY THIS WORD...
OH, BOY.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
DALTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, MIKE, THIS IS
GONNA BE PRETTY EASY.
SENTENCES ARE
MADE UP OF THESE.
YEARS IN PRISON?
NO, OKAY.
NO, NO, NO.
THIS HAS LETTERS IN IT.
A MAILBOX?
NO, UH --
OKAY, UM,
WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
WHAT ARE WE
DOING RIGHT NOW?
WHAT IS THIS?
TELEVISION.
YEAH, I KNOW,
BUT WHAT ARE WE
DOING ON TELEVISION?
THAT'S WHAT
EVERYBODY SAYS.
OKAY, UM --
ALL RIGHT, THIS
IS AN EXPRESSION.
MUM'S THE --
EXOTIC DANCER?
NO.
OKAY, MIKE,
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
CARD THERE'S SOMETHING.
IT'S NOT A NUMBER,
IT'S A --
SECRET.
YES, I KNOW, BUT WHAT'S WRITTEN
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE CARD?
THE CORRECT ANSWER.
I KNOW,
BUT WHAT IS IT?
WELL, IF I KNEW THAT,
I'D WIN THE GAME.
TIME'S ALMOST UP, RED.
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON, MIKE, USE YOUR
HEAD ON THIS, WILL YOU?
I BEG TO DIFFER,
Mr. GREEN.
YOU GIVE BAD CLUES.
YOU ALWAYS GIVE
BAD CLUES.
I DO NOT.
HEY, THAT'S THE
WORD ON THE STREET.
THERE WE GO!
[ APPLAUSE ]
HEY, HAROLD, HOW COME
YOU'RE LOOKING SO LOW?
SOMEBODY ELSE TAKE
THE LAST BRAN MUFFIN?
NO, I'VE BEEN
HUMILIATED,
PUBLICLY.
WELL, YOU GOTTA BE
USED TO THAT, HUH?
THANK YOU.
NO, NO, NO.
I MEAN --
THIS IS THE
BIG CITY, HAROLD.
PEOPLE AREN'T GOING TO TREAT
YOU WITH KINDNESS THE WAY
WE DO AT THE LODGE.
OKAY, WELL, SAY SOMEBODY
AT THE OFFICE COMES
UP TO YOU
AND SAYS, "YOU WANNA
GET IN THE POOL?"
WHAT WOULD YOU THINK?
WELL, THEY'RE GIVING
ME A CHANCE TO MAYBE
GAMBLE ON SOMETHING.
EVEN YOU KNOW?
OH, I'M WORSE OFF
THAN I THOUGHT.
I SHOULDN'T BE ALLOWED
TO WRITE CHEQUES.
HAROLD, HAROLD, YOU GOTTA
BE EXAGGERATING HERE, EH?
CAN'T BE THAT
BAD, HUH?
WHAT DID YOU
THINK IT MEANT?
OH.
WELL, MAYBE NOBODY
NOTICED, EH?
WELCOME TO
TALKING ANIMALS
WITH LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER, ED FRID.
WHAT DO YOU GOT
FOR US TODAY, ED?
SOMETHING A
LITTLE TAMER.
UM, A LITTLE CALMER
BECAUSE I HAVE BEEN
HAVING SOME NERVE
PROBLEMS.
YEAH. YEAH.
STILL HAVING
TROUBLE GETTING OVER
THE VAMPIRE BAT SEGMENT?
YEAH, THAT WAS A
LOT OF BATS.
IT WAS.
TOO MANY, REALLY.
YEAH.
I HEARD THEY
INFESTED YOUR HOME.
YEAH.
OKAY.
BUT IT'S NOT SO BAD IF YOU
SLEEP WITH THE LIGHTS ON.
SO WHAT YOU GOT
IN THE BOX?
OH, I THINK THE KIDS
OUT THERE ARE REALLY
GONNA LOVE THIS.
THIS -- THIS -- THESE ARE
REALLY CUTE LITTLE GUYS.
KIND OF SMALL
AND FUZZY, EH?
SOUNDS GREAT,
YEAH.
MUST BE PRETTY SMALL IF
IT FITS IN THAT BOX.
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY
AIR HOLES, I SEE.
NO, BUT DON'T
WORRY, RED.
THERE'S NO
TARANTULAS HERE.
THERE'S ONLY
CARPENTER ANTS.
OH! OH! OH!
OKAY! OKAY!
OKAY! OH!
THIS COULD BE A BIT OF A
PROBLEM IF, UH -- IF, UH --
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING
HERE THAT'S MADE OF WOOD?
WELL, UH, A
FEW THINGS, YEAH.
OH!
OKAY. OKAY.
I'LL GET 'EM.
GET 'EM.
THERE'S ONE THERE.
OH! OH!
OVER THERE!
HEY, I THINK THEY'RE
HEADING FOR THE DOOR!
OKAY, THEY'RE
OUTTA HERE.
THANKS, ED.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
NEED TO HAVE
A LITTLE FUNDRAISER
FOR THE POSSUM LAKE
HULA DANCING CLUB
TO HELP THEM GET TO
THE FINALS IN HONOLULU.
AND I FIGURED WE'D HAVE A
CRIBBAGE TOURNAMENT.
BUT I WENT INTO TOWN --
I NEED 30 CRIBBAGE BOARDS.
WENT TO BUY ONE.
EIGHT BUCKS!
EIGHT BUCKS
FOR A CRIBBAGE BOARD.
MAN, BY THE TIME WE PAY OFF
THE GAMING COMMISSION
AND THE LIQUOR CONTROL PEOPLE
AND THE FIRE MARSHAL,
THERE WON'T BE ENOUGH MONEY LEFT
TO BUY THE GRASS SKIRTS
OR THE COCONUT SHELL
BIKINI TOPS.
SO I FIGURE I CAN MAKE THE
DARNED CRIBBAGE BOARDS
CHEAPER AND QUICKER,
AND HERE'S THE BEST PART,
I WON'T HAVE TO BUY
ANY SPECIAL MACHINERY
BECAUSE, LIKE CAPPUCCINO FOAM,
IT'S ALL UNDER MY NOSE.
OKAY, MAYBE YOU DON'T
HAVE A TABLE SAW,
BUT I BET YOU HAVE
A TABLE AND A SAW.
JUST PUT 'EM
TOGETHER.
I CAN STILL HEAR THE
SOUND OF UNCLE AL'S TRUSS
WHEN HE'D LUNGE ACROSS THIS
TABLE TO FIGHT THE KIDS FOR
THE STRING OFF THE ROAST.
MEMORIES.
NOW ALL I NEED IS A SHAPER,
OR AS I CALL IT,
A BLENDER.
YOU KNOW, THIS BLENDER WILL GIVE
ME A NICE BEVELED EDGE
ON HER THERE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW THAT I GOT THE
SIDES ALL SHAPED THERE,
I GOTTA BE DRILLIN'
SOME HOLES.
NOW, THE CRIBBAGE BOARD,
YOU GOT TWO ROWS OF HOLES, EH?
NOW, THAT'S A
LOT OF DRILLING,
EVEN IF YOU HAD A DRILL.
BUT HERE'S A WAY TO USE
A COMMON HOUSEHOLD MIXER
TO SAVE TIME AND MONEY.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, MAYBE CLEAN-UP
IS A FACTOR FOR YOU,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T HAVE MY
LOCATION OR MY ATTITUDE.
MAYBE YOU'RE IN A CONDO
OR A FREEHOLD TOWNHOUSE
OR CARDBOARD ENCLOSURE
OF SOME KIND,
YOU CAN'T AFFORD A HEAVY DUTY
INDUSTRIAL VACUUM CLEANER.
YOU DON'T NEED IT.
ALL YOU NEED IS A VEHICLE,
AND I'M SURE YOU'VE GOT
ONE OF THOSE AROUND.
YEAH, 'CAUSE A CAR ENGINE
IS JUST BASICALLY
JUST A BIG AIR PUMP.
YOU KNOW, I GOT THIS IDEA
FROM A TEENAGER IN TOWN.
HE YELLED AT ME,
HEY, MAN, YOUR CAR SUCKS!
HERE'S ANOTHER BONUS.
A HIGH COMPRESSION ENGINE MAKES
GREAT LITTLE DOWELS
THAT YOU CAN USE
AS GAME PIECES.
IT IS JUST THAT SIMPLE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
52, 54, 56, 58,
DOUBLE RUN, 16,
TWO FOR THE NINE,
ONE FOR THE JACK --
I WANNA TALK TO YOU OLDER GUYS
ABOUT THE SCARIEST PAGE
IN THE NEWSPAPER,
THE OBITUARIES.
OH, WHEN YOU'RE YOUNG,
YOU DON'T EVEN LOOK
AT THEM, DO YOU?
THEN MAYBE A FRIEND OF
YOURS HAS A GREAT UNCLE
WHO PASSED AWAY DURING AN
ALTERCATION WITH A CLIFF.
AND YOU LOOK IN THE OBITUARIES,
AND YOU FIND HIS NAME.
THEN AS TIME GOES ON,
YOU FIND MORE AND MORE
PEOPLE THAT YOU KNOW
ARE PACKING IT IN.
BUT THEY'RE USUALLY OLDER
THAN YOU, YOU KNOW?
LIKE DOCTORS,
PRINCIPALS, GOLF PROS,
THAT KIND OF THING.
AND THEN MORE TIME GOES BY,
AND PEOPLE YOUR OWN AGE
ARE LEAVING US, YOU KNOW?
AND YOU START GOING DOWN
THE COLUMN THERE,
LOOKING FOR FAMILIAR NAMES.
IT'S LIKE LOOKING AT THE LIST OF
THE HIGH SCHOOL FOOTBALL TEAM
AND BEING REAL GLAD YOU
DIDN'T MAKE THE CUT.
NOW, IT WORRIES ME 'CAUSE YOU
GET TO THE POINT WHERE YOU'RE
LOOKING AT THE OBITUARIES
THE FIRST PAGE EVERY TIME YOU
PICK UP THE NEWSPAPER.
SO I THINK WE SHOULD MAKE
A LITTLE DEAL HERE, ALL RIGHT?
THE BUNCH OF US,
ON MY 85th BIRTHDAY,
LET'S ALL OF US MEET
HERE AT THE LODGE.
WE'LL DO A DRIVE-BY
MOONING OF CITY HALL.
SO YOU GOTTA STAY
ALIVE TILL THEN;
OTHERWISE WE'LL BE
DOWN A PAIR OF CHEEKS
PRESSED UP AGAINST THE
WINDOW OF THE TOUR BUS.
SO I'M TELLING YOU,
I'M GOING TO DO EVERYTHING
I CAN TO STAY IN SHAPE
AND LIVE THAT LONG,
AND I'M EXPECTING YOU
TO HOLD UP YOUR END.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, I'M ALMOST READY FOR MY
PLUNGE OVER ROCK REEF FALLS
IN A BEER BARREL.
YOU KNOW, SOME PEOPLE ARE
ASKING ME WHY I WOULD DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
AND I HAVE NO
ANSWER FOR THEM.
BUT THEN THERE'S OTHER GUYS,
GUYS LIKE ME,
GUYS WHO HAVE NEVER
DONE ANYTHING SIGNIFICANT
IN THEIR WHOLE LIVES,
EXCEPT MAYBE ONE TIME AT
AN ALL YOU CAN EAT THING.
THEY KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
THEY UNDERSTAND THAT SOMETIMES
A MAN'S JUST GOTTA DO
WHAT A WOMAN WOULD
NEVER CONSIDER.
I GOT THE PADDING
AND I GOT THE SAFETY GEAR.
RED.
YEAH.
I GOTTA
TALK TO YOU.
WHAT?
WELL, I'VE BEEN DOING SOME
MEASURING AND WHAT NOT,
AND I THINK YOU HAVE SOME
ENGINEERING FLAWS
IN THIS BEER IMPREGNATED
DAREDEVIL FIASCO OF YOURS.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, WINSTON?
WELL, OKAY, GIVEN THE DIMENSIONS
OF THE INSIDE OF THE BARREL
AND THE BARREL'S
STRUCTURAL INTEGRITY,
YOU'RE THE WRONG MAN
FOR THE JOB.
OH, YEAH, YOU GOT
TOO MUCH HEIGHT
AND TOO MUCH, UH --
WHAT?
HOW DO I PUT
THIS DELICATELY?
DENSITY!
TOO MUCH DENSITY.
YOU SAYIN' THE BARREL
WILL BREAK APART?
YEAH, TRY TO IMAGINE A WATER
BALLOON HITTING THE PAVEMENT
FROM 12 FLOORS UP.
YEAH, YOU NEED A SMALLER,
LIGHTER GUY.
YOU KNOW, SOMEBODY ABOUT
MY SIZE, FOR INSTANCE.
AND SOMEBODY WHO
ISN'T MARRIED, EITHER.
I'M SURE BERNICE ISN'T TOO
THRILLED WITH THIS IDEA.
NO, SHE'S
FINE WITH IT.
YOU, UH, YOU HAVEN'T
TOLD HER, HUH?
NO, NO, I --
HM-MMM.
BUT, WINSTON,
HOW CAN I BE A MAN
IF I DON'T EVEN DO
THE STUNT MYSELF?
'CAUSE IT WAS
YOUR IDEA.
THAT'S THE MAIN THING.
OH, SURE, ANYBODY CAN DO
SOMETHING STUPID.
IT'S BEING ABLE
TO THINK IT UP.
THERE'S THE
REAL GIFT.
YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT, WINSTON.
HEY,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I REALLY APPRECIATE YOU
LOOKING OUT FOR
ME LIKE THAT.
UH, YOU WERE LOOKING
FOR ME, WINSTON?
NO, I WASN'T.
NO, Mr. GREEN
HERE WAS.
YEAH, HE'S GOT A VERY
EXCITING OPPORTUNITY
FOR YOU THERE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
NO.
YEP.
THANKS FOR LETTING ME
FINISH MY LAUNDRY, RED.
I'LL TELL YOU,
THE SPIN CYCLE
SCARED ME A LITTLE.
WELL, I DON'T GET
AS DIZZY AS I USED TO.
GORD, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
ARE YOU GETTIN' ENOUGH
TO DO UP HERE?
OH, SURE, I'VE GOT
LOTS TO DO.
I MAY BE TOO BUSY.
YEAH?
YEAH, WITH MY
AUDIO RECORDINGS.
OH, BY THE WAY, THIS IS
CALLED AN AUDIO CASSETTE.
IT'S WAY BETTER
THAN AN EIGHT-TRACK.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THESE THINGS
MAY JUST CATCH ON.
YEAH, I'M MAKING
MY VERY OWN TAPES.
OH, NO, YOU'RE NOT
GONNA SING, ARE YOU, GORD?
NO, NO, I DON'T LIKE
MUSIC ANYMORE,
NOT SINCE THE
CAPTAIN & TENILLE SPLIT UP.
NO, I'M RECORDING THE
SOUNDS OF NATURE ON TAPE.
WELL, THAT'S
A GOOD IDEA
'CAUSE YOU'RE UP HERE
IN NATURE, YOU KNOW.
AND YOU CAN JUST GET
ALL THE SOUNDS.
PEOPLE WOULD PROBABLY GIVE
YOU MONEY FOR THOSE
TAPES, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE ENVIRONMENTAL SOUNDS
ARE VERY POPULAR THESE DAYS.
WELL, DUH.
OH.
SO WHAT HAVE YOU
RECORDED SO FAR?
NO, I CAN'T SHOW YOU YET.
I'M ONLY HALF DONE.
BUT I'M JUST ABOUT
TO DO SOME RECORDING,
SO SH-H-H!
SH-H-H!
NO, THAT'S FINE.
[ HOWLING ]
That's the sound of
a wolf howling
at the moon.
GORD, NATURE RECORDINGS,
THEY SHOULD --
SHH, RED!
PLEASE, I'M RECORDING.
OH, GREAT!
GREAT, RED!
NOW, I'VE GOT THE SOUND
OF YOU AND ME ARGUING.
BUT THAT'S --
THAT'S NOT HOW NATURE --
WHAT YOU DO IS TAKE
THE MACHINE OUTSIDE.
YOU HIT RECORD AND LET THE
MICROPHONE CATCH WHATEVER
SOUNDS ARE IN THE AIR.
WELL, WHAT A COP-OUT.
THAT WOULD TAKE
NO EFFORT AT ALL.
WHO WOULD WANNA BUY
A TAPE LIKE THAT, HUH?
NOW, PLEASE, I'M TRYING TO
RECORD SOME BIRD CALLS.
ALL RIGHT?
CUCKOO!
THAT WAS A
LARGE CUCKOO.
CUCKOO.
THAT WAS A
LITTLE CUCKOO.
NO KIDDING.
Red:
KIND OF A SAD
DAY AT THE LODGE.
BURYING A SNAKE,
ED'S SNAKE.
OKAY, ED.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE MADE A NICE
LITTLE HEADSTONE FOR HIM.
HE'S PRETTY UPSET.
NO, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
PRETTY UPSET.
THESE THINGS HAPPEN.
NATURAL CAUSES,
NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED OF HERE
WE NEED SOME CLOSURE HERE,
SO WE GOTTA DIG A PRETTY
LONG -- LONG --
THERE'S THE COFFIN THERE.
TOO BAD.
THEY NEVER CURL UP
WHEN THEY DIE, APPARENTLY.
ANYWAY, WE GOT THE STICKS.
EVERYBODY USE THE STICKS AS -
THE PALL BEARERS CAN USE THE
STICKS AND JUST SLIDE THEM
UNDER THE COFFIN.
COUPLE OF US ON EACH END,
AND, YOU KNOW,
SHOULDN'T BE TOO --
COME ON, NOW, ED.
COME ON. COME ON.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, NOW WE JUST GOTTA GET HE
OUT TO THE ACTUAL GRAVE SITE.
'COURSE, EVERYBODY WANTS
TO GO THEIR OWN --
NO, UP THE --
OVER THIS WAY.
YOU ALL RIGHT THERE, ED?
YOU'RE OKAY.
UNFORTUNATELY WEDGED HER
BETWEEN THE TREES HERE.
OH!
OH, OH, MAN.
OKAY, SORRY.
IT'S THE GUY'S SNAKE, GUYS.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT.
GET HER UP.
NO PROBLEM.
NO, I DON'T THINK
IT HURT HIM, ED.
YEAH, I KNOW.
THAT WAS A BAD ONE.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
NO, YOU SEEM FINE.
YOU'RE GOOD.
YOU'RE FINE.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE GOOD. YOU'RE GOOD.
OH, FOR GOSH SAKE.
THEY COULDN'T DECIDE WHICH
WAY TO GO ON THIS FORK,
SO THEY  --
OH, MAN.
GET BACK THERE!
GET OVER THERE AND GET IT.
HURRY UP!
AND NO PROBLEM.
THE TROUBLE HERE --
I DON'T KNOW WHO
MEASURED THIS.
IT'S A LITTLE TOO LONG.
MAYBE WE CAN JUST ENLARGE --
WINSTON!
NO, WINSTON!
AH, COME ON!
SHOW A LITTLE RESPECT.
HEY!
HEY, DALTON, DIG THE
HOLE A LITTLE BIT --
OH.
ALL RIGHT, WHAT DO
WE DO NOW, GUYS?
WELL, NOW, WINSTON GOT
AN IDEA THERE.
THEY COULD RAM IT,
KINDA LIKE A --
A RAM THING.
YOU KNOW, LIKE A --
GIVE HER ONE
GOOD ONE, BOYS.
THERE WE GO.
OH, OH, OH!
O-O-OH!
O-O-OH.
ALL RIGHT,
EVERYBODY'S OKAY.
NO -- NO HARM --
OH, MY GOSH!
UH-HO.
OH! OH! OH!
EW!
REST IN PEACE.
PLANET EARTH.
LAST STOP THIS GALAXY.
YOU MIGHT WANNA STRETCH
YOUR TENTACLES THERE.
YOU KNOW, RED, IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN A DIFFERENT STORY
IF THOSE HAD BEEN
REAL ALIENS.
OH, TOUCHé.
BUT YOU KNOW, I WOULD'VE THOUGHT
THAT MAN WHO GOT ME UP IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
BECAUSE THE COPS HAD PICKED
HIM UP TRYING TO GET
CHOSEN BY ALIENS
TO FLY OFF INTO
THE FINAL FRONTIER,
MIGHT FEEL HE OWED ME
AT LEAST AN EXPLANATION.
ALL RIGHT, RED,
IF YOU MUST KNOW.
IT WAS THE POLICE
BAND RADIO IN MY CAR.
THOSE ARE ILLEGAL, DALTON.
EVERYBODY HAS
'EM UP HERE.
I'M RIDING IN MY CAR,
I TURN ON THE RADIO,
AND THERE ARE THE COPS,
THEY'RE ALL EXCITED ABOUT
SOME REPORTED U.F.O.
IN THE FIELD NORTH
OF THE OLD SWITCH ROAD,
AND I HEAD RIGHT OVER THERE,
AND IT IS A TRAP.
EVERY CAR IN TOWN WITH A POLICE
BAND RADIO WAS THERE.
THE COPS NAILED
EVERY ONE OF THEM.
THAT'S PRETTY SMART.
YOU SURE IT
WAS OUR COPS?
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE RIGHT.
MAYBE THOSE WEREN'T OUR COPS.
MAYBE THOSE WERE ALIENS IN
THE BODIES OF OUR COPS.
OH,
COME ON, DALTON.
IF YOU WERE AN ALIEN,
AND YOU COULD PICK ANY
BODY IN POSSUM LAKE,
WOULD YOU PICK CHIEF
TACKLEBERRY'S?
YOU SEEM TO HAVE THIS
BELIEF THAT SOMETHING'S
GONNA COME OUT OF THE SKY
AND TAKE YOU AWAY
FROM ALL THIS.
WELL, IT HAPPENS.
YEAH, IT'S
CALLED LIGHTNING.
WELL, MIKE'S RIDE OVER
ROCK REEF FALLS IN
A BEER BARREL
HAD A COUPLE
OF SNAGS.
SEEMS LIKE NO MATTER HOW
WELL YOU THINK THESE
THINGS THROUGH --
YOU KNOW WHAT, WE SHOULD'VE
KNOWN WE WERE IN TROUBLE.
YOU KNOW, WHEN WE PUT
THE BARREL IN THE CREEK,
AND THERE WASN'T ENOUGH
WATER FOR IT TO FLOAT.
YEAH, IT JUST KINDA WENT
ALONG THE BOTTOM THERE,
BOUNCED ALONG.
THEN IT WENT WAY
OFF COURSE.
DIDN'T EVEN GO OVER
ROCK REEF FALLS, REALLY.
WENT OVER
ROCK REEF POINT.
BOY, DID HE PICK
UP SPEED, EH?
THAT THING DROPPED
LIKE A DEATH CHARGE.
WELL, IT IS THE BEER
THAT GOES DOWN FAST.
THAT'S TRUE.
OH, HERE HE IS.
LET'S HEAR IT FOR HIM.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I DON'T WANNA GO ON
THAT RIDE AGAIN, DADDY.
COME ON.
WE'RE OVER HERE.
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
THERE WE GO, MIKE.
SO, MIKE, HOW FAR DID
YOU GET BEFORE SHE
FLEW APART?
ABOUT 20 MILES.
I'VE NEVER GOTTEN TO PORT
ASBESTOS THAT FAST IN MY LIFE.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, DID I JUST RUN
OVER ANOTHER POSSUM?
NO, NO,
IT'S MEETING TIME.
IT'S MEETING TIME NOW.
LET'S GO.
YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN
A MINUTE.
BYE, DADDY.
OKAY.
HE'LL BE FINE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
I'LL BE COMIN' STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I LEARNED A LOT TODAY.
I CAME UP WITH A STUPID IDEA,
AND I SAW IT THROUGH
BUT WITH NO PERSONAL INJURY TO
MYSELF OR PUBLIC EMBARRASSMENT
BECAUSE I KNOW NOW,
THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS ARE FOR.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHIN'.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND THE
WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
closed captioning performed
by INTERCAPTION CANADA
www.intercaption.com
ALL RIGHT,
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY
SIT DOWN, GUYS.
SIT DOWN.
OKAY.
ALL RISE!
[ GROANING ]
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.