IF YOU TAKE A LOOK AT
EVOLUTION OVER THE
LAST MILLION YEARS,
THE ONE SPECIES THAT
HAS SURVIVED WITHOUT
ADAPTING IS MAN.
THAT'S BECAUSE AS SOON
AS HE PICKED UP ROCKS
AND STICKS,
HE REALIZED HE
COULD HIT THINGS,
HE STARTED ADAPTING
NATURE TO HIM.
THAT'S WHY MEN FLY
INTO HURRICANES,
THAT'S WHY THEY BUILD THEIR
HOMES ON EARTHQUAKE
FAULT LINES,
THAT'S WHY THEY TURN
RAIN FORESTS INTO MALLS.
THAT TAKES SOME
KIND OF AN EGO.
WE DON'T JUST STAND BACK
AND ADMIRE THE GLORY
OF THE UNIVERSE,
WE FIGURE WE CAN
IMPROVE IT.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT MAKES
US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
RED GREEN:
ON TODAY'S SHOW,
I'M GOING TO TURN
A BED SPRING
INTO A BUG ZAPPER,
RANGER GORD IS HAVING HIS
CORRESPONDENCE SCHOOL
CLASS REUNION,
GLEN AND I ARE GOING
TO PINSTRIPE A BOAT
AND THEN BILL IS GOING
TO TAKE AN UNEXPECTED
JOG IN THE FOREST,
I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW EASY IT IS
TO WORK WITH THE
SELF-STICKING
FLOOR TILES.
AND NOW LET'S MEET
A MAN WHO STILL LOOKS
LIKE HIS GRADE SIX PICTURE,
EVEN THOUGH IT WAS TAKEN
ALMOST SEVEN YEARS AGO,
MY UNCLE,
MR. RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
AND HERE'S A GUY WHO LOOKS
EXACTLY LIKE HIS X-RAYS,
MY NEPHEW, HAROLD.
SEE WHAT HAPPENS
TO TEENAGERS
WHEN THEY'RE NOT
ALLOWED TO USE
HEAVY EQUIPMENT?
WE HAD A BIG WEEK
THIS WEEK UP AT
THE LODGE HERE.
A BUNCH OF US TOOK
THE ROOF RIGHT OFF
OF BUSTER'S HOUSE.
NOW, BUSTER'S HAD
SOME GREAT IDEAS BUT
THIS ONE IS REALLY SUPER.
OH, YEAH, BETTER THAN
HIS UNDERWATER POOL?
BETTER THAN HIS
LIGHTNING TRAP?
SURFACE TO AIR
CLOTHES LINE?
HAROLD, BUSTER HAS
PAID HIS LAST
LIGHTING BILL.
HE TOOK OFF ALL THE
SHINGLES, TOOK OUT
THE CEILINGS OF HIS HOUSE,
REPLACED THEM
ALL WITH GLASS.
EXCUSE ME, UNCLE RED,
BUT WHAT ABOUT AT NIGHT?
WELL, HAROLD, HE'S
GOING TO FILL THE WHOLE
ATTIC WITH FIREFLIES.
AND AT NIGHT WHEN THOSE
LITTLE GUYS LIGHT UP,
SO WILL BUSTER'S HOUSE.
WELL, PERHAPS
HE SHOULD REMEMBER
THAT ANCIENT SAYING,
HE WHO LIVE IN GLASS
HOUSE SHOULD NOT
HAVE BUGS IN ROOF.
DON'T FORGET THAT
OTHER ANCIENT SAYING,
BUG-EYED GOOF WITH
GLASSES NOT ALLOWED
IN MY HOUSE.
HI, I'M RANGER GORD.
WHAT YEAR IS IT?
JACK WENT LOOKING
FOR FIREWOOD
SO HAL WENT
LOOKING FOR JACK
STAN WENT LOOKING
AN HOUR AGO
AND NONE OF THEM
EVER COME BACK
SO GEORGE WENT OUT
WITH A FLARE GUN
STAN WENT TO SEE
WHERE THEY ARE
THIS IS ONE OF
THE COMPLICATIONS
WHEN YOU CAMP RIGHT
NEXT DOOR TO A BAR
WELL, YOU KNOW, WHEN
YOU STARTED GOING
OUT WITH HER,
YOU WERE JUST
SEPARATED FROM
YOUR FIRST WIFE.
YOU PROMISED THAT
YOU'D MARRY HER.
THEN YOUR DIVORCE
CAME THROUGH.
YOU PROMISED
YOU'D MARRY HER.
SO YOU STARTED
LIVING TOGETHER.
YOU PROMISED HER
YOU'D MARRY HER.
NOW, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BE A WHITE HAT
TO SEE A PATTERN
DEVELOPING HERE.
YOU PROMISED HER
YOU'D MARRY HER.
AND TO DATE YOU HAVE
NOT AND I WOULD SAY
THAT HER ANGER IN YOU
IS WHAT THEY WOULD
CALL JUSTIFIED.
YEAH, BUT, WE'RE NOT
HERE TO SELL YOU
ON THE VIRTUES
OF GETTING MARRIED.
NO, WE DON'T WANT
TO TALK YOU INTO
SOMETHING
YOU ALREADY
SCREWED UP ONCE.
WE'RE HERE TO
HELP YOU STALL
FOR MORE TIME.
'CAUSE EVEN IF
YOU PROPOSE TO
HER TONIGHT,
AND WE HOPE YOU WILL,
THERE'S STILL A LOT
OF SPEED BUMPS
YOU CAN USE
TO KIND OF DELAY THE
PROCESS TO GET YOU
UP THE AISLE THERE.
LIKE PICKING
THE RING.
NOW, THAT SHOULD
TAKE TWO MONTH'S
SALARY.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW
MUCH THAT IS UNTIL
YOU GET A JOB.
THEN THERE'S
SCHEDULING THE DATE.
THERE'S SO MANY THINGS
TO WORK AROUND THERE,
ALL THE
SPORTS PLAYOFFS.
AND TAKE
PICKING CHINA.
I MEAN, THAT COULD
TAKE MONTHS EVEN IF
YOU ARE BEING HELPFUL.
THEN THERE'S
WHICH CHURCH.
OH, YEAH, MINISTER,
JUSTICE OF THE PEACE.
GUEST LIST.
FLOWERS.
A CAKE.
YOU CAN STRETCH THIS
OUT WELL INTO THE
NEXT MILLENNIUM.
OH, YEAH, YOU'LL
BE PULLING PENSION
SITTING IN A WHEELCHAIR
BY THE TIME THEY
ROLL YOU DOWN
THE AISLE.
AND IF YOU STILL
NEED TO STALL
FOR MORE TIME,
YOU CAN RIG THE
WHEELS TO FALL OFF.
BY THAT POINT I WOULD
IMAGINE THE WHEELS
WILL BE FALLING OFF
PRETTY NEAR EVERYTHING.
WHILE, BUSTER HADFIELD
WAS CORRALLING ALL THE
FIREFLIES IN THE AREA,
I THOUGHT I'D SHOW
YOU HOW TO HANDLE
SOME OF THE OTHER BUGS
THAT WE GET UP HERE.
I'M ASSUMING YOU CAN
STILL KILL INSECTS
WITHOUT OFFENDING A
LOBBY GROUP OF
SOME KIND.
ALL RIGHT, FOR STARTERS
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS COMBINE A COUPLE
OF FLY SWATTERS
WITH ANOTHER COMMON
HOUSEHOLD KITCHEN
APPLIANCE, THE RAT TRAP.
NOW, DON'T WORRY,
THIS ISN'T OCCUPIED.
THIS IS MOOSE
THOMPSON'S SOCK.
HE PROBABLY GOT
NAILED TRYING TO
RAID THE FRIDGE.
ALL RIGHT.
THE FIRST THING
YOU WANT TO DO
IS TO ATTACH THE
FLY SWATTERS TO
THE RAT TRAP
USING THE HANDYMAN
SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW I
GOT THE FLY SWATTERS
ATTACHED TO THE RAT TRAP
AND NOW I GOT
TO JUST BAIT IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY
SAY ABOUT HONEY
ATTRACTS FLIES.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW TO WAIT FOR A FLY.
HAROLD SAYS THERE'S
A FLY IN THIS BOX
OVER HERE.
AH, I SEE.
THAT'S MY FAULT.
I'M THE ONE WHO
TRUSTED HAROLD.
ALL RIGHT.
SO THE FLY
COMES FLYING IN.
LANDS ON THE TRAP.
I THINK WE GOT HIM.
THAT IS GREAT.
MIGHT WANT TO STAND
WELL BACK ON THAT.
NOW, FOR THOSE OF
YOU WHO LIKE TO KILL BUGS
SAY A HUNDRED AT
A TIME OR SO,
I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW TO MAKE A
GIGANTIC FLY STRIP.
WHAT YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED ARE SOME
OF THESE
PEEL AND STICK
FLOOR TILES
THAT YOU GOT LEFT
OVER FROM THAT
KITCHEN PROJECT
WHERE YOU MEASURED WRONG,
MULTIPLIED WRONG,
CONVERTED TO METRIC WRONG
AND THEN DIDN'T LET YOUR
WIFE CHOOSE THE PATTERN.
ALL RIGHT, NOW YOU'RE GOING TO
NEED SOMETHING TO STICK
THESE THINGS ON TO
TO BECOME YOUR FLY
STRIP, SOMETHING BIG.
I'M THINKING A WINDOW.
[ GLASS BREAKING ]
ALL RIGHT.
NO, NO.
I'M THINKING DOOR.
HERE WE GO.
THIS THING WILL CATCH
THE BUGS ON THEIR WAY IN
OR ON THEIR WAY OUT,
DEPENDING ON HOW CLEAN
YOU KEEP YOUR HOUSE.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS BECOME YOUR FLY
STRIP AND NOW WHAT
YOU GOT TO DO
TO MAKE THAT ALL WORK
IS PUT THE FLOOR TILES
ON STICKY SIDE OUT
USING THE STAPLE GUN.
BOY THESE THINGS
REALLY STICK.
THIS IS GOING
TO WORK GREAT.
OH MAN.
ALWAYS A GOOD IDEA TO HAVE
EXTRA TOOLS AND EXTRA
CLOTHES ON THIS PROJECT
OR YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU COULD DO
IS TO STAPLE ALL
THE TILES ON FIRST
AND THEN PEEL
THE BACKING OFF.
YEAH, YEAH.
THAT WOULD WORK.
LEARN FROM MY MISTAKES,
SOMEBODY SHOULD.
ANOTHER TIP, YOU MIGHT
WANT TO LEAVE THE
STICKY STUFF
OFF OF THE BOTTOM
COUPLE FEET OF THE DOOR
IF YOU HAVE A DOG
OR A LITTLE KID
OR SOMETHING.
NOW THIS IS GOING
TO WORK GREAT AND
EVERYTHING
BUT IT'S A LITTLE
PASSIVE FOR MY TASTE.
I LIKE SOMETHING THAT USES
POWER SO I'M THINKING
ELECTRIC BUG ZAPPER.
AND WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO
NEED FOR THIS IS ONE OF
THESE OLD BEDS
'CAUSE YOU WANT THE
METAL SPRING OUT OF
THE BOTTOM
AND YOU'RE GOING TO
NEED YOURSELF A ROLL
OF CHICKEN WIRE.
NOW, I'VE WRAPPED THE
CHICKEN WIRE ALL AROUND
THE OLD METAL BED SPRING
SO NONE OF THE BUGS
WILL BE ABLE TO SLIP
THROUGH THE CRACKS.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS HOOK THIS WHOLE RIG UP
TO THE BIGGEST POWER BOX
YOU GOT IN YOUR HOME.
I'LL TELL YOU, THE NEIGHBOURS
WILL HAVE SOMETHING TO
TALK ABOUT HERE
IF THEY CAN HEAR
THEMSELVES OVER THE
SOUND OF BUGS FRYING.
REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
LET'S SEE IF WE GOT
ANY FLYING PESTS
AROUND HERE.
BOY, THAT WORKS GREAT.
KIND OF AN
ODD SMELL THOUGH.
I COULD OPEN UP ONE OF
THEM CAJUN RESTAURANTS,
MOSQUITO COOKING.
RED GREEN:
STAY TUNED, COMING UP
I'M GOING TO DO
SOMETHING TO BILL
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO,
AND HAROLD, LIKE
SO MANY TEENAGERS,
HAD A LITTLE SOMETHING
EXTRA IN HIS PANTS.
WELL THE GUYS HAVE
INSTALLED THE GLASS
ROOF IN BUSTER'S HOUSE
AND IT'S LOOKING
REAL GOOD.
ONE GIANT SKYLIGHT.
FROM THE TOP OF
THE HILL LOOKING
DOWN IT LOOKS LIKE
A GIANT SANDWICH
CONTAINER WITH A
SEE-THROUGH LID.
IT'S TIGHT, IT'S
DRY AND IT'S READY
FOR THE FIREFLIES.
BUSTER FIGURES A COUPLE
HUNDRED THOUSAND WILL GIVE
HIM ENOUGH LIGHT AT NIGHT
AND THEN PRIVACY
DURING THE DAYTIME.
AND MRS. HADFIELD
IS A LOVELY WOMAN
BUT YOU JUST DON'T WANT
TO SEE A LOT OF HER BEFORE
TEN O'CLOCK IN THE MORNING.
WHERE IS BUSTER GOING
TO GET ALL THESE
FIREFLIES FROM?
HE'S PAYING FOR
THEM HAROLD, A
PENNY A PIECE.
I FIGURE I'M GOING TO
MAKE A FEW BUCKS WITH
THIS JAR RIGHT HERE.
OH, OH, OH, OH,
OH, UNCLE RED,
WHEN IT COMES
TO CATCHING BUGS,
I AM THE CHAMP.
YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
THEY'RE DRAWN TO
YOU LIKE FLIES TO
SOMETHING OR OTHER.
MAYBE WHEN THE BUGS SEE
YOU THEY THINK IT'S A
FAMILY REUNION, HAROLD.
OR MAYBE BECAUSE IT'S
I'M AN ICKTHEOLOGIST.
BOY, THERE'S A FANCY
WORD FOR DOOFUS.
PORTIONS OF THIS SHOW
WOULD HAVEBEEN BROUGHT TO
YOU BY BRACKSTON'S MARINA,
BUT WE'RE
HAVING AN OFF YEAR.
LOST, A LARGE
EUROPEAN LYCOSA TARANTULA.
THAT SOUNDS
INTERESTING.
ALSO OWN AS THE
TARANTULA SPIDER.
OKAY, IT ESCAPED FROM A CAGE.
LIKES DARK WARM PLACES.
CONTACT STINKY
IF YOU SEE HIM
OR IF YOU SUDDENLY FEEL
A PAINFUL, SHARP BITE.
IT GROSSED ME OUT.
WHAT'S THAT?
OH, OH, OH.
OW DON'T BITE THERE,
DON'T BITE THERE.
OH I'M YOUNG,
DON'T BITE THAT.
OH.
UNCLE RED, HELP!
[ BITING SOUND ]
OH!
RANGER GORD.
RED.
RED, COME ON IN.
COME ON IN.
YOU TOO, HAROLD.
COME ON,
PLEASE.
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME.
WHAT'S GOING
ON HERE, GORD?
WELL, MY CORRESPONDENCE
SCHOOL IS HAVING
A REUNION TODAY.
WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
WELL, IT'S A
CORRESPONDENCE
SCHOOL, RED,
EVERYBODY IS WHERE
THEY'VE ALWAYS BEEN,
AT HOME.
THAT'S WHERE WE
WENT TO SCHOOL, SEE.
AND I MIGHT
SAY I THINK I'VE
HELD UP PRETTY WELL.
I STILL HAVE
ALL MY OWN HAIR.
SEE THAT?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
MY GOOD SPORTS
JACKET STILL
FITS ME.
OH, THERE'S MY OLD
PEN AND PENCIL SET.
THAT BRINGS BACK
SOME MEMORIES.
OH, FOR GOSH SAKE.
YOU KNOW, IF I WAS
AT A REAL SCHOOL
WITH REAL PEOPLE,
I BET THEY'D TEASE
THE HECK OUT OF ME
ON HOW I NEVER LET
ANYBODY BORROW THESE.
YEAH.
OH, YEAH, FOR SURE.
GORD BEFORE WE GET
TOO FAR INTO THIS,
WHAT CAN YOU TELL
ME ABOUT CATCHING
FIREFLIES?
NOT TOO MUCH, RED.
OH.
BUT I KNOW
SOMEBODY WHO DOES.
I KNOW SOMEBODY WHO DOES.
WAIT.
YEAH.
THERE HE IS,
HARRY WELL,
HE MAJORED
IN ENTOMOLOGY.
OH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S HIS ADDRESS
IF YOU WANT.
YEAH.
HE WAS THE CLASS
CLOWN I REMEMBER.
OH, WHAT A
CHARACTER, OH.
GORD, GORD, YOU
NEVER MET THIS GUY.
NO, NO.
BUT IN MY MIND.
IN MY MIND I
IMAGINED THAT
HE WAS.
THERE IS JOANNA
ARMSTRONG.
OH I HAD A CRUSH
ON HER SOMETHING
FIERCE.
WHY DON'T YOU GO
TELL HER AT THE
REUNION, YOU KNOW,
THE ADDRESS IS
RIGHT THERE.
LOOK.
THERE WE GO.
NO, THAT'S JUST
THE ADDRESS OF THE
CORRESPONDENCE SCHOOL.
YEAH, WHERE EVERYBODY
IS MEETING TODAY FOR
THE REUNION, YOU KNOW.
READ WHAT IT SAYS.
WHAT?
YEAH.
OH, NO, I COULDN'T.
I MEAN, IT WOULD BE
DERELICTION OF DUTY.
I COULDN'T LEAVE HERE.
OH, SURE.
I TELL YOU WHAT
I TELL YOU WHAT,
I'LL COVER FOR YOU
FOR A DAY, WON'T
YOU HAROLD?
NO.
IT'S MY DUTY.
IT MAKES ME WHO I AM.
YEAH, THAT'S
FOR SURE GORD.
SOME PUNCH?
HAROLD DO YOU
WANT SOME PUNCH?
HAROLD YOU SEEN MY
BAIT BOX ANYWHERE?
UNCLE RED, I HAVE
A TARANTULA IN
MY PANTS.
NO THANKS.
I'M GOING TO
USE DEW WORMS.
HELP ME.
HELP ME, PLEASE.
WHAT?
SPEAK UP, HAROLD.
I HAVE A HUGE KILLER
TARANTULA IN MY PANTS.
WHAT IS WITH
YOU YOUNG PEOPLE?
FIRST YOU GOT
THE EARRINGS,
THEN YOU GOT
THE NOSE RINGS,
NOW YOU'RE PUTTING KILLER
SPIDERS IN YOUR PANTS.
LYCOSA TARANTULA,
WARM DARK PLACE,
SHARP PAINFUL BITE.
WELL, WHY IS IT
IN YOUR PANTS, HAROLD,
DON'T THEY FEED
THOSE THINGS?
ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
I'LL GET IT.
WHERE IS IT?
IN THE BACK LEFT SIDE.
ALL RIGHT.
HOLD STILL.
OKAY.
WAIT.
ALL RIGHT.
HANG ON, HANG ON.
THERE.
GOT IT.
DO YOU WANT TO SEE IT?
SHOULD I JUST TAKE
IT OUTSIDE AND
DISPOSE OF IT?
ALL RIGHT, BUT
YOU OWE ME ONE.
NO, NO, WE'RE EVEN.
WELL, IT'S TIME
FOR ADVENTURES
WITH BILL.
AND WHAT DO YOU GOT
FOR US TODAY BILL?
I DON'T WEAR HATS.
NOT THAT KIND OF HAT.
OH, IT'S A BEE KEEP,
A BEE KEEP.
OH BOY, I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'RE GOING
TO BE A BEEKEEPER, BILL?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN KIND
OF LEERY ABOUT BEES.
OH MY GOSH, LOOK
AT THAT HIVE.
OH BOY.
STAY BACK.
I'M NOT ALLERGIC OR
ANYTHING BUT I DON'T
WANT -- OH MAN.
NOW APPARENTLY THEY
DON'T GO FAR
FROM THE HIVE
SO YOU'RE REALLY NOT
IN AS MUCH DANGER AS YOU,
YOU KNOW -- STRAIGHT
ON THE END OF THE.
BILL YOU HUNG --
BILL YOU HUNG YOUR STUFF
RIGHT ON THE END
OF THE BRANCH,
THE SAME HIVE.
WELL, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
I WOULDN'T SHAKE THAT.
I TAKE IT -- I'D BE REAL
CAREFUL OF THAT BILL.
NOW, APPARENTLY
THESE BEE --
BILL, OH, OH...
APPARENTLY THESE
OUTFITS ARE MADE OF
SOME KIND OF MATERIAL
THAT THE BEE STINGER
WON'T GO --
I'M PUTTING
THE HAT ON.
YEAH, I DON'T --
BILL DON'T PULL.
BILL DON'T.
BILL.
NO, I WOULDN'T
PULL TOO HARD.
OH. DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT THAT
ANYMORE.
NOW I FEEL LIKE I'M A
KINDERGARTEN TEACHER
TRYING TO HELP
HIM GET HIS LITTLE
COVERALLS ON THERE.
WHAT WAS THAT?
I THINK SOMETHING
WENT BY THERE, BILL.
DID YOU HEAR
SOMETHING GO BY?
NO?
OH WELL.
I GUESS WE'RE OKAY.
NOW HE'S GOING
TO COLLECT THE HONEY.
APPARENTLY IF YOU STICK
A KNIFE IN THE BOTTOM
OF THE HIVE,
THE HONEY WILL JUST
DRIP OUT OF THERE
JUST LIKE JIMMY ROGERS
WAS SINGING A SONG
ABOUT IT.
SO THAT'S MY
JOB I GUESS.
LIKE HECK IT IS.
I'M GOING ANYWHERE NEAR IT.
WHERE'S THE HIVE?
WHERE DID IT GO?
WHERE DID THE HIVE GO?
WAIT A MINUTE,
I HOPE THAT'S A HIVE.
I GOT A KNIFE HERE
SO JUST STAND
STILL BILL.
THIS WILL BE PERFECTLY
SAFE, I THINK.
I'M PRETTY SURE.
OR MAYBE NOT.
WOW.
LOOK AT THAT.
LOOKS LIKE ONE
OF THOSE TAP DANCERS,
YOU KNOW, THOSE
SINGING, DANCING GUYS?
MAYBE HE SHOULD BE
IN ONE OF THOSE
BEE MOVIES.
RED GREEN:
COMING UP HAROLD IS
GOING TO USE HIS FACE
TO PROVE THAT BUGS
WILL EAT EVERYTHING
AND OUR HOME RENO EXPERT
MIKE IS GOING TO DO
SOME WIRING FOR US.
IF A LITTLE KNOWLEDGE
IS A DANGEROUS THING,
POSSUM LODGE HAS GOT TO
BE THE MOST DANGEROUS
PLACE ON EARTH.
I DON'T REMEMBER
CATCHING FIREFLIES
EVER BEING
LIFE-THREATENING.
I COULD BE FLIRTING
WITH MALARIA.
WELL, IF IT WORKS
LIKE YOUR OTHER
FLIRTING
YOU'VE GOT NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
SO HOW MANY FIREFLIES
HAVE YOU CAUGHT SO FAR?
ROUGHLY, NONE.
HAH, HAH, HAH,
GOOD, WE'RE TIED.
WELL, I STOPPED TRYING
HAROLD UNTIL BUSTER
GETS THE FIRE PUT OUT.
HE HAD A FIRE?
YEAH, SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE ANGLE OF THE SUN
HITTING THE PITCH
OF THE ROOF
AND THEN WHEN THEY
PUT THE GLASS IN,
THEY KIND OF CRIMPED
'ER SO SHE'S A BIT BENT
AND IT MADE LIKE A LASER
BEAM INTO HIS HOUSE.
THAT'S COOL.
YEAH.
THAT'S LIKE
WHEN YOU TAKE A
MAGNIFYING GLASS
AND YOU HOLD IT
JUST SO, YOU KNOW,
SO YOU CAN BURN THE
LEGS OFF ANTS.
WELL, THIS ACTUALLY BURNED
THE LEGS OFF OF BUSTER'S
DINING ROOM SUITE.
AND THEN AS THE DAY
WENT BY WITH THE
SUN MOVING,
THAT BEAM SCORCHED
A STRAIGHT LINE
ACROSS THE RUG,
CUT THE COUCH IN HALF,
BISSECTED THE COFFEE TABLE,
MELTED THE FRIDGE
AND COOKED THE KISSING
GOURAMIS IN HIS AQUARIUM.
WOW.
WHAT'S HE GOING TO DO NOW?
A RAIN DANCE
I WOULD THINK.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE
HARDEST PART OF
THIS JOB IS?
LEAP YEARS, MAN.
THIS WEEK IN OUR DREAM
HOME RENOVATION SEGMENT,
WE'RE GOING TO DO
SOME WORK ON THE
LODGE ITSELF.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW
THAT OLD SAYING,
CHARITY BEGINS AT HOME.
OF COURSE,
NOT MY HOME.
YOU KNOW TO ME THE
MARK OF A TRULY
WONDERFUL HOUSE
IS THE NUMBER
OF ELECTRICAL
OUTLETS IT HAS.
YOU CAN'T HAVE
ENOUGH OF THOSE
BABIES.
SO I'VE ASKED MIKE,
HERE TO PUT ANOTHER
ELECTRICAL OUTLET
UP INTO MY BEDROOM
RIGHT ABOVE US HERE.
PLEASE WELCOME
OUR CONTRACTOR, MIKE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
HI, MR. GREEN.
WELL, HERE IT IS, A PLUG
TO YOUR BEDROOM JUST
LIKE YOU ASKED FOR.
MIKE, IT LOOKS
LIKE YOU TOOK A
WIRE FROM THE BASEMENT,
COME UP THROUGH
THE FLOOR
AND WENT STRAIGHT UP
THROUGH THE CEILING THERE.
YEAH, AND I
TELL YOU WHAT.
YEAH.
IF YOU GOT A PLUG
IN THE MIDDLE OF
YOUR ROOM.
YOU CAN PLUG INTO
ANYTHING YOU WANT IN
THE WHOLE WIDE ROOM.
IT'S CONVENIENT.
YEAH.
SEE I'M APPLYING
MYSELF, MR. GREEN.
YEAH.
JUST LIKE YOU AND THE
PRISON CHAPLAIN
TOLD ME TO.
WELL, NO, NO,
THAT'S GOOD.
I JUST, YOU KNOW,
I JUST DON'T KNOW
HOW I FEEL ABOUT THIS CABLE
HANGING RIGHT THROUGH
THE CENTRE OF THE
LIVING ROOM HERE.
WELL, NOBODY
WILL NOTICE.
NO, I THINK THEY
MIGHT, MIKE,
YOU KNOW.
IT KIND OF CATCHES
YOUR EYE THERE.
I KNEW IT WOULDN'T WORK.
I MEAN, I'M USELESS.
I'M JUST A
PIECE OF GARBAGE.
I'M JUST USELESS.
NOW, MIKE, DON'T
GET DOWN ON YOURSELF.
YOU TRIED SOMETHING,
IT JUST DIDN'T FLY,
THAT'S ALL.
HEY, I GOT A
GREAT IDEA.
WE BUILD A WALL,
COVER UP THE WIRE,
RIGHT, RIGHT DOWN
THE MIDDLE HERE, RIGHT?
YOU SEPARATE YOUR
LIVING ROOM INTO
TWO ROOMS.
YOU GOT TWO
LIVING ROOMS, RIGHT?
WELL, TWO HALF
LIVING ROOMS.
OKAY.
THEN YOU BUILD A WALL
JUST UP TO HERE,
LIKE A HALF WALL.
LIKE IF YOU WANT
TO TALK YOU CAN SAY
HELLO HOW ARE YOU.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH.
I LIKE IT.
LIKE A DUTCH...
A DUTCH WALL.
A DUTCH WALL, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
AND THEN WHAT WOULD
YOU DO WITH THE CABLE
THAT GOES FROM
THERE ON UP?
OH GEEZ.
I'M A PIECE--
OF HUMAN FARM MANURE.
THAT'S WHAT I AM.
JUST SEND ME BACK.
LOCK ME UP.
TAKE ME AWAY.
I'M A PIECE
OF USELESSNESS,
THAT'S WHAT I AM.
GOT A THOUGHT.
WHAT?
YOU SEE THAT
VERTICAL BEAM
THERE?
WHY DON'T WE BRING
THAT OVER HERE,
PUT THE WIRE
UP INSIDE IT.
NOBODY IS GOING TO SEE
AND NOBODY IS GOING
TO BE ANY THE WISER.
THAT'S A SUPPORTING
BEAM, ISN'T IT?
YEAH, BUT WE'LL
MOVE IT REALLY FAST.
HUH?
MR. GREEN.
I KNOW.
YOU'RE A GENIUS,
YOU KNOW.
AND HERE WE ARE AT
BRACKSTON'S MARINA
WITH GLEN
BRACKSTON, HERE.
I UNDERSTAND BUSINESS
IS BOOMING, GLEN.
OH, NOT BAD RED.
LAST YEAR
WE LOST $50,000.
YEAH.
THIS YEAR, ONLY HALFWAY
THROUGH THE SEASON, WE'RE
ONLY DOWN 12,000,
SO WE'RE PRETTY
EXCITED.
WELL, THAT IS A BIG
SUCCESS STORY RIGHT
THERE, YEAH.
OH THINGS HAVE
TURNED AROUND, RED
WHAT WITH FREE TRADE
AND INTEREST RATES
AND THAT
INSURANCE CLAIM.
YEAH, AND THIS YEAR
WE'RE OFFERING
BETTER SERVICE TO
OUR CUSTOMERS, TOO.
OH, I WOULD THINK SERVICE
WOULD BE A HUGE GROWTH
AREA FOR YOU.
OH AND WE CHANGED HOURS,
SO NOW WE'RE OPEN
DURING THE SEASON.
RIGHT.
AND WE JACKED PRICES
UP WAY UP, TOO.
AND OF COURSE YOU'RE
DOING THE BOAT CARE
DEMONSTRATION
AS PART OF
OUR SHOW.
EXACTLY, WHICH BRINGS
US TO TODAY'S
BOATING TIP,
IS HOW TO MAKE YOUR
BOAT LOOK BETTER.
NOW, IF IT
DOESN'T RUN GOOD,
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
IT CAN'T LOOK GOOD.
NO, I GUESS WITH
A BOAT LIKE THIS,
WE GO SEE EDGAR, GET SOME
DYNAMITE AND BLOW THIS --
THE INSURANCE COMPANY
WON'T BUY THAT TWICE.
SO ANYWAY,
RED, PINSTRIPING.
THAT'S THE KEY.
OH GOSH.
I CAN'T DO IT.
I GET DIZZY
WHEN I BEND OVER.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
NOW WHAT KIND OF
TAPE IS THIS, GLEN?
AH, GORTEX, VORTEX.
THE SALESMAN TOLD
ME THEY USED IT ON THE
HUBBLE SPACE TELESCOPE.
NO KIDDING.
YEAH.
IT'S WATER PROOF,
FIRE PROOF, NON-FADING
AND METEOR RESISTANT.
WOW, YOU KNOW BUSTER
SHOULD RUN A STRIP
OF THIS
RIGHT ACROSS HIS LIVING
ROOM FLOOR TO BLOCK THAT
SUNBEAM THING.
OH, SURE HE COULD
DO THAT, YEAH.
YOU KNOW HE COULD
PUT IT RIGHT ACROSS
THE HARDWOOD FLOOR
BECAUSE IT'S MADE
FOR WOOD BOATS.
FOR GOSH SAKES.
YOU'RE ONLY
LIMITED BY YOUR
IMAGINATION, RED.
WELL, LET'S SEE IF
I CAN CATCH MY LIMIT.
GLEN, YOU GOT
ANYMORE TAPE THERE?
NO, THAT WAS ALL
THE FREE SAMPLES RED.
DID YOU SAVE ENOUGH
FOR THE NAME?
WELL, YEAH, AS
LONG AS THE BOAT
IS CALLED HYPHEN.
I DON'T THINK IT'S
GOING TO MATTER, RED.
NO?
YOU ONLY USE A
NAME TO IDENTIFY
A BOAT.
I THINK WE GOT
THAT COVERED.
WELL, BUSTER HADFIELD'S
FIREFLY SKYLIGHT
IS GOING INTO THE POSSUM
LODGE RECORD BOOKS,
THE FIRST PROJECT
THAT DID NOT CAUSE
SERIOUS INJURY
AND ALMOST WORKED.
ALMOST?
I THOUGHT IT LOOKED
GREAT LAST NIGHT.
ALL THOSE FIREFLIES
ALL OVER THE PLACE
IN THE CEILING.
IT LOOKED LIKE
SHOOTING STARS.
YEAH, HE HAD HIS
OWN PLANETARIUM
FOR A WHILE, THERE.
BUT BUSTER DIDN'T
TAKE INTO ACCOUNT
THE BATS.
I MEAN, THE BATS
SAW ALL THEM
FIREFLIES,
LOOKED TO THEM LIKE
ONE OF THEM ALL YOU
CAN EAT BUG BUFFETS.
THEY STARTED DIVE
BOMBING THE HOUSE.
OH, NO.
SPLAT?
YEAH, BUT NOT
THAT SPLAT.
THEY PULLED OUT OF
THE DIVE BECAUSE THEIR
RADAR DETECTED THE GLASS.
BUT THE BAT
DROPPINGS, HAROLD,
OH MAN, BLOCKED
OUT THE SUN.
SO TO SCRAPE THEM
OFF, BUSTER HAD
TO HOOK UP
A GIGANTIC
WINDSHIELD WIPER.
EXCUSE ME, UNCLE RED,
BUT WHAT DID HE USE?
WELL, HE WENT
AND RIPPED OFF
ONE OF THEM
FLASHING ARMS FROM
THE RAILROAD CROSSING.
THAT IS ILLEGAL
AND DANGEROUS.
OH, NO, IT
WORKED GREAT.
OH, YOU MEAN
THE TRAIN CRASH.
WELL, HAROLD, NOBODY
CAN PROVE THAT
THAT ARM
WOULD HAVE STOPPED
THE COW FROM GOING
ON THE TRACKS, ANYWAY.
YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T
REALIZE HOW MANY
PARTS THERE ARE IN A COW
UNTIL YOU SEE
ONE BROKEN DOWN INTO
ITS COMPONENTS LIKE THAT.
OH BOY.
WHERE'S THE BEEF?
ALL OVER BUSTER'S
ROOF ACTUALLY.
SO HE'S GOING BACK
TO REGULAR SHINGLES.
BUT THE GOOD NEWS IS
HE'S GOING TO HAVE
A BARBECUE
AND INVITE US ALL OVER
AS SOON AS HE SCRAPES
ALL THE HAMBURGER OUT
OF THE EAVESTROUGHS.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
DON'T MENTION THAT AT
THE MEETING TONIGHT.
NO, NO, I WILL BE DOWN
IN A LITTLE WHILE,
A HALF HOUR OR SO.
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING
AND I'M BRINGING US
A LITTLE PET,
A LITTLE FIREFLY
NAMED SPARKY.
I FIGURE WE CAN KEEP
HIM DOWN AT THE FOOT
OF THE BED
AND THAT WAY MAYBE I WON'T
STUB MY TOE WHEN I GET UP
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
MIND YOU, THE BED HAS
TO BE SHAKING FOR
HIM TO WORK.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
AND UNTIL NEXT TIME
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.