MEN PRIDE THEMSELVES
ON TAKING THE LONG VIEW.
WE ALWAYS CONSIDER THE
ONGOING RAMIFICATIONS
OF OUR ACTIONS.
LIKE WEARING A SUIT
AND TIE, AS SOON AS
YOU DO IT ONCE,
EVERYBODY EXPECTS
YOU TO MAKE IT A HABIT.
SAME THING GOES WITH
GETTING OUT OF BED EARLY
OR EATING BEAN SPROUTS
OR BEING POLITE TO
RELATIVES.
WE'RE VERY CAREFUL
ABOUT MAKING ANY
CHANGES
THAT ARE ULTIMATELY
NOT IN OUR BEST INTEREST.
IT'S NOT SMART OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF THINGS
THAT MAKES US
WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red Green: IN TODAY'S SHOW,
BILL IS GOING TO HUMILIATE
EVERYBODY FROM SCOTLAND,
I, ON THE OTHER HAND,
AM GOING TO TAKE
SOME OLD JUNK
AND MAKE A
HEART/LUNG MACHINE,
GLEN BRACKSTON IS
GOING TO USE ME
AS A TRACTOR
AND HAROLD AND I ARE
GOING TO TRY TO HAVE
SOME QUIET TIME
BUT HE KEEPS TALKING.
AND NOW HERE HE IS,
THE HOT PIZZA PIE
OF HOOLIGAN,
THE MAN WHO DELIVERS
IN 30 MINUTES
AND IT'S FREE,
MY UNCLE,
RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AND HERE'S THE
REASON IT'S FREE,
THE GUY THEY CALL
HOLD THE ANCHOVIES,
MY NEPHEW HAROLD.
AND NOW HERE IS
SOMETHING THAT ISN'T FREE,
THE VACANT LOT NEXT
DOOR IS UP FOR SALE
AGAIN, $30,000.
OF COURSE THE YAMMERING
ALL STARTS UP
ABOUT WHETHER OR
NOT WE SHOULD BUY IT.
OH, WHY DO WE WANT
TO BUY THAT EYE SORE?
IT'S JUST A BUNCH
OF JUNKIE CARS,
OLD FRIDGES, BALD TIRES,
EMPTY BARRELS.
WHAT A DUMP.
THAT'S A RECYCLING
CENTRE THERE, HAROLD.
WE NEED TO GET ACCESS
TO ALL THOSE OLD
REFRIGERATOR
COMPRESSORS AND RUSTED
OUT DRIVE TRAINS
TO WORK ON OUR
SPECIAL PROJECTS.
WELL, WHAT GIVES YOU
THE RIGHT TO, YOU KNOW,
TRESPASS ON SOMEONE
ELSE'S PROPERTY
AND STEAL ALL THEIR
ABANDONED JUNK?
WE'RE THE ONES WHO
ABANDONED IT THERE, HAROLD.
THAT'S KIND OF LIKE
OUR STORAGE LOCKER.
IF WE DON'T HAVE
THE STUFF THERE,
IT'S GOING TO BE
IN YOUR BEDROOM.
I THINK BUYING THE
LOT IS A GREAT IDEA.
YEAH.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING
TO GET THE $30,000?
I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT
THE 30,000, HAROLD,
IT'S THE 2,000 DOWN.
IT IS PHYSICALLY
IMPOSSIBLE TO DRINK
A FIVE-GALLON PAIL
FULL OF WATER
WHILE LYING DOWN.
OH ME AND THE WIFE
WE'RE GETTING A DIVORCE
IT WASN'T ADULTERY
THAT SET US OFF COURSE
BUT KEEPING IT TOGETHER
WAS TOO MUCH OF A STRAIN
WHEN WE TRIED TO PUT UP
A NEW TENT IN THE RAIN
SO SHE FINALLY RUN
OFF WITH THE COOLER
AND I YELLED AND I CRIED
FOR THE REST OF
OUR POSSESSIONS
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
LET THE COURTS DECIDE
WE'LL HAVE NO PROBLEM
REACHING A SETTLEMENT
AND WE'RE SURE
NOT GOING TO FIGHT
OVER WHO GETS TO
KEEP THE G.D. TENT
OKAY, IT'S
THURSDAY NIGHT
AND THAT MEANS MEATLOAF
AND MASHED POTATOES.
YOU GO THROUGH
THE BACK DOOR
AND YOUR NOSE GOES
ON RED ALERT.
TWO WORDS FLASH
THROUGH YOUR MIND.
NEW RECIPE.
AND WHEN YOU SEE IT
LYING THERE ON
YOUR PLATE,
YOU JUST KNOW YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO LIKE IT.
TOO MANY VEGETABLES,
TOO MUCH RICE,
AND A QUICK VISUAL
SCAN REVEALS VERY
LITTLE EVIDENCE
OF A MEAT-LIKE PRODUCT.
SO WHAT DO YOU DO?
SHE'S GOING TO
TELL YOU THAT'S
HEALTHY EATING.
AND THEN SHE'S
GOING TO ASK
THE BIG ONE,
DO YOU LIKE IT?
NOW, CHANCES ARE RICE
IS A KEY INGREDIENT
IN THIS NEW RECIPE.
NOW, THIS IS TO
YOUR ADVANTAGE.
TELL HER ABOUT
YOUR DARK PAST.
TELL HER THAT EATING
RICE BRINGS BACK BAD
MEMORIES OF VIETNAM,
POST-TRAUMATIC SHOCK.
OR DO WHAT I DO,
GET UP FROM THE TABLE
AND BOLT INTO
THE BATHROOM, STAY
THERE FOR TWO HOURS,
TELL YOUR WIFE YOU'RE
NOT FEELING GOOD AND
GO STRAIGHT TO BED.
YEAH IT'S EARLY.
YES, YOU'RE HUNGRY,
BUT YOU WON'T HAVE TO
EAT ANYTHING FOREIGN.
THEN NEXT THURSDAY
MAKE SURE YOU GET
HOME EARLY.
MAKE SURE YOU'RE
IN THE KITCHEN.
YOU MAKE THE MEATLOAF
AND MASHED POTATOES.
AND WITH ANY LUCK
IT WILL BE A DISASTER
OF SUCH BIBLICAL
PROPORTIONS,
SHE'LL SPEND TWO HOURS
IN THE BATHROOM NOT
FEELING WELL
AND GOING TO
BED EARLY.
AND THEN NEXT THURSDAY
SHE'LL GO BACK
TO MAKING MEATLOAF
AND MASHED POTATOES
THE SAME OLD WAY
JUST TO SHOW YOU UP.
YOU KNOW WITH THIS
LOT BEING UP FOR
SALE NEXT DOOR,
I THOUGHT I WOULD
USE HANDYMAN CORNER
TO PROVE A POINT
ABOUT THE VALUE
OF HAVING AN AVAILABLE
PARTS SUPPLY FOR OUR
VARIOUS PROJECTS.
FOR EXAMPLE, THIS MIGHT
JUST LOOK LIKE A PILE
OF USELESS CRAP
TO SAY YOUR GIRLFRIEND
OR YOUR WIFE OR
YOUR MOTHER,
BUT THE REST OF US
KNOW THAT THIS IS
A TREMENDOUS SOURCE
OF RAW MATERIAL
FOR ANYTHING WE
WANTED TO MAKE.
THERE MIGHT BE A CAR
IN HERE THAT'S NEVER
BEEN BUILT BEFORE
OR MAYBE SOME KIND
OF A CUSTOMIZED
HOVERCRAFT
OR, HEY, LET'S BUILD
SOMETHING USEFUL,
HOW ABOUT A
HEART/LUNG MACHINE, HUH?
THE PERFECT FATHER'S DAY
GIFT THAT KEEPS ON GIVING.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, WHAT YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED FOR THAT,
YOU GOT TO GO THROUGH
THE PILE AND PICK
OUT ANYTHING
THAT YOU CAN USE TO SUCK,
PUMP, COMPRESS
OR BLOW.
ALL RIGHT.
FIRST THING
YOU WANT TO DO
IS LIE YOUR PATIENT
DOWN INSIDE THE FREEZER.
THIS GOES DOWN
TO AROUND ZERO,
BUT NOT TOO CLOSE OR
THERE'S NO POINT
GOING ANY FARTHER.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW YOU WANT TO TAKE
ONE OF THESE WINDSHIELD
WASHER UNITS WHICH
BECOMES THE INPUT
TO TAKE THE BLOOD
OUT OF THE VICTIM --
OUT OF THE PATIENT, SORRY.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS YOU WANT TO
HOOK THIS IN
TO WHICHEVER ONE
OF HIS ORIFICES GIVES
YOU THE SNUGGEST FIT.
AND THEN OUT OF THE
WINDSHIELD WASHER PUMP
YOU GO INTO
YOUR CARBURETOR.
ALL RIGHT, THIS
IS WHERE THE BLOOD
GETS MIXED WITH OXYGEN.
NOW IF IT'S A FAT
GUY, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO GO WITH A FOUR BARREL
AND MAYBE PUT A
SUPER CHARGER ON THERE.
ANOTHER GREAT THING
ABOUT THE CARBURETOR UNIT
IS IT'S AN IDEAL PLACE
WHERE YOU CAN ADD MEDICINE
DIRECTLY INTO THE BLOODSTREAM,
BE IT CORTISONE
OR MAYBE A MEDICINAL
ALCOHOL LIKE VERMOUTH.
AND THEN OUT OF THE
CARBURETOR YOU WANT
TO GO DIRECTLY
INTO YOUR WATER PUMP.
AND THEN OUT OF
THE WATER PUMP YOU
BLAST THE BLOOD BACK OUT
ONE OF THESE RAD HOSES
BACK INTO THE PATIENT.
IT MIGHT BE HARD
FINDING AN ORIFICE
THAT SIZE,
ESPECIALLY
IF HE'S COLD.
ANYWAY, GET ALL THAT
STUFF IN THERE.
THAT TAKES CARE OF THAT.
NOW YOU WANT TO DEAL
WITH THE LUNG PART
OF THE HEART/LUNG
MACHINE.
OKAY, FOR THAT
YOU WANT TO TAKE
A FUNNEL LIKE THIS,
DUCT TAPE THAT
RIGHT ALL OVER
THE PATIENT'S FACE,
MAYBE PUT SOME PUTTY
IN THERE AND MAKE IT
A REAL GOOD SEAL.
AND THEN YOU HOOK
THE OTHER END OF
THE GARDEN HOSE
UP TO ONE OF THE
TAPS ON THE SINK
AND THEN THAT RUNS
INTO THE NOZZLE
AND YOU HAVE REPLACED
THE NOZZLE WITH,
WELL, LET'S CALL
IT A BALLOON.
THAT'S HOOKED UP
TO ANOTHER HOSE
WHICH RUNS DOWN
INTO A COMPRESSOR.
WE HAVEN'T HOOKED
THAT UP YET.
AND WHAT HAPPENS IS
WHEN THE COMPRESSOR
STARTS UP, YOU SEE,
IT PUTS AIR INTO
THE BALLOON AND THEN
THAT RELEASES BACK
INTO YOUR PATIENT.
YEAH.
SO I WILL PUT
THAT ALL IN THERE.
TAKE THE HOSE OUT.
HOOK HER UP
INTO OUR COMPRESSOR.
AND, AS YOU CAN SEE,
THE WHOLE UNIT IS
ALL DRIVEN BY A
GAS LAWN MOWER,
SO YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT ELECTRICITY
CUTTING OUT
IN THE MIDDLE OF
OPEN HEART SURGERY,
WHICH I WOULD
CALL A SETBACK.
OKAY.
SO ANOTHER THING --
YOU MIGHT WANT TO DO
ALL YOUR OPERATIONS
OUTSIDE,
BECAUSE I'LL TELL
YOU THE GAS FUMES
IN ONE OF THEM SMALL
OPERATING THEATRES.
SO THERE, YOU'RE
ALL SET TO GO.
ALL YOU GOT TO
DO NOW IS WAIT FOR
THE SURGEON TO SAY,
OKAY, WE'RE READY FOR
THE LIFE SUPPORT
THING TO START.
BUT BEFORE I DO THAT,
I JUST WANT TO
REMIND YOU,
IF WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
ALL RIGHT, GET TO WORK
NOW, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1,
BEGIN LIFE SUPPORT.
THERE.
NO, IT CHOKED.
HANG ON.
MAYBE IT'S OUT OF GAS.
NO.
Red Green: STAY TUNED
AS THE POSSUM LODGE
HIGHLAND GAMES
COMES FLASHING
ACROSS THE STREAM,
AND HAROLD FISHES
FOR THE MEANING OF
LIFE WITH NO BAIT.
I WANT TO TALK TO
YOU YOUNG FOLKS THERE
IN THE GENERATION X OR
Y OR WHATEVER IT IS.
ANYWAY, I HEAR A LOT
OF WHINING ABOUT
THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE NOT
BABYBOOMERS AND MAYBE
YOU MISSED OUT ON THE 60S,
BUT I THINK YOU SHOULD HEAR
THE REAL STORY FROM SOMEONE
WHO WAS THERE.
THE 60S WAS NOT
ALL PEACE AND LOVE AND
UNDERSTANDING, BELIEVE ME.
YEAH, THERE WERE SOME
KIDS WHO PRACTICED
FREE LOVE
AND THEN THEY WENT
TO THE FREE CLINIC,
AND SOME OF THEM
TRIED NEW STUFF,
THEN THEY HAD THEIR
STOMACHS PUMPED.
AND IT'S TRUE THE 60S
DID INSPIRE SOME REAL
GREAT PROTEST SONGS.
BUT WE ALSO HAD THE
PARTRIDGE FAMILY AND
THE 1910 FRUIT GUM COMPANY,
AND THE WOMEN'S MOVEMENT
FOR THE FIRST TIME
STARTED TO GET
A FAIR SHAKE ON THAT,
BUT THEY ALSO GOT THEIR
OWN CIGARETTE, BABY.
AND, YEAH, I KNOW WE
HAD A QUARTER OF A
MILLION PEOPLE
SHOW UP AT WOODSTOCK
BUT A LOT MORE THAN THAT
WENT OVERSEAS
TO FIGHT.
SO THE NEXT TIME SOMEBODY
TRIES TO PUT DOWN YOUR
GENERATION
AND MAKES YOU FEEL BAD
ABOUT MISSING OUT
ON THE 60S,
JUST HUM BACK A FEW
BARS OF YUMMY YUMMY
YUMMY, I GOT LOVE IN MY TUMMY.
WELL, THE DEED IS DONE,
THE VACANT LOT
NEXT DOOR IS SOLD.
GOOD FOR YOU.
CONGRATULATIONS.
WE DIDN'T
BUY IT, HAROLD
I KNOW, GOOD FOR YOU.
CONGRATULATIONS.
NOT EVERYBODY
FEELS THAT WAY.
MOOSE THOMPSON
AND STINKY PETERSON
ARE SCREAMING AT ME
FOR NOT BUYING THE LOT
WHEN WE HAD THE CHANCE.
I TOLD THEM WE DIDN'T
BUY IT BECAUSE NOBODY
ELSE WANTED IT.
MEN ONLY BUY THINGS
THAT OTHER MEN WANT.
THIS IS SO EXCITING,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
NEW NEIGHBOURS.
ARE THERE ANY
OTHER TEENAGERS?
YOU KNOW, ARE THERE
ANY -- ARE THERE ANY
NON-MALES, YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW, LIKE BABES?
NO IDEA, HAROLD.
THE GUY AT THE LAND
DEED OFFICE SAID IT WAS
BOUGHT BY A NUMBERED COMPANY.
THAT SCARES
ME A LITTLE
BECAUSE WHEN A NUMBERED
COMPANY BUYS A PROPERTY,
IT USUALLY MEANS ITS
LAND DEVELOPERS
OR BAPTISTS.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT
WE SHOULD DO,
WE SHOULD ACT LIKE
THE WELCOME WAGON.
YOU KNOW, WE'LL TAKE
THEM OVER A GIFT
AND WE'LL WELCOME
THEM TO POSSUM LAKE
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S A BEAN CASSEROLE
DOWN IN THE BOATHOUSE
FRIDGE,
THAT WILL
BE PERFECT.
THAT'S NOT
A BEAN CASSEROLE.
THAT'S A PAIL
OF FISH BAIT.
WELL, IF THEY'RE REAL
FISHERMAN THEY'LL
KNOW THAT
AND IF THEY'RE NOT
THEY SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
WHAT YOU ARE WATCHING
COULD HAVE VALUE
SOME DAY.
IT COULD BE AWHILE.
[ HEART MONITOR BEEPING ]
WE'RE LOSING HIM.
WELL, AS MOST OF YOU KNOW,
WE'RE AT BRACKSTON'S
MARINA
WITH THE OWNER
GLEN BRACKSTON.
HE'S GOT THIS WEEK'S
BOATING TIP FOR US.
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT, FOLKS,
YOU GOT TO TAKE
CARE OF YOUR HEALTH.
YOU KNOW, ONCE
THAT SHIP SAILS,
SHE DOESN'T COME BACK.
I FOUND THAT OUT
AFTER TWO HEART
ATTACKS.
IS THAT YOUR
BOATING TIP, GLEN?
NO.
THAT'S A LITTLE
LIFE LESSON, RED.
ALL RIGHT.
TODAY'S BOATING
TIP WILL BE
HOW TO PROPERLY MOVE
A BOAT ON A TRAILER.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO BE DOING.
ALL RIGHT.
SO, RED, MAYBE YOU
COULD SWING YOUR LEG
OVER THE TONGUE THERE?
DON'T YOU HAVE A
MACHINE TO DO THIS?
DON'T YOU HAVE LIKE A
TRUCK OR A TRACTOR
OR WHAT ABOUT
YOUR CAR?
NOPE.
ALL GOT REPOED.
OH.
YEAH.
EVERYTHING.
YOU KNOW
THAT NEW GUY THAT
LIVES NEXT DOOR TO YOU?
HE'S GOT A LOT
OF NICE STUFF.
REALLY?
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
HE'S GOT A BACKHOE,
A BOBCAT, A BRUSH HOG,
A FRONT-END LOADER,
HE'S GOT IT ALL.
WOW.
YOU SHOULD MAKE
FRIENDS WITH THAT GUY.
YEAH.
I MIGHT.
WELL, THERE'S
A ANOTHER LITTLE
LIFE LESSON, RED,
MAKE FRIENDS WITH PEOPLE
THAT CAN DO SOMETHING
FOR YOU.
THERE YOU GO.
OKAY, RED, OL' BUDDY,
DO YOU WANT TO WING
DOWN THERE
AND GRAB
THAT THING?
NOW BE CAREFUL,
JUST USE YOUR LEGS,
OKAY, BECAUSE YOU
DON'T WANT TO END UP
GETTING A BAD
BACK LIKE I GOT.
I DON'T WANT A
BAD BACK BUT WOULDN'T
MIND ONE LIKE YOU GOT.
LIFT HER UP THERE.
THAT'S IT.
NOW JUST WALK
AHEAD SLOWLY, RED.
SEE, RED.
YEAH?
YOU GOT TO
PAY ATTENTION.
YOU FORGOT TO MOVE
THE ROCK HERE.
YOU CAN'T GO ANYWHERE
WITH THE ROCK THERE.
LET ME GET
IT FOR YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU WERE GOING TO
NOTICE BUT YOU DIDN'T.
THANKS FOR DOING THAT.
I HOPE IT'S NOT
TOO MUCH TROUBLE.
OH SORRY, HAROLD.
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
GET UP.
OKAY, RED,
LET'S GO.
ALRIGHTY.
JUST STICK HER OVER
BY THE SHED THERE,
WILL YOU RED?
I GOT A GUY
COMING TO RENT IT
A LITTLE WHILE LATER.
WHY DON'T WE PUT
IT IN THE WATER THEN?
I JUST TOOK IT
OUT OF THE WATER, RED.
OH, YEAH, I CAN CLIP
THE GUY FOR ANOTHER
HUNDRED BUCKS OR SO
BY LAUNCHING
HIS BOAT.
YOU GOT TO BE THINKING
IN THIS BUSINESS, RED.
I GUESS THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE DOING SO WELL.
OH YEAH.
YEAH.
USE YOUR BRAIN,
SAVE YOUR MUSCLE.
YOU KNOW, RED,
THERE'S A LOT OF GUYS
WHO WOULD HAVE DONE
THIS BY THEMSELVES.
THAT WOULD BE CRAZY.
OH YEAH.
MUCH EASIER WITH
THE TWO OF US.
[ HEART MONITOR -
STEADY TONE ]
OH BOY.
SORRY.
UNCLE RED, HOW COME
OLDER MEN, SOME OF THEM,
YOU KNOW, THEY LIKE
LEAVE THEIR WIVES
AND START GOING OUT
WITH YOUNGER GIRLS?
BECAUSE THEY CAN.
WHAT?
NO, NO, I'M
KIDDING I GUESS.
BUT YOU KNOW IT WORKS
BOTH WAYS, HAROLD,
I HEAR A LOT OF
OLDER WOMEN ARE
LEAVING THEIR HUSBANDS
AND GOING OFF
WITH YOUNGER MEN.
MAYBE THERE'S
HOPE FOR YOU.
OH, YEAH.
UNLESS I GET TOO
OLD TO QUALIFY.
OH, HAROLD, WITH YOUR
PERSONALITY YOU WON'T
BE ALLOWED TO GET OLD.
I READ AN ARTICLE ABOUT
THESE YOUNGER/OLDER
RELATIONSHIPS,
IT WAS CALLED MAY/
DECEMBER ROMANCE.
WHAT DO THEY MEAN
BY THAT, UNCLE RED?
OH, HAROLD, A LOT OF
TIMES WHEN A COUPLE
HAS BEEN MARRIED
A LONG TIME,
THEY ONLY, LET'S SAY,
GET INTIMATE TWICE
A YEAR,
ONCE AT CHRISTMAS
AND ONCE IN THE SPRING
WHEN THEY OPEN
UP THE COTTAGE.
ARE YOU A MAY/
DECEMBER KIND
OF PERSON?
WELL, THAT'S A
LITTLE PERSONAL
I THINK, HAROLD.
BUT I CAN ANSWER YOU
I THINK DISCREETLY
WITH TWO WORDS,
LONG WEEKENDS.
ALL RIGHT.
LONG WEEKEND.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
Red Green: TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE HIGHLAND GAMES
ON THIS WEEKS
ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
OH BOY.
WOW.
I GUESS THIS WOULD BE
THE OPENING CEREMONIES.
SOME GUYS WEAR
THEIR HEART ON
THEIR SLEEVE, NOT BILL.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW THIS IS MY
OPENING CEREMONIES.
SORRY, BILL.
WHAT HE'S SHOWING
YOU HERE --
MOST OF YOU DON'T
KNOW THE HIGHLAND GAMES
OF COURSE COME
FROM SCOTLAND.
THIS IS A
LITTLE EVENT THEY HAVE
CALLED TOSSING THE CABER,
NOT TO BE CONFUSED
WITH TOSSING THE COOKIES
WHICH WE DO A LOT
OF AT THE LODGE.
AND BILL THIS IS VERY --
WHAT BILL?
NO, NO, NO.
SO I PUT THE BUNGIE CORD,
ONE OF THE OTHER
SECRET WEAPONS
AT THE LODGE,
AROUND THERE.
THAT WILL HELP.
I THINK THAT WILL
HELP A LOT.
THAT SHOULD KEEP
IT RIGHT --
THERE WE GO.
NO.
DROPPED THAT DOWN, BILL,
THERE'S A TRAIN COMING.
THAT A BOY.
ALL RIGHT.
I THOUGHT THIS TIME IF
I CAN HELP HIM BALANCE IT,
MAYBE GIVE HIM A LITTLE
PUSH, YOU KNOW,
GET HIM GOING IN
THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
THERE THAT LOOKS BETTER.
OH, THE SIGN.
OH.
YOU KNOW THERE'S
A LOT MORE TO THIS
THAN MEETS THE EYE.
MAYBE IF HE HAD PANTS ON.
WHERE DID THAT GO?
END OVER END.
BILL, BILL, I THINK
IT'S BEHIND YOU,
BILL, OH YEAH.
THAT'S GOING WELL.
I SEE WHY SCOTLAND
DOESN'T RULE THE WORLD.
THAT'S A LITTLE
HORIZONTAL, BILL.
OH.
WELL NOW YOU REALIZE
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
SCOTTISH TO DO THIS,
YOU JUST GOT
TO BE ANGRY.
I'LL TAKE IT OUT THERE.
I THINK ABOUT WHERE
I WOULD LIKE TO
TOSS THE CABER,
BUT INSTEAD OF THAT
I THROW HER UP
INTO THE AIR.
LET HER GO, RED.
OH, THAT'S A BEAUTY.
THAT IS A BEAUTY.
IT'S OVER HERE, BILL.
OH BOY.
AND OF COURSE FOR THE
CLOSING CEREMONIES,
THEY HAVE THE TRADITIONAL
HIGHLAND DANCING.
Red Green: COMING UP,
DALTON HUMPHRIES
IS GOING TO SHOW
US SOME VALUABLE
ANTIQUES
AND YOU CAN LEARN SUCCESS
FROM MR. SUCK-CESS,
WINSTON ROTHCHILD.
WELL, THIS GOOF WHO
BOUGHT THE LOT
NEXT DOOR
IS DEFINITELY NOT
ONE OF THE GUYS.
BUT YOU MET HIM.
YOU LIKED HIS BACKHOE
AND HIS BOBCAT AND
HIS BULLDOZER.
HAROLD, YOU CAN'T
JUDGE A MAN BY
HIS EQUIPMENT.
HE USED ALL THAT STUFF
TO CLEAN UP THE LOT.
THE NERVE.
HE GOT ALL THE TRUCKS IN
THERE AND HAULED AWAY
ALL THE RUSTED JUNK.
OUR ENTIRE
PARTS DEPARTMENT
UP AND HAULED AWAY.
I KNOW THERE
WERE TWO GREAT
SNOW TIRES IN THERE.
I'LL TELL YOU, WHEN
HE TOWED AWAY THAT
'74 TORINO
WITH THE LAND ROOF
HANGING DOWN THE SIDE,
THERE WASN'T A DRY
EYE IN THE LODGE.
AND THEN HE HOOKED
UP A BRUSH HOG
AND USED THAT TO REMOVE
EVERY PIECE OF SCRUB.
YEAH, SURE, HE'S
GOT A GREAT VIEW
BUT HE'S TAKEN AWAY
EVERYTHING WORTH
LOOKING AT.
WELL, UNCLE RED,
IT'S HIS PROPERTY NOW.
HE CAN DO WHAT
HE WANTS WITH IT.
BUT THERE ARE COMMUNITY
STANDARDS, HAROLD.
IS HE GOING TO
BUILD A NICE HOUSE?
IS HE GOING TO CUT
THE GRASS EVERY WEEK?
IS HE GOING TO
LANDSCAPE THE
PROPERTY?
AND, IF SO, HOW DO
WE TO STOP HIM?
Red Green: WE'RE OUT
HERE BY THE MAIN HIGHWAY
AT HUMPHRIES EVERYTHING STORE
TO GET ANOTHER SLANT
ON THESE CITY PEOPLE
MOVING UP TO THE COUNTRY.
AND HERE'S
OUR RESIDENT
ANTIQUE SPECIALIST,
DALTON HUMPHREY.
I'M A LIFESTYLE
RECYCLER.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THESE URBAN REFUGEES
MOVING UP
HERE, DALTON?
YOU KNOW, I SAY GOD
BLESS THEM, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE, RED, THE
FIRST THING THEY DO
AFTER THEY PUT IN
THEIR SATELLITE DISH
IS FILL THEIR COUNTRY
HOMES WITH RUSTY PLATES,
BROKEN CHAIRS AND
OLD PHONES THAT
DON'T WORK.
ANTIQUES?
BINGO.
YEAH, I GOT THESE
ANTIQUE MAGAZINES HERE.
WELL, NO,
THOSE ARE A GOOD
INVESTMENT, RED.
REALLY?
THEY'RE FULL OF ANTIQUES.
YEAH, WELL, ANTIQUES
ARE NEVER OLD NEWS.
NOW, YOU GET
A NEWS MAGAZINE,
IT'S NOT WORTH
ANYTHING A WEEK LATER.
GOOD POINT.
SURE.
LOOK WHAT THEY
GOT FOR SALE HERE.
PARTIALLY RESTORED
CARRIAGE HOUSE,
CIRCA 1840.
NO, YOU HAVE TO WATCH
THE LANGUAGE IN THOSE
ADS, RED.
PARTIALLY RESTORED THAT MEANS
IT'S AN UNSALVAGEABLE
MONEY PIT
AND THE OWNER
IS BAILING OUT.
CIRCA 1840,
WELL SEE THAT WAS
PRE-BUILDING CODE.
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO FIND A LOT OF
GREAT PLUMBING
AND ELECTRICAL
WORK BACK THEN.
I GUESS THAT'S WHY
THIS GUY WHO BOUGHT
NEXT TO POSSUM LODGE
IS BUILDING
HIS OWN HOUSE.
YEAH.
AND IN THE PROCESS
RAISING VALUES
OF PROPERTY
ALL OVER THE AREA,
EVEN POSSUM LODGE.
WHAT'S THAT GOING
TO DO TO OUR TAXES?
OH, NOTHING GOOD.
NO.
THAT'S WHY I RECOMMEND
ANYONE COMING FROM
THE CITY,
JUST BUY THEMSELVES
ONE OF THOSE BIG
LONG TRAILERS
AND JUST PARK
IT SOMEWHERE.
YEAH AND THEN
FILL IT FULL OF
EXPENSIVE ANTIQUES.
AMEN TO THAT.
WELCOME.
AND TODAY ON THE
EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW
WE'RE BEING JOINED
BY MR. WINSTON ROTHCHILD.
[ APPLAUSE ]
ALRIGHTY, WE GOT A LETTER
AND IT GOES AS FOLLOWS:
IT'S FROM A PERSON.
DEAR EXPERTS,
I HAVE A L
PRACTICE IN TORONTO
AND MY DAUGHTER
IS ALSO A LAWYER.
I HAVE ALWAYS
ENCOURAGED HER TO
STRIVE TO BE THE BEST
BUT SHE IS NOW DOING
BETTER THAN I AM
AND I'M HAVING TROUBLE
DEALING WITH THAT.
IS THERE ANYTHING
I CAN DO?
OH, YOU KNOW, I'VE
WAITED MY WHOLE LIFE
TO GIVE ADVICE TO LAWYERS,
BUT THIS ONE HAS
GOT ME STUMPED.
HOW ABOUT YOU, WINSTON?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW,
LET'S TAKE IT
FROM THE DAUGHTER'S SIDE
OF THE POINT OF VIEW
OF THE PERSPECTIVE
OF THING, EH?
THIS TO ME SOUNDS
LIKE A CLASSIC CASE
OF YOUR POT CALLING
THE KETTLE BACK.
SO WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING IS THAT MAYBE SHE'S
NOT TRYING TO SURPASS HIM,
MAYBE HE'S JUST LIKE,
YOU KNOW, A LOUSY LAWYER.
OH, OH, LIKE THAT
DISTRICT ATTORNEY
ON THE PERRY MASON SHOW.
THAT GUY -- THAT GUY
NEVER WON A CASE
EVER NEVER.
WELL, YOU KNOW, AT
LEAST NOT ONES THEY
TELEVISED, YOU KNOW.
HE MUST HAVE WON SOME
THAT THEY DIDN'T SHOW
BECAUSE HE WAS ON
THAT PROGRAM FOR
LIKE 12 SEASONS
HAMBURGER.
NO, IT'S TRUE.
NO, NO, THAT WAS
HIS NAME, HAMILTON BURGER.
YOU KNOW, THAT
GUY REMINDED ME
A LOT OF MY
OLD MAN, EH?
OH, YEAH, BECAUSE MY
DAD WAS ALWAYS WINNING
AND I WAS ALWAYS
HAMBURGER, EH?
I'LL NEVER FORGET,
YOU KNOW,
HE USED TO SAY
THINGS TO ME LIKE,
HEY, WINSTON,
YOU'RE USELESS.
I'M SURE
HE WAS PROBABLY
KIDDING, YOU KNOW.
YEAH, IT'S JUST LIKE
WHEN UNCLE RED CALLS
ME DOUGH HEAD.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW
SOMETHING, IT WAS
GOOD FOR ME.
SURE.
IT HELPED PULL MYSELF
UP BY THE BOOT LICKERS.
OH, YEAH.
I MEAN, DO I SIT OR
DO I GET OFF THE POT, EH?
AND NOW LOOK
AT ME, EH,
I GOT THE NUMBER
ONE SEPTIC SEWAGE
SUCKING BUSINESS
IN THE WHOLE
COUNTY.
I AM SITTING
PRETTY.
OKAY.
WHAT WE LEARNED TODAY
THEN IS THAT
IT'S WHAT YOU
THINK OF YOURSELF
THAT IS IMPORTANT
AND NOT TO LET YOUR
SELF-WORTH BE DICTATED
TO YOU BY YOUR FATHER
OR YOUR DAUGHTER.
OR YOUR NEPHEW.
OR YOUR UNCLE.
WORMS, BY ME.
SPRING HAS HIT
THE CITY,
THERE'S LEAVES
ON EVERY TREE,
AND WORMS FESTOON
THE SIDEWALKS
AS FAR AS THE
EYE CAN SEE.
TRAMPLED UNDER
BOOTS AND HEELS,
THEY'RE FLATTER
THAN BOBBY V.,
AT THE LODGE THE
WORMS ARE LUCKIER,
THEY GET TO GO
FISHING WITH ME.
I'LL TELL YOU,
REAL ESTATE IS A
COMPLICATED BUSINESS.
THE GUY NEXT DOOR
JUST GOT FINISHED
IMPROVING THE VALUE OF
ALL OUR PROPERTIES
AND NOW HE'S PUT
THE LOT UP FOR SALE.
I TELL YOU, HE MUST
BE SEEING SOMETHING
THAT NONE OF US CAN SEE.
YEAH, POSSUM LODGE.
ONCE HE GOT A
CLEAR VIEW OF WHAT THIS
PLACE REALLY LOOKED LIKE,
HE DIDN'T WANT
TO LIVE BESIDE IT.
SUITS ME FINE.
NATURE TAKES CARE
OF IT'S OWN, HAROLD.
NO, BUT JUST THINK
OF IT, UNCLE RED.
IF WE CLEAN THIS
PLACE UP, WE CAN
REALLY INCREASE ITS VALUE.
YEAH, BUT IT WILL
DO THE SAME THING
TO THE LOT, HAROLD,
AND THEN THE
PRICE WILL BE TOO
HIGH FOR US TO AFFORD.
WELL, SO WHAT,
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO BUY IT ANYWAY.
ONLY BECAUSE
WE DON'T HAVE TO.
SEE, IF WE FIX
UP THE LODGE,
THEN THE VALUE OF
THE LOT NEXT
DOOR GOES UP
AND THEN
SOMEBODY IS GOING
TO WANT TO BUY IT,
AND WE GOT TO OUTBID
THEM, WHICH WE CAN'T
AFFORD TO DO,
AND WE END UP
WITH NEW NEIGHBOURS
WHICH WE DON'T WANT.
THIS WAY WE DON'T
HAVE TO DO ANY WORK,
WE KEEP THE PROPERTY
TAXES REAL LOW,
NOBODY MOVES
IN NEXT DOOR,
WE GET A FREE
PLACE TO STORE ALL
OUR BURNT OUT EQUIPMENT.
NAME ME ONE THING
WRONG WITH THAT PLAN.
WELL, IT'S UGLY,
IT'S AN EYE SORE,
IT'S AN ENVIRONMENTAL
HAZARD AND IT'S ILLEGAL.
I SAID ONE THING.
OKAY, IT SMELLS.
WELL, YOU GET
USED TO THAT.
REAL MEN DO.
I SAID IT SMELLS GOOD.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH CRY OF THE POSSUM.
THAT'S MEETING
TIME, ISN'T IT?
WELL, I GUESS I WILL
JUST GO BE WITH
THE OTHER MEN.
SOMEBODY SHOULD
WARN THEM.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I WILL BE A LITTLE
BIT LATE TONIGHT
'CAUSE WE'RE GOING
TO GO OVER TO THE
LOT THERE
AND THROW ALL OUR
BROKEN FURNITURE
AND A FEW RUSTED OUT
HOT WATER TANKS,
WE GOT A '75 OMNI
WE'RE TOWING OVER
THAT'S GOT NO
DOOR, NO MOTOR IN
IT AND EVERYTHING.
WE GOT ABOUT 200 ARMY
SURPLUS METAL BED FRAMES.
I TELL YOU
SOMETHING, BERNICE,
WE'RE GETTING OUR
LIVES BACK HERE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
WINSTON'S GOT A SPECIAL
PRESENTATION FOR
YOU TONIGHT.
HE'S GOT
SOMETHING SO GREAT.
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
DON'T LOOK.
OH, YOU CAN LOOK NOW.