WORK IS BAD.
AND DIGGING POST HOLES
IS THE WORST.
UNLESS, YOU HAVE THE RIGHT TOOL.
AND, OF COURSE, WE DO.
NOW, ALL YOU HAVE TO
DO IS JACK SQUAT.
GET YOURSELF A JACK AND SQUAT.
AND THE HEAVIER THE VEHICLE
AND THE WETTER THE HOLE,
THE DEEPER YOUR POST HOLE.
REMEMBER, ANY TOOL
CAN BE THE RIGHT TOOL.
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW!!!
AND NOW, HERE'S THE MAN WHO
TURNED TELEVISION ON ITS EAR
AND GOT IT STUCK UP HIS NOSE.
YOUR HOST AND HERO, MY UNCLE:
RED GREEEEEN!!!
[applause]
THANK-YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S ELECTION TIME HERE
IN THE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
LOOKS LIKE ANOTHER SHOE-IN
FOR OUR MAYOR, WALLY KIBLER.
WE CALL HIM "KICKBACK" KIBLER.
I DO NOT KNOW
HOW THIS GUY KEEPS
GETTING RE-ELECTED.
WELL, NOBODY RUNS AGAINST HIM.
THAT HELPS.
THE GUY IS SUCH A CROOK.
SEE, THAT'S IT.
EVERYBODY JUST
COMPLAINS ABOUT HIM.
YOU CAN'T JUST COMPLAIN
YOU HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
WELL, PEOPLE LIKE
COMPLAINING, HAROLD.
IT FEELS GOOD, AND IT
MAKES YOU FEEL IMPORTANT
AND YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO ANYTHING.
YEAH, BUT IT'S NOT GOING
TO GET US A NEW MAYOR.
WE NEED ANOTHER
CANDIDATE, YEAH.
I WAS ACTUALLY THINKING
OF THROWING MY OWN HAT
IN THE RING.
YOU DON'T HAVE A HAT.
THAT'S TRUE, BUT YOU DO.
YOU THINK I MIGHT MAKE
A GOOD MAYOR, HAROLD?
ABSOLUTELY, YEAH.
YOU SAID PEOPLE
LOVE TO COMPLAIN.
WITH YOU AS A MAYOR,
THEY WOULD HAVE
A MILLION REASONS.
IT'S TIME TO PLAY
"THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME."
MR. MIKE HAMAR IS PLAYING
FOR ONE MILLION DOLLARS.
[applause]
PROVIDING HE SCRATCHES
THREE IDENTICAL SYMBOLS.
UNCLE RED,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS TO GET
MR. HAMAR TO SAY THIS WORD:
GO!!!
ALL RIGHT, MIKE,
TWO PEOPLE
JOINED LEGALLY.
CELLMATES?
YOU'RE AT A WEDDING.
THE BRIDE AND
GROOM GET...
LUCKY!
OKAY, MIKE.
BERNICE AND I,
WE ARE...?
OLD.
HEY, HEY, HEY!
HOME SHOPPING NETWORK?
C'MON!
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT
OF TIME, UNCLE RED.
THERE'S A SONG:
I'M GETTING SOMETHING
IN THE MORNING.
YOU'RE GETTING SOMETHING
IN THE MORNING?
YEAH.
WELL, THAT'S UNUSUAL
FOR A MARRIED GUY.
[ring! ring! ring!]
OH MAN...
I DON'T KNOW IF THAT
WAS SUCH A GREAT IDEA.
NO, IT'S GREAT,
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
RUNNING FOR MAYOR.
HA! HA! HA!
THAT'S GREAT!
HAVE YOU EVER RUN
FOR ANYTHING BEFORE?
COVER.
[laughter]
THIS IS GOING
TO BE DIFFERENT
'CAUSE WE'RE GOING TO RUN
A GOOD, CLEAN CAMPAIGN
AND KNOCK MAYOR KIBLER
RIGHT OUT OF OFFICE.
NO, HAROLD.
YOU'RE MY
CAMPAIGN MANAGER
AND I'M RUNNING.
THAT'S TWO VOTES.
WE'VE GOT BERNICE,
SO THAT'S THREE.
IF THEY GET THE SAME TURNOUT
AS THEY DID LAST YEAR,
WE'RE GOING TO NEED
EIGHT MORE VOTES TO WIN.
YOU'RE FORGETTING
OUR MAJOR ADVANTAGE.
WHAT'S THAT?
YOU'RE A TELEVISION STAR.
OKAY, NOT A STAR,
BUT A PERSONALITY.
A PERSONALITY.
IT'S NOT A GOOD
PERSONALITY.
WE NEED A SLOGAN!
THAT'S WHAT WE NEED,
YOU KNOW, JERRY SPRINGER
WAS MAYOR OF CINCINNATI.
THAT'S NOT GOING
TO HELP US, REALLY.
I NEED A PHRASE.
THEY HAVE THE POSTERS
AND THEY HAVE BUTTONS.
THE POLITICIANS GO AND
THEY GET THE WINNEBAGOS.
I WOULD LOVE A 37 FOOTER.
I'D GET THE
"BIG 8" IN THERE
AND I'D GET
THE AUTOMATIC
THE MICROWAVE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'S THE DECOY FOR?
I'M GOING TO TAKE
A PICTURE FOR THE SLOGAN.
WHAT'S OUR SLOGAN?
ISN'T IT OBVIOUS?
"THE BUCK STOPS HERE."
[laughter and applause]
IF YOU'RE LOOKING TO MARRY
LATER IN LIFE
I KNOW HOW YOU CAN
FIND A GOOD WIFE
A WOMAN WITH SAVVY
WHO KNOWS THE SCORE
A WOMAN WHO'S SEEN
IT ALL BEFORE
OH, MARRY A WIDOW
SOMEONE WHO CAN'T BE FOOLED
LISTEN KIDDO
YOU'RE THE KIND WHO
NEEDS TO BE RULED
A WIDOW WILL SCARE YOU
LIKE NOBODY CAN
ESPECIALLY IF SHE KILLED
HER FIRST OLD MAN
YOU KNOW, ALMOST EVERYBODY
IN THE WORLD HAS A DREAM.
SOME DREAM ABOUT
TRAVELLING IN SPACE,
OR FINDING A CURE FOR A DISEASE,
OR FINALLY HAVING WORLD PEACE.
ME, I HAVE A DREAM.
I NEVER TOLD ANYBODY THIS.
I DREAM OF NOT GETTING
ANY ELECTRICAL BILLS.
SO, THIS WEEK ON
"HANDYMAN CORNER,"
I'M GOING TO MAKE
MY DREAM COME TRUE.
YOU KNOW, THE CHEAPEST
FORM OF ELECTRICITY
IS WATER FALLING
THROUGH A TURBINE.
THEY CALL THAT HYDRO.
NOT HYDRA.
HYDRA IS A MYTHICAL BEAST WITH
NINE HEADS THAT CAN'T BE KILLED.
YOU DON'T WANT THAT.
YOU WANT HYDRO...
LIKE NIAGARA FALLS WHERE
THE HONEYMOONERS GO
TO GET THE SPARKS FLYING.
HOW DO YOU MAKE A TURBINE?
WELL, A TURBINE IS
JUST A WATER WHEEL.
WHICH IS THE SAME
AS ONE OF THOSE...
GET AWAY!
EXERCISE...
EXERCISE WHEELS IN
A HAMSTER'S CAGE.
VICIOUS LITTLE FELLOW.
SEE WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
GET TOO MUCH EXERCISE?
SO, ALL WE'VE GOT TO DO IS...
MOUNT THIS WHEEL ON
THE SHAFT OF A CAR ALTERNATOR.
LIKE THAT ONE.
AND, THAT'S OUR HYDRO GENERATOR.
NOW, ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS
PUT THE WHOLE THING INTO
SOME FALLING WATER.
YOU HAVE GOT LOTS
OF OPTIONS, HERE.
WHAT YOU CAN DO IS GO TO
ONE OF YOUR DOWNSPOUTS,
CUT A SLOT IN THE SIDE
AND MOUNT THE UNIT
WITH THE WHEEL INSIDE.
THEN, WHEN THE WATER
FALLS OFF THE ROOF,
THE WHEEL SPINS.
IT CRANKS UP THE GENERATOR
AND YOU'VE GOT ELECTRICITY.
THE PROBLEM THERE IS YOU ONLY
GET ELECTRICITY WHEN IT RAINS.
WHICH IS FINE, IF YOU LIVE
IN ENGLAND OR VANCOUVER,
BUT FOR NORMAL PEOPLE,
WE NEED A MORE CONSTANT
SOURCE OF FALLING WATER.
SO, I SUGGEST INSTEAD,
WHAT YOU DO IS GET A PIECE OF
YOUR NORMAL HOUSEHOLD DRAINPIPE,
AND YOU MOUNT YOUR
TURBINE UNIT IN THAT.
CUT A SLOT AND
STICK HER RIGHT IN.
AND YOU STICK THIS
INTO THE MAIN DRAIN IN
THE BASEMENT OF YOUR HOUSE.
THAT WAY, ALL THE WATER THAT
COMES FROM YOUR SINK,
YOUR BATHTUB, WASHING MACHINE,
SHOWER, TOILET, OR WHATEVER.
IT IS GOING TO
GENERATE ELECTRICITY.
IN FACT, IF YOU GET A COUPLE
OF DOZEN BEER DRINKERS OVER,
YOU CAN LIGHT UP A STADIUM.
I'M GETTING AHEAD OF MYSELF.
THE FIRST THING
WE'VE GOT TO DO
IS MOUNT THE WHEEL ONTO
OUR CAR ALTERNATOR, HERE.
[smash!]
[clang!]
SHE'S RUSTED OUT A LITTLE
AND THAT'S A SETBACK.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
ONE OF THE GREAT THINGS
ABOUT THE LODGE,
IT'S AN UNLIMITED SOURCE
FOR CAR ALTERNATORS.
OH, YEAH!
UNFORTUNATELY,
A LOT OF THEM ARE STILL
IN THEIR ORIGINAL PACKAGE.
BUT, "FINDERS KEEPERS."
[clang!]
[bang!]
[whack! whack! whack!]
ALL RIGHT, IF THE MOUNTAIN
WON'T COME TO MOHAMMED,
WE'LL JUST ADD
A FEW EXTENSION CORDS.
AND ALSO, WE'VE GONE
TO A DIFFERENT SYSTEM.
BECAUSE IT'S A BETTER SYSTEM
AND ALSO BECAUSE,
THAT ALTERNATOR WASN'T COMING
OUT WITHOUT SOME KIND OF
NUCLEAR INTERVENTION.
WE'RE STILL GOING TO GET
OUR POWER OFF THE ALTERNATOR.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE IT
RIGHT OUT OF THE CAR.
NOW, WE'RE COOKING WITH GAS.
ACTUALLY, A CIGARETTE LIGHTER.
[buzzzz!]
YOU KNOW, THERE'S A LOT
OF BENEFITS TO THIS, EH?
IT'S SAFER THAN
NORMAL ELECTRICITY
BECAUSE IT'S ONLY 12 VOLTS
AND IT'S GOT TO BE CHEAPER
BECAUSE WE'RE NOT GOING
ANYWHERE IN THE CAR.
I DON'T SEE A DOWN SIDE.
UNLESS, THE OWNER SHOWS UP.
SO, REMEMBER...
"IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY."
[engine roaring]
[electricity flowing]
[kaboom!]
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU GUYS
WHO WHEN YOU WERE A KID,
REALLY ADMIRED THOSE
TOUGH T.V. HEROES.
YOU KNOW THE GUYS I MEAN.
THE ONES THAT WERE OUTCASTS,
STANDING TALL, ALONE,
READY TO TAKE ON ANYONE.
AND, NOW THAT YOU'RE AN ADULT,
YOU'VE BEEN THERE, HAVEN'T YOU?
AN OUTCAST,
STANDING TALL, ALONE.
USUALLY, IN FRONT
OF YOUR OWN HOME.
YOU MIGHT EVEN HAVE BEEN
TEMPTED TO DRAW A LINE
IN THE DRIVEWAY
AND MAKE A STAND.
AND IT MIGHT HAVE WORKED,
IF ANYBODY HAD LOOKED OUT
THE LIVING ROOM WINDOW.
BUT, YOU'RE SMART
ENOUGH TO REALIZE
THAT LYING COMFORTABLY IN YOUR
OWN BED IS BETTER THAN STANDING
TALL IN THE TOOLSHED.
SURE, SUCKING UP AND
APOLOGIZING HURTS.
IT HURTS BAD.
I MEAN, THE GROVELLING ALONE CAN
FEEL LIKE YOU'RE GOING TO DIE.
BUT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE TOUGH.
MARRIED TOUGH.
AND IF YOU'RE NOT HURTING,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING.
[applause]
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YA.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
I'VE BEEN DRIVING ALL OVER TOWN
IN THE POSSUM VAN, CAMPAIGNING.
I LOVE THE SMELL OF EXHAUST
FUMES IN THE MORNING.
SMELLS LIKE VICTORY.
I DON'T KNOW, UNCLE RED.
"KICKBACK" KIBLER HAS
A LOT OF FRIENDS
IN THE BUSINESS COMMUNITY.
THE CIVIL SERVICE, THE PTA,
AND ALL THE CHURCH GROUPS.
WHO DO WE HAVE?
MOOSE THOMPSON AND
STINKY PETERSON.
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK SAID
HE'S LEANING YOUR WAY,
BUT I THINK
HE WAS REFERRING
TO HIS BAD POSTURE.
DON'T WORRY, HAROLD.
MY CAMPAIGN PROMISES ARE
WINNING EVERYBODY OVER.
HI, I'M RED GREEN.
VOTE FOR A CHANGE.
I'M REALLY
GETTING INTO THIS.
THESE ARE GOOD.
"I PROMISE NOT TO RAISE TAXES."
"I PROMISE TO INCREASE
SPENDING ON EDUCATION."
YEAH, BUT NOT TOO MUCH.
IF THEY GET TOO SMART,
THEY WON'T VOTE FOR ME.
"I PROMISE FULL EMPLOYMENT
AND MORE HAPPINESS."
"I PROMISE GOOD WEATHER
ON EVERY WEEKEND."
HOW DO YOU PLAN ON
KEEPING THAT ONE?
WELL, I'M GOING WITH
A FLEXIBLE WORKWEEK.
IF IT'S A NICE DAY,
IT'S A SATURDAY.
[laughter and applause]
THERE'S NO WAY YOU CAN
KEEP THESE PROMISES.
YEAH, I KNOW,
THAT'S NUMBER 12.
VOTERS DON'T EXPECT YOU
TO KEEP YOUR PROMISES.
UNCLE RED, YOU'VE GOT
A DEBATE IN TWO HOURS
WITH YOUR OPPONENT.
PEOPLE ARE EXPECTING
GOOD PLATFORMS AND
GOOD IDEAS.
HAROLD, THEY ARE NOT.
I TRIED THAT AND
NOBODY LIKED IT.
SO NOW, I JUST GIVE
THEM WHAT THEY WANT.
FALSE HOPE AND LIES?
AND YOU THOUGHT I'D MAKE
A LOUSY POLITICIAN.
ALL RIGHT GUYS,
IT'S NEW MEMBER NIGHT
AND EARL BATTERSBY IS HERE
WITH A GUY HE'S PRESENTING.
JUST DON'T JUDGE
A BOOK BY ITS COVER.
[laughter]
THANK-YOU, RED.
GENTLEMEN, I WANT YOU
TO OPEN YOUR MINDS
TO THE POSSIBILITY
OF OTHER REALITIES.
THAT MAYBE, SOME PEOPLE
ARE NOT LIKE YOU.
FOR EXAMPLE, TAKE
ELMO RAY THORNTON, HERE.
ELMO IS AN UNUSUAL
HUMAN BEING.
SURE, HE APPEARS
SLOW-WITTED.
Earl:
HE'S BORING TO TALK TO.
HE MAY BE A
LITTLE STANDOFFISH
AND MAYBE HE DOESN'T BATHE
AS OFTEN AS YOU OR ME,
OR A CAT.
BUT, THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
PEOPLE ARE ABDUCTED BY ALIENS.
I HAVE CONCRETE EVIDENCE
THAT ELMO WAS KIDNAPPED
BY EXTRATERRESTRIALS
EARLY LAST SUMMER
AND HE HAS MARKINGS
ON HIS LOWER BACKSIDE
THAT HE WOULD BE HAPPY
TO SHOW ANY SKEPTIC.
IF THAT'S NOT ENOUGH PROOF,
TAKE A CLOSE LOOK AT ELMO.
RECOGNIZE HIM?
MAYBE YOU REMEMBER HIM
AS ELLIE MAY THORNTON
PRIOR TO THE ALIEN ABDUCTION?
AND HE CAME BACK WITH
A WHOLE NEW HANDLE.
THIS MAN HAS SUFFERED ENOUGH.
MAKE HIM A NEW MEMBER
OF THE POSSUM LODGE,
SO, HE CAN TAKE THAT FIRST STEP
ON THE PATH OF A NORMAL LIFE.
THANK-YOU.
ALL THOSE IN FAVOUR?
IF YOU'RE NOT CONVINCED,
WE CAN SHOW YOU THE MARKS
ON HIS BACKSIDE, IF YOU LIKE?
[lodge members]
AYE!!!
CONGRATULATIONS, ELMO.
[narrated by Red]
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE OUT THERE
DOING A LITTLE BACKPACKING.
I'VE GOT THE TRADITIONAL
SIZED BACKPACK.
BILL'S GOT A LITTLE BIGGER SIZE.
YEAH, THE FOREST IS NOT AS
NARROW AS IT USED TO BE.
WE'VE COME TO A DITCH, HERE.
AND THIS IS SOMETHING
I DIDN'T REALIZE.
BILL KNOWS THE TECHNIQUE.
HE'S THE EXPERT.
WHAT YOU DO IS THROW IT AND...
BILL'S GONNA THROW HIS.
THAT'S A PRETTY BIG RIG, BILL.
OH, NO!
THAT WASN'T A TOTAL SUCCESS.
WHY DON'T WE REVERSE IT, BILL?
YOU JUMP ACROSS AND I'LL
THROW YOUR GEAR TO YOU.
AWAY YOU GO.
OOOOH!!!
BILL, THERE'S A POST THERE.
THERE'S YOUR STUFF.
BILL'S FOUND SOMETHING HERE.
OH, I SEE.
OH, BOY!
A SHOPPING CART, EH?
I SEE, BILL'S GONNA
TAKE THE EASY WAY.
IT'S A REAL TIME SAVER.
I'M NOT SURE THIS IS CAMPING.
ATTENTION SHOPPERS:
WE'VE GOT A LOOSE ONE HERE.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO GO
AROUND THAT, BILL.
GO AROUND IT, BILL.
JUST GO AROUND IT.
OH! OH! OH!
OH, THERE SHE GOES.
OW!!!
HE'S MAKING GOOD TIME NOW.
OH! OH! OH!
OH, NO!
THAT'S SUCH A SHAME.
THERE YOU GO!
ALWAYS RETURN YOUR CART.
[crowd noises]
WELCOME TO THE
CANDIDATES DEBATE.
JUST SETTLE
DOWN, PLEASE.
THE SOONER WE GET STARTED,
THE SOONER WE'LL FINISH
AND WE CAN GET TO
THE FREE BEER AND
SANDWICHES.
[silence]
OKAY.
WELCOME TO THE CANDIDATES DEBATE
FOR THE MAYOR OF POSSUM LAKE.
I'M DALTON HUMPHREY,
YOUR MODERATOR
AND IT IS MY PLEASURE
TO INTRODUCE THE CANDIDATES.
GIVES YOU SOME IDEA HOW LITTLE
PLEASURE THERE IS IN MY LIFE.
NOT THAT I BLAME
ANYONE BUT MYSELF.
I'M THE ONE WHO TOLD MY DAUGHTER
THAT SHE COULD MOVE BACK HOME
AFTER GETTING EXPELLED
FROM MANICURIST COLLEGE.
I JUST NAILED MY
FOOT TO THE FLOOR.
I SHOULD HAVE USED
BETTER JUDGMENT.
SORRY.
OUR FIRST MAN UP HAS LIVED
ALL HIS LIFE IN POSSUM LAKE.
RED GREEN.
THANK-YOU VERY MUCH.
VOTE FOR ME,
IT WILL BE...
AH, RED.
I'LL ASK YOU TO WAIT
UNTIL I'VE INTRODUCED ALL
THE OTHER CANDIDATES.
VOTE FOR ME.
THANK-YOU, RED.
OUR NEXT CANDIDATE IS
THE INCOMPETENT...
THE INCUMBENT...
WHO REWROTE THIS?
I TOOK A RUN AT IT.
IT'S THE INCUMBENT
WALLY "KICKBACK"...
OH!!!
WALLY KIBLER.
LOOK AT THAT.
HE DIDN'T EVEN HAVE
THE GUTS TO SHOW UP.
IT'S NOT LIKE HIM TO MISS
FREE BEER AND SANDWICHES.
OUR THIRD CANDIDATE IS
A MAN WHO JUST ANNOUNCED
HIS CANDIDACY AN HOUR AGO:
HAROLD GREEN.
WHAT?
THANK-YOU VERY MUCH.
HEY, WAIT A SEC.
WHAT?
I CAN DO IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS, HAROLD.
WHY?
IF I KNEW YOU
WERE TAKING PART,
I NEVER WOULD HAVE TOLD
KIBLER IT WAS CANCELLED.
IF YOU PREVENTED ANOTHER
CANDIDATE FROM ATTENDING,
I MAY HAVE TO TAKE
DISCIPLINARY ACTION.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO?
I'M WITHDRAWING FROM
THE MAYOR RACE, RIGHT NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING THAT FOR?
WELL, I DON'T MIND
MUD-SLINGING STRANGERS,
BUT I DON'T WANT TO BE
DOING IT WITH FAMILY.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA BECAUSE
I KNOW TOO MUCH ABOUT YOU.
AND HOW LONG COULD I GO
WITHOUT SAYING THE PHRASE:
BED WETTING.
[laughter]
BESIDES HAROLD,
IF YOU AND I ARE GOING
AFTER THE SAME THING,
THEN I MUST'VE MADE
A HORRIBLE MISTAKE.
SO, I'M TELLING
YOU RIGHT NOW,
I'M THROWING ALL MY
SUPPORT BEHIND HAROLD.
WELL, I HOPE YOU
WASHED IT FIRST.
THIS IS A SPECIAL FEATURE
ON THE SHOW CALLED:
"YOU AND YOUR ANIMAL."
HOSTED BY LOCAL ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICER, ED FRID.
WELCOME, ED.
[applause]
SOME OF OUR VIEWERS
PROBABLY REMEMBER
GARTH HARBLE.
HE WAS ANOTHER ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICER.
GARTH WORKED WITH YOU?
YEAH.
Red:
IS HE STILL THERE?
NO.
GOT BITTEN BY A TOAD,
SO HE RETIRED.
MEDICAL REASONS, TERRIBLE.
I NEVER THOUGHT A TOAD BITE
WOULD BE THAT SERIOUS.
IT CAN BE.
CAN BE, YEAH.
AND GARTH LOST HIS NERVE.
ONCE YOU LOSE YOUR NERVE
IN THIS BUSINESS,
IT'S OVER, YOU'RE GONE.
YOU'RE DEAD, YOU'RE MEAT.
YOU'RE RED MEAT,
YOU'RE DEAD, RED MEAT.
OKAY.
SO, WHAT DID YOU
BRING US TODAY?
MUSKRAT.
[laughter]
IT'S LIKE A BEAVER,
BUT SMALLER
WITH A SKINNIER TAIL.
AND THE MUSKRAT IS...
WELL, IT'S MORE RAT.
UGH!!!
[loud laughter]
AND MORE MUSK.
YEAH.
[laughter]
HERE, I'LL SHOW YOU.
ED, IS THIS
A GOOD IDEA?
PROBABLY NOT.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
COME HERE, LITTLE GUY.
[muskrat screeching]
NO, NO, NO!
EASY, EASY!!!
I GOT HIM, I GOT HIM.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
I GOT HIM, I GOT HIM,
I GOT HIM, I GOT HIM.
[muskrat screeching]
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
HE'S OUT THE DOOR.
GO GET HIM.
[laughter]
WHOA!!!
[muskrat screeching]
THERE IT GOES!
WELL, THAT'S WHAT A
MUSKRAT LOOKS LIKE.
AND SMELLS LIKE.
AND BITES LIKE.
THANK-YOU, ED.
IT LOOKS LIKE KIBLER IS GOING
TO WIN THE ELECTION, THERE.
WE WON'T KNOW UNTIL HAROLD GETS
HERE WITH THE FINAL RESULTS.
[laughter]
HOW DID IT GO?
NOT GREAT.
KIBLER GOT RE-ELECTED
AND THEY TRIED TO
BURN ME IN EFFIGY.
I DON'T CARE BECAUSE
I GAVE IT MY BEST SHOT
AND I'M NOT GOING TO CHANGE
WHO I AM JUST TO GET ELECTED.
AND YOU'D HAVE TO,
BELIEVE ME, BUDDY.
[squeal of the Possum]
IT'S MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'VE GIVEN UP ON BEING MAYOR,
BUT I'M HOPING TO HAVE ANOTHER
SHOT AT BEING STALLION.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
AT POSSUM LODGE:
"KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE."
[applause]
TAKE YOUR SEATS,
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
HERE HE COMES.
TAKE YOUR SEATS AND
GET COMFORTABLE.
ALL RISE.
[lodge members]
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
OUR NEWLY RE-ELECTED MAYOR
WOULD LIKE ME TO THANK YOU
FOR YOUR CONTINUED SUPPORT
FOR HIM AS MAYOR
AND HE WOULD LIKE ME TO ASK YOU
FOR YOUR CONTINUED SUPPORT
FOR HIS CONTINUED SUPPORT
OF POSSUM LODGE.
SO, UNCLE RED, IF YOU WOULD
LIKE TO START THE GRATUITIES.
I DON'T KNOW.
COME ON, IT'S BETTER
THAN PAYING TAXES.