I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT TO ME THERE IS
NOTHING WORSE
THAN TAKING YOUR WIFE OUT
FOR A ROMANTIC DINNER
ON A RAINY EVENING
ONLY TO GET YOUR ARM SOAKED
WHEN THEY HAND YOUR ORDER
OUT THROUGH
THE WINDOW TO YOU.
WHAT YOU NEED IS
A COLLAPSIBLE ROOF
THAT ATTACHES TO THE OUTSIDE
OF YOUR VEHICLE
AND THEN EXPANDS OVER
TO THE DRIVE-THRU WINDOW
LIKE ONE OF THOSE N.A.S.A.
DOCKING STATIONS,
EXCEPT THIS ONE WON'T BE
USED FOR SOME USELESS
SCIENCE PROJECT.
OKAY, NOW, WHAT ARE
WE GOING TO USE
FOR OUR COLLAPSIBLE
UMBILICAL DOCKING STATION?
I BELIEVE I HAVE
JUST THE THING.
I'M GOING TO USE THE
BELLOWS OFF THIS ACCORDION.
I'M NOT A BIG FAN
OF ACCORDION MUSIC.
TO ME THE ONLY DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN AN ACCORDION
AND A TRAMPOLINE
IS YOU TAKE YOUR SHOES OFF
TO JUMP ON A TRAMPOLINE.
IF THERE ARE ANY MUSIC LOVERS
OUT THERE, YOU'RE WELCOME.
[cheering and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
THANK YOU. APPRECIATE THAT.
ACTUALLY, IT'S NOT A GREAT
WEEK TO BE UP AT THE LODGE.
HAROLD HAS BEEN PROMOTING
US AS TOURIST FRIENDLY,
AND NOW HE'S RENTED THE WHOLE
PLACE OUT FOR THE WEEKEND
TO THESE TREE-HUGGING
NATURALISTS.
I MEAN, IT'S SOME KIND
OF A CORPORATE THING.
THEY'RE SENDING ALL THEIR
SENIOR PEOPLE OR SOMETHING.
SO NOW I FIGURE
I'VE GOT TWO CHOICES...
I CAN EITHER HANG
AROUND HERE
AND APOLOGIZE FOR
EVERYTHING I'VE EVER DONE
AND AM GOING TO DO,
WHICH IS JUST LIKE
BEING AT HOME,
OR I CAN GO FISHING.
AND I'VE MADE MY DECISION.
UNCLE RED, IT'S A
BEAUTIFUL DAY, ISN'T IT?
[cheering and applause]
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL DAY.
A BEE-OOTIFUL DAY.
SOMETHING'S WRONG,
ISN'T IT, HAROLD?
WRONG, NO, WHY DOES
SOMETHING HAVE TO BE WRONG?
IT IS A BEAUTIFUL DAY!
BEAUTIFUL DAY.
YOU MESSED UP,
DIDN'T YOU?
MESSED UP?
HOW DID I MESS UP?
OH, NO.
YOU MESSED UP.
I DIDN'T MESS UP!
YOU'RE GOING TO GET $500
FOR THE USE OF THE
LODGE THIS WEEKEND.
IF THAT'S MESSING UP,
THEN MAYBE I SHOULD JUST
MESS UP MORE OFTEN.
OKAY, SO EVERYTHING'S GOOD
AND WE'RE GONNA GET PAID?
'CAUSE THIS IS AN
INCONVENIENCE, HAROLD.
IT'S NOT AN INCONVENIENCE.
IT'S BUSINESS.
SEE, THE LODGE HAD TO
FIND SOME WAY TO START
GENERATING FUNDS,
SO THIS IS WHAT
WE'RE GOING TO DO.
AN INCONVENIENCE.
BEING FORECLOSED ON
AND GOING TO JAIL,
THAT'S AN INCONVENIENCE.
EVERYTHING'S GOOD.
SO EVERYTHING'S GOOD?
EVERYTHING'S PERFECT?
I KNEW IT.
YOU MESSED UP, DIDN'T YOU?
IT WAS A TYPO.
IT WAS JUST A TYPO.
THAT'S ALL.
WELL, I WAS UNDER THE
IMPRESSION THAT THESE GUESTS
WERE SENIOR NATURALISTS.
WHAT?
I WAS WRONG.
TURNS OUR THEY'RE
SENIOR NATURISTS.
WELL, UM --
DOES THAT MEAN?
WHAT THE HECK
[laughter and applause]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheering and applause]
TODAY'S WINNER RECEIVES
A WEEKEND PASS
AT THE BIGAMIST
ARMS HOTEL,
INCLUDING THE
HONEYMOON SUITE
AND A BED THAT
SLEEPS SEVEN.
OKAY, DALTON,
COVER YOUR EARS.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON TO SAY
THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, DALTON, THIS IS
SOMETHING YOU SHOULD FEEL
WHEN YOU THINK
OF YOUR WIFE.
FEAR.
NO.
GUILT.
REGRET.
NO, DALTON, THIS IS
SOMETHING POSITIVE.
OKAY, OKAY.
NEVER MIND ABOUT THAT.
YOU SEE A YOUNG COUPLE
KISSING UNDER A STREET LIGHT,
YOU SAY, THEY'RE IN...
HEAT.
ALMOST OUT
OF TIME, RED.
YEAH, UM,
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON.
OKAY, DALTON, WHAT IS THE
POINT OF VALENTINE'S DAY?
OH, I'M WITH YOU 100%
THERE, RED.
I -- YOU KNOW, I THINK
THIS IS TOO TOUGH.
I'D LOVE TO.
DO YOU WANT TO JUST QUIT?
THERE WE GO!
IF YOURS IS THE STINKIEST
HOUSE ON THE ROAD,
AND NEIGHBORS FEAR
YOUR LAWN MAY EXPLODE,
ME AND MY TRUCK WILL
GRACE YOUR ABODE.
I MAY ARRIVE EMPTY-HANDED,
BUT I'LL SURE
LEAVE WITH A LOAD.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT VERY SMART
WHEN IT COMES TO HISTORY
OR MATHEMATICS
OR PHYSICS OR CHEMISTRY
OR BOTANY OR ZOOLOGY
OR LANGUAGES OR
CALCULUS OR HOME EC.,
BUT I CAN TELL YOU ONE THING.
I KNOW HOW CARS WORK.
UNLESS THEY'RE NEW CARS OR
DIESELS OR METRIC OR
SOME STUPID THING.
BUT FOR EXAMPLE,
I KNOW THAT THIS...
IS A SUPERCHARGER.
RIGHT. GOOD.
THAT WAS LUCKY.
NOW, A SUPERCHARGER
IS BASICALLY A HIGH
SPEED AIR PUMP
THAT MAKES AN ENGINE WORK
BETTER BY RAMMING THE
FUEL THROUGH IT.
OKAY, I'M NOT A DOCTOR.
I DON'T EVEN PLAY
ONE ON TELEVISION.
BUT IT SEEMS TO ME
THAT THE HUMAN BODY
IS VERY SIMILAR TO
AN AUTOMOBILE.
YOU'VE GOT YOUR
INTAKE MANIFOLD;
YOU'VE GOT
YOUR CARBURETOR;
YOU'VE GOT YOUR ENGINE;
AND YOU'VE GOT YOUR
WHOLE EXHAUST SYSTEM.
AND JUST LIKE
AN AUTOMOBILE,
IT'S BUILT FOR BOTH POWER
AND ENTERTAINMENT.
OKAY, BUT JUST LIKE A CAR,
ONCE A GUY GETS A FEW
MILES ON HIM,
HE STARTS TO HAVE PROBLEMS.
THAT'S BECAUSE OVER TIME
THE QUANTITY AND TYPES
OF MATERIAL THAT ARE
GOING IN HERE
FAR EXCEED THE QUANTITY
AND TYPES OF MATERIAL
THAT ARE COMING OUT HERE.
THIS CREATES A SURPLUS
IN THIS AREA,
WHICH CAUSES A HIGH BLOOD
PRESSURE SITUATION
UP IN HERE.
NOW, THE DOCTORS ARE GOING
TO GIVE YOU ALL KINDS
OF TREATMENTS
FOR HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE.
THEY WANT YOU TO TAKE PILLS.
THEY WANT YOU TO EXERCISE.
THEY WANT YOU
TO LOSE WEIGHT.
LET'S BE SERIOUS.
OH, NO, WE NEED
A BETTER WAY.
AND I'M THINKING
SUPERCHARGER.
BECAUSE IF A SUPERCHARGER
CAN HELP A CAR ENGINE BY
MOVING FUEL FASTER,
IT SHOULD BE ABLE
TO HELP A HUMAN ENGINE
BY MOVING BLOOD FASTER.
JUST GIVE ME A FEW
MINUTES TO HOOK THIS UP.
I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW IT WORKS.
BY THE WAY,
THIS ISN'T REAL BLOOD.
IT'S CREAM SODA.
AND THIS IS
NOT A REAL PERSON.
IT'S A CIVIL SERVANT.
OKAY, I GOT ALL MY TUBES
HOOKED UP TO A SUPERCHARGER,
AND I MOUNTED A HIGH-SPEED
CORDLESS DRILL ON THERE
TO DRIVE THE UNIT.
TAPED THE WHOLE THING TOGETHER
USING THE HANDYMAN'S SECRET
WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
I DON'T THINK PEOPLE
WILL EVEN NOTICE IT.
OF COURSE, NOW, YOU DON'T
WANT THE THING RUNNING
ALL THE TIME.
IT'S JUST FOR EMERGENCIES
WHEN YOUR BLOOD PRESSURE
HITS A SPIKE,
YOU KNOW, LIKE WHEN YOU'RE
OPENING A LETTER FROM
THE GOVERNMENT,
OR MAYBE A FRIEND'S
HUSBAND COMES HOME EARLY.
SO WHAT I DID IS
I ATTACHED A SWITCH
TO THIS BLOOD
PRESSURE READER THING,
AND THAT HOOK UP TO THE
DRILL AND DRIVE THE THING,
AND THEN AS SOON AS THE BLOOD
PRESSURE GETS UP TO,
SAY, HEART ATTACK RANGE,
THE SUPERCHARGER COMES ON.
NOW, IT'S NOT GOING TO
LOWER YOUR BLOOD PRESSURE,
BUT IT TAKES THE LOAD
OFF YOUR HEART
BECAUSE THE SUPERCHARGER
IS DOING MOST OF THE WORK.
I DON'T REALLY
SEE A DOWNSIDE HERE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[applause]
OH, I HAD A
THOUGHT LAST WEEK,
AND I WANT TO SHARE WITH YOU
BEFORE IT SLIPS AWAY.
YOU KNOW WHEN
I WAS IN HIGH SCHOOL,
THE PARENTS AND THE TEACHERS
ALWAYS LIKED THE KIDS
WHO WERE SELF-CONFIDENT
AND SELF-ASSURED.
YOU KNOW THE ONES I MEAN,
THE ONES WHO WOULD TALK
TO YOUR MOM AND DAD
LIKE THEY WERE
THEIR BUDDIES;
OR THEY'D PHONE OVER TO
YOUR HOUSE AND IF YOU
WEREN'T THERE
THEY'D HAVE A CONVERSATION
WITH WHOEVER ANSWERED
THE PHONE.
PARENTS ALWAYS LIKE KIDS
WHO HAVE THOSE KINDS OF
PEOPLE SKILLS.
MY MOM WOULD SAY, "BOY, THAT
BRIAN IS SUCH A NICE KID.
"HE'S SO OUTGOING."
AND EMPLOYERS
FELT THE SAME WAY.
THESE OUTGOING KIDS
BECAME OUTGOING ADULTS.
THEY GOT GREAT JOBS.
THEY DID REAL WELL, BECAME
LEADERS IN THEIR COMMUNITY,
AND GOOD FOR THEM.
OH, YEAH.
THEY MADE A
CONTRIBUTION TO SOCIETY,
AND THEY WERE
REWARDED FOR IT.
NOW, WOULD SOMEONE PLEASE
TELL THEM TO KNOCK IT OFF.
AT MY AGE, I DON'T WANT
TO BE AROUND ANYBODY
THAT OUTGOING.
I'D MUCH RATHER SPEND
TIME WITH MY FRIEND ED,
WHO HARDLY EVER
SAYS ANYTHING.
AND WHEN HE DOES,
IT'S ALWAYS IMPORTANT,
STUFF LIKE
"THAT'S A COP."
THESE DAYS, I JUST DON'T
WANT ANYBODY OUTGOING
BUGGING ME WITH
THEIR GOOD MOOD.
I'M OLD AND SOMETHING
PROBABLY HURTS.
I'M WELL AWARE I'M IN
THE LAST THIRD OF MY LIFE,
AND TO BE HONEST WITH YOU,
I WANT THE TIME TO DRAG.
SO PUT A SOCK IN IT, BRIAN,
I'M GOING FISHING WITH ED.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
YOU JUST GOT HOME AND
THERE'S A NEW DENT
IN THE CAR.
YEAH.
PUT THERE.
A DENT YOUR WIFE
YOU'RE ABOUT TO GO
RIGHT OFF THE DEEP END.
BUT BE CAREFUL.
A LOT OF GUYS
HAVE DROWNED
UNDERESTIMATING JUST
HOW DEEP THE DEEP END IS.
YEAH, WE KNOW YOU'VE
NEVER PUT A DENT
IN THE CAR.
OTHER PEOPLE HAVE.
LIKE THAT IDIOT WHO
TORE YOUR DOOR OFF
WHEN YOU LEFT IT OPEN TO
GO IN AND BUY MILK.
OR WHEN YOU GOT REAR-ENDED
BECAUSE SOME GOOF
NEVER NOTICED
THAT YOU STOPPED ON
THE HIGHWAY TO PICK UP
WHAT YOU THOUGHT
WAS A DIME.
OR WHEN THE
ENGINE SEIZED-UP
BECAUSE NONE OF YOUR
FRIENDS REMINDED YOU
TO CHECK THE OIL.
YOU KNOW, YOU TAKE BETTER
CARE OF THE CARE THAN
YOUR WIFE DOES.
BUT THERE'S NO POINT IN
GETTING ALL BENT OUT OF
SHAPE ABOUT A LITTLE DENT
AND THEN HAVE A HEAD-ON
COLLISION AT HOME.
NO, DON'T BE THE ONE
TRAPPED IN YOUR VEHICLE.
YOU MAY HAVE A BIG MOUTH,
BUT IT'S NOT
JAWS OF LIFE.
NO, YOU JUST SMILE AND SAY,
"THAT'S OKAY, HONEY."
WE KNOW YOU STILL
LOVE YOUR CAR.
JUST NOT ENOUGH
TO SLEEP IN IT.
OKAY, I'M TRYING TO DO
THE RIGHT THING HERE.
I MEAN, HAROLD
PUT A LOT OF WORK
INTO MARKETING THE LODGE
TO THESE OLD NUDISTS,
AND THEY DON'T REALLY
MEAN ANY HARM, YOU KNOW.
PLUS, 500 BUCKS,
WELL, THAT'S GOOD MONEY.
SO, I MEAN, I'VE ONLY
GOT ONE MORE DAY TO GO,
AND I BELIEVE I'LL
GET THROUGH THIS.
I JUST KEEP LOOKING AT THE
FLOOR AND THINKING
ABOUT BASEBALL.
MR. GREEN, I NEED
TO TALK TO YOU.
JUST TAKE IT EASY,
MIKE, ALL RIGHT?
I DIDN'T MEAN TO LOOK.
I DIDN'T WANT TO LOOK.
THESE PEOPLE ARE LIKE
MY GRANDPARENTS.
THEY SHOULDN'T BE NAKED.
THEY SHOULD BE ON A PORCH
SOMEWHERE, WHITTLING.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
BUT IT'S ONLY ONE
MORE DAY, ALL RIGHT?
YOU DIDN'T
SEE WHAT I SAW!
WORSE.
LAWN BOWLING?
TRAMPOLINE.
WHAT?
UNCLE RED,
WE GOT A PROBLEM.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
WE GOT A PROBLEM?
IT'S ABOUT
THE 500 DOLLARS.
SEEMS OUR GUESTS FEEL
THAT WE'RE NOT
EMBRACING THE NUDIST
LIFESTYLE QUITE ENOUGH.
SO TOMORROW AT NOON
THEY'RE GOING TO PRESENT
THE $500 CHEQUE TO A
LODGE REPRESENTATIVE.
BUT THAT LODGE REPRESENTATIVE
HAS TO BE NAKED.
500 BUCK NAKED.
BUCK NAKED?
[applause]
I THINK THEY
WANT YOU TO GO.
I THINK WE'RE NOT
GONNA GET PAID.
Red:
WAS OUT FOR A
DRIVE IN THE WAGON,
AND UM, I NOTICED THE
SHERIFF'S CAR IN KIND
OF A PROBLEM.
LOOKED LIKE HE HAD RUN HER
UP ON A HUMP THERE.
AND I WAS LOOKING FOR
THE SHERIFF INSIDE,
BUT IT WASN'T THE SHERIFF.
IT WAS MIKE.
SO ALL THE MORE REASON
TO GET HER DOWN.
WELL, I'VE GOT A SHOVEL
IN THE WAGON,
BUT MIKE HAD
ANOTHER IDEA.
HE HAS A A DIFFERENT APPROACH
TO MOST THINGS IN LIFE.
I DON'T TOTALLY UNDERSTAND
THE KIND OF LOGIC THAT
MIKE USES HERE, BUT --
ANYWAY, I LIKE
HAVING A WAGON.
YOU CAN GET A LOT OF
STUFF INTO A WAGON.
YOU'RE PRETTY MUCH
READY FOR ANYTHING.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN A
SING-SONG MIGHT SPRING UP.
THERE WE GO,
THERE'S THE SHOVEL.
ALL RIGHT AND
GET BACK THERE.
AND FAIR ENOUGH, SINCE MIKE
HAD GOTTEN INTO THE PROBLEM,
HE WAS MORE THAN WILLING
TO ACTUALLY DO THE WORK,
WHICH I
APPRECIATED UNTIL --
UNTIL HE BROKE THE SHOVEL
AND THEN THE MIRROR.
AND OF COURSE MIKE ALWAYS
HAS ANOTHER IDEA
SO WHAT HE FIGURED HE'D DO
IS HE TOOK THE CHAIN OUT
OF THE TRUNK THERE
AND WENT FROM THE BACK
AXLE OF THE COP CAR
AND WRAPPED HER AROUND
THE BACK AXLE OF THE WAGON.
AND HE SAID, "DON'T WORRY.
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY
GO WRONG?"
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
NO, THAT'S GOOD.
NOW WE DEFINITELY HAVE TO
GET THE COP CAR OFF
OF THE HUMP.
MIKE SAYS THERE'S A
CONCRETE BLOCK THERE.
IF I COULD STICK THE CONCRETE
BLOCK, WEDGE HER UNDER
THE WHEEL,
GIVE HIM SOME TRACTION,
THEN HE COULD THROWN
IT INTO REVERSE
AND THAT MIGHT JUST HUMP
IT RIGHT OFF THERE.
WELL, I'LL GIVE HER A GO.
HE REVS HER UP,
POPS HER INTO REVERSE,
AND IT DID CATCH
FOR A SECOND.
AND INTO THE RAVINE.
OKAY, MIKE, NOW WHAT?
WELL, MIKE FIGURED WE'VE
STILL GOT THE CHAINS
BETWEEN THE TWO
SETS OF REAR ENDS,
SO WHY DON'T WE PUT
THE WHEELS UP IN THERE?
THAT'LL SHOOT
THE WHEELS BACK,
AND CHAIN WILL PULL
THE UNIT OFF THE HUMP.
AND I WAS REALLY TOO TIRED
TO THINK OF ANYTHING ELSE,
SO I --
BUT THIS TIME MIKE DIDN'T
GET INTO THE VEHICLE,
WHICH ULTIMATELY
WAS A GREAT IDEA.
THEY KICKED OFF THERE.
PULLED HER OFF AND AWAY --
BUT SHE'S HEADING
THE RAVINE, MIKE.
DO YOU THINK PERHAPS
WE SHOULD...
YES, LET'S...
NO, SHE HIT A TREE!
WE'RE GOOD.
NO, WE'RE GOOD.
OKAY.
EVERYTHING'S FINE OFFICER.
NOTHING TO SEE HERE.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERTS
PORTION OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE ADDRESS THOSE THREE
LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
EXCELLENT.
AND JOINING RED TODAY
IS LODGE MEMBER
AND LOCAL ANTIQUE,
MR. DALTON HUMPHREY.
THAT'S ANTIQUE DEALER.
OH, SORRY.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
TODAY'S LETTER
READS AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"RECENTLY I BOUGHT ONE OF
THOSE HOME BARBER KITS
FOR MY FAMILY.
"IT WORKS REALLY WELL,
AND WE ALL HAD A LOT
OF FUN WITH IT.
"MY QUESTION IS CAN YOU
RECOMMEND A STYLE OF HAT
"THAT MY WHOLE FAMILY COULD
WEAR FOR THE NEXT
MONTH OR TWO?"
YEAH, OKAY. I MEAN HATS
CAN BE SMART LOOKING,
AND THIS GUY
NEEDS SOMETHING
TO MAKE HIM LOOK SMART
AT THIS POINT, I WOULD SAY.
WE HAVE A FINE SELECTION
OF HATS AT HUMPHREY'S
EVERYTHING STORE.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T
PERSONALLY DON'T WEAR HATS.
NO, YOU'D HAVE TO
GO WITH AN ONION BAG.
YOU KNOW,
I RECOMMEND
THE HARD-HAT.
THAT WAY YOU CAN COMBINE
STYLE WITH SAFETY.
WELL, SEE, OKAY, I HAVE
A PROBLEM WITH THAT.
SEE, I DON'T THINK PEOPLE
SHOULD WEAR HATS
THEY DON'T HONESTLY USE
IN THEIR DAILY LIFE.
NOW A HARD-HAT, WELL,
THAT'S FINE FOR YOU, WINSTON,
BECAUSE THERE'S
A REASON FOR THAT.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN YOU EITHER
USE IT IN YOUR WORK,
OR YOU HAVE A SOFT
HEAD OR SOMETHING.
BUT THAT GUY
IN THE VILLAGE PEOPLE,
I DON'T THINK SO.
SO YOU'RE SAYING DON'T WEAR
A COWBOY HAT IF YOU'RE
NOT A COWBOY.
WELL, EXACTLY.
IF YOU'RE OUT
THERE DRIVING CATTLE
OR MENDING FENCES, FINE.
BUT EATING BAKED
BEANS IS NOT ENOUGH.
OKAY, BUT, UH, BUT WHAT
ABOUT A BERET?
SAME DEAL.
SAME DEAL WITH A BERET.
IF YOU WEAR A BERET
YOU'D BETTER
EITHER BE PART OF A SPECIAL
MILITARY STRIKE FORCE
OR ON YOUR WAY TO
A POETRY READING.
AND IF YOU'RE BOTH,
YOU'VE GOT SOME SERIOUS
DECISIONS TO MAKE
ABOUT WHERE YOUR
LIFE IS GOING.
THAT'S A MILITARY HAT
YOU'RE WEARING,
ISN'T IT, RED?
YEAH, HOW MANY YEARS WAS
IT THAT YOU SERVED,
AGAIN, RED?
UH, WELL, UH, HEY, I'VE
BEEN MARRIED 35 YEARS,
I SERVED
EVERY ONE OF THEM.
NO, NO, THAT'S NOT AN
OFFICIAL MILITARY ASSIGNMENT.
THAT'S MORE OF A VOLUNTEER
CIVILIAN POSITION.
WELL, OKAY, OKAY.
BUT I'VE HAD THIS HAT
A LONG TIME, ALL RIGHT?
IT'S CALLED A
FIELD MANOEUVRES CAP.
I GOT IT DURING
MY DATING YEARS,
AND I HAD A FEW FIELD
MANOEUVRES, BELIEVE ME.
TOO BAD YOU NEVER
SAW ACTIVE SERVICE.
[laughter and applause]
I'LL TELL YOU THE MAIN
PROBLEM WITH DOORBELLS.
THEY'RE TOO DARN CLOSE
TO THE HOUSE.
YOU DON'T GET TIME TO
GET YOURSELF READY TO
ANSWER THE DOOR.
THIS WAS MADE VERY
CLEAR TO ME LAST WEEK.
I WAS ON MY WAY
INTO THE SHOWER,
AND I WAS DRESSED
APPROPRIATELY FOR
THAT ASSIGNMENT.
SUDDENLY MY DOORBELL RINGS.
WELL, I ASSUMED IT WAS
ONE OF THE GUYS,
AND I DIDN'T REALLY
HAVE TIME TO GET DRESSED,
SO I JUST ANSWERED
THE DOOR ALFRESCO.
OF COURSE, IT'S NOT
ONE OF THE GUYS.
IT'S AN OLDER LADY
COLLECTING MONEY
FOR THE HEART ATTACK
AND STROKE FOUNDATION.
SHE TOOK ONE LOOK AT ME,
AND I BELIEVE SHE HAD
ONE OF EACH.
SO I NEED SOMETHING TO GIVE
ME MORE TIME TO PREPARE
FOR MY VISITORS.
SO I'M MOVING THE
DOORBELL FROM THE DOOR
OVER HERE TO THE DRIVEWAY.
NOW, I JUST NEED SOME
SORT OF TRIGGERING DEVICE.
ANYONE WHO'S EVER DRIVEN
A CAR KNOWS THAT A POP CAN
EMITS A WEIRD KIND OF
GRAVITY TO ANY DRIVER.
YOU CAN'T SEE A POP CAN
WITHOUT DRIVING OVER IT.
SO WHAT I'M GOING TO DO IS
ATTACH ONE WIRE TO THE TAB
AND THEN THE OTHER ONE I'VE
GOT A LEAD SINKER ON THERE,
I'M GOING TO DROP THAT
DOWN INSIDE THE HOLE
AND I GOT A WAD OF THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON
TO STOP THE SINKER FROM
HITTING THE BOTTOM
OF THE CAN.
BUT LISTEN TO WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN THE CAN MOVES.
[doorbell buzzer]
BUT TALK IS CHEAP.
LET'S HAVE A DEMONSTRATION.
BETTER YET,
LET'S HAVE
A CHEAP DEMONSTRATION.
[doorbell buzzing incessantly]
[doorbell continues buzzing incessantly]
COME ON, UNCLE RED.
IF YOU WANT TO SEE ANY
OF THAT MONEY YOU BETTER
GET THOSE CLOTHES OFF.
HAROLD, CAN YOU IMAGINE
SOMEBODY TUNING
IN RIGHT NOW?
WHAT WOULD
THEY THINK?
OH.
O-O-H!
NO!
WELL, DO YOU WANT TO SEE
ANY OF THAT $500 OR NOT?
WELL, HAROLD, JUST A SEC.
I HAVE SOME PRIDE HERE.
IT'S HARD TO PUT
A PRICE TAG ON THAT.
COME ONE, 30 BUCKS TOPS.
COME ON.
JUST A MINUTE
HERE, HAROLD.
THE NUDISTS SAID THEY WOULD
PAY A REPRESENTATIVE
OF THE LODGE
AS LONG AS
HE WAS NAKED.
IT DOESN'T
HAVE TO BE ME.
YOU'RE NOT GOING
SEND A DOG, ARE YOU?
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S ALL TAKEN
CARE OF, HAROLD.
COME ON
IN HERE, MIKE.
[laughter and applause]
I DON'T HAVE A GOOD
FEELING ABOUT THIS.
WELL, HE'S NOT
EXACTLY NAKED.
WELL, I'VE GOT TO WEAR THIS.
I'M A NON-SWIMMER.
HEY, THEY'RE THE ONES WHO
PICKED THE MAIN DOCK
TO DO THIS.
SAFETY TAKES PRECEDENCE
OVER EXHIBITIONISM.
C'MON, MIKE.
I'LL HOLD THE
DOOR FOR YOU.
YOU'RE A VERY
BRAVE MAN, MIKE.
THANK YOU,
HAROLD.
WELL, HERE GOES
NOTHING.
[pop!]
[Mike screaming]
[applause]
[possum squealing]
OH, GOOD.
IT'S MEETING TIME!
OH, YEAH!
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN
IN A MINUTE.
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME FROM THE MEETING.
AND ACTUALLY I SAVED YOU THE
EMBARRASSMENT OF SHOWING
THE WHOLE WORLD
WHAT YOU HAVE TO LOOK
AT EVERY NIGHT.
WELL, MAYBE NOT EVERY NIGHT,
BUT HOPEFULLY TONIGHT.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
Dalton: SIT DOWN.
OH, ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
WANT TO SIT DOWN?