YOU NOTICE HOW PEOPLE DRIVE
TOO FAST THROUGH YOUR
NEIGHBOURHOOD?
MAYBE THEY'RE LATE FOR WORK
OR OUT OF BEER,
OR SOMEBODY'S HUSBAND
CAME HOME EARLY.
WHATEVER THE REASON,
IT'S DANGEROUS,
AND YOU GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO GET 'EM TO SLOW DOWN.
HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
GET YOURSELF A
LIGHT BLUE SHIRT,
SOME DARK BLUE PANTS,
A CAPTAIN'S HAT,
AND A HAIR DRYER.
AND IF A COP ASKS YOU,
YOU TELL HIM YOU'RE NOT
IMPERSONATING AN OFFICER,
YOU'RE A RETIRED
TUG BOAT CAPTAIN
TRYING TO GET
INTO HAIRDRESSING.
[ BRAKES SCREECHING ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG DAY UP
AT THE LODGE.
I'M COMING HOME FROM TOWN
WITH FLINTY McCLINTOK
IN HIS SCHOOL BUS.
HE'S HOPING TO GET
THE CONTRACT FOR
THE POSSUM LAKE
PUBLIC SCHOOL.
ANYWAY, WERE DRIVING ALONG,
AND ALL OF THE SUDDEN, BANG!
TRANSMISSION DROPS
RIGHT OUT OF HER,
ROLLS ONTO THE LAWN
OF CITY HALL THERE.
I FIGURE, FAIR ENOUGH,
WE'LL GIVE THEM
THE GEARS FOR A CHANGE.
WELL, IT TURNS OUT THE
SCHOOL BUS HAS BALD TIRES,
NO BRAKES, NO MUFFLER,
HAS 700,000 MILES ON HER,
AND FLINTY HAS NO LICENSE.
SO HE OFFERS ME
THE SCHOOL BUS.
FOR NOTHING!
I MEAN, A WHOLE SCHOOL BUS.
I MEAN, CAN YOU
BELIEVE IT?
A SCHOOL BUS.
A SCHOOL BUS!
OKAY, WE MADE IT.
SCHOOL BUS IS IN
THE PARKING LOT, RED.
ANY TROUBLE TOWING
IT, OR ANYTHING?
OH, NO, NOT WITH
THE SEWAGE TRUCK.
NO, IT'S USED TO
THAT KINDA LOAD.
WHY DID WE BRING
IT HERE, Mr. GREEN?
IT'S TOO BIG FOR THE
GARBAGE MAN TO
TAKE IT AWAY.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
ALL YOU SEE IS A DEAD
SCHOOL BUS, RIGHT?
YOU GOTTA USE
YOUR IMAGINATION.
WELL, I USED TO USE
MINE ALL THE TIME.
THAT'S HOW I ENDED
UP IN THE SLAMMER.
OKAY, WHAT ARE WE
GOING TO DO WITH IT?
WELL, WE'LL PUT AN
OUTBOARD MOTOR ON
THE BACK BUMPER,
COVER THE HOLES IN
THE FLOOR WITH
STORM WINDOWS.
CAN YOU SAY,
GLASS-BOTTOM BOAT?
CAN YOU SAY BIG,
YELLOW SUBMARINE?
IT'S TIME TO PLAY THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S PRIZES
ARE PROVIDED BY,
ELLIE'S ELECTROLYSIS EMPORIUM.
AND THE WINNER OF TODAY'S GAME
WILL BE AWARDED THIS COUPON,
FOR A COMPLETE
BIKINI TREATMENT
AND A BACK HAIR
CONSULTATION.
PLAYING TODAY
IS Mr. ED FRIG.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Mr. FRIG IS A LOW-CAL
ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER.
LOCAL.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, OKAY, Mr. GREEN,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET Mr. FRIG
TO SAY THIS WORD.
COVER YOUR EARS.
THE WORD IS --
MIKE!
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT, ED,
UH, PEOPLE FALL IN THIS.
OH, QUICKSAND.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
ALL YOU NEED IS...
THICK GLOVES AND
A TRANQUILIZER GUN?
UH, OKAY.
THIS MEANS NEVER HAVING
TO SAY YOU'RE SORRY...
BUMPING INTO
A DEAF GUY?
NO, NO.
IN TENNIS THIS
MEANS NOTHING.
OH, GOOD MANNERS.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
POETS.
POETS WRITE
ABOUT THIS.
A HERMIT NAMED DAVE.
OKAY, LET'S GET BACK TO
WHEN YOU WERE A KID,
AND YOU WERE ACTING KINDA
GOOFY AND YOUR PARENTS SAID,
DON'T WORRY,
IT'S ONLY PUPPY --
WORMS.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, ED,
FOR YOU TO BE BORN YOUR
PARENTS HAD TO MAKE --
COMPROMISES.
ALMOST OUT OF
TIME, Mr. GREEN.
ROMEO AND JULIET
WERE IN --
OH, I GOT IT.
A PLAY!
YES, I WIN.
I LOVE THIS GAME.
THERE YOU GO.
YES, SIR, ABSOLUTELY.
THAT IS THE NUMBER ONE PRIORITY.
ABSOLUTELY, I GOT IT.
BYE-BYE.
HAROLD, I GOT THOSE
STICKY NOTES
YOU WANTED.
OH, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THAT'S PERFECT.
THANK YOU,
THANK YOU.
THEY'RE GREEN!
I CAN'T USE THESE.
I NEED PINK!
I CAN'T WORK --
I CAN USE THESE, THOUGH.
THESE WILL BE FINE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'LL DO?
I'LL USE A PINK HIGHLIGHTER,
AND EVEN THOUGH THEY ARE GREEN,
I'LL STILL KNOW IT'S
NUMBER ONE PRIORITY
BECAUSE IT'S
WRITTEN IN PINK.
SEEMS SIMPLE
ENOUGH, HAROLD.
YEAH, I HAVE EVERYTHING
PRIORITIZED BY COLOUR CODES.
NOW THAT YOU GOT STICKYS,
I CAN TAKE THAT OFF MY LIST.
THIS IS GREAT.
I'M MAKING MY
LIST SMALLER.
GET STICKYS,
GET STICKYS --.
AH, GET STICKYS!
THIS IS QUITE A
SYSTEM YOU'VE GOT
GOING HERE, HAROLD.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
PROBLEM IS
I GOT SO MUCH ON THE GO,
I NEED MORE ROOM.
I NEED SPACE.
I'VE EVEN GOT STICKYS ON
THE BACK OF MY CHAIR.
OH, BOY.
THEY'RE LOW PRIORITY
ONES, THOUGH,
SO IT'S OKAY IF I DON'T
SEE THEM THAT OFTEN.
I EVEN HAVE STICKYS ALL
OVER MY COMPUTER MONITOR.
I HATE DOING THAT.
I GOTTA DO IT.
I'M OUT OF ROOM.
SO I'M GONNA PUT A BIG
WALL RIGHT IN HERE, EH.
STICKYS EVERYWHERE!
HAROLD, HOW ARE YOU GOING
TO GET ANY WORK DONE?
YOU GOT NOTES ALL
OVER EVERYTHING.
UNCLE RED,
WHAT AM GOING TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S WHAT YOU ARE
GONNA DO, OKAY?
YOU'RE GOING TO ABANDON
THIS WHOLE STUPID SYSTEM.
GET YOURSELF A
CALENDAR WITH A PENCIL
WITH A GREAT
BIG ERASER ON IT.
CALENDAR AND A PENCIL
WITH A GREAT BIG
ERASER ON IT.
THAT'S WHAT
I'M GONNA DO.
ABSOLUTELY.
AND THAT'S A NUMBER
ONE PRIORITY NOW.
THAT'S --.
HERE.
AW, THANKS.
GOTTA MAKE A NOTE THAT
THERE'S A NOTE THERE.
RED, DO YOU FIND
ME ATTRACTIVE?
I DON'T MEAN
PHYSICALLY.
EVERYONE FINDS ME
PHYSICALLY ATTRACTIVE.
I MEAN MAGNETICALLY.
ARE YOU GETTING
ENOUGH SLEEP, HAP?
NOT REALLY.
I THINK IT GOES BACK TO
WHEN I WAS IN THE WAR.
KOREAN.
THE Moo Goo Guy Pan DELTA.
BUNCH OF US GUYS WERE
HORSING AROUND,
TRYING TO KILL
THE BOREDOM.
I PUT ON MY HELMET,
NOT KNOWING THERE WAS
A LIVE GRENADE INSIDE IT.
THEN IT WENT OFF.
THAT WOULD BE PRETTY
LOUD, I WOULD THINK.
CAVED IN THE WHOLE
LEFT SIDE OF MY HEAD.
WE WERE MILES AWAY FROM
THE NEAREST HOSPITAL,
SO THEY TOOK ME TO
THE NEAREST RESTAURANT,
WHERE THEY HAD A CHEF PUT
A METAL PLATE IN MY HEAD.
A REAL METAL PLATE.
IT WAS HANGING
ABOVE THE STOVE.
I THINK, ACTUALLY,
IT WAS A STRAINER.
YEAH, I WISH I HAD
ONE OF THOSE RIGHT NOW.
SOMEHOW, OVER THE YEARS,
I THINK THAT
METAL PLATE IN MY HEAD
HAS BECOME MAGNETIZED.
HAP, I DON'T THINK
THAT'S POSSIBLE.
EVEN IN YOUR WORLD.
THAT SO?
YOU THINK THAT'S
MAGNETISM HOLDING
THAT ON?
YES, I DO.
HAP, THAT'S AN
ALUMINUM POP CAN.
ALUMINUM'S
NOT MAGNETIC.
IT'S A DIFFERENT
KIND OF MAGNETISM.
YEAH,
I'M SURE IT IS.
I BELIEVE IT'S
CALLED GUM.
TAKE A LOOK.
I CAN'T LOOK
AT IT, RED.
WHY NOT?
MY HEAD ONLY
POINTS NORTH.
THIS WEEK ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO GIVE
YOU YOUNG PEOPLE
A HISTORY LESSON
AND A LIFE LESSON;
UNLESS YOU HAVE STAPLED SO
MUCH JEWELLERY TO YOUR HEAD
THAT YOU CAN'T HOLD IT
HIGH ENOUGH TO SEE THE TV.
THIS UNIT HERE IS AN OLD,
WRINGER-WASHER CLOTHES
WASHING MACHINE.
TECHNOLOGY HASN'T REALLY
CHANGED ALL THAT MUCH.
STILL GOT AN
AGITATOR IN THERE,
YOU PUT YOUR DETERGENT,
YOUR WATER, AND YOUR CLOTHES --.
I GOT A REAL GOOD
FEELING ABOUT THIS.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
TO EMPTY THE MACHINE OUT,
WHAT YOU WOULD DO IS
TAKE THIS HOSE AND HOOK
IT ONTO YOUR LAUNDRY TUB,
AND THEN YOU PUSH
THIS KNOB HERE.
WHOA.
MAN.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
THIS IS WHERE IT
GETS REAL INTERESTING.
TO SQUEEZE THE WATER
OUT OF THE CLOTHES,
THAT'S WHERE THE
WRINGER COMES IN.
YOU WOULD JUST FEED THE
CLOTHES THROUGH THE WRINGER,
AND YOU WOULD GET
ENOUGH WATER OUT,
YOU COULD THEN HANG
THEM OUT ON THE LINE TO DRY.
THE DANGER WAS THAT YOU LEAN IN
SO CLOSE TO THE RINGER,
YOU MIGHT GET YOUR TIE
OR YOUR NOSE HAIRS
CAUGHT IN THERE.
SO TECHNOLOGY MOVED ON.
NOW MY WIFE WANTS ME TO
THROW THIS OLD THING OUT.
BUT IF SHE HAD HER WAY,
WE ALSO WOULD'VE THROWN OUT
THOSE OLD OIL DRUMS SITTIN'
ON THE BACK PORCH.
THEN WHERE WOULD WE BE
WHEN WE NEEDED
AN OLD OIL DRUM?
THAT'S WHERE THE
LIFE LESSON COMES IN.
RECYCLE.
GET CREATIVE.
BREAK NEW GROUND.
USE YOUR NOGGIN TO FIND A
NEW WAY TO USE AN OLD THING.
YOU MARRIED GUYS KNOW
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
I'M GOING TO USE THE
AGITATOR TO MIX UP THE
OLD CANS OF PAINT.
AND THE COLOUR
DOESN'T REALLY MATTER.
WE'RE ONLY PAINTING THE
FENCE, FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
AND YOU SEE WHAT
I'VE DONE HERE?
I MOUNTED THESE
SHOWER HEADS
THE SAME DISTANCE APART
AS THE FENCE BOARDS.
SEE, THEN WHEN I PUSH IN THE
KNOB TO DRAIN THE MACHINE,
THE PAINTS GOING TO SPRAY
OUT THESE SHOWER NOZZLES.
SEE WHAT I'VE DONE?
I'VE TURNED A USELESS
OLD WRINGER-WASHER,
INTO A FENCE PAINTER
THAT DOESN'T USE A BRUSH
AND ALMOST NEVER
NEEDS PAINT.
NOW, HERE'S A BONUS.
IF YOU TIE A PIECE OF ROPE TO
THE OTHER END OF THE FENCE,
AND YOU RUN IT THROUGH
THE RINGER LIKE THAT.
THE WHOLE UNIT
BECOMES SELF PROPELLED.
SO REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I WANT TO TALK
TO YOU OLDER GUYS
WHO AT ONE TIME OR
ANOTHER MAY HAVE SAID,
YOU KNOW, I FORGOT WHAT
I WAS GOING TO SAY.
YOU MAY THINK THAT'S
SENILITY, BUT IT IS NOT.
IT IS VERY GOOD HEALTH.
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE GOT A
FEW STORIES YOU'VE TOLD
A TIME OR TWO OVER --
YOU KNOW THE KIND
OF STORIES I MEAN.
NO, NO, NOT THAT KIND.
I MEAN THE KIND THAT --.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE KIND
YOU WOULD TELL YOUR WIFE.
YOU KNOW WHEN YOU --
YOU JUST GET STARTED
INTO THE STORY,
AND YOU LOOK AT YOUR FRIENDS,
AND THEY'RE LOOKING AT
THEIR WATCH, EH.
AND THEN THEY START CHECKING
THAT THEIR WATCH IS WORKING.
AND THEY START USING THEIR WATCH
TO CHECK THEIR OWN PULSE.
YOU GLANCE OVER TO YOUR
WIFE FOR SOME SUPPORT,
AND SHE'S STARRING AT YOU
LIKE YOU'RE THE SOURCE OF
THE BAD SMELL IN THE FRIDGE.
THESE PEOPLE
AREN'T FEELING WELL.
THEY HAVE A DISEASE
CALLED BOREDOM,
AND AT THAT MOMENT,
YOU ARE THE CARRIER.
YOU ARE THE TYPHOID MARY OF
MONOTONY, I'LL TELL YOU.
AND I'LL TELL YOU THE
MOST DANGEROUS THING,
YOU RUN THE RISK OF
BORING YOURSELF TO DEATH.
YOU'RE SUBCONSCIOUS
KNOWS THAT, SEE.
SO WHAT IT DOES IS
YOU GET INTO ONE
OF THOSE STORIES,
IT RAISES THE DRAW BRIDGE
BETWEEN THAT STORY,
AND YOUR MOUTH.
SHUTS THE WHOLE THING DOWN,
JUST LIKE THE TEAMSTERS.
AND IF YOU NEED
SOME PROOF,
NEXT TIME YOU BLURT OUT,
"I FORGOT WHAT I
WAS GOING TO SAY,"
JUST LOOK AT THE LOOKS
OF JOY AND RELIEF
ON THE FACES OF
YOUR FRIENDS AND FAMILY,
AND IN THE DEEP RECESSES
OF YOUR OWN MIND.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WELL, FORGOT WHAT I
WAS GONNA SAY.
EVERYBODY THESE DAYS WANTS AN
INTERLOCKING BRICK DRIVEWAY.
SETS THE PLACE
OFF REAL NICE.
AND IT DOESN'T
JUST SAY MONEY,
IT SAYS INTERLOCKING MONEY.
SO HERE'S A CHEAP WAY TO HAVE
YOURSELF AN INTERLOCKING
BRICK DRIVEWAY.
BEFORE YOU
POUR YOUR CEMENT,
YOU LAY DOWN A TIGHT GRIDWORK OF
PRIMER CORD INSIDE THE AREA.
I WOULD RECOMMEND NOT SMOKING
WHILE YOU'RE DOING THIS.
YOU WILL BE SMOKING LONG
AFTER YOU ARE DONE.
AND THEN,
YOU JUST SPREAD IT
SMOOTHLY OVER THE GRID.
YOU KNOW, WE HAVE A SAYING
IN THE DEMOLITIONS BUSINESS,
WHAT DOESN'T KILL ME,
MAKES ME HARD OF HEARING.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN WE
HAVE NO COMMON SENSE.
MAYBE WE BETTER TAKE COVER
BEHIND THIS PROTECTIVE BARRIER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ SOUND OF FIRE EXTINGUISHER ]
OKAY, UM --
WELL, WE'RE GETTING THERE,
YOU KNOW, UH --
ACTUALLY, WHEN WE WELDED THE
STORM DOORS ONTO THE FLOOR
OF THE SCHOOL BUS,
WE FORGOT TO ALLOW
FOR THE FLAMMABILITY
OF ALL THE STUFF THE KIDS
HAVE DROPPED UNDER THE SEATS
OVER THE LAST 30 YEARS.
THERE WAS LUNCH BAGS,
EXPLODING PENS,
PORTABLE NUCLEAR DEVICES.
IT WAS A MESS --
OKAY, Mr. GREEN,
IT'S STILL SMOKIN',
BUT THE REALLY BAD SMELL IS
STARTING TO DIE DOWN NOW.
YOU KNOW, RED, I THINK YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO GIVE THIS WHOLE
BOAT THING A RE-THINK.
I'M WAY PAST
THE BOAT IDEA.
NOW, DID YOU GUYS
NOTICE WHAT HAPPENED,
WHEN THE FLOOR CAUGHT
ON FIRE IN THE BUS?
YEAH, YOU MEAN THE WAY THE FIRE
DEPARTMENT REFUSED TO COME?
NO, NO, NO.
I MEAN, DID YOU
NOTICE THE WHOLE BUS
KINDA ROSE UP
A LITTLE BIT.
NO.
YOU KNOW, IT WAS OKAY FOR
YOU TO SMELL THE SMOKE.
I JUST DON'T THINK YOU
SHOULD HAVE INHALED.
NO, ALL THE HOT AIR,
ALL THE HOT GASES
TRAPPED INSIDE
THE ROOF.
HOT AIR RISES, THAT'S WHY
THEY HAVE HOT AIR BALLOONS.
AND, OF COURSE,
THE SCHOOL BUS IS
MADE OUT OF ALUMINUM.
SHE'S GOT NO ENGINE,
NO TRANSMISSION,
SO SHE'S KINDA LIGHT,
AND UP SHE COMES.
SEE WHERE I'M
GOING WITH THIS?
YEAH, THE PRISON HOSPITAL.
NO, NO, IF WE CAN
LIGHTEN THE SCHOOL
BUS EVEN MORE,
TAKE THE WHEELS OFF,
TAKE THE BUMPERS OFF,
START A FIRE INSIDE,
HEY,
WHAT DO WE HAVE?
A GREAT BIG
ALUMINUM HOT THING?
NO, NO.
NO, NO!
WE'LL HAVE AN ORANGE
ALUMINUM AIR SHIP.
IT'LL BE LIKE
THE GOODYEAR BLIMP,
BUT IT WILL
BE A SCHOOL BUS.
IS THAT GOOD?
WELL, YEAH!
'CAUSE WE'LL HAVE
ALL THOSE SEATS.
WE CAN ALL RIDE
AROUND IN THERE.
WE CAN CONTROL THE
ALTITUDE BY HOW HOT
WE MAKE THE FIRE.
YOU KNOW, I'M JUST TRYIN'
TO FIGURE OUT, UM --
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH THIS IDEA.
OH, YEAH.
I REMEMBER NOW.
WE'LL ALL BE KILLED!
NO, I'LL TELL
YOU WHAT WE'LL DO.
WE'LL JUST FLOAT
AROUND, MAYBE A FEW
FEET ABOVE THE GROUND,
JUST TO BE SURE
WE'RE SAFE.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT OTHER
AIRCRAFT BUMPING INTO US?
THAT WOULD
BE INCONVENIENT.
IT'S A SCHOOL BUS!
WHEN WE SEE 'EM COMING,
WE'LL JUST FLICK ON
THE FLASHING LIGHTS.
THEY'LL HAVE TO STOP.
Red:
SO WE'RE GONNA PLAY GOLF.
JUST WAITIN' FOR MIKE.
OH, BOY.
OKAY, WE'RE ALL
SET TO TEE UP.
I GOT ALL OF THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, GIVE ME FIVE.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
GIVE 'ER A GO.
HE'S LITTLE, BUT HE'S GOT
QUITE AN UNUSUAL SWING.
I THINK HE PICKED
IT UP IN PRISON.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
GIVE --
OH, THERE WE GO.
OKAY, GIVE 'ER A GO.
WE DON'T COUNT THAT.
THERE IT GOES.
OH, OH, OH!
OH, THAT'S A SH --
NO, GOOD.
IT WAS GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S THE TANDEM PAIRS.
DON'T SEE THIS TOO OFTEN.
WE WERE PLAYIN'
A LITTLE SLOW, SO --
A COUPLE OF BEAUTIES!
COUPLE OF BEAUTIES.
I THINK ONE OF THEM
ACTUALLY OUTDROVE ME.
SO WE PICK UP OUR GEAR.
MIKE'S GONNA GO IN THE CART.
NO, THIS WAY, MIKE.
THIS WAY.
SO WE'RE GONNA WALK DOWN TO OU
DRIVES FOR OUR SECOND SHOT.
WHO'S AWAY?
WHO'S AWAY.
MIKE GOES TO GET HIS BALL.
MIKE THAT'S NOT --
THAT'S NOT --
NOT REALLY IN THE RULE --
NOT REALLY --
HI, MIKE!
YES, THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
SO NOW WE GOT
A LITTLE THING GOING.
THIS IS OUR APPROACH SHOT
INTO THE GREEN.
WINSTON'S THE FIRST ONE UP,
AND HE HITS
A REAL NICE SHOT HERE.
NOW HE'S ONE OF THOSE GUYS
HITS ONE GOOD SHOT,
AND LOOK AT THAT, EH.
NOW HE'S ALL Mr. BIG.
HE DIGS OUT HIS WALLET,
AND HE SAYS,
"HEY, GUYS, I GOT 10 BUCKS SAY
THAT'S CLOSEST TO THE PIN."
OH, FELLA BACK THERE
CUTTIN' THE LAWN.
TEN BUCKS, OKAY.
YEAH, WE GOT IT.
BIG DEAL.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, I'M IN.
I'M ALWAYS IN.
MIKE'S GOT A PRETTY GOOD
WAD OF CASH THERE.
MUST'VE BEEN PAYDAY.
OH!
YEAH, DALTON'S WALLET HASN'T
BEEN OPENED IN A WHILE.
BUT GOOD TO SEE HE'S
IN FOR THE TEN.
ALL RIGHT, WHO'S UP?
WHO'S UP NEXT?
I DON'T WANNA GO RIGHT NOW.
SOMEONE ELSE GO.
MIKE, YOU GO.
GIVE 'ER A GO.
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
THAT'S A NICE ONE.
OKAY!
WINSTON'S OUTTA THE MONEY.
THAT'S GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, DALTON.
OH, MAN.
HOLY SMOKES.
ALL RIGHT, DALTON.
LOOSEN UP THAT SWING.
LET 'ER RIP.
OH, HEY.
NOT BAD.
OH, BOY, THIS IS
GONNA BE TOUGH.
THIS IS GONNA BE TOUGH.
ALL RIGHT, I GOTTA REALLY
THINK ABOUT THIS ONE.
OH, OH, STRAIGHT UP.
SKIED IT.
LOOK OUT, GUYS.
LOOK OUT.
GET AWAY FROM
THE MONEY, DALTON.
INCOMING!
LOOK OUT!
OH, BOY.
OH, OH, OH.
WHAT'S HE DOING?
OH, LOOK OUT.
OH.
ALL RIGHT!
THERE WE GO.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW, SPENDING
QUALITY TIME WITH
THE YOUNGSTER
DOESN'T MEAN YOU ALWAYS
HAVE TO BE RISKING LIVES AND
DESTROYING THE ENVIRONMENT.
TEACH THEM SOME
GENTLE SKILLS,
LIKE HOW TO BUILD
AND FLY A KITE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS KITE'S GONNA
GO A MILE HIGH.
YEAH, YOU'LL SEE.
YOU KNOW, I REMEMBER
WATCHIN' MY DAD BUILD KITES.
THAT WAS SOMETHING.
I GUESS THAT'S WHERE
I LEARNED MOST OF
MY SWEAR WORDS.
THAT WAY,
DAD'S ALWAYS WITH ME,
INSTEAD OF IN A
CONDO IN FLORIDA.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE GONNA
REMEMBER THIS DAY
FOR A LONG,
LONG, LONG TIME.
YOU SEE, IT'S NOT WHAT
YOU DO WITH THE CHILD --
AH! AH!
WE DON'T NEED THAT.
THAT'S OKAY.
THERE YOU GO.
THAT'LL STILL FLY.
GO ON, NOW.
NOT GONNA FLY
IF YOU JUST STAND THERE.
YOU GOTTA RUN!
GO ON, RUN!
MOVE, MOVE, MOVE!
THERE HE GOES.
WHAT A LITTLE GUY, HUH?
SOME DAY HE'LL HAVE
A BOY OF HIS OWN,
AND HE'LL TAKE HIM
OUT KITE FLYING,
AND HE'LL REMEMBER
THIS DAY.
GO ON.
YOU'RE RUNNIN' LIKE A GIRL.
RUN!
[ BELL RINGING ]
OH,
THE HUMANITY!
WE WERE SO CLOSE.
SO CLOSE.
MIND YOU, WE'RE NOT
BLAMING ANYBODY.
NO, IF GOD HAD MEANT
FOR MAN TO FLY,
HE WOULD NEVER HAVE
GIVEN US SCHOOL BUSES.
WE HAD 17 BARBECUES
HOOKED UP TO
THE FRAME.
WE HAD THEM RUNNIN'
REAL GOOD,
REALLY PUMPIN' THE
HEAT OUTTA THERE.
AND AFTER THE FIRST HOUR,
WE HAD LIFT-OFF.
YOU KNOW, IT WAS KINDA SPOOKY
WHEN WE CLEARED THE TREES.
SCARED THE HECK OUTTA
OLD MAN SEDGWICK,
DIDN'T IT?
SURE DID.
YOU KNOW, WHEN WE BUZZED
OVER HIM, HE THOUGHT WE
WERE A BUNCH OF ALIENS.
HE YELLED UP,
"YOU F.O.!"
YEAH,
THAT WAS AMAZING.
NOBODY'S BEEN UP THAT HIGH IN A
SCHOOL BUS SINCE THE '60s.
WE HAD ALL THE HOT AIR
TRAPPED INSIDE THE BUS.
IF WE WANTED TO
ADJUST THE HEIGHT,
WE JUST TURNED UP
THE OLD BARBECUES.
BOY, WE COULD'VE FLOATED
LIKE THAT FOREVER,
BUT, LIKE I SAY,
WE'RE NOT
BLAMING ANYBODY.
OKAY, LOOK.
I'M SORRY, OKAY.
I'M SORRY.
IT WAS INSTINCT, YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, I SAW THE RAILROAD
CROSSING COMING UP --
WE'RE IN A SCHOOL BUS.
I JUST HIT THE BRAKES
AND OPENED THE DOOR.
WE DROPPED
LIKE A STONE.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETIN' TIME.
YEAH,
YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
SAVE ME
A SEAT, MIKE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I THOUGHT WE COULD PLAY
A LITTLE GAME TONIGHT,
I'LL SHOW YOU SOME BRUISES,
AND YOU GUESS HOW I GOT 'EM.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHIN'.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
Closed Captioning performed
by INTERCAPTION CANADA
www.intercaption.com
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, NOW.
SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, EVERYBODY.
EVERYONE TAKE A SEAT.
EVERYONE GET THEMSELVES --
ALL RISE!
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
BOW YOUR HEADS FOR
THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
FIRST ORDER OF BUSINESS.
WE NEED A SHOW OF HANDS
OF GUYS WHO ARE WILLING
TO DRIVE THE KIDS TO SCHOOL.
OKAY, WELL, THAT MEANS YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO STAY HOME
AND LOOK AFTER THEM ALL DAY.
OKAY.
KEEP 'EM UP.