We invite you and yours to join us and ours
for the next 30 minutes on the Red Green
Show. You know, time is money and this is
only half an hour, but it seems a lot longer,
you know, so it's really a bargain.
And I love doing this show.
I couldn't do it without my uncle and well,
because he's the head honcho around here.
Well, that is until, of course, he realizes
that he's actually passed it, and that's the
day that I get to take over.
Oh, but until that time, here is the head
honcho, the big guy with the twinkle in his
eye and then the twilight of his career.
The current host of the red green show, Mr.
Red Green.
Thank you, Harold. Thank you.
Welcome to Possum Lodge.
That intro made me feel 20 years younger.
Well, I'm glad to hear that you feel 50
again.
You need me around here because without me,
you couldn't do this.
And if I could, I wouldn't herald something
going on with Bob Stevenson this week, I
realize he's real excited about something or
other.
Well, maybe it's his job, you know, he works
for national resources.
Well, what could be exciting about that here
other than the government pension?
Well, maybe, just maybe he's like, created
some new oversized vegetable.
No, Harold, but I think your parents may
have.
Why are you being so cruel to me, what did I
ever
Do to you?
Well, that introduction comes to mind.
Fair enough.
Now there's only two things that excite a man
expensive toys and real expensive toys.
That was Bob. I'd say this toy has something
to do with golf since he happens to be a golf
like a maniac.
You think you think maybe like you bought
like a golf course?
Well, if he did, Harold, I'm going to go work
for natural resources.
Oh, yeah, right?
Too expensive, isn't it?
Yeah. Well, maybe he bought a golf ball.
You know it was orange ones with the huge
dimples on.
It could be like that or designer tease.
Maybe we got designer tees. They make
designer tees.
They made designer tees. He probably got
those or megaphone.
Maybe he got a megaphone, but then he could
just yell for really loud for.
If you got like. But, yeah, OK.
All right. How is he going to hold a
megaphone and his clubs?
Yeah. You know what it could be like a
customized, hat mounted mini megaphone and it
automatically
Dispenses keys right into the ground.
Back, back, back, back, back, back.
What it owes. That's what it got.
That's so great.
Harold, maybe you should just go right into
the next segment, you know, there's already
too much violence on television.
Ok? You picked up on that and you kept things
moving and everything that's good, you know,
shows you mellowed. Shut up, Harold.
You slip back a little bit there, though.
Hey, Bob, that new set of gloves came in
today.
I brought them over.
Oh, that's great news, Marie.
This might be the set that helps me break
par or even break a hundred.
You've never broken a hundred.
Well, not on nine consecutive holes.
No.
Ok, bring them in, Dwayne.
Oh, great. All right, that'll be two hundred
plus tax.
And then they're shipping and handling
delivery charges from the store over to here.
Let's just call that an even four hundred,
huh?
All right. Will you take a check?
Hmm. Oh, it's a government check.
I'm buying these for the Department of
Natural Resources.
I use them at work, you know, for checking
out nature and stuff.
Cash. Fine.
Well, I'm going to need a receipt.
Oh, all right. Yeah, yeah.
Come on. Great.
Oh, I love the smell of new clubs.
It smells like victory.
Yeah. All right. Look, your receipt is in the
pocket with the TS.
Ok? Happy hacking!
All right. Go, Duane.
Thanks, Mary. Wait a minute.
Well, these are all woods.
So where are the irons?
Who needs irons?
Oh, trust me, these clubs are going to bring
your score right down.
Well, good kid golf was all drivers I've
ever tried golfing with just drivers.
No. Huh? Well, have you ever played a good
game of golf?
No. Well, then what do you know?
Huh? Come on, just try it out one round,
huh?
Well, look at this. They're old, they're old
drivers.
I mean, there's no irons.
There's not even a putter. Oh, there's a
putter in here.
Oh, Dwayne, you let the putter in the back
of the truck.
Oh, sorry. Mm-hmm.
Get just another set of golf clubs, did you,
bob?
Yeah. Murray is selling me these miracle
clubs.
They're supposed to reduce my score by half
or even to par.
Oh, that was the money back guarantee.
Oh, really? You actually guaranteeing
something yourself, Murray?
Well, why not? You know, if it doesn't work
out, I'll take them back.
If it does, I've unloaded a set of left
handed clubs.
What? Left what are all left, I got right
handed, Marie.
Well, just try it once.
Go backwards.
How can I do this and expect a half decent
score?
Have you ever gone backwards?
No. Have you ever had a half decent score?
No, Dwight.
Guess I'll try them. Tried just about
everything else.
We're possibly go wrong.
I guess so.
That's great. So what?
So yeah, you saw your take two hundred
strokes in nine holes, huh?
Yeah. Well, at least it's a step in the right
direction.
All right. I'll give them a try again when
no one else is around.
I don't know. Might be just crazy enough to
do the trick.
Here's the putter.
Oh boy. They say on the river
A long time ago,
The paddle wheelers would come steaming to
and fro.
They wave and they'd whistle as they had it
from the locks, and they plow over a bunch of
swimmers and wipe out all the docks.
They leave arms and legs and deck chairs in
their wake.
But that much polluting the wonder the dams
in the lake.
Long time ago.
And the rivers in the wind and the paddle
wheelers and come.
This week in the handymen corner, we're
going to show you how you can make your own
cheap transportation.
You know what, with the price of the car is
getting up there where it's, I believe, well
over $500 now and even a motorcycle is going
to cost you ninety eight.
So I say, why not do what the handyman does?
Build yourself a moped?
I picked up this bike for about five bucks
now at the police auction, but that's too
much for you. You can get one for free over
at the public schools during nap time or, as
they call it, history class.
All you need is some extra chain, a couple
of rolls of handyman, secret weapon duct tape
and something to use as a motor to use a
chainsaw.
But you couldn't use an outboard motor or
you don't care about going real slow.
You can use one of them garage door openers.
Ok, now first step is you've got to get the
pedals and the chain.
Oh boy,
Off the hook.
Well, OK, now there's a there's a trick to
this.
Yeah, I don't think that's the trick.
I know there might have been some kind of a
wrench or something to use on this.
Oh no.
Now.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. No.
It's going to have a lot of miles out with
Hammond down.
All right, don't try us on that off with a
hacksaw.
You know, just ruin a perfectly good hacksaw
blade.
Harold had the right wrench in his bike,
kept us safe these pedals because next week
we're going to show you how to make a foot
powered egg slicer.
All right. The next step is to get the chain
off the.
Now you'll find there's a there's one
special link on the chain.
It just comes apart and you can you can try
that open or you can cut it off with snips or
if you have a heavy vehicle at all, just
back right over the next thing.
Ok, no. The engine right onto the bike.
Now I was going to bolt this onto the frame
of the bike, but I'm not sure how that would
work, and at this point, I have no idea what
I was thinking of.
So I think what I'll do is I'll use a few
key clamps and a little bit more of the handy
man's secret weapon duct tape.
And when you put it on, make sure you snug
her up.
Real good. You don't want this thing
whipping off between your legs 50 miles an
hour. Or maybe you do.
You know, duct tape is great stuff, isn't
it?
You can build a house with this stuff.
Just make sure you smoother down good.
Nothing says poor craftsman like lumpy tape
another.
In other words, you want to put a little bit
of slack in the chain, but not too much
because you don't want that chain flopping
around, lapping into whatever you got
flopping around. And it's a real eye catcher
as Nick.
Imagine driving through the park in this.
They're going to see you. Now let's get
real.
Go.
There you have nothing to it.
Nothing.
I got nothing I forgot to tell you to be
sitting on the bike.
When I started anyway.
Remember the next time the women don't find
you handsome, they should at least find your
handy. Oh my golly, the Texas moped
massacre.
It is winter. I shoveled my driveway, a snow
plow passes.
The driver smiles, a wintry smile and waves
a hand as he fills my driveway with snow
again. I went back with my finger.
I read them
On the car, have you?
Of course, yeah. Oh, yes, of course.
Yeah, I went out for a quick 18.
How's your new left handed woodworker?
Oh, well, better than I expected.
You know, ask me how much better?
All right. How much better?
Six under par.
Oh no.
Oh, 18 holes.
Sixty six strokes.
Oh, wow.
Could you manage that?
Well, two birdies, an eagle and a hole in one
on the fifth on the dog leg.
On the dog leg.
No one has ever done that on the course.
No one. Oh, I was great.
That was great. Which will see me one stroke
bang right under the green.
I sank a 20 foot putt with a, you know, a
goalie stick, a 12 hole.
I had 40 guys following me around and
applauding, applauding me.
An eagle. Can you believe this?
Oh man. Oh man, oh man.
That's great. Congratulations.
Oh, those are some miracle clubs there, Bob.
Well, it's not just the clubs red.
It was magic serendipity.
It was the greatest day of my life.
Oh, you'll never have another game like that
again.
I know. I know this was the greatest day of
my life.
You know, I could play golf for another
hundred years and never have a game like that
again, ever.
I mean, this was the greatest day of my
life.
This was it. It happened from now on.
It's all.
It's all downhill. I'll never play a game
like that ever again.
I did it. I had a dream and.
No, it's over.
I have nothing left to live for, do I?
Oh, sure you do. I'm sure you do.
Well, how can you be six under par seven
under par?
So there seven under par.
I used to take seven strokes just for one
haul.
I mean, I may improve just a bit more, but
never like I did today.
Don't fall over.
What am I going to do now?
Well, you can
Grab your putter and take up hockey.
Well, this week on Adventures with Bill and
Bill said he wanted to do some fishing as I
think the fishing line down, but he had he
had something else totally in mind.
I've never seen one of these.
I heard about them. It's a kind of a rig
that you don't need a boat to go fishing.
You put these, you put these big, huge.
They don't call them flippers, but they look
like flippers.
But if they call them flippers, they
couldn't charge as much.
Put them on your feet and then you put the
rig in there and you just showing that they
go on. Just like I say, not going quite as
easy as flippers, but they come off a lot
easier. Anyway, he's going to have one
engine instead of two, I guess.
And what you do is almost like a diaper
thing.
You step into the rig and it's basically a
portable fishing boat.
Kind of well.
Oh boy, you don't want to be a fish looking
up at that point.
Oh, OK.
Well, we know where we're going with this,
don't we?
Yeah. And he lost his tube, and it's called
a float tube.
That's why I say that last night at this
time, Glenn, from the ladder, maybe a little
bit lower and get the one foot in there and
then try to get the other to the other foot
in there, too. Now that's only one.
That's just. Oh, it's amazing you still want
to go fishing, Anthony.
Now he's going to just put it on on the dock
and then just jump in, but the flipper and
hook and between the boards, he didn't
notice that and I tried to point it out to
him. But he just. You know, you pay for not
listening.
Anyway, he finally got into it there and
then you wanted some help because you had to,
you know, something handy around the dock
like a boat hook is such a handy thing you
never know what you're going to use it for.
Now what I want to do is I had them all
because there's compartments in the float
tube. You can put your tackle box in there
and your thermos and a flashlight because you
don't know how long is going to be out
there.
And the bait, I just kind of threw in there
and I thought.
Keep them awake, you know?
And the fishing rod, and he's ready to rip
us a little apron on the front goes right up,
keep everything dry and even what's with the
ones that he could get out to where he wanted
to fish and look, I'm there.
So I thought I'd just take the boat out and
kind of go boat and join them, you know?
And it looked like kind of fun.
But I had brought my fishing line, as I
said, if he got it.
What do you do with a real big one anyway?
Do you want me? Oh, come on over.
But you know, by golly, when you get the you
get the nine point nine open up there, it
kind of raises the boat a certain extent.
And she wasn't running real good.
She was seemed to me she was running rich,
and I'm trying to adjust the mixture on that
because you run the rate, you're going to
bring a lot of gas and harness.
Oh, the thing was, I never I never did see
Bill, I went way up the link.
I hope he's OK. I don't.
Well, Buster Hatfield and I went down to the
store to ask Murray about the stolen clubs.
Of course, Murray had denied everything
before we'd even asked.
Duane nodded a lot and then he sold Buster,
a fishing hat that he'd made out of a guitar.
Mr has trouble finding hats, but that small
round head of his fit perfectly into the
sound hole had that kind of home straight
out here and three strings under each year.
He looked like somebody who'd stood too
close to the stage during a Pete Townsend
guitar solo on the way back to the lodge he
was.
He was doing bar cards with his comb, and
then he got caught in a cross wind that
produced about the loudest e minor seventh
I've ever heard.
Oh, uncle ran, excuse me.
But this has very little or nothing actually
to do with Bob's midlife crisis and his golf
clubs. I think your mind is kind of
wandering there.
Well, my mind may wander Harold, but at least
it gets out once in a while.
Ok, so where was I?
Oh yeah. The tuning pegs kind of shot up
Buster's nose there,
But they by a possum.
It's mating time.
Come on, let's get downstairs.
See what's going on.
Yeah, OK, well, I'll just go head down to the
lodge meeting here, and we're going to try
and find a new hobby for Bob.
I wonder if he'd like Harold's job?
Excuse me, a minute. Great.
Great. Great.
Great. Yes.
Yeah. All right.
One. It's.
Now, but all members please remove their
hats.
Thank you, Mr Floor recognizes Noel
Christmas
Bakery, right?
I've got proof that Bob's new clubs are hot.
Oh, well, I know.
I'm sorry, Bob, I couldn't have known that.
Remember? Caveat emptor.
Well, I don't care.
Oh, Bob, I'm going to have to impound those
as evidence.
Take them down to the station.
Sorry. Oh, wait there.
Well, I want my money back, though, Murray.
Oh, sorry, no, can do.
Bob, the goods have been confiscated.
You see one more point.
Bob Murray drink.
You're all under arrest for dealing in
stolen goods.
Oh. What are you accusing us of knowingly
dealing with stolen goods?
No, no, wait a minute. I didn't even know
that they were stolen.
Yeah, he wasn't even there when the guy who
swiped them came to the store.
I mean, we don't know any.
We don't know anything. All right, Bob.
You can go free. Go on.
Murray, Duane, you're under arrest.
We didn't know they were stolen.
Now this guy just came into the store.
He said he was going to become a missionary
and work in Africa, and he wanted to sell off
his collection of left handed clubs to
finance his missionary work well and buy a
new hat. He went to Africa.
Yeah, he got a missionary position.
You got any proof, huh?
I mean, can anybody here corroborate this
story?
Well, I think a refund might refresh my
memory memory.
Oh, well, how about a half a refund and a
game of golf with a debit brain here?
Well, Noel, I was there.
It's all true. This guy was going to Africa
to convert heathens and stuff like that, and
and Marie bought his clubs just to help him
out.
That's your story.
Well, it is at this point.
Yeah, I'll be watching.
All right. We'll be watching you.
Oh, no. Oh.
Well, there's no other large business, and I
call on Bob here to give us some evening's
entertainment, I got a new kind of a new
lease on life right now.
Well, thank you very much, Richard.
Well, I guess I'm a man with a purpose
again.
No, I realized that it was those clubs.
I mean, anyone could get a six under par
score with those clubs.
Well, I think everybody learned a little
something tonight, and the beauty of it is
it'll be totally lost on them by tomorrow
morning.
I'll go back to being Bob Murray.
I'll go back to being Murray.
Harold, go back to me and Harold, but I'll
fix them.
I'll go back to being me anyway.
If my wife is watching, I'll be coming
straight home after the meeting tonight and
Buster Hadfield is going to serenade us
outside the bedroom window with his hat.
So be sure and have a few potted plants
ready.
So until next time, on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole gang up here at Possum
Lodge. Keep your stick on the ice.
It's right at the
First hole I stepped up to the tee first aid,
but I hit this ball and I just felt at that
moment that this was not going to be a
regular golf game.
So when I had the ball down there, I and I
could feel that the energy coming from the
ball going right up my club joy.
But I pulled back because I felt like I was
even playing golf at all.
It was more like I was, Oh, I don't know,
flying or something.
It just seems a little bit more natural to
me.
Anyway, that ball that just took off.
It was hard, perfectly perpendicular to my
body part, right?