THAT I ENJOY
A GAME OF GOLF.
I THINK IT'S THE
IDEA OF BEING OUTDOORS
WITH LOTS OF
WIDE OPEN SPACES
AND A BAG FULL OF
ASSORTED WEAPONS.
AND WHEN IT'S FINALLY SPRING
AFTER A LONG COLD WINTER,
THE ITCH IS
PRETTY UNBEARABLE.
AND THE SAME
THING WITH GOLF.
BUT OF COURSE MANY OF US
WHO HAVE CHOSEN MARITAL BLISS
AS AN ALTERNATE LIFESTYLE
ARE NOT FREE TO GO GOLFING
UNTIL THE YARD IS
CLEANED UP
OF ALL THE WINTER
FLOTSAM AND JETSAM.
MEANWHILE MY NEIGHBOUR,
WHO OWNS THE PROPERTY ON
THE OTHER SIDE OF THAT FENCE
AND IS A LESS SENSITIVE, MORE
CHAUVINISTIC KIND OF A GUY,
HAS ALREADY TEED OFF,
IN, OH, SO MANY WAYS.
HERE'S WHAT I DO.
BEFORE WINTER CAME I TIED
THIS TARP TO THAT SAME FENCE
AND I LAID THE TARP OVER
MY YARD TO CATCH ALL
THE WINTER CRAP.
THEN I TIED THIS EDGE UP
TO AN OLD WORK SOCK HERE.
ALL I GOTTA DO IS
DROP A GOLF BALL DOWN
INSIDE THE SOCK,
GET HER ALL THE
WAY DOWN TO THE TOE.
AND THEN I JUST
TEE HER UP NICE,
AND SUDDENLY MY ROUGH BECOMES
MY NEIGHBOUR'S FAIRWAY.
FORE!
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WELL, I APPRECIATE THAT.
KIND OF A DISTURBING WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
WE'VE GOT A BIT OF A
CRIME WAVE GOING ON UP HERE.
PETTY THEFT. ODDBALL STUFF.
ALL OF JUNIOR SINGLETON'S
LAWN ORNAMENTS WERE STOLEN.
HE'S GOT A BIG COLLECTION OF
THOSE FAT PEOPLE BENT OVER.
IT'S A REAL LANDMARK UP HERE.
SO NOW JUNIOR AND HIS WIFE
HAD TO SPEND THE WHOLE DAY
BENT OVER ON THEIR FRONT LAWN
JUST SO PEOPLE CAN FIND
THEIR WAY AROUND.
MR. GREEN,
WE'RE GETTING A
GIFT FOR DALTON,
AND I WAS WONDERING IF YOU'D
BE WILLING TO CHIP IN?
WELL, WHAT'S THE GIFT?
WHAT'S THE GIFT FOR?
AND HOW MUCH IS
IT GONNA COST ME?
ANSWER THE
LAST ONE FIRST.
FIVE BUCKS.
ALL RIGHT,
GO ON.
OKAY, WELL, DALTON'S GOT,
LIKE, A BIG BIRTHDAY
COMING UP,
AND WE THOUGHT WE'D GET
HIM, LIKE, A SPECIAL GIFT.
ONLY IT'S A SURPRISE,
SO WE DON'T WANT
HIM TO KNOW ABOUT.
YEAH, I UNDERSTAND THE
BASIC CONCEPT OF A
SURPRISE, MIKE.
SURE YOU CAN PUT ME
DOWN FOR FIVE BUCKS.
AH, GEE,
THANKS A LOT, MR. GREEN.
I GOT THIS REALLY GREAT DEAL
ON THIS REAL SPECIAL BARBECUE.
IF I GET 20 GUYS TO
COUGH UP FIVE BUCKS EACH,
THEN WE'RE THERE.
JUST YOU.
YOU GOT SO FAR?
WELL, HOW MANY DO
WHAT ABOUT
YOURSELF?
OH, SURE,
I'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
OH, GOTTA GO.
MUM'S THE WORD.
HEY!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT?
NOTHING.
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S
ANYBODY'S BIRTHDAY
OR ANYTHING.
I'M TALKING
ABOUT THEFT, RED.
YEAH, SOMEBODY BROKE
INTO MY STORE
AND TOOK THE DELUXE
BARBECUE OUT OF THE
WINDOW DISPLAY.
HOLY SMOKES, I DON'T
THINK I'M EVER GOING
TO GET THAT BACK.
WELL, NOW, YOU
JUST MIGHT, DALTON.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
AND TODAY THE
WINNER WILL GET
12,000 GALLONS OF
BUNKER "C" CRUDE OIL,
TO BE PICKED UP AT
YOUR CONVENIENCE.
THE OIL IS CURRENTLY FLOATING
AT THE NORTH END OF
POSSUM LAKE.
GOOD. GOOD.
CLOSE YOUR EARS.
HAROLD, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET YOUR UNCLE RED
TO SAY THIS WORD...
AND GO!
OKAY, OKAY, UNCLE RED,
WHAT DO YOU CALL A PERSON
WHO'S NEVER HAD ANY
FORM OF SEXUAL ACTIVITY?
HAROLD.
COME ON. COME ON.
HERE FOR THIS, YOU KNOW!
I DON'T HAVE TO BE
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
NO, IT'S NOT A NAME.
BUT IT IS A DESCRIPTIVE
WORD FOR SOMEONE WHO
DOESN'T HAVE SEX.
UGLY.
NO. NO. NO.
THIS IS A PART OF
SOMEONE'S LIFE
WHERE THEY'RE NOT INTERESTED
IN INTIMATE CONTACT.
DEATH?
NO. NO.
OKAY, IT'S A DECISION
THEY MAKE,
AND THEY SAY, NO SEXUAL
ACTIVITY FOR ME,
BECAUSE I'M...
MARRIED.
NO.
OKAY, MOST RELIGIOUS
WORKERS ARE THIS.
TAX EXEMPT?
WHY WOULD YOU EVEN
THINK TAX EXEMPT!?
OKAY, OKAY.
TIME'S ALMOST UP.
UNCLE RED, WHAT DO YOU
DO DURING TROUT SEASON
TO EARN EXTRA MONEY?
SELL BAIT?
OH, COME ON!
WHEN THE FUMES HAVE MELTED
YOUR PATIO CHAIRS
'CAUSE YOUR LAWN
IS A TOXIC SPILL,
WHEN YOU BREATHE IT BURNS
ALL YOUR NOSTRIL HAIRS
AND MAKES YOUR
PET SKUNK ILL,
WHEN YOUR SEPTICS HAVE YOU
AT THE END OF YOUR ROPE,
CALL US, THE PEOPLE
WITH SKILL.
WITH ROTHSCHILD'S YOU KNOW
YOU ALWAYS HAVE HOPE,
'CAUSE WE CAN TAKE IT,
AND WE WILL.
YOU KNOW, ONE OF THE GREAT
FRUSTRATIONS IN LIFE
IS WANTING THINGS
YOU CAN'T HAVE.
LIKE, A CURE FOR A FATAL
DISEASE OR WORLD PEACE
OR HAVING YOUR OWN
AUTOMATIC GARAGE DOOR OPENER.
WELL, I'VE GOT GREAT
NEWS FOR YOU.
THIS TIME I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW TO BUILD YOUR OWN
GARAGE DOOR OPENER.
ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS TAKE OFF
THESE BIG SPRINGS.
THESE SPRINGS HOLD
THE DOOR OPEN,
BUT YOU DON'T WANT THAT.
YOU WANT THE DOOR
TO STAY CLOSED.
OKAY, GOOD.
NO, THAT'S GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, I'VE ATTACHED
ONE END OF A CHUNK OF ROPE
TO THE TOP OF
MY GARAGE DOOR.
SO WHEN THE ROPE IS PULLED,
THE DOOR WILL OPEN.
OKAY, NEXT WE JUST NEED
A PULLEY OF SOME KIND.
OH, THERE WE GO.
I'LL JUST THREAD THE
OTHER END OF THE ROPE
THROUGH ONE OF THE RIMS
ON MY OLD BIKE.
SEE, THAT'S THE BEAUTY OF
NEVER THROWING ANYTHING OUT.
NEVER KNOW WHEN YOU'RE
GOING TO NEED IT AGAIN.
I BET BERNICE HAS TRIED A
MILLION TIMES TO TO GET
RID OF THAT BIKE.
SHE SHOULD SEE THIS.
BERNICE!
BERNICE.
NEVER MIND.
OKAY, NOW WE'RE
GETTING THERE.
SO AS SOON AS ANYTHING
PULLS ON THE ROPE,
THE DOOR OPENS.
OKAY, NOW ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS RUN IT AROUND SOMETHING
STRONG AND SMOOTH,
AND I DON'T MEAN A GLASS
OF SINGLE-MALT WHISKEY.
I'M TALKING ABOUT A POLE
OR A FIRE HYDRANT
OR AN IMBEDDED MISSILE
OF SOME KIND.
THEN YOU RUN THE ROPE
ACROSS THE DRIVEWAY
AT ABOUT
WINDSHIELD HEIGHT.
THAT OUGHTA KEEP THE
SNOWMOBILERS OUTTA THERE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GIVE
HER A TRY.
OKAY, NOW, YOU WANNA GET
YOURSELF A CAR WITH A
POWER ANTENNA.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE
ONE OF THOSE,
YOU PROBABLY LIVE IN A DUMP
THAT DOESN'T HAVE A
GARAGE ANYWAY.
SO REMEMBER IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
Red: BERNICE!
[applause]
YOU KNOW, A LOT
OF US MIDDLE-AGED
GUYS ARE PRETTY RUGGED.
WE DON'T COMPLAIN IF WE NAIL
A FINGER TO THE WORKBENCH,
OR MAYBE TAKE A
FLYING TIRE IN THE FACE.
EVEN SHOOT OFF
THE OCCASIONAL TOE.
BUT IF WE GET A COLD
OR THE FLU,
WE GO DOWN LIKE A
CHEAP LAWN CHAIR.
NOW, BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
THIS IS PART OF THE MANLY
ART OF BEING MANLY.
YOU SEE, MOST MEN LIKE
TO PRETEND THEY'RE
INDESTRUCTIBLE.
AND IT STOPS THEM
FROM SAYING THINGS LIKE,
I CAN'T LIFT MY
END OF THE PIANO;
OR, I DON'T WANNA GO
UP ON THE ROOF;
OR, THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE USED AN ARC WELDER.
YOU SEE, IT'S MEN LIKE ME
WHO CAN'T ASK FOR HELP
THAT CREATES MOST
OF THE PROBLEMS.
THAT'S WHY WE LET A COLD
BRING US TO OUR KNEES.
WE KNOW A COLD
IS NO BIG DEAL,
BUT WE FIGURE IF WE CAN SAY,
HEY, I NEED HELP,
WHEN WE DON'T
REALLY NEED HELP,
THEN MAYBE WE WON'T HAVE
TO SAY, HEY, I NEED HELP,
WHEN WE REALLY
DO NEED HELP.
I'LL TELL YOU IF MIDDLE-AGED
MEN COULD GET HELP WITHOUT
ASKING FOR IT,
THERE'D BE A LOT MORE OF
US SITTING AT HOME FEELING
BETTER ABOUT OURSELVES
AND A LOT FEWER OF US SITTING
IN THE EMERGENCY ROOM
TRYING TO COME UP WITH
AN EXPLANATION.
REMEMBER I'M
PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
[film projector running]
OH, HI, EVERYBODY.
RANGER GORD HERE.
WELCOME TO THE EDUCATIONAL
PORTION OF THE SHOW
AND THE ONLY SEGMENT
OF THIS PROGRAMME
THAT HAS ANY REAL LASTING
VALUE IN THE PUREST SENSE.
I'M PLEASED TO PRESENT
ANOTHER IN MY SERIES
OF ANIMATED SHORTS.
AND YOU KNOW, BEING ALONE
IN THE FIRE TOWER FOR AS
LONG AS I'VE BEEN,
THERE'S NOTHING I LIKE
MORE THAN ANIMATED SHORTS.
[laughter]
TRUST ME.
ANYWAY, TODAY'S FILM IS
ALL ABOUT BEING READY.
SO ARE YOU READY NOW?
NO?
[whistling]
HOW ABOUT NOW?
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
[quirky upbeat music]
TODAY I'M GOING TO TEACH
EVERYONE IN THE WORLD
ABOUT PREPARATION.
DO YOU TWO KNOW
WHAT PREPARATION IS?
SURE, I BELIEVE IT'S THAT
MEDICINE THAT COMES IN A TUBE.
YOU KNOW, UNCLE RED, NOT
EVERYTHING RANGER GORD SAYS
IS JUST A SET-UP
FOR A CHEAP JOKE.
HAROLD IS RIGHT.
THIS IS NO JOKE.
PREPARATION IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING IN LIFE.
WELL, OTHER THAN WOMEN
AND DRY UNDERWEAR.
THE BOY SCOUTS HAVE A MOTTO,
"BE READY."
I THINK IT'S
"BE PREPARED."
I THINK.
WHO CARES WHAT
YOU THINK, HAROLD?
HERE, LET ME SHOW YOU.
ARE YOU READY?
UH, I THINK SO.
I WASN'T TAKING TO YOU.
[laughs]
SEE HOW THAT WORKS?
FOLLOW ME.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
AS A FOREST RANGER,
I HAVE TO BE READY AT ALL
TIMES FOR ANY EMERGENCY.
YOU KNOW, I GUESS YOU COULD
SAY I'M A SUPER EL PRIMO
BOY SCOUT.
UH, NO,
I COULDN'T SAY THAT.
I KNOW YOU THINK FOREST
RANGERS ARE ONLY HERE TO
PROTECT THE ENVIRONMENT.
BUT THERE'S A LOT MORE
TO IT THAN THAT.
YEAH, YOU HAVE TO ALSO
BE A WEIRDO.
NO, THAT'S NOT CORRECT.
BEING A WEIRDO IS
COMPLETELY OPTIONAL.
BUT A FOREST RANGER DOES
NEED TO BE READY
FOR ANYTHING.
AH! WERE YOU READY FOR
THIS, RANGER GORD?
ABSOLUTELY!
DON'T TELL ME THE SUPER
EL PRIMO BOY SCOUT
CAN FLY.
NOPE,
DON'T NEED TO.
HEY, THAT'S NOT FAIR!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW, GORD?
TRY THIS.
[screaming]
[laughing]
[quirky upbeat music]
[applause]
WELL, THE CRIME
WAVE CONTINUES.
MOOSE THOMPSON HAD HIS LAUNDRY
STOLEN RIGHT OFF HIS
CLOTHESLINE.
NOW, THAT'S GOTTA
BE VANDALISM.
THERE'S NOBODY AROUND HERE
BIG ENOUGH TO WEAR
HIS CLOTHES,
UNLESS MAYBE THE
CIRCUS IS IN TOWN.
HEY, MR. GREEN!
HEY!
HAVE A LOOK AT
THIS BARBECUE WE'RE
GIVING TO DALTON.
OH, YEAH.
OR WHAT?
IS IT A BEAUTY
AND GET A LOAD OF
THE PRICE,
100 BUCKS.
HOW CAN YOU BEAT THAT?
YEAH, THAT'S A
REAL STEAL.
GO AHEAD, OPEN IT UP.
TAKE A LOOK.
NO, I DON'T WANNA PUT MY
FINGERPRINTS ON IT, MIKE.
YEAH, WE GOTTA KEEP IT
NICE FOR DALTON.
CAN I HIDE IT IN HERE
UNTIL DALTON'S BIRTHDAY?
HE'D NEVER THINK TO LOOK
IN THE LODGE FOR ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW, MIKE, I HATE
TO ASK YOU THIS,
BUT IS THAT
BARBECUE HOT?
OH, YEAH, IT GOES
UP TO 500 DEGREES!
NO, THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEAN.
I MEAN DID YOU STEAL
THAT BARBECUE?
MR. GREEN, WHAT MUST
YOU THINK OF ME?
WE DON'T HAVE
TIME FOR THAT, MIKE.
DID YOU STEAL
THE BARBECUE?
ABSOLUTELY NOT,
AND I'M DISGUSTED THAT
YOU WOULD EVEN THINK
SUCH A THING!
WELL, I APOLOGIZE.
IT'S JUST THAT WHEN A GUY
GOES TO JAIL 37 TIMES
FOR THEFT,
WELL, A PERSON CAN JUMP
TO CONCLUSIONS.
HIYA, DALTON.
HOW YOU DOIN'?
WELL, THERE'S STILL NO
SIGN OF THAT MISSING
BARBECUE.
I PHONED THE POLICE,
GAVE THEM A COMPLETE
DESCRIPTION.
YEAH, IT'S GOT A NICE HOOD
ON IT, ENAMELED GREEN.
A LITTLE SHELF ON EACH
SIDE WITH A BURNER.
IT'S A
BEAUTIFUL THING.
YEAH, I CAN ALMOST
PICTURE IT.
$1200, RED!
BOY, THE GUY THAT'S GOT
THAT IS GOING TO SPEND
A LONG TIME IN JAIL.
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S NOT A BARBECUE IF
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
THINKING.
NO, THERE'S SOMETHING
JUST WEIRD,
NOT QUITE RIGHT.
WHAT -- WHAT --
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I CLEANED.
I CLEANED, DALTON,
AND I PAINTED.
THAT'S ALL WET PAINT.
YOU DON'T WANNA GET WET
PAINT ON YOU, DALTON.
IT DOESN'T LOOK WET.
IT LOOKS DUSTY.
THAT'S THE COLOUR.
DUSTY BROWN.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
IT'S THE FUMES,
THE DUSTY BROWN
PAINT FUMES.
REMEMBER DUSTY SPRINGFIELD?
WASN'T SHE GREAT, EH?
SHE'S GREAT.
LET'S GO.
Red: WINSTON AND I WERE
BLOWING UP BALLOONS
FOR A PARTY,
AND I WAS HAVING PROBLEMS.
HE OBVIOUSLY HAS A LITTLE
MORE WIND THAN I DO.
AND HE WAS KINDA RAZZING ME
ON IT AND EVERYTHING,
WHICH I DIDN'T
APPRECIATE TOO MUCH.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW
THERE'S A BEE.
I DON'T LIKE THE BEES 'CAUSE
THEY CAN MAKE YOU SWELL UP
AND EVERYTHING.
I KIND DIRECTED HIM OVER --
OH! THERE YOU GO.
NOW WHO'S THE
FUNNY ONE, HUH?
I'M LOOKING AT THE BEE,
I'M THINKING --
OH, THERE HE IS.
I KNEW THERE'D BE
A HIVE AROUND THERE.
I'M JUST MORE COMFORTABLE
GETTING IT OUT OF THERE.
WE CAN TAKE THE STEP LADDER
OVER AND TAKE A BURLAP BAG
AND JUST GO ON UP AND THAT.
AND I THINK IT'S SAFER
IF YOU GO UP, WINSTON.
THEN I CAN HOLD THE LADDER.
SO WINSTON GETS UP
THERE AND --
YEAH, AWAY YOU GO.
YOU'RE FINE.
NO, YOU'RE FINE.
THE PROBLEM THERE IS
HE'S JUST NóT QUITE TALL
ENOUGH TO GET TO THE HIVE,
AND THAT'S THE
ONLY LADDER WE'VE GOT,
SO I DID WHAT I HAD TO DO.
AND THAT GOT HIM UP,
AND HE GOT THE HIVE.
AND HE GOT IN THE BAG,
AND THEN HE DROPPED
THE WHOLE UNIT.
I COULDN'T HANG AROUND.
SO THEN THE BEES ARE
FLYING INSIDE THE BAG.
THE WHOLE THING HAS
TAKEN OFF THERE.
FIRST THING I GOTTA DO
IS BRING WINSTON BACK
DOWN TO EARTH,
WHICH IS A BIG JOB
ALL ON ITS OWN.
AND THEN I THOUGHT,
WELL, YOU KNOW,
I'VE GOT THE FISHING GEAR.
IF THAT THING IS FLOATING
AROUND THROUGH THE SKY,
WE MIGHT BE ABLE TO JUST,
UH, GET A GOOD LURE.
I'M USUALLY PRETTY GOOD
WITH THIS THING.
AND JUST, UH, REEL BACK,
AND ONE GOOD CAST...
AND GOT HER!
GOT HER.
ALL RIGHT, NOW
JUST REEL HER IN.
GENTLE.
THAT'S ONLY A
10-POUND TEST ON THERE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
MUCH THESE BEES W --
BUT YOU KNOW, WHAT CAME
DOWN WAS REALLY JUST
THE EMPTY BAG.
AND NOW I'M WONDERING DOES
THE HIVE FLOAT UP IN THE SKY
OR WILL IT DROP?
I DON'T KNOW WHETHER --
DOES IT DROP OR --
I'M NOT SURE WHAT
WOULD HAPPEN NEXT.
YEAH. YEAH.
NOW, I'VE HEARD OF A PERSON
WITH A BEE IN THEIR BONNET,
BUT WINSTON WENT
TO A WHOLE NEW LEVEL.
[applause]
I'M NOT A BIG FAN
OF SMALL CARS.
I KNOW THEY'RE CHEAPER
ON GAS AND EASIER TO PARK,
BUT YOU FEEL LIKE SUCH
A WEENIE DRIVING THEM.
AND YOU CAN ONLY RUN INTO
SMALL THINGS WITHOUT
HURTING YOURSELF.
I'LL TELL YOU THE WORST
PART ABOUT A SMALL CAR,
THE HORN.
NO INTIMIDATION
FACTOR AT ALL.
IT SOUNDS LIKE SOMEBODY
STEPPING ON A FROG.
HERE'S A BETTER IDEA.
GO DOWN TO YOUR LOCAL AUTO
WRECKERS AND PICK OUT
AS MANY WORKING CAR HORNS
AS YOU CAN GET YOUR HANDS ON.
THEN YOU MOUNT 'EM IN ANY
OPEN SPACE UNDER THE HOOD.
AND BELIEVE ME, WITH AN
ENGINE THE SIZE OF AN
ELECTRIC RAZOR,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
PLENTY OF ROOM.
THE OTHER CARS MAY
NOT SEE YOU COMING;
THEY MAY NOT EVEN CARE
IF YOU'RE COMING;
BUT I PROMISE YOU ONE THING,
[chuckles]
THEY'LL HEAR YOU COMING.
JUST BE SURE YOU START HER
UP BEFORE YOU HONK THE HORN.
OTHERWISE, YOUR BATTERY
WILL DIE FASTER
THAN A BLOND JOKE AT
THE MISS AMERICA PAGEANT.
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
REMEMBER, HONK IF YOU
HATE NOISE POLLUTION.
[honk!]
[applause]
MIKE HAS PUT US IN A
TERRIBLE POSITION HERE.
I'M GLAD TO GET DALTON
A BIRTHDAY GIFT,
BUT BOY, NOT WORTH GOING
TO JAIL FOR, EH?
NOT FOR A LOUSY
BARBECUE ANYWAY.
GET READY.
HE'S HERE!
WINSTON'S
BRINGING HIM IN.
WHERE ARE THE
EXOTIC DANCERS?
DALTON, WE BROUGHT YOU
HERE FOR A SPECIAL
SURPRISE.
EXOTIC DANCERS?
NO, DALTON.
WE KNOW IT'S
YOUR BIRTHDAY,
SO WE GOT YOU
A SPECIAL PRESENT.
WELL, EVEN ONE EXOTIC
DANCER WOULD BE FINE.
DALTON!
MR. GREEN, WOULD YOU
DO THE HONOURS?
DALTON, WE GOT TOGETHER
AND WE GOT THIS FOR YOU.
AND WANNA WISH YOU
A HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
WOW!
WHAT IS THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, IT'S
A BARBECUE.
IT'S A
BARBECUE!
IT'S A YELLOW
BARBECUE.
OH, THAT IS SO NICE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T NEED A BARBECUE.
REMEMBER THE ONE THAT WAS
STOLEN FROM THE WINDOW
OF MY STORE?
YEAH?
WELL, IT TURNS OUT
ANN MARIE HID IT
TO GIVE IT TO ME
FOR MY BIRTHDAY.
[laughs]
BOY, IT'S A
BEAUT TOO.
[possum squealing]
OH, MEETING
TIME.
YEAH, YOU GUYS
GO AHEAD.
OKAY.
RIGHT DOWN.
I'LL BE
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I WAS REMINDED TONIGHT
OF OUR DATING YEARS,
BECAUSE MIKE WAS LOOKING AT
ME EXACTLY THE WAY YOUR
DAD USED TO.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheers and applause]
Winston
GUYS, GUYS, SIT DOWN.
COME TO ORDER.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
I'M SORRY,
ALL RIGHT?