IT’S THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW!
HERE'S THE MAN WITH A FIRM
GRASP ON THE BOAT AND DOCK --
THAT GREAT CAST-OFF,
MY UNCLE, YOUR HERO, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
YOU'RE THE MAN!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I WAS HOPING TO GET
INTO A NEW PROJECT.
I GOT SOME GOVERNMENT PAPERWORK
THAT I GOTTA CLEAR UP.
ABOUT YOUR MISSING
BIRTH CERTIFICATE?
THEY FOUND
THE DEAD SEA SCROLLS.
(Audience laughing)
NO, HAROLD, COME OFF IT.
THE LODGE IS ON LEASED LAND.
WE'VE HAD THE LEASE
FOR 99 YEARS, BUT SHE'S UP.
THEY'RE GONNA RAISE
OUR RENT 500%.
500%?!
YES, SIR.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS!
THEY CAN'T
DO THAT!
THEY DID IT.
THEY GOT US UP TO FIVE BUCKS.
FIVE BUCKS
FOR 100 YEARS?
DON'T I WISH!
IT'S FIVE BUCKS FOR 99 YEARS.
IT WAS GONNA BE
THREE BUCKS, BUT
OLD MAN SEDGWICK TALKED TO THEM
AND NOW IT'S FIVE.
WELL, REALLY,
FIVE BUCKS
ISN'T TOO BAD.
DO YOU HAVE
YOUR WALLET
ON YOU?
NO, NO, NO!
NO, NO, NO, NOT MY MONEY --
YOUR MONEY.
YOU WANT TO RAISE IT, THEN
YOU CAN RETURN YOUR EMPTIES.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
WE WEREN'T DRINKING --
WE WERE INVESTING.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MAIN MESSAGE BEING,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
HAROLD, YOU CAN REST EASY.
CLEARED THE EMPTIES
OUT OF THE STORAGE SHED.
WE COVERED THE FIVE BUCKS.
EVEN HAD MONEY
LEFT OVER.
HOW MUCH LEFT OVER?
783 BUCKS.
WOW.
THAT'S A LOT.
YOU SHOULD SEE
HOW MUCH ROOM
WE GOT IN THAT STORAGE SHED.
WE SHOULD USE THAT
TO STORE STUFF.
DID YOU READ
THIS ENTIRE LETTER?
THAT'S A GOVERNMENT LETTER --
YOU DON'T READ THOSE.
YOU LOOK AT THE BOX
SAYS HOW MUCH MONEY YOU OWE.
IT SAYS, IN THE MIDDLE, THAT
YOU GOTTA MAKE A PRESENTATION.
WHAT?!
YOU GOTTA
MAKE A SPEECH
TO A COMMITTEE
AND CONVINCE THEM
THAT THE LEASE
SHOULD BE RENEWED.
THEN THE COMMITTEE DECIDES
WHICH ORGANIZATION WILL GET IT.
HAROLD, WHO'S COMPETING
WITH US ON THIS?
EVERYBODY!
THE ROTARIANS,
THE POSSUM LAKE CANOE CLUB,
THE VINTAGE CAR CLUB,
THE GIRL SCOUTS...
THERE'S EVEN A MOTORCYCLE CLUB,
SATAN'S SECOND CHOICE.
THEY CAN'T
DO THIS!
THIS IS
OUR SPOT!
YOU SAID YOU LIKE COMPETITION.
THIS IS JUST COMPETITION.
I ONLY LIKE COMPETITION
WHEN I WIN!
(Audience laughing)
(Red): LATER ON,
IN "ADVENTURES WITH BILL",
GONNA DO SOME WATER-SKIING.
GETTING READY
AND STARTING UP...
THAT MOTOR DOES NOT--
IT'S GOT THE OLD HAND-PULL.
I DIDN'T REALIZE THE SKI ROPE
WAS ACROSS
THE PULLER, AND
BILL SET THE HANDLE DOWN
AND APPARENTLY HOOKED IT
ONTO A ROCK
AND, WOULDN'T YOU KNOW IT,
THERE GOES THE MOTOR!
UNFORTUNATELY, THE SKI ROPE
STARTED WINDING AROUND
AND STARTED PULLING ME
A LITTLE--
YEAH, MM-HMM, YEAH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHTY.
SO, UH, WE'LL THINK
OF SOMETHING ELSE.
OHHH! OHHH!
WE'LL GET A PLAN "B"-- OHHH!
AND WE'LL GET RIGHT ON THAT.
MMM!
OHHH, SHE WAS A CEDAR-STRIP
CRUISING YACHT
THE NICEST BOAT
I EVER BOUGHT
NOT CONCERNED WITH
HOW MY HEART WOULD BREAK
SHE'S GONE
BUT NOT FORGOTTEN
SHE WAS A GOOD BOAT
BUT TOTALLY ROTTEN
MY LOVE IS DEEP
UNFORTUNATELY,
SO IS THE LAKE
THIS IS FOR THE BIG ONE!
THE GRAND PRIZE OF A SET
OF MINIATURE LAWN DARTS
FROM WANG FU'S
ACUPUNCTURE CENTRE.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO MAKE MR. BUZZ SHERWOOD
SAY THIS WORD.
BUZZ.
OH!
THE WORD IS...
HA-HA! WA-HAHHH...
(Audience laughing)
AHHHH... NUDIST!
(Giggling)
ALL RIGHT, BUZZ.
SOMEONE
WHO IS NAKED
IS...
... FUN!
NO, NO, NO.
IF A WOMAN DOESN'T BELIEVE
IN WEARING CLOTHES,
YOU WOULD CALL HER A...
... A LOT!
(Audience laughing)
OK, NO, NO.
THIS IS THE NAME OF SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T WEAR CLOTHES.
OH, SUSAN.
NO, NO, MORE THAN ONE PERSON.
THE MURPHY SISTERS?
I'M LOOKING FOR
A GENERIC WORD, HERE.
A MAN OR WOMAN
WHO DOESN'T WEAR CLOTHES.
OH, LIKE THAT
DONALD GUY!
WHAT'S HE GOT,
ANYWAY?
WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
THESE PEOPLE GO AROUND
IN THE BUFF.
NUNS!
I THINK THAT'S TIME --
WE'RE OUT OF TIME.
THANKS FOR PLAYING.
NUNS GO AROUND IN THE BUFF?
OH, I THOUGHT YOU SAID "BUS"!
(Audience laughing)
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
WE'LL DO A PROJECT
THAT SHOWS YOU
HOW TO MAKE DO
WITH WHAT YOU HAVE.
I HAVE A LEAKY ROOF.
MANY PEOPLE
WOULD TRY AND FIX THAT.
THAT'S BECAUSE THEY THINK
THE ROOF WILL HOLD
THEIR WEIGHT.
I KNOW BETTER.
INSTEAD, I'M GONNA MAKE
HOME-MADE BEER.
THEN I WON'T CARE
IF IT'S RAINING.
WATER IS THE BIG INGREDIENT
WHEN YOU'RE MAKING BEER,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE MAKING
AMERICAN BEER.
SO... WITH THE WATER COMING
DOWN THROUGH THE ROOF,
IT REALLY ADDS TO THE FLAVOUR
OF THE BEER
AND IT HELPS ME GIVE IT A NAME.
SHE'S COMIN' OFF A BIG CEDAR LOG
SO I'LL CALL MY BEER
"BIG CEDAR LAGER...
"THE WOODSMAN'S BEER
THAT MAKES YOU CUT AND SPLIT."
THIRSTY YET?
(Thunder)
THE NEXT THING YOU NEED IS
SOMETHING THEY CALL
"BITTERING HOPS".
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THAT IS,
SO I ASKED THE GUYS
AT THE LODGE
AND AFTER FIVE HOURS,
IT BECAME CLEAR
THEY HAD NO IDEA, EITHER,
WHICH IS AMAZING,
CONSIDERING THEIR FAMILIARITY
WITH THE FINAL PRODUCT.
I DECIDED TO BREAK HER DOWN.
YOU GOT BITTERING
AND YOU GOT HOPS.
I FIGURE... "BITTERING"
HAS GOT TO BE FOR YOUR LEMONS
AND "HOPS" HAS GOTTA BE
RABBIT FOOD.
IT DOESN'T AFFECT
THE ALCOHOL CONTENT
SO IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER.
FIRE THAT IN THERE
AND PUT YOUR WASHING MACHINE
ON TO THE "PRE-WASH",
LET THE BITTERING HOPS WORK
FOR A WHILE.
WONDERED WHERE THAT SHIRT WENT.
ALL RIGHT,
ONCE THAT CYCLE'S DONE,
YOU WANT TO ADD MALT EXTRACT.
YOU'RE PROBABLY GUESSING
THIS HERE IS A CHOCOLATE MALT.
(Sniffing)
AND EARLIER THIS YEAR,
IT PROBABLY WAS.
ALL RIGHT, PUT THAT IN THERE.
THEN YOU START 'ER UP
ON WHATEVER CYCLE
SUITS THE BEER YOU'RE MAKING.
FOR ENGLISH BEER,
SET 'ER ON "PERMANENT PRESS".
FOR THE LIGHT BEER,
MAYBE GO "DELICATE".
FOR A BEER THAT DOESN'T
MAKE YOU GO TO THE BATHROOM,
SET 'ER ON "RINSE AND HOLD".
ALL RIGHT, I'M SUPPOSED TO ADD
SOMETHING CALLED
"FINISHING HOPS".
AGAIN, I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THAT IS
SO THEY MUST JUST MEAN
THE REST OF THE RABBIT FOOD.
DON'T FORGET.
I'M MAKING DO WITH WHAT I HAVE,
PLUS I DON'T CARE.
ALL RIGHT, WHEN THAT'S DONE,
I'M GONNA FILTER THE BEER.
I GOTTA STORE IT
SOMEWHERE COLD FOR TWO WEEKS.
THIS IS NOW MY BEER FRIDGE.
I GOT MY PIPES RUNNING IN
THROUGH THE FRIDGE
WHERE I'M GONNA STORE THE BEER.
I GOT 'EM COMING OUT
TO MY BEER TAP
FOR DISPENSING THE BEER.
I'VE USED THE MAIN CHAMBER
OF THE FRIDGE
BUT YOU COULD RUN THE PIPES
THROUGH THE FREEZER
IF YOU WERE MAKING AN ICE BEER.
NOW WE COME TO THE MOST
IMPORTANT INGREDIENT
WHENEVER YOU'RE MAKING BEER,
AND THAT IS YOUR YEAST.
WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T TRY TO MAKE DO.
DON'T TRY TO USE BAKING SODA
OR DISH DETERGENT.
THE YEAST IS
WHAT MAKES IT BEER.
THAT'S WHAT GIVES YOU YOUR
COLOUR, CLARITY, YOUR FLAVOUR,
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
YOUR ALCOHOLIC CONTENT.
(Audience laughing)
THERE WE GO.
YOU WANT TO IMMEDIATELY
PUMP THE BEER
INTO YOUR STORAGE VAT, WHICH,
IN THIS CASE, IS THE FRIDGE.
NOW I NEED SOMETHING
TO MAKE DO AS A FILTER.
OH!
THERE, THIS PIECE
OF SHIRT WILL WORK
ABSOLUTELY FINE.
NOW WHAT WE WANT TO DO IS
TAKE THE DRAIN-PUMP
FROM THE WASHING MACHINE
AND JUST PUMP 'ER
RIGHT THROUGH.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS
ACTUALLY CALLED "WART"
AND THIS IS CALLED
"TRANSFERRING THE WART".
I WAS GONNA CALL IT
"REMOVING THE WART"
BUT I THOUGHT IT WOULD MAKE
THE BEER HARD TO DRINK.
SHE'S LEAKING A LITTLE.
WE'VE WAITED THE TWO WEEKS...
OR CLOSE ENOUGH.
FELT LIKE TWO WEEKS.
I'M GUESSING THE BEER
IS READY FOR TASTING.
THE BEAUTY IS,
WE'VE MADE OUR MICRO-BREWERY
RIGHT IN OUR OWN HOME.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
AFTER A COUPLE OF BEERS, THEY
MIGHT EVEN FIND YOU HANDSOME.
THE BEAUTY IS,
WE DIDN'T BUY ANYTHING.
WE JUST MADE DO.
(Spitting)
OR MAYBE WE MADE DOO-DOO.
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
WANT TO TALK TO YOU GUYS
ABOUT THOSE 4:00-IN-THE-MORNING
CAN'T-SLEEP THOUGHTS
THAT WANDER INTO YOUR HEAD.
YOU KNOW THOSE THOUGHTS.
SCARY THOUGHTS.
THOUGHTS ABOUT HOW PERFECT
LIFE USED TO BE...
BEFORE YOU WERE MARRIED...
BEFORE YOU WERE EMPLOYED...
BEFORE YOU WERE IN HOCK
UP TO YOUR EYEBALLS...
BACK IN THE DAYS
WHEN YOUR BELT WAS SHORTER
THAN YOUR IN-SEAM...
WHEN GOING TO THE BATHROOM
ONCE BEFORE BEDTIME
WOULD DO 'ER.
YOU'RE LYING THERE,
DREAMING ABOUT STARTING OVER,
GETTING IN SHAPE,
CHANGING YOUR JOB,
BUYING A NEW CAR,
AND MOVING SOMEWHERE
WHERE PEOPLE WILL THINK
YOU'RE DANGEROUS.
I KNOW -- AT 4:00 A.M.
IT'S EASY TO IMAGINE
THAT YOU'RE ANTONIO BANDERAS.
THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU CAN'T SEE THE MIRROR.
LOOK AT IT THIS WAY.
YOUR STOMACH'S FULL,
YOU'RE WARM, YOU'RE LYING DOWN.
WHY WOULD YOU GIVE THAT UP TO
ROLL OVER AND TELL THE MISSUS
THAT YOU'RE LEAVING TO GO OUT
AND START A GARAGE BAND?
DON'T DO IT --
JUST COUNT YOUR BLESSINGS.
YOU GOT MOST OF YOUR HEALTH,
SOME OF YOUR MORTGAGE PAID OFF,
AND THE SEMI-RESPECT
OF SOME OF YOUR FRIENDS.
THAT'S GOING TO LOOK GOOD
IN THE MORNING,
EVEN IF YOU DON'T.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause)
WELL, EVERYTHING
IS TOTALLY UNDER CONTROL.
IN A FEW HOURS,
I'M GONNA HAVE THAT COMMITTEE
EATING OUT OF MY HAND.
YOUR SPEECH
WILL IMPRESS THEM?
NOT SO MUCH THE SPEECH.
IT'S SLAMMING THE COMPETITION,
IS WHAT IT'S DOING...
ESPECIALLY THOSE GIRL GUIDES
WITH THAT COOKIE SCAM.
NO, NO, UNCLE RED,
RULES FORBID PRESENTERS
FROM CRITICIZING
OTHER CONTENDERS.
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
BRIBE SOMEBODY OR SOMETHING?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
YOU GOTTA MAKE THE SPEECH
AS TO ALL THE GOOD THINGS
ABOUT POSSUM LODGE.
WE HAVE GOOD THINGS HERE?
YEAH, WE GOT
LOTS OF GOOD THINGS.
WE GOT, UM...
UH...
NO, THAT WAS IN "BAYWATCH".
(Audience laughing)
I KNOW ONE.
REMEMBER THAT RADIOACTIVE SCARE
WE HAD?
THOSE READINGS WERE
WELL WITHIN ACCEPTABLE LEVELS.
THAT'S IT! THAT'S WHAT WE DO!
WE'LL DO WHAT POLITICIANS DO.
I CAN'T -- I GOT A CONSCIENCE
AND A BAD BACK.
(Audience laughing)
WHAT WE DO... THIS IS SO GOOD,
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE IT.
(Siren)
COME ON,
COME ON!
POSSUM 911 --
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
UH, RED, IT'S DALTON HUMPHREY.
CAN'T HELP YOU THERE --
ANY OTHER PROBLEMS?
(Laughing)
I'M JUST NOT QUITE SURE.
UH, FAMILY'S OUT OF TOWN AND...
I JUST DON'T FEEL SO GOOD.
WHAT IS IT? THE TICKER?
YOU GOT PRESSURE, SHOOTING
PAINS, SLURRED SPEECH?
DO YOU SMELL BURNED TOAST?
NO, I'M STRONG AS A HORSE
BUT, YOU KNOW...
I THINK I MISS MY FAMILY.
OH, BOY,
DALTON.
YEAH, WEIRD, HUH?
I COULDN'T WAIT
FOR THEM TO LEAVE
AND NOW, I MEAN...
WELL, I'M EMBARRASSED
TO BRING IT UP
BUT I FEEL BAD, RED.
THEY'VE ONLY BEEN GONE
A DAY OR TWO AND I...
I GUESS IT'S BEEN FOUR DAYS.
WHAT IS THE DATE TODAY?
THE 14th.
OK, THEY'VE BEEN GONE
TWO WEEKS, BUT, UH...
I THINK I MIGHT BE
A LITTLE BIT LONELY.
OK, OK, TAKE IT EASY, DALTON.
WE'VE SEEN THIS BEFORE.
JUST RELAX -- I'M GONNA PUT
HAROLD ON THE LINE.
TELL DALTON
WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT.
OK, LAST NIGHT,
I WAS WATCHING T.V.
I SPILLED POP
ALL OVER THE COUCH.
I WAS EATING POTATO CHIPS
AT THE SAME TIME.
THIS SYRUP GOT
ALL OVER THE COUCH.
THE CHIP CRUMBS GOT STUCK
IN THERE, TOO.
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD, HAROLD!
HOW MANY TIMES HAVE I TOLD YOU,
NO POP ON THE COUCH!
IF YOU'RE EATING CHIPS,
CLEAN UP AFTER YOURSELF!
YOU KNOW WHAT IT COSTS
TO HAVE A COUCH CLEANED?
THAT HELP,
DALTON?
PERFECT, RED --
THAT'S JUST THE FIX I NEEDED.
(Audience laughing)
(Red): HERE WE ARE
WITH PLAN "B" ON WATER-SKIING.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, BILL --
SO HE'S, UH...
HE'S POINTING AWAY
FROM THE WATER.
I GOT THE ROPE HOOKED
AROUND THE OLD POSSUM VAN.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY THAT MOTHER
IS THE INVENTION OF...
UH... THERE'S AN EXPRESSION
OF SOME KIND THERE --
AWAY WE GO.
WOW, LOOK AT THAT, EH?
DON'T YOU KIDS TRY THIS.
YOU COULD HARDLY GET THE VAN
INTO YOUR HOME.
LOOK -- ISN'T THAT GREAT?
CYPRESS GARDENS,
INCLUDING THE GARDENS.
YOU DON'T SEE THAT EVERY DAY.
LOOK AT HIM, RIPPING ALONG.
I THOUGHT HE MIGHT SLALOM
BUT BILL'S SUCH A CHICKEN.
WHERE I MADE THE MISTAKE
WAS LOOKING BACK ALL THE TIME
AND THEN-- OHHH! BY GOLLY!
(Laughing)
NOW THERE'S NOBODY DRIVING
THE VAN, BILL!
YOU GOT NO DRIVER!
YOU MIGHT WANT TO JUST...
YOU MIGHT WANT TO STOP.
ALL RIGHT, GOOD, GOOD.
I WOULD WORK ON THE BRAKING...
THE BRAKING ASPECT.
WANT TO GO AGAIN, LITTLE BOY?
ONLY THIS TIME,
THERE'S A DOOR CHARGE.
OH, YOU'RE FINE.
YEAH!
YOU GOTTA RETURN THOSE SKIS.
A VIEWER SENT
RED GREEN WORK SOCKS,
AS IF YOU'D SEE "RED GREEN" AND
"WORK" IN THE SAME SENTENCE.
I'VE BEEN WORKING
ON MY PRESENTATION.
THAT COMMITTEE'S
GONNA BE IMPRESSED.
LOOK AT THIS -- THE FUTURE SITE
OF THE POSSUM LODGE
WATERFRONT AREA, HUH?
HOW MANY COOKIES WILL THOSE
GIRL SCOUTS HAVE TO SELL
TO BUILD THIS BABY?
(Laughing)
UNCLE RED, IT'S A TRAVEL POSTER
OF THE CARIBBEAN.
CHECK THE FINE PRINT.
LOOK -- READ THAT --
WHAT DOES THAT SAY?
"ARTIST'S
CONCEPTION".
(Laughing)
I LOVE A LOOP-HOLE!
I TOOK YOUR ADVICE.
LOOK AT THIS SPEECH -- I PUT
A POSITIVE SPIN ON EVERYTHING.
I STARTED
WITH AN ENVIRONMENTAL ISSUE.
"METAL RECOVERY PROGRAMME" --
WHAT'S THAT?
EVERY SPRING, WE PULL OUR
SNOWMOBILES OUT OF THE LAKE.
IF YOU CHECK THERE, I ENDED
BY POINTING OUT THAT WE'RE
PRESERVING A HERITAGE SITE.
YOU'VE NEVER FIXED ANYTHING
HERE IN YOUR LIFE!
WE'RE KEEPING THIS PLACE IN ITS
ORIGINAL HISTORIC CONDITION.
(Laughing)
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT?
OHHH... OHHH...
REVISIONIST.
(Audience laughing)
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON!
COME ON, COME ON.
JUST ONCE,
YOU OUGHT TO USE YOUR BRAIN
BEFORE YOU USE YOUR MOUTH.
SHE'S GOT THAT BEAUTIFUL,
ROMANTIC EVENING PLANNED.
THE CANDLELIGHT, WINE,
THE KIDS OFF AT SLEEP-OVERS.
JUST AS SHE'S HAMMERING AWAY
ON THE KETCHUP BOTTLE,
SHE ASKS --
YOU KNOW, WHIMSICALLY...
"WHAT WAS THE HAPPIEST DAY
OF YOUR LIFE?"
AND YOU BLURT OUT, "THE DAY
"THE TORONTO MAPLE LEAFS
TRADED FOR DOUGIE GILMOUR."
(Audience laughing)
NICE WORK -- REAL SMOOTH.
YEAH, YEAH, GOOD.
NO WONDER
SHE'S IN THE BATHROOM,
BAWLING HER EYES OUT.
SHE WON'T BE COMING OUT.
CAN YOU BLAME HER?
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO IS TELL HER
WHAT YOU MEANT WAS
THAT YOUR LIFE WAS
ON A LOSING STREAK
UNTIL SHE CAME TO YOU.
YES! "JUST LIKE DOUGIE
COMING TO THE LEAFS, YOU'RE...
"YOU'RE THE CAPTAIN
OF MY HEART."
WOW, EH?
"YOU GAVE ME MY GOALS...
"EVEN BANKED A FEW
OFF THE POST."
(Audience laughing)
"JUST LIKE DOUGIE, YOU'RE
THE CENTRE WHO MADE IT WORK."
YEAH, YOU LOVE HER MOVES.
AND YOU'D LIKE TO
GIVE HER BODY A CHECK!
OR, UH... OR LOVE HER
END TO END.
I THINK THE HOCKEY THING
CAN GO A LITTLE TOO FAR.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO START MENTIONING
THAT DOUGIE HAS
NO FRONT TEETH, FOR EXAMPLE.
I'D ALSO STAY AWAY
FROM THE TERM "FACE-OFF".
BUT EVENTUALLY, SHE'LL COME OUT
AND RECOGNIZE YOU
FOR THE ROMANTIC LUG
THAT YOU ARE.
AND THEN, YOU KNOW
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
A LITTLE ONE-ON-ONE!
SUDDEN DEATH OVERTIME.
HOLD IT -- HOCKEY STOPS
WHEN YOU HIT THE BEDROOM DOOR.
THE LEAFS HAVEN'T GONE
ALL THE WAY SINCE '67!
(Laughing and applause)
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION,
WHERE WE EXAMINE
THOSE THREE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY.
(Audience):
"I DON'T KNOW!"
HA-HA! EXCELLENT! OK.
THIS WEEK, JOINING MY UNCLE RED
IS HIS VERY BEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE WIDE ROOM,
FERRYBOAT CAPTAIN
MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSY!
(Applause and cheering)
OK, ALL RIGHTY.
OK, OUR VIEWER WRITES...
"DEAR EXPERTS" -- WAHHH --
"MY HUSBAND SAYS THAT
"EVERYTHING ON TELEVISION
IS A LOAD OF CRAP.
"I PREFER TO SAY
'A LOAD OF BAD STUFF'.
"DO YOU THINK TELEVISION IS
A LOAD OF BAD STUFF?"
I DO -- IT'S ALL CRAP,
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
WELL, EVERYTHING
EXCEPT THIS SHOW.
RIGHT, UNCLE RED?
NOT THIS SHOW.
ALL RIGHT, IF YOU SAY SO.
OHHHH... HOW ABOUT YOU,
MR. SHAUGHNESSY?
DO YOU THINK
TELEVISION'S
A LOAD OF BAD STUFF?
YEAH... YES, I DO, HAROLD.
YEAH, IT'S
ALL CRAP.
(Audience laughing)
IT COULD HAVE BEEN SO GREAT --
THAT'S WHAT HURTS.
I'M ALMOST SORRY I INVENTED IT.
INVENTED WHAT, HAP?
CRAP?
(Audience laughing)
NO!
TELEVISION.
I WAS GONNA CALL IT
"HAP-EVISION"
BUT I CHANGED ME MIND
WHEN I SAW SO MANY
OF THOSE EARLY PILOTS
AND THE WAY THEY TURNED OUT.
EVERYONE WAS SAYING,
"WHO INVENTED TELEVISION?"
AND I SAID,
"I'LL NEVER TELL."
THEY STARTED CALLING IT
"NEVER TELL-EVISION",
THEN THEY CALLED IT
"TELEVISION"
AND THE REST IS HISTORY.
(Audience laughing)
HISTORY IN THE MAKING, I'D SAY.
SO I WASHED MY HANDS
OF THE WHOLE THING,
OUTSIDE OF A BRIEF STINT WHEN
I TOOK OVER "THE TONIGHT SHOW"
FROM JACK PAAR.
I COULDN'T STAND
THAT HOLLYWOOD SCENE.
IT WAS SO PHONY.
TOUGH FOR YOU TO STAND OUT
IN THAT CROWD.
(Laughing)
(Singing)
YEAH.
(Laughing)
WE GOT IT -- THE LEASE IS OURS.
EXCELLENT WORK ALL THE WAY --
WE WERE SO COOL.
IT HELPED THAT ALMOST ALL
THE OTHER COMPETITORS WITHDREW.
NEVER UNDERSTOOD
WHY THAT HAPPENED.
THEY DROVE BY
AND CHANGED THEIR MINDS.
A LOT OF THEM NEEDED
THE BUILDINGS
TO BE SAFE OR INSURABLE, SO...
YOU COULD FIX
THIS PLACE UP.
THAT'S A PRETTY EXPENSIVE
PROPOSITION!
CONSULTANTS SAID
IT'S CHEAPER TO BLOW IT UP
AND LIVE IN THE HOLE.
THE MAIN THING IS,
WE ONLY HAD ONE COMPETITOR.
THAT WAS LEECH LODGE
FROM UP NEAR PORT ASBESTOS.
THEY ACTUALLY GOT THE OK
FROM THE COMMITTEE
BEFORE WE DID --
THAT WAS SCARY FOR A WHILE!
THEY HAD TO ASK FOR TIME
TO COME UP WITH THE FIVE BUCKS.
(Laughing)
YES, THEY DID --
IT WAS VERY ODD
THAT AT THAT PARTICULAR MOMENT,
THEIR TREASURER
LOST HIS WALLET.
THE MAIN THING IS,
WE GOT THE LEASE
AND WE'RE BACK IN BUSINESS.
YOU STOLE THAT MAN'S WALLET.
NO, I DID NOT, SIR.
YES, YOU STOLE
THEIR RENT MONEY, UNCLE RED.
I BORROWED THE WALLET
FOR THE HEARING,
GAVE IT TO THEM AFTERWARDS.
ANYBODY WHO LEAVES THEIR WALLET
LYING AROUND...
IT WAS IN HIS POCKET!
IT WAS A REALLY BAGGY POCKET.
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
WE GOT THE LEASE, HAROLD!
WHOOO!
BY GOLLY!
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M THINKING,
THEY SAY TIME IS MONEY.
IF 99 YEARS IS FIVE BUCKS,
THEN MY LIFE SO FAR
ADDS UP TO $2.39...
AND I HOPE YOU'LL AGREE
THAT I'M WORTH IT.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): OH, OK, ALL RIGHTY!
STAND UP, STAND UP!
ALL RISE!
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN.
BUSTER HADFIELD WANTED ME
TO ANNOUNCE THAT
THAT ANIMAL YOU SAW
AT HIS PLACE IS NOT A CAMEL.
IT'S JUST A DONKEY
WITH TWO BAD MOSQUITO BITES.
OW!
MEETING'S ADJOURNED.