HERE IS A GREAT TIP THAT WILL SAVE
YOU ALOT OF TIME AND ENERGY
COME LAWN-CUTTING DAY --
OR LAWN-CUTTING WEEK OR
LAWN-CUTTING MONTH,
WHATEVER YOUR SCHEDULE IS...
INSTEAD OF TRYING TO PULL
START YOUR OLD LAWN MOWER
AND END UP SEPARATING YOUR
SHOULDER AND MOST OF
YOUR WILL TO LIVE,
GET YOURSELF A HOUSEHOLD FAN;
TAKE THE GRID OFF OF ONE SIDE
AND BEND THE BLADES UP THROUGH
AT A 45-DEGREE ANGLE.
OR A 47-DEGREE ANGLE,
OR ANY ANGLE, REALLY.
NOW YOU JUST THROW YOUR OLD,
WORN OUT, HARD-TO-START
LAWN MOWER ON TOP,
AND YOUR DAYS OF PULL
STARTING ARE OVER.
[ FAN BLADES WHIRRING ]
[ LAWN MOWER STARTS ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
OH, YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE THAT.
BIG SURPRISE UP AT THE
LODGE THIS WEEK.
SHAKY FARNSWORTH --
KIND OF AN OLD --
HE'S AN OLD TOWN DRUNK,
REALLY, IS WHAT HE IS.
HE PASSED AWAY.
THAT'S NOT THE
SURPRISE, THOUGH.
TURNS OUT THE GUY'S
WORTH A FORTUNE.
NOBODY KNEW.
APPARENTLY FOR
THE LAST 60 YEARS,
SHAKY HAS BEEN MAKING DONATIONS
TO THE SPERM BANK
FOR THE CASH.
I MEAN, IT SEEMS LIKE AN ODD
WAY TO MAKE YOUR FORTUNE,
BUT I GUESS WHEN YOU FIND
SOMETHING YOU'RE GOOD AT...
RED! RED! RED!
YOU WON'T
BELIEVE IT!
WHAT?
THE FARNSWORTH ESTATE.
I'M INHERITING A PIECE OF
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
HE HAS NO DIRECT RELATIVES,
BUT THE SPERM BANK SAYS
HE COULD BE POTENTIALLY
RELATED TO HUNDREDS OF
PEOPLE AROUND HERE.
OH, YEAH, WELL,
OKAY, BUT THEY'RE
ALL DIFFERENT MOTHERS,
SO HOW DO YOU
PROVE ANYTHING?
BECAUSE THEY HAVE A DNA CLINIC
DOWN AT THE LAWYER'S OFFICE.
THEY'VE GOT A CHART OF
SHAKY'S DNA PATTERN,
AND I COMPARED MINE TO IT,
AND IT IS IDENTICAL!
GOSH, SO YOU'RE SAYING YOUR
FATHER IS NOT ACTUALLY
YOUR FATHER?
WELL, THAT'S NOT
NECESSARILY A
BAD THING.
WELL, HOW MUCH OF THE CASH
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO GET, DALTON?
WELL, IT DEPENDS ON HOW
MANY PEOPLE MATCH UP.
IT COULD BE HUNDREDS,
YOU KNOW.
YOU SHOULD GO DOWN THERE
AND GET TESTED YOURSELF.
NOW, WHY WOULD
I DO THAT?
MY MOTHER NEVER WENT
OUT WITH SHAKY.
YEAH, YOU SEE, USING A SPERM
DONOR TO BE ARTIFICIALLY
INSEMINATED
ISN'T TECHNICALLY A DATE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
BESIDES, YOU'VE GOT
NOTHING TO LOSE.
I MEAN, THERE'S A MILLION
BUCKS UP FOR GRABS.
LET'S GO!
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO?
YOU JUST HAVE TO
GIVE A FEW DROPS
OF BLOOD.
NO! NO! NO!
COME ON.
IT'LL BE FUN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
HI, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
IF IT'S HUMMING
THROUGH THE HOSES,
YOU'RE COMING UP PURE ROSES.
IF IT'S SQUIRTIN'
THROUGH THE PLASTER,
YOU'RE FLIRTIN'
WITH DISASTER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
AND TODAY'S PRIZE IS A
BOTTLE OF Dr SHOTT'S
CORN REMOVER
AND OVEN CLEANER.
OKAY, RED,
YOU HAVE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET MIKE TO SAY
THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
DALTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, MIKE, WHAT
IS NATURE'S MOST
PERFECT FOOD?
A TOASTED WESTERN.
UM, ALL RIGHT,
THINK OF AN EXPRESSION...
DON'T CRY OVER SPILLED...
BEANS.
OKAY, MIKE, HOMO...
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, NEVER MIND.
NEVER MIND.
THINK BEDTIME --
DIFFERENT SUBJECT.
THINK BEDTIME.
WHAT DO YOU ASSOCIATE
WITH COOKIES?
TOSSING 'EM.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU GET FROM A COW?
ATTITUDE.
TIME'S ALMOST UP, RED.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE, WHAT DID YOUR
MOTHER GIVE YOU TO DRINK WHEN
YOU WERE A LITTLE KID?
HOW LITTLE?
10 YEARS OLD.
WELL, AT THAT AGE,
ALL SHE WOULD GIVE
ME WAS A LIGHT BEER.
UNLESS SHE WAS MAD AT ME,
LIKE WHEN I DISCOVERED
HER WITH THE MILKMAN.
THERE WE GO!
[ APPLAUSE ]
HI, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE.
I OFFER THE BEST SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICE
IN THE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
BUT, HEY, DON'T TAKE
MY WORD FOR IT.
( staccato ) I WOULD
NOT TRUST ANYONE
BUT WINSTON WITH MY SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICE --
NEEDS.
WINSTON'S A REAL HONEST GUY.
HE'D NEVER RIP YOU OFF AND
CHARGE YOU FOR WORK
HE DIDN'T DO.
HE'S WEIRD LIKE THAT.
SO CALL NOW.
ANY SERVICE OVER $100 WILL
RECEIVE A FREE ROLL
OF MY FASHIONABLE
BATHROOM TISSUE,
WITH MY FACE ON EVERY SQUARE.
SO NEXT TIME YOU HAVE
PLUMBING PROBLEMS,
I'M EASY TO REACH.
HERE'S LOOKING AT YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELCOME TO
'TALKING ANIMALS'
WITH LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER ED FRID.
ED HAS BROUGHT IN KIND OF
AN UNUSUAL ANIMAL TODAY,
A TASMANIAN DEVIL.
COME ON UP HERE.
NO, NO, COME ON.
IT'S FINE.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
UM, YES, THE TASMANIAN DEVIL.
IT'S AN EXOTIC
KIND OF ANIMAL.
UM, IT, UH, IT SPINS AROUND
WILDLY WHEN DISTURBED.
AND, UH, IT'S
A CUTE ANIMAL.
BUT IT WOULD JUST AS SOON
RIP YOUR SKULL OFF
AS LOOK AT YOU.
NOW, I UNDERSTAND THEY EAT
FRUIT, DON'T THEY, ED?
WHEN THEY'RE IN A GOOD
MOOD THEY EAT FRUIT, YES.
WHEN THEY'RE IN A BAD MOOD,
THEY EAT WHATEVER MADE
THEM THAT WAY.
ALL RIGHT, I'VE GOT
AN APPLE HERE.
WHY DON'T WE GIVE
HIM A TREAT?
WHOA! WHOA, RED,
THEY DON'T LIKE
YELLOW APPLES.
AH! AH! AH!
OH! OH! OH!
GEEZ, HE'S GOT
A PRETTY GOOD ARM.
YEAH, THEY'RE
ALL MUSCLE.
THIS ONE'S BEEN SCOUTED
BY THE BLUE JAYS.
WELL, HERE, LET'S GIVE
HIM A RED ONE.
MAYBE I'LL JUST TOSS
THIS ONE IN, EH?
OH. OH. OH.
[ GLASS BREAKING ]
THEY DON'T LIKE IT WHEN
YOU THROW IT TO
THEM, RED.
WELL, HE'S GONNA FIT
RIGHT IN WITH THE JAYS.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
FEED HIM ONE, ED.
YOU FEED HIM ONE.
YEAH -- UH, WHAT?
YOU SEEM TO KNOW
EVERYTHING ABOUT THEM.
OH, YEAH, SURE.
OKAY, HERE I COME.
GIVE HIM AN APPLE.
EASY. EASY.
HERE IT COMES.
OH, IT'S FINE.
NO, I THINK HE'S OKAY.
AH! AH! AH!
HE'S OKAY.
YEAH, HE'S OKAY.
[ TASMANIAN DEVIL BELCHES ]
OH, MAN.
WELL, HE SEEMS TO HAVE
SETTLED DOWN A LITTLE, EH?
YEAH, I THINK
HE'S FINE NOW.
AHHH!
[ LAUGHTER ]
I HOPE THAT'S
APPLE JUICE.
EVERY ONCE IN AWHILE IT'S GOOD
TO GET OFF THE BEATEN PATH.
GET OUT TO THE WOODS
TO BE BY YOURSELF
AWAY FROM ALL THE
STUPID QUESTIONS,
LIKE FROM THAT GUY FROM
THE DEPARTMENT OF
HIGHWAYS YELLING,
"HEY, WERE DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
GOING WITH THAT FENCE?"
SO TODAY ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA TURN THIS CAR INTO
AN OFF-ROAD BUSH BUGGY.
FIRST THING WE GOTTA DO IS
TAKE OFF THESE SISSY
STREET TIRES
AND REPLACE THEM WITH
THESE KNOBBY BAD BOYS.
[ CRACKING SOUND ]
NOW, FOR SOME PEOPLE, PUTTING
TIRES ON LIKE THAT
WOULD BE ENOUGH,
BUT SOME PEOPLE AREN'T ME.
SUITS ME FINE;
SUITS THEM EVEN BETTER.
SO INSTEAD, I'M GONNA CUT UP
THE CHAIN LINK FENCE
AND MOUNT HER ON THERE LIKE
A BIG TANK TREAD.
I'VE GOT THESE HEAVY
DUTY TIN SNIPS.
CUT THROUGH THIS
STUFF LIKE BUTTER.
[ GRUNTING ]
FROZEN BUTTER WITH
A TITANIUM COATING.
YOU KNOW, WE GET THE ODD
COMMENT ABOUT THE LACK
OF SAFETY ON OUR SHOW,
SO I'M GOING TO ADD A
LITTLE SAFETY FEATURE
RIGHT AT THIS POINT
AS MY WAY OF
PRETENDING TO CARE.
SOMETIMES WHEN YOU'RE
BUSHWHACKING, YOU'LL
GET PROJECTILES
COMING THROUGH
THE WINDSHIELD...
ROCKS, TREES, WILDLIFE,
THAT KIND OF THING.
SO WHAT I'M GOING TO DO IS
I'M GOING TO WEAR THIS DOG
KENNEL AS A SAFETY CAGE
WHILE I'M DRIVING.
IT WON'T BE THE FIRST TIME
I'VE BEEN IN THE DOG HOUSE.
HOLD ON, I GOT AN IDEA.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
NOW, I'M JUST GONNA ADD A
LITTLE TECHNOLOGY TO THE UNIT.
SOMETHING THAT WILL ALLOW US
TO PINPOINT OUR LOCATION.
IT'LL BE REAL HELPFUL WHEN
WE'RE CALLING FOR THE
RESCUE VEHICLES.
I'M GONNA TAKE THIS
LARGE FIRE HOSE WHEEL
AND I'M GONNA MOUNT THAT
ON THE ROOF OF THE CAR.
I ACTUALLY SWIPED THIS
FROM THE FIRE DEPARTMENT,
BUT I DON'T THINK
THEY'LL MIND.
IT'S RAINY SEASON.
PLUS, I LEFT THEM THE HOSE.
I DON'T NEED THE HOSE.
ONCE I GET THIS UP THERE,
I'M GONNA ATTACH A WHOLE
BUNCH OF GARDEN HOSES
MOUNTED END TO END.
ALL RIGHT, I PROBABLY GOT
A COUPLE DOZEN GARDEN
HOSES ON THERE.
YOU COULD GO WITH
THREE OR FOUR HUN DRED,
IF YOU WANTED TO.
I JUST SWIPED THESE
FROM THE NEIGHBOURS,
BUT I DON'T THINK
THEY'LL MIND.
LIKE I SAY,
IT'S RAINY SEASON.
JUST MAKE SURE YOU
ONLY USE 50-FOOTERS.
AND YOU TAKE A
BIG MARKER LIKE THIS
AND YOU NUMBER EVERY ONE
OF THE CONNECTIONS.
THEN AS YOU'RE DRIVING,
YOU JUST LET HER UNWIND,
AND YOU'LL ALWAYS KNOW
EXACTLY WHERE YOU ARE
WITHIN 50 FEET.
I CALL IT MY G.P.S.,
GARDEN POSITIONING SYSTEM.
( chuckling )
NOW WE'RE JUST ABOUT READY
TO GO WHERE NO MAN HAS
GONE BEFORE.
BUT LET ME SHOW YOU SOMETHING
THAT'S REALLY GONNA CLEAR
A PATH FOR ME.
I'VE ATTACHED A CHAIN SAW
TO ONE SIDE OF THE CAR,
AND I TOOK A BUNCH OF CHAINS
AND PUT THEM END TO END
ALL THE WAY THROUGH TO THAT
CLOTHESLINE PULLEY ON
THE OTHER SIDE.
I DON'T THINK THAT BERNICE WILL
MIND THAT I STOLE HERE
CLOTHESLINE,
'CAUSE LIKE I SAY --
WELL, YOU KNOW.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
[ METAL CREAKING,
CHAIN SAW WHIRRING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
I WANNA TALK TO YOU
MIDDLE-AGED GUYS OUT THERE.
YOU KNOW, BY THE TIME
YOU GET TO OUR AGE,
YOU'VE PRETTY MUCH SEEN IT,
DONE IT, FOUND IT,
LOST IT, WRECKED IT,
FIXED IT, KISSED IT,
MISSED IT,
BOUGHT IT, SHOT IT,
STOPPED IT AND DROPPED IT.
AT THIS POINT YOU'RE THINKING,
"IS THAT ALL THERE IS?"
THE SMART ANSWER IS YES.
BECAUSE IF YOU TRY TO
MAKE YOUR LIFE BETTER NOW,
YOU'RE RISKING A
HEAD-ON COLLISION
WITH THE LAW
OF DIMINISHING RETURNS.
THIS LAW SAYS THAT FOR THINGS
TO BE BETTER THE SECOND
TIME AROUND,
YOU GOTTA WORK WAY HARDER
THAN YOU DID THE FIRST TIME.
DOES THAT MAKE SENSE TO YOU,
FOR A MAN IN YOUR PHYSICAL
AND MENTAL CONDITION,
TO HAVE TO WORK 10 TIMES
HARDER TO MAKE YOUR
LIFE 5% BETTER?
OF COURSE NOT.
DON'T ROCK THE BOAT.
MAYBE YOU GOT
A 40-YEAR MORTGAGE
AND A 30-YEAR MARRIAGE,
AND YOU'RE BARELY MEETING YOUR
OBLIGATIONS ON EACH OF THEM.
MAYBE YOU'VE GOT A CAR THAT'S
AS OLD AS YOUR ADULT SON,
BUT AT LEAST IT WORKS.
HEY, MAYBE YOU'LL
NEVER BE PRESIDENT,
BUT ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
YOU'LL NEVER BE PRESIDENT.
SO DON'T MESS WITH THE LAW
OF DIMINISHING RETURNS.
THE DIVORCE COURTS AND THE
CARDIAC CARE UNITS
ARE FULL OF GUYS JUST
LIKE YOU AND ME,
EXCEPT THEY FOUGHT THE
LAW AND THE LAW WON.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, I HAD THE
DNA TEST DONE.
THAT WAS NO FUN.
THIS NURSE COMES AT ME WITH
A NEEDLE THE SIZE OF A
CAULKING GUN.
I TRIED TO GET OUT OF THERE,
BUT SHE CHASED AFTER ME.
SHE WRESTLED ME TO THE GROUND;
SHE PUTS ME IN A HALF-NELSON.
SHE DIDN'T LOOK THAT STRONG,
BUT A LOT OF THOSE
SENIORS ARE WIRY.
WHAT?
HEY, RED!
GOOD NEWS, YOUR DNA
WAS A MATCH.
YOU'RE IN THE
MONEY TOO!
WELL, HOW DOES THIS --
LET ME SEE YOURS AGAIN.
THESE ARE KINDA SIMILAR.
OH, MY GOSH.
SIMILAR?
THEY'RE EXACTLY
THE SAME, DALTON!
THAT MEANS YOU
AND I MUST BE --
IDENTICAL TWINS!
HEY, GUYS!
I'M A FARNSWORTH.
OH, NO.
WAIT A SECOND.
THIS HAS GOTTEN
WAY OUTTA HAND.
IF EVERYONE IN
THE POSSUM LAKE
AREA HAS THE SAME DNA,
AND WE'VE ALL BEEN
MARRYING EACH OTHER --
ACTUALLY, THAT
EXPLAINS A LOT.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T CARE,
AS LONG AS I GET MY
CHUNK OF THE MILLION.
OH, WELL,
SOME CHUNK.
WE'RE EACH GONNA
GET 10 BUCKS,
AND THE DNA
TEST COST 15.
YEAH, WELL, I'LL GET MORE
BECAUSE I HAVE TWO SHARES.
MIKE, GETTING TESTED
TWICE DOESN'T COUNT.
I DIDN'T.
THIS IS MY DOG'S CHART.
[ RED MUTTERING ]
HI, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
WHEN THE AFFAIR IS OVER
THE LAST THING YOU WANT
IS A LINGERING GOOD-BYE.
YOU'RE OUT IN
YOUR BACKYARD, RIGHT,
REPAIRING YOUR FENCE.
AND THOSE CUTE LITTLE
JONES KIDS FROM NEXT DOOR
GATHER AROUND
TO HAVE A LOOK.
IT'S PRETTY WELL RIGHT OUT
OF A NORMAN ROCKWELL
PAINTING.
YEAH, OR AT LEAST IT WAS,
UNTIL YOU HAMMERED
YOUR THUMB ABOUT AN
INCH INTO THAT FENCE POST.
AND THAT'S WHEN
YOU TREATED THOSE CUTE
LITTLE PRE-SCHOOL JONES KIDS
TO THE RICH TAPESTRY AND
DIVERSITY THAT IS THE
ENGLISH LANGUAGE.
YES, AND YOUR PITHY
REFERENCES TO ACTS THAT
ARE ANATOMICALLY IMPOSSIBLE
AND ILLEGAL EVERYWHERE
EXCEPT CALIFORNIA.
YEAH, THOSE LITTLE
JONES KIDS WERE PRETTY
IMPRESSED ALL RIGHT.
MAYBE EVEN IMPRESSED
ENOUGH TO TRY OUT SOME
OF THOSE WORDS
BACK AT THE JONES' HOME.
AND THAT'S GONNA LEAD
TO A VISIT FROM THEIR FATHER,
THE REVEREND JONES.
HE IS GOING TO ASK SOME
VERY DIFFICULT QUESTIONS.
BUT DON'T WORRY.
HERE'S THE PLAN.
YOU GO DOWN TO THE PLAYGROUND
WHERE THE JONES KIDS AND
THEIR FRIENDS HANG OUT.
AND YOU TAKE A
TAPE RECORDER, RIGHT.
THEN YOU HIDE BEHIND A TREE
AND RECORD WHAT THE KIDS
SAY TO EACH OTHER
WHEN THERE'S
NO ADULTS AROUND.
YOU WILL CAPTURE PHRASES
THAT WOULD BLANCHE
A KUMQUAT.
AND WHEN THE REVEREND COMES
BY TO CONFRONT YOU WITH
THE GUTTER LANGUAGE
THAT HIS LITTLE ANGELS HAVE
LEARNED FROM YOU --
YEAH!
THE TAPE.
YOU PLAY HIM
HE'LL RECOGNIZE
THE VOICES.
OH, YEAH, HE'LL HEAR
THE CALL ALL RIGHT.
PERHAPS THOSE LITTLE JONES
BOYS WILL BE CONFINED TO
HOME FOR A FEW DAYS.
YEAH, AND THEN YOU CAN GET
BACK TO SLAMMING YOUR FINGERS
AND EXPLORING
THE DICTIONARY.
BUT DON'T THANK US.
THAT'S WHAT
FRIENDS ARE FOR!
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red: YOUNG WALTER AND MIKE
HAD ASKED ME COME --
THEY'RE GONNA
HAVE A CONTEST
TO SEE WHO IS THE
WORLD'S STRONGEST MAN.
JUST AGAINST THE TWO OF THEM,
BUT I HAD A PLAQUE MADE UP.
LOOKS PRETTY GOOD.
AND THEY'RE FILLING THE OIL
DRUMS WITH WATER THERE.
AND THEY GOTTA HOLD THEM
UP OVER THERE HEAD.
WHOEVER CAN HOLD IT
UP THE LONGEST WINS.
IT'S A TWO-PARTER.
THIS IS THE FIRST PART.
THERE'S A SECOND PART.
I FIGURE THESE THINGS
WEIGH ABOUT 500 POUNDS.
AND, LIKE, WALTER'S
IN PRETTY GOOD SHAPE,
MIKE IS --
HE'S JUST THERE, BASICALLY.
HIS RING CAN SLIP OFF
HIS FINGER EITHER WAY.
UP THEY GO,
AND LOOK AT THIS.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
COULDN'T BELIEVE MY EYES.
AND THEN HE
STARTS SHOWING OFF.
OH, MY GOSH.
MUST BE A LOT OF --
[ WALTER GROANING ]
NO PROBLEM.
SO MIKE --
I DON'T KNOW HOW HE DID IT.
OH, YES, I DO.
NOW, THE SECOND PART.
THE BIG KILLER.
AND MIKE IS ACTUALLY PUTTING
SOME EXTRA BAR ON HIS,
BUT THEY GOTTA PULL
THE CARS BY HAND.
HE PUT THE SECOND BAR ON
THERE, JUST ADDS WEIGHT.
KIND OF STUPID.
ONE, TWO, THREE
AND AWAY YOU GO.
AWAY THEY GO,
AND WALTER'S OFF.
MIKE'S NOT MOVING AN INCH.
OH, I SEE.
I GOT IT, YEAH.
I SEE.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, OKAY.
NOW HE'S GOT A PROBLEM.
BUT LOOK,
HE'S GOT MORE ROPE!
AND HE'S THE WINNER --
[ CRASH ]
BUT I THOUGHT I NEEDED TO
ALTER THE PLAQUE A
LITTLE BIT
AND CHANGE THE
"O" TO AN "A"
BECAUSE THAT'S THE WORLD'S
STRANGEST MAN RIGHT THERE.
REMEMBER WHEN
YOU WERE A KID
AND YOU USED TO GO
EVERYWHERE ON YOUR BIKE?
NOW MAYBE AS AN ADULT YOU'D
LIKE TO DO THE SAME THING.
SAVE A FEW DOLLARS,
OR MAYBE YOUR LICENSE
HAS BEEN SUSPENDED.
THE PROBLEM IS THAT YOU'RE NOT
AS SUITED TO BIKE RIDING
AS YOU USED TO BE.
AFTER 20 YEARS OF MARRIAGE,
YOU'VE LOST A LOT OF BALANCE.
AND NOW MAYBE YOUR
POSTERIOR HAS EXCEEDED
THE DESIGN LIMITATIONS
OF THE BICYCLE SEAT.
[ POP ]
IT'S A BOY.
I KNOW I COULD GO ON A DIET
AND START WORKING OUT
AND WHATEVER.
I PREFER IT WHEN
REALITY ADAPTS TO ME
RATHER THAN THE
OTHER WAY AROUND.
SO GET YOURSELF A COUPLE OF
BIKES, A FEW HOCKEY STICKS
AND A PARK BENCH
AND DO A LITTLE CUSTOMIZING.
[ RINGING BICYCLE BELL ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
WE NOW COME TO THAT
PORTION OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE ADDRESS THOSE THREE
LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
AND, UH, TODAY'S
LETTER READS...
"DEAR EXPERTS, I AM IN MY
SECOND YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL
"AND WILL PROBABLY BE
GRADUATING IN A DECADE OR SO.
"I WAS WONDERING IF YOU HAVE
ANY SUGGESTIONS
"AS TO WHAT LINE OF WORK
I SHOULD GET INTO.
"SIGNED, NO BIG RUSH."
OKAY, WELL, I WOULD RECOMMEND
THAT YOU RUN A LODGE UP NORTH.
NOBODY PUTS ANY
EXPECTATIONS ON YOU,
AND YOU SURE CAN'T
BEAT THE DRESS CODE.
CAN YOU MAKE A
LIVING AT THAT?
OH, YEAH, AS LONG AS
YOUR WIFE HAS A GOOD JOB.
SEE, I'VE BEEN IN THE
FUNERAL BUSINESS FOR
THE LAST 15 YEARS,
AND IT'S A HOOT.
AND GOOD COIN TOO,
NOT JUST IN THE POCKETS.
WELL, YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT
JUST ABOUT MONEY, YOU KNOW.
I THINK THAT IT'S
IMPORTANT THAT YOU
DO SOMETHING YOU ENJOY.
OH, SO PETTY THEFT WAS A
CAREER CHOICE FOR YOU, WAS IT?
OH, I'M NOT RECOMMENDING
IT AS A LIFESTYLE.
THAT WAS ONE OF THE
CONDITIONS OF MY PAROLE.
CRIME DOESN'T PAY,
RIGHT, MIKE?
WELL, IT DOES,
BUT IT'S NOT STEADY.
OKAY, WELL, I RECOMMEND THAT
THIS GUY GETS HIMSELF INTO
ONE OF THE
GROWTH INDUSTRIES.
THAT'S WHAT I LIKED
ABOUT THE LODGE
BECAUSE WE GET MORE
CUSTOMERS EVERY YEAR.
WELL, SO DO WE.
YEAH, BUT NOT REALLY
REPEAT CUSTOMERS,
EXCEPT FOR
SHIRLEY MacLAINE.
WELL, HOW'S YOUR
BALANCE SHEET LOOK?
OH, WE'RE DOING
PRETTY GOOD.
WELL, WE HAVE AN OPERATING
CAPITAL THAT'S COMPLETELY
SELF-FINANCED.
WE HAVE AN OVERALL YEAR
OVER YEAR INCREASE
IN NET INCOME,
17% AFTER TAXES.
AND OUR CAPITAL INVESTMENT HAS
INCREASED THE EQUITY QUOTIENT
OF OUR PORTFOLIO HOLDERS
UP TO 23% A SHARE.
WE'RE DOING PRETTY GOOD.
WELL, LIKE I SAY, ALL I HAVE
TO DO IS LOOK AT,
SAY, THE RETIREMENT RATE,
AND I KNOW ALL THOSE PEOPLE
ARE GONNA COME UP TO THE LODGE
FOR A COUPLE OF WEEKS,
YOU KNOW, THIS SUMMER.
WELL, ALL I DO IS CHECK
THE BIRTHRATE ABOUT
75 YEARS AGO.
LET'S ME KNOW WHAT KIND
OF YEAR I'M GONNA HAVE.
WELL, MAYBE THIS KID SHOULD
COMBINE THE TWO BUSINESSES.
HAVE A COMBINATION LODGE
AND FUNERAL HOME.
AND THEN YOU GET PEOPLE
COMING AND GOING.
WELL, THE MYSTERY
HAS BEEN SOLVED.
SHAKY FARNSWORTH IS
NOT THE FOUNDING FATHER
WE WERE AFRAID
HE MIGHT BE.
THERE WAS A PROBLEM
WITH THE DNA TESTING.
NOT REALLY THE TESTING.
IT WAS THE CONTAINERS
THAT HAD THE PROBLEM.
SOMEBODY STOLE ALL
THE TEST TUBES,
WHICH WAS JUST
A SENSELESS THEFT.
THEY'RE ALMOST
IMPOSSIBLE TO FENCE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
SO INSTEAD OF
TEST TUBES,
THEY USED LIDS OFF
OF MASON JARS
FROM THE BIG-BOY
PICKLE FACTORY.
AND I'M TALKING THE EXTRA
SPICY WITH MEGA-CRUNCH.
SO THE DEAL IS THAT WHAT
WE ENDED UP TESTING
WAS THE CHEMICAL
EVALUATION OF PICKLE JUICE.
AND THAT'S WHY ALL THE
TESTS CAME OUT THE SAME.
AND THE FACT THAT SHAKY WAS
ALWAYS PICKLED HIMSELF.
BUT THE GOOD NEWS IS
THAT WE GOT OURSELVES
ALL RE-TESTED.
AND WE ARE, IN FACT,
DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
YEAH, YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
MEETING TIME.
OKAY.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
UM, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I LEARNED TODAY THAT IF
YOU GO FATHERING CHILDREN
ALL OVER TOWN,
YOU'RE GONNA END
UP IN A PICKLE,
AND I'M TALKING THE
EXTRA SPICY WITH MEGA-CRUNCH.
AND THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND WHOLE
GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR
STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT, SIT, SIT.
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
All: I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF HAVE TO, I GUESS.
Red: ALL RIGHT, MEN, WE'VE ALL
HAD THE DNA TESTING DONE NOW,
AND I WOULD JUST LIKE TO SAY
THAT ANYONE WHO CAN PROVE
THAT THEY'RE
NOT RELATED TO ME,
IS WELCOME AT
MY HOUSE ANY TIME.