♪ ♪ ♪
>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN
IN TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD
GOES STAG DANCING,
BILL SHOWS YOU HOW
TO CUT THE LAWN,
AND I'M GOING TO TURN
A CAR INTO A WHOLE SET
OF LIVING ROOM FURNITURE.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(SHATTERING GLASS)
>>HAROLD: HE'S WARM,
HE'S CUDDLY, HE'S FURRY
AND HE HANGS AROUND
IN THE FOREST
I GUESS THAT'S WHY THEY
CALL HIM 'THE POSSUM'
PUT YOUR HANDS TOGETHER
MORE THAN ONCE FOR THE STAR
OF OUR SHOW, MR. RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
THANK YOU FOR TUNING US IN
AND IF YOU DO SEE SOMETHING
THAT YOU DON'T LIKE JUST
BLAME HAROLD ESPECIALLY
IF IT IS HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: WELL UNCLE RED
AS THE DIRECTOR/PRODUCER
I TAKE ALL THE BLAME
OF COURSE I ALSO TAKE
ALL THE CREDIT.
>>RED: WELL I THINK YOU JUST
EXCEEDED YOUR CREDIT LIMIT
THERE HAROLD.
BIG BIG WEEK AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK THE SALMON ARE
RUNNING IN MERCURY CREEK,
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK SAYS THAT
THAT'S THE FIRST FISH THAT
HE'S SEEN IN THERE IN
LIVING MEMORY, WHICH IS
AMAZING BECAUSE LIVING
AND MEMORY ARE 2 THINGS HE
DOESN'T HAVE A LOT LEFT OF.
>>HAROLD: WOW THAT'S AMAZING!
MERCURY CREEK'S REALLY MAKING
A COMEBACK EVER SINCE THEY
CLOSED THE PAPER MILL.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>HAROLD: AND OF COURSE THE
ASBESTOS MINE AND YOU KNOW
THEN THE PAINT FACTORY AND
THE OIL REFINERY.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH, WHO SAYS
FREE TRADE HASN'T BEEN GOOD
FOR US EH HAROLD.
WHO NEEDS JOBS WHEN
YOU'VE GOT SALMON RIGHT?
YOU CAN'T EAT JOBS.
>>HAROLD: OF COURSE YOU
CAN'T EAT THAT SALMON
THOUGH EITHER.
>>RED: BUT WE WANTED TO
HAVE SOME KIND OF AN EVENT
YOU KNOW TO COMMEMORATE
THE RETURN OF THE SALMON.
>>HAROLD: OH PLEASE NOT
A SALMON FEAST, OH YOU DON'T
WANT TO PUT ONE OF THOSE
SALMONS IN YOUR MOUTH
OH THAT DOES NOT MAKE FOR
GOOD EATING I'LL TELL YOU
ALL THAT MERCURY,
IT MIGHT MAKE A GOOD
THERMOMETER THOUGH.
>>RED: YEAH AND YOU STILL
WOULDN'T HAVE TO STICK
THEM IN YOUR MOUTH.
NO, NO, WE'RE THINKING
MORE OF HAVING A SALMON
PARADE YOU KNOW WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE A PARADE THAT WILL
GO RIGHT FROM POSSUM LODGE
ALL THE WAY INTO TOWN
AND OF COURSE THE THEME OF
THE PARADE WILL BE SALMON.
>>HAROLD: GOOD.
>>RED: SO WE'RE TELLING
ALL THE PARTICIPANTS TO MAKE
SOMETHING THAT KIND OF
CAPTURES THE SPIRIT OF
THE SALMON IN MERCURY CREEK.
>>HAROLD: WELL I GUESS
THERE'S GOING TO BE LOTS
OF FLOATS THEN.
♪ IN MURPHY'S BUSH ♪
♪ THE TREES ARE TALL ♪
♪ WITH MOSS AND FUNGUS ON THEM ♪
♪ ALL MURPHY'S BUSH HAS ♪
♪ BRAMBLES TOO ♪
♪ WITH SHOOTS AND ROOTS ♪
♪ AND SWAMP AND GOO ♪
♪ I MAY PULL ♪
♪ AND YOU MAY PUSH ♪
♪ BUT IT'S REALLY REALLY HARD ♪
♪ TO DRAG A DEAD MOOSE ♪
♪ THROUGH MURPHY'S BUSH ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER'
WE'RE GOING TO TALK
ABOUT RECYCLING.
NOW WE'VE GOT AN OLD CAR HERE
THAT ORDINARILY WOULD BE
READY FOR THE DUMP
OR AS WE CALL IT HERE AT
THE LODGE THE MALL.
BUT INSTEAD OF JUST ROLLING
THIS INTO A RAVINE OR
BURYING IT SOMEWHERE
OR TRYING TO SELL IT ON
THAT HOME RIPOFF CHANNEL
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW YOU CAN DO A LITTLE
RECYCLING AND TURN THIS OLD
CAR INTO WHOLE HOUSE FULL
OF FINE FURNITURE.
FOR EXAMPLE HERE'S A COUPLE
OF GOOD LOOKING SEATS IN THERE
AND NOW WHAT WE HAVE IS A
REAL NICE LIVING ROOM COUCH
AND THE BACKSEAT HERE BECOMES
OF COURSE A MATCHING LOVESEAT.
FINALLY A LOVESEAT WITH PROOF!
AND YOU KNOW THERE'S OTHER
STUFF THAT YOU CAN GET OUT
OF A CAR LIKE I LOOK OVER
HERE AND I SAY WELL BY GOLLY
THERE'S A COUPLE OF NICE
LAMPS THERE, AND HOW ABOUT
THIS BUMPER WOULDN'T THAT
MAKE JUST AN EXCELLENT
FIREPLACE GRILL?
IF YOU LIKE SCANDINAVIAN
FURNITURE YOU COULD DO THIS
WITH SAY A VOLVO OR A SAAB
OR IF YOU WANTED LAWN
FURNITURE USE A LADA.
WELL IS THIS COZY OR WHAT?
I'VE GOT THE HEADLIGHTS SETUP
TOP HERE AND I'VE GOT
THE JUMPER CABLES RUNNING
ACROSS THE BATTERY AND
WHAT YOU CAN DO IS HOOKUP
A HIGH BEAM SWITCH AND FIRE
HER ONTO HIGH BEAMS WHEN YOU
WANT TO READ THE TV GUIDE.
AND HERE'S ANOTHER BONUS,
IF YOU HANG THIS ON YOUR
FRONT DOOR AND YOU GOT
YOURSELF A REALLY UNIQUE
AND INTERESTING DOORBELL.
(HORN HONKS)
AND YOU KNOW YOU'RE
THINKING WOULDN'T A LITTLE
MUSIC GO GOOD NOW?
WELL HOW ABOUT THE CAR RADIO,
YOU WERE GOING TO THROW THAT
THING OUT AND IT COMES WITH
A BUILT IN STEREO SYSTEM
WITH BUILT IN SPEAKERS.
TAKE A LOOK AT THAT,
WE'LL GET MOOSE THOMPSON
TO LIE DOWN AND WEDGE
HIS HEAD BETWEEN THOSE
AND PUT ON SOME CLOGGING
MUSIC AND HE PRACTICALLY
KICKS THE WALLS DOWN.
OH IT'S A GREAT SETUP
SEATING FOR EVERYBODY AND
WE'VE GOT THE GREAT FIREPLACE
SETUP HERE WITH THE BUMPER
AND SO ON BUT TO ME NOW IT
JUST SCREAMS FOR A COFFEE TABLE
SOMETHING THAT YOU CAN PUT
THE TV CONVERTER ON THE ODD
TIME WHEN YOU DO ACTUALLY
SET IT DOWN,
LET'S GET OURSELVES
A COFFEE TABLE.
NOW TO ME THE ROOF WOULD MAKE
AN IDEAL COFFEE TABLE
SO STEP ONE IS TO REMOVE
THE ROOF, ACTUALLY THAT'S
THE ONLY STEP...
AND YOU CAN USE A SAW
WITH THAT OR ONE OF THOSE
ELECTRIC KNIVES OR WHAT HAVE
YOU OR JUST WAIT UNTIL IT
RUSTS OFF BUT I DON'T HAVE
THAT KIND OF TIME SO I LIKE
USING THE OXYACETYLENE
CUTTING TORCH AND THESE TO
ME I'VE BEEN MESSING WITH
THESE FOR YEARS AND THEY'RE
A VERY EFFECTIVE TOOL BUT
YOU'VE GOT TO PROTECT
YOUR EYES OF COURSE.
I THINK I STARTED USING
THESE WHEN I WAS AROUND
10, 11, 12, 13 I GUESS
I WAS AROUND 6 OR 7 YEARS OLD.
THAT'S NOT WORKING TOO GOOD
SO I'M JUST I'VE GOT A
LIGHTER HERE AND I'LL
GET THAT GOING,
(INHALING DEEPLY)
BOY YOU CAN SURE SMELL
THAT ACETYLENE.
WHERE'S THE TORCH?
WHERE IS THAT TORCH?
(LOUD EXPLOSION)
>>RED: ALRIGHT THAT'S GOT HER.
(COUGHS) OH HERE SHE COMES
NOW FREE DELIVERY.
MAN TO THINK YOU WERE GOING
TO THROW THIS STUFF OUT HUH?
REMEMBER UNTIL NEXT TIME
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY,
OH THIS IS GREAT ISN'T IT?
♪ CAR STEREO PLAYS ♪
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S TIME TO
EXPOSE THOSE 3 LITTLE WORDS THAT
MEN FIND SO DIFFICULT TO SAY
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE ONCE AGAIN TO
PROVE THAT POINT ON THE
EXPERT FEATURE OF OUR PROGRAM
IS MY UNCLE RED AND HIS
GOOD FRIEND MR. GLEN BRAXTON.
>>HAROLD: OKAY, 'DEAR EXPERTS
MY BROTHER IS GAY,
MY BROTHER IS GAY AND I TRIED
TO TALK HIM OUT OF IT
BUT HE SAYS HE WAS BORN
THIS WAY HOW CAN I GET HIM TO
STRAIGHTEN OUT AND FLY RIGHT?'
>>GLEN: WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
LOOKING AT ME FOR?
I'M AN EXPERT ON BOATS
AND R.V.'S AND HUNTING.
>>RED: YEAH I KNOW GLEN
BUT I JUST THOUGHT MAYBE
YOU KNOW YOU COULD.
>>GLEN: RED I'M MARRIED
I'VE GOT 7 KIDS
I GOT 7 KIDS AT HOME PAL.
>>RED: I KNOW I JUST
THOUGHT YOU WOULD BE MORE
COMFORTABLE WITH THE.
>>GLEN: RED HEY I DON'T
THINK YOU GOT ANY KIDS
DO YOU RED?
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY KIDS!
NOW GO AHEAD FEEL THAT,
FEEL THAT, GO AHEAD RIGHT
THERE COME ON NO FEEL IT,
COME ON HERE FEEL IT
HERE HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: I'D RATHER NOT.
>>GLEN: I BUILD OUTBOARD
MOTORS EVERY DAY
DON'T TELL ME.
>>RED: ALRIGHT ALRIGHT
I JUST THOUGHT YOU'D FEEL MORE
COMFORTABLE YOU GOT THE KIDS
YOU KNOW AND EVERYTHING
YOU'RE SO MASCULINE
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE FINE.
>>GLEN: YEAH, YOU BET.
>>RED: MIND YOU GLEN
YOUR KIDS ARE ALL GIRLS.
>>GLEN: SO?
>>HAROLD: WELL EXCUSE ME
I JUST THINK WHAT MY UNCLE
IS TRYING TO SAY IN HIS
PRIMITIVE POLITICALLY
INCORRECT WAY IS THAT YOU
KNOW BEING THE FATHER OF
7 DAUGHTERS PERHAPS YOU'D
BE MORE IN TOUCH WITH YOUR
FEMININE SIDE THAN THE
OTHER GUYS AROUND HERE.
>>GLEN: WHOA! WHOA!
FEMININE SIDE HAROLD,
I DON'T HAVE A FEMININE SIDE
I'VE GOT 2 SIDES FRONT AND BACK
AND THEY'RE BOTH MASCULINE OKAY.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
>>RED: GEEZ FOR GOSH SAKE
DON'T PROVE IT FOR US.
LOOK, LOOK, ALRIGHT IF
YOU'RE UNCOMFORTABLE WITH THIS.
>>GLEN: I'M NOT UNCOMFORTABLE
NO, NO, I WISH THERE WERE
MORE GAY GUYS IN THE WORLD
THEN I WOULDN'T HAVE TO
WATCH MY TEENAGE DAUGHTERS
LIKE A HAWK.
>>HAROLD: OKAY I THINK
WE'VE OFFENDED EVERYBODY WITH
ANY SENSITIVITY NOW SO WHY
DON'T WE JUST WRAP THIS UP.
>>GLEN: NO, NO, NO, I CAN
ANSWER THIS, I MEAN YOU CAN'T
TALK SOMEBODY OUT OF BEING
GAY YOU KNOW YOU SEE IT'S
BIOLOGICAL, LIVE AND LET LIVE
DO WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
YOU KNOW JUST MIND YOUR
OWN BUSINESS.
>>HAROLD: WOW COOL ANSWER
MR. BRAXTON, BOY I WISH
MORE GUYS AROUND HERE HAD
SENSITIVITY LIKE YOU.
>>RED: WHY IS THAT HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: NO, NO, NO WAY
NO FEEL THAT, FEEL THAT.
>>BOB: OH! OH! OH!
>>RED: WHAT DO YOU CALL
THAT CLUB BOB, TREE IRON?
I THOUGHT WE MIGHT NEED SOME
KIND OF A PERMIT TO HAVE OUR
SALMON PARADE SO I WENT OVER
TO TALK TO BOB STUYVESON
ABOUT THAT BECAUSE HE WORKS
FOR THE GOVERNMENT AND ANOTHER
THING IS IT'S EASY TO FIND
BOB CAUSE YOU KNOW HE'S
ALWAYS ON THE GOLF COURSE
AND HE CLAIMS HE'S ACTUALLY
WORKING THERE YOU KNOW
HE'S TAKING AIR TEMPERATURE
READINGS AND SOIL HUMIDITY
AND WIND AND WEATHER AND
STUFF AND THAT THE GOLF
IS ACTUALLY JUST A FAKE.
>>BOB: THIS GOLF THING IS
JUST A COVER, ANY POLLUTERS
SEE ME THEN THEY JUST FIGURE
I'M JUST ANOTHER GOLFER.
>>RED: UNLESS THEY SEE
YOU GOLF...
WELL HOW'S THE AIR TEMPERATURE
AND SOIL HUMIDITY TODAY BOB?
>>BOB: WHAT? OH YEAH
IT SEEMS FINE I'M MORE CONCERNED
WITH THINNING TREES TODAY RED.
>>RED: I'LL GET OUT
OF YOUR WAY HERE.
(THUD OF BALL HITTING TREE)
>>BOB: YEAH THERE'S
ANOTHER ONE THAT'S
GOT TO COME DOWN.
>>RED: OH GOSH DOING
A LITTLE EXCAVATING TOO ARE
YOU BOB TRYING TO BUILD A
SUBDIVISION IN THAT DIVET?
>>BOB: AERATING RED IT'S
THE BEST WAY TO GET OXYGEN
INTO THE SOIL.
>>RED: ALRIGHT.
>>BOB: LISTEN MAYBE YOU'D
LIKE TO JOIN ME IN MY GAME OF
GOLF YOU CAN PLAY FROM WHERE
I LIE, THAT WAY IT WOULD HELP
WITH YOUR RECOVERY SHOTS.
>>RED: OH NO BOB I'M NOT
AS GOOD A GOLFER AS YOU BOB
I COULD NEVER RECOVER FROM YOUR
LIES BUT YOU KNOW I DID WANT
TO ASK YOU DO WE NEED A
PERMIT TO HAVE OUR
SALMON PARADE?
>>BOB: I DON'T THINK SO
YOU'RE NOT EXPECTING
A BIG CROWD ARE YOU.
>>RED: OH NO I MEAN THERE'S
ONLY 50 GUYS IN THE LODGE
AND MOST OF THEM ARE IN THE
PARADE SO I WOULD SAY
UNDER A 1,000.
>>BOB: IT COULD EVEN BE
UNDER 10.
NOW RED COULD YOU HELP
ME OUT FOR MY BALL?
>>RED: OH SURE IT WENT
IN HERE I THINK.
>>BOB: OH NEVER MIND
FOUND IT IT'S RIGHT HERE.
>>RED: ARE YOU SURE BOB?
THERE'S A BALL BACK HERE
BEHIND THIS ROCK IT'S A SUPER
DOT 3, WHAT ARE YOU HITTING.
>>BOB: THIS ONE.
>>RED: NO YOU'RE NOT.
>>RED: WELL THE PARADE
TO CELEBRATE THE RETURN
OF SALMON TO MERCURY CREEK
IS ON, EVERYBODY IS
BUILDING A FLOAT,
BUSTER HADFIELD COMPLETELY
REDID HIS TRUCK,
IT LOOKS LIKE A TRUCK NOW.
AND MOOSE THOMPSON IS HELPING
ME WE DUCT TAPED ONE OF THEM
ABOVE GROUND POOLS TO THE
ROOF OF THE POSSUM VAN,
WE'RE GOING TO PAINT HER
ALL RED AND GO AS A GIANT
CAN OF PACIFIC SALMON.
>>HAROLD: STINKY PETERSON
DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO THAT
WOULD CAPTURE THE TRUE ESSENCE
OF A SALMON SO JUNIOR SINGLETON
HE SUGGESTED THAT STINKY JUST
STAND DOWNWIND OF HIMSELF
FOR A MINUTE,
WELL STINKY TOOK EXCEPTION
TO THAT REMARK
SO NOW JUNIOR IS ENTERING
THE SALMON PARADE AS
A SOCKEYE.
>>RED: WELL OF COURSE
I'M GOING TO BE THE GRAND
MARSHAL OF THE PARADE AND
I'LL BE LEADING EVERYBODY
IN SINGLE FILE FROM POSSUM
LODGE RIGHT DOWN TO MEMORIAL
PARK WHERE WE'LL HEAR A
SPEECH BY THE MAYOR AND THEN
WE'LL ALL WAKE UP AND HAVE
A PARTY.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
DO FOR THE PARADE HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: I'M GOING AS
A ONE MAN BAND.
>>RED: THAT WOULD BE
PRETTY MUCH THE STORY OF
YOUR LIFE WOULD IT NOT.
>>HAROLD: WELL I'M GOING TO
GO AS ONE OF THOSE GUYS THAT
CRANKS THE CALLIOPE YOU KNOW
AND THEN THE MONKEY JUMPS
AROUND ON THE STRING
AND EVERYTHING.
>>RED: WELL THAT SOUNDS KIND
OF CUTE HAROLD, NOT REALLY
ANYTHING TO DO WITH SALMON
BUT OKAY LET ME KNOW IF YOU
NEED ME TO BE THE GUY
CRANKING THE CALLIOPE.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
♪ 99 BOTTLES OF BEER ♪
♪ ON THE WALL ♪
♪ I DON'T CARE WHAT ♪
♪ ANYBODY SAYS ♪
♪ IT'S MY DEN ♪
♪ I'LL DECORATE IT ♪
♪ THE WAY I WANT ♪
>>RED: THIS IS A LITTLE
SAFETY TIP, THIS WEEK IF
YOU'RE EVER OUT IN THE LONG
GRASS BE AWFUL CAREFUL OF
BENDING OVER PICKING ANYTHING
UP WHEN SAY SOMEBODY IS
COMING ALONG IN A VAN.
BUT WE KNOW WE'RE HAPPY TO SERVE
THIS PURPOSE OF SHOWING YOU WHAT
NOT TO IN THE LONG GRASS,
ARE YOU OKAY THERE BILL?
HE'S ALRIGHT WELL HE WAS
GRILLED FOR QUESTIONING.
ALRIGHT SO HIS NOSE IS BACK
CROOKED THE WAY IT SHOULD BE
AND HE'S LOOKING, OH HE
DROPPED THE SHEARS BECAUSE
BILL'S PLANNING THIS WEEK
BECAUSE HE WANTED TO CUT THE
LAWN OUT IN THE BACK OF THE
LODGE AND MAN THAT
HASN'T BEEN CUT...
>>BILL: OH! OH!
>>RED: OH WELL SLIPPERY STUFF
OUT THERE AND THE GOOD NEWS
IS HE FOUND THE SHEARS.
OH WELL THAT'S WHAT THEY
CALL A PAIR OF SHEARS!
NOW YOU'VE GOT 2 SINGLES.
WELL NOW LOOK AT THAT
OH YEAH LIKE THE OLD DAYS
THE OLD WAYS, THE OLD DAYS,
WELL THAT BRINGS BACK A
LOT OF FEELINGS OF MY GRAND
DADDY OH LOOK AT THAT
THE SCYTHE, YOU KNOW THE
OLD SCYTHE AND SICKLE
YOU KNOW SICKLE SCYTHES
SCYTHE AND SICKLE WHOA!
WHOA! WHOA! PUT YOU IN
THE HOSPITAL YOU KNOW.
OH CAREFUL NOW
CAREFUL, CAREFUL, CAREFUL,
BOY SHE'S IN THE CLAY HERE
IT'S A LITTLE STICKY
WELL GIVE HER A GOOD GIVE HER
A GOOD HOIST THERE.
OH, OH, OH, WELL THE BLADE
IS NO, NO, BILL THERE'S NO
BLADE ON THAT BILL.
BLADE BILL, THE BLADE IS
WELL IT'S MISSING BUT IT'LL
BE BACK IN A MINUTE THERE.
BILL JUST STAND BILL RIGHT
THERE AND HOLD YOUR ARMS OUT
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH
THERE IT IS YEAH CAME OUT
OF THE SKY BILL YEAH THAT
BLADE CAME OUT OF THE SKY
BILL YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
OH THAT'S RIGHT.
YEAH, YEAH, WELL IT'S TOO
LATE NOW BILL IT MISSED YOU.
SO NOW HE SAYS ALRIGHT
LET'S MECHANIZE THE THING
NOW THIS IS A GAS LAWN MOWER
AND YOU KNOW THE DARN THING
A LOT OF TIMES THEY TAKE
7 OR 800 PULLS BUT BILL'S
GOT THAT FIGURED, WHAT HE
DOES IS HE PUT A REAL LONG
PULL ROPE ON THAT THING.
YEAH THERE WE GO AND AND GET
HER GOING ONE MORE, ONE MORE,
ONE MORE, ONE MORE, ONE MORE
YEAH THAT'S IT, THAT'S IT
OH, OH, BY GOLLY IT'S ONE
OF THOSE SELF DRIVEN ONES,
EXCELLENT!
WELL WE'LL CATCH YOU LATER BILL.
WELL THAT DIDN'T WORKOUT SO THEN
HE BROUGHT OUT ONE OF THEM
ELECTRICAL NOW TO ME THE
ELECTRIC MOWER JUST DOESN'T
HAVE THE POWER OF THE GAS
WELL BILL I DON'T THINK YOU
KNOW THEY JUST YEAH ZAP, ZAP,
THAT'S NOT GOING TO DO IT
NOW WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO,
OH LOOK WHOSE COMING THROUGH,
YEAH WE'LL WAIT HERE BILL.
WHAT'S HE GOING TO DO?
OH TAKING THE HANDLE OFF,
WHAT DO YOU WANT THE
HANDLE FOR BILL?
IT'S ALREADY GOT A HANDLE
ON THE ELECTRIC ONE
YOU DON'T NEED...
OH FOR GOSH SAKES!
OKAY OKAY GOING TO MOUNT
THE OTHER HANDLE ON THERE AND
YOU GOT A HANDLE ON EACH END
AND NOW WE CAN YEAH,
WE CAN PICK HER UP AND THAT
WAY WE CAN CUT THE HIGHER
OH OF COURSE YEAH SO PUT THE
CLICKER ON THERE AND THIS IS
BUT YOU KNOW INSTEAD OF THE
THING COMING DOWN IT ACTUALLY
STARTED GOING UP NOW LET HER GO!
LET HER GO BILL! LET HER GO!
LET HER GO!
OH SAY BILL HANG ON,
HANG ON, HANG ON, HANG ON,
AND THE WIRE IS GOING UP SO
YOU GOT TO THINK FAST YOU GOT
TO THINK FAST SO I'LL JUST
UNPLUG THAT AND MAYBE MAYBE
THAT'LL BRING HIM DOWN, IS
THERE A CHANCE THAT THAT'S
GOING TO BRING HIM DOWN?
IS THERE, IS THERE, IS THERE,
IS THERE YEAH, YEAH THAT DID IT.
>>BILL: OH!
>>RED: HE'S OKAY, I GUESS
WE HAVEN'T CUT A LOT OF THE
LAWN YET THERE BILL,
ARE YOU ALRIGHT?
NO OVER HERE, OVER HERE,
OVER HERE, THERE YOU GO.
THERE YOU GO HE SEEMS OKAY,
BILL WE WON'T CUT THE LAWN
WE'LL JUST FLATTEN IT.
THIS NEXT PART OF THE SHOW
IS FOR ALL THE KIDS WHO WATCH
AND THEY TELL ME THERE'S A LOT
OF YOU BUT I THINK BY THE END
OF THIS SEGMENT THERE
MAYBE NOT ANY.
>>HAROLD HI, WELL WELCOME
TO THE YOUTH ORIENTED PORTION
OF THE SHOW OR AS WE LIKE
TO SAY IN THE BIZ
THE INTERESTING PART...
I'M HAROLD AND TODAY'S TOPIC IS
OKAY STAG DANCING
YOU KNOW NOT THIS KIND OF STAG
NOT LIKE YOU KNOW A MALE DEER
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
STAG DANCING OKAY
STAG DANCING IS PERFECTLY
ACCEPTABLE AS LONG AS
NOBODY KNOWS.
>>RED: HAROLD NO ONE KNOWS
AND NO ONE CARES.
>>HAROLD: OH CONTRARE UNCLE RED
OH CONTRARE, YOU SEE BECAUSE
WE SINGLE TEENS ARE ALWAYS
LOOKING FOR WAYS TO FIT IN
AND BE ACCEPTED, SO HERE'S
THE SECRET TO STAG DANCING,
IF YOU SEE 2 GIRLS AT A
SOCIAL FUNCTION AND THEY'RE
DANCING TOGETHER AS GIRLS
SO OFTEN ARE APT TO DO
BUT ANYWAY WHAT YOU DO IS
JUST SIDLE ON UP IN THERE AND
YOU START DANCING RIGHT WITH
THEM YOU KNOW AND FROM THE
CASUAL OBSERVER'S POINT OF
VIEW HE'LL THINK YOU'RE
A REAL STUD.
>>RED: THAT'S SPELLED D-U-D.
>>HAROLD: ANYWAY THE SAME
DEAL GOES IF IT'S A GUY AND
A GIRL DANCING YOU JUST GET
IN THERE REAL CLOSE AND MANY
OBSERVERS WON'T EVEN SEE
THE GUY.
>>RED: YEAH WELL WHAT ABOUT
THE OBSERVERS WHO CAN'T SEE
THE GIRL, THEY'LL THINK
YOU'RE DANCING WITH
ANOTHER GUY HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: WELL THEN WELL
AVOID THE SLOW SONGS.
>>RED: NO KIDDING.
>>HAROLD: I WONDER IF
THAT'S WHY I GOT PUNCHED?
>>RED: OH HAROLD IT COULD
BE A MILLION REASONS
SEE WHAT I MEAN?
>>RED: I KNOW I CAN'T EXPECT
YOU TEENAGERS TO DO WELL
IN SCHOOL OR TO HAVE SOME
MANNERS OR TO BACK OFF
ON THE LOOTING AND RIOTING
BUT I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT YOU'D
HAD THE BRAIN POWER TO FIGURE
OUT WHICH WAY A CAP IS
SUPPOSED TO GO ON.
NOW THIS PART HERE IS THE
HARD PART IT'S THE PEAK
AND ITS JOB IS TO KEEP
THE WEATHER OFF YOUR FACE
BECAUSE UP UNTIL THIS GENERATION
THAT WAS THE MOST VALUABLE
SIDE OF A PERSON'S HEAD.
WHEN YOU WEAR THE PEAK ON
THE SIDE SOMEBODY'S LIABLE TO
COME TO YOU AND WHISPER RIGHT
INTO YOUR NOSE AND IF THEY'D
JUST EATEN AT A VIETNAMESE
RESTAURANT THAT COULD BE
SERIOUS SO WEAR THE PEAK THE
WAY IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
NOT TO THE SIDE OR AT THE
BACK 'CAUSE THAT LOOKS LIKE
YOU DON'T KNOW WHICH WAY
YOU'RE GOING AND THAT
SHOULDN'T HAPPEN UNTIL
YOU'RE AT LEAST 30.
>>RED: I WAS HOPING
DOUGIE FRANKLIN WOULD LEAD
THE PARADE WITH THIS MONSTER
TRUCK BUT HE HAD OTHER PLANS
HE WANTED TO TURN THIS OLD
CAR OF HIS INTO A GREAT
BIG FISH.
>>DOUGIE: I BROUGHT THIS.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>DOUGIE: PUT THIS
IN HERE LIKE THIS.
>>RED: AH HAH.
>>DOUGIE: A LITTLE
BIT OF SPOT WELDING.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>DOUGIE: IT LOOKS LIKE
A HOOK HANGING OUT OF THE
FISH'S MOUTH YOU KNOW.
>>RED: OKAY I SEE THAT'S
YOUR FISH HOOK.
>>DOUGIE: ARE YOU READY FOR
THE PIESTA RESISTANCE.
>>RED: I THINK I AM DOUG.
>>DOUGIE: PAINT HER PINK.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>DOUGIE: HANG HER ON THERE.
>>DOUGIE: WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
>>RED: A WORM.
>>DOUGIE: YOU GOT YOUR
WORM ABSOLUTELY.
>>RED: OH YEAH.
>>DOUGIE: SO I'M THINKING
YOU KNOW WELL I THINK MAYBE
HAROLD COULD DRIVE
OLD ZELDA HERE.
>>RED: OH NO, NO, NO,
THANKS ANYWAY DOUG
BUT I MEAN HAROLD DOESN'T EVEN
HAVE A DRIVER'S LICENSE.
>>DOUGIE: YOU DON'T NEED
A DRIVER'S LICENSE FOR A PARADE
YOU JUST NEED A BIG BABY
LIKE THIS UP FRONT IN CASE
YOU RUN INTO ANOTHER PARADE
OR A FUNERAL OR SOMETHING.
>>RED: OR A PARADE THAT
TURNS INTO A FUNERAL.
>>DOUGIE: OH YEAH
LIVING ON THE EDGE RED, I DO.
>>RED: I DON'T.
>>RED: WELL THIS WHOLE
SALMON PARADE THING RAN
INTO A FEW SNAGS.
>>HAROLD: SNAGS? SNAGS?
I THINK IT RAN INTO A LOT
MORE THAN THAT.
>>RED: WELL IN HINDSIGHT
I THINK IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
THE PARADE ROUTE
IT WAS A 20 MILE LONG WINDING
DIRT ROAD INTO TOWN WHICH WAS
POPULATED BY I BELIEVE I COUNTED
3 PEOPLE 2 OF WHOM WERE
HITCHHIKING AND SO AFTER
THE FIRST MILE A FEW OF
THE GUYS STARTED TO FIDGET.
>>HAROLD: I LOVE THIS
FIDGET IS THAT WHAT
YOU CALL IT, FIDGET?
>>RED: WELL THAT'S WHAT
I TOLD THE COPS.
IT STARTED WHEN JUNIOR SINGLETON
TRIED TO PASS STINKY PETERSON
BECAUSE HE COULDN'T STAND
THE FUMES COMING OFF HIS FUMES
OR THE FUMES COMING OFF HIS
SHIRT EITHER, SO THEN JUNIOR
AND STINKY STARTED TO JOCKEY
FOR POSITION AND THEN OF
COURSE OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
DIDN'T WANT TO BE LAPPED AND
AT THAT POINT IT GOT A LITTLE
OUT OF CONTROL AND THE WHOLE
PARADE KIND OF SPED UP A TAD.
>>HAROLD: YEAH I THINK WHEN
YOU BROKE THE SPEED LIMIT
TECHNICALLY IT WAS
NO LONGER A PARADE.
>>RED: NO AND OF COURSE
A LOT OF THE FLOATS WERE
BUILT FOR THE SLOWER SPEEDS
SO YOU KNOW THE PLYWOOD AND
THE CARDBOARD STARTED FLYING OFF
YOU KNOW PRETTY SOON IT WAS
MORE OF AN OBSTACLE COURSE
MOTOCROSS KIND OF A THING.
>>HAROLD: THEN YOU KNOW
STINKY JUNIOR AND MOOSE ALL
CAME YOU KNOW SLAMMING INTO
THAT ONE LANE BRIDGE OVER
MERCURY CREEK THERE IT SORT
OF BECAME A DEMOLITION
DERBY THING.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
ANYWAY I MEAN ALL INSURANCE
CLAIMS ASIDE AND EVERYTHING
I THINK IT CAME OUT PRETTY
EVEN BUT OF COURSE WE COULD
NO LONGER MAKE IT INTO
TOWN SO I CANCELLED
THE SALMON PARADE.
>>HAROLD: YOU HAD TO CANCEL?
YOU HAD TO CANCEL IT!
AFTER THE CRASH ALL THE GAS,
OIL AND TRANSMISSION FLUID
HIT MERCURY CREEK
THE SALMON SAW IT AND DID
A QUICK 180 BACK TO OPEN WATER.
OUTTA THERE!
(POSSUM SQUEALS)
>>HAROLD: OH HEY THAT'S
THE POSSUM, THAT MEANS WE HAVE
A MEETING UNCLE RED.
>>RED: YEAH YEAH ALRIGHT HAROLD
YOU GO AHEAD AND GO DOWN
THERE HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
>>RED: I'LL BE DOWN
IN A MINUTE.
>>HAROLD: ALRIGHTIE.
>>RED: WELL USUALLY I LOVE
A PARADE BUT I CAN'T
SAY I HAD A LOT OF FEELING
FOR THIS ONE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING AND I TOLD
THE GUYS THAT THEY CAN KEEP
ALL THEIR FLOATS IN OUR DRIVEWAY
UNTIL THEY STOP SMOLDERING
SO YOU MIGHT WANT TO CLOSE
THE LIVING ROOM DRAPES FOR
A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU ON
BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE AT
POSSUM LODGE THANKS FOR WATCHING
AND KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
(POSSUM SQUEALS)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>ALL: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTITATI.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca