IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW!"
AND NOW, HERE'S A MAN WHO
LAUGHS ALL THE WAY
TO THE BANK,
BUT DRIVES ALL
THE WAY BACK.
YOUR HOST,
YOUR HERO,
MY UNCLE,
RED GRE-E-E-N!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG EVENT
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
A DOGSLED RACE.
ALL THE MEMBERS HAVE
BROUGHT THEIR DOGS OVER.
WE'VE GOT ENOUGH
FOR A TEAM NOW.
WE'VE EVEN GOT ENOUGH
FOR A FEW SPARES.
THEY'RE NOT HUSKIES,
BUT THEY ARE HUSKY.
IT'S AMAZING HOW
THEY RESEMBLE THEIR
OWNERS THAT WAY.
HAROLD, WHAT YOU
GOT IN YOUR HAIR THERE?
WHAT?
RIGHT THERE.
OH, IT'S A TWIG.
YOU KNOW, I THINK YOU MAY BE
DRINKING TOO MUCH WATER.
NO, NO, I WAS A VICTIM
OF GANG VIOLENCE.
WHAT?!
YES, YES,
I WAS SWARMED.
YEAH, NINE GUYS!
THEY THREW ME DOWN
AND SAT ON MY HEAD.
NINE GUYS SAT
ON YOUR HEAD?
WHO WAS IT,
THE CIRQUE DU SOLEIL?
OKAY, IT WASN'T NINE,
BUT THE OTHER EIGHT
DIDN'T STOP HIM.
IT'S THAT NEW KID,
TUBBY JOHANSSEN.
I DON'T KNOW HIM, HAROLD,
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO LEARN TO
STICK UP FOR YOURSELF.
JUST NAIL THE KID, HAROLD.
A COUPLE OF QUICK ONES.
JUST NAIL HIM...
POW-POW!
NO!
THAT'S WHAT I'D DO.
I KNOW.
IT'S NO!
VIOLENCE NEVER
SOLVED ANYTHING.
LOOK AT YOU THIS MORNING
TRYING TO HARNESS THOSE
CHIHUAHUAS TO THE SLED.
WELL TUBBY AND I,
WE'RE GOING TO RESOLVE OUR
DIFFERENCES THROUGH MEDIATION.
OH, HAROLD,
JUST NAIL HIM.
NO, WHAT IS THE
MATTER WITH YOUR HEAD?
WELL, FOR ONE THING,
NOBODY EVER SAT ON IT.
(APPLAUSE)
[♪♪♪]
Red Green:
WELL, THIS WEEK ON THE SHOW,
WE'VE GOT WALL-TO-WALL
ACTION FOR YOU.
LOTS OF ACTION HAPPENING.
BOY, LOTS OF ACTION HAPPENING
EVERYWHERE WE GO THERE,
OUT ON THE POND,
EVERYWHERE.
HERE'S SOMETHING
YOU DON'T SEE VERY OFTEN.
EVEN HAROLD IS GETTING
A LITTLE ACTION.
YOU KNOW THIS WHOLE DOGSLED
PROJECT IS SHOWING US
THAT THERE'S NO SUCH
THING AS PROBLEMS;
JUST OPPORTUNITIES.
SEE, OUR DOGS ARE ALL
DIFFERENT HEIGHTS, RIGHT?
SO WHAT WE'RE DOING,
WE'RE PUTTING THE DACHSHUNDS
AND CHIHUAHUAS UP FRONT,
AND WE COME BACK THROUGH
WITH THE BASSET HOUNDS
AND THE SETTERS
AND THEN THE SHEPHERDS,
AND RIGHT UP TO THE
GREAT DANES AT THE BACK THERE.
AND THIS WAY, EVERY DOG
GETS TO SEE WHERE HE'S GOING,
WHICH YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
IS A LOT BETTER VIEW
THAN THEY GET WHEN THEY'RE
ALL THE SAME HEIGHT.
(LAUGHTER)
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
SO, HOW DID
IT GO, GANDHI?
TUBBY SAT ON
MY HEAD AGAIN.
I THINK NEXT TIME
YOU SHOULD TAKE A CHAIR.
WELL, THERE'S NOT GOING
TO BE A NEXT TIME.
I REALIZE NOW THAT TUBBY
IS JUST A PRODUCT OF A
DYSFUNCTIONAL FAMILY.
I'M SIMPLY GOING TO GO
OVER THERE AND SIT DOWN AND
DISCUSS THIS WITH HIS PARENTS.
OH, HAROLD,
DON'T BE SUCH A WUSS!
JUST MEET THE KID
IN THE SCHOOLYARD
AND NAIL HIM!
POW! POW!
JUST LIKE THAT.
HE'S A BULLY;
HE'S PROBABLY A COWARD.
HE WON'T EVEN SHOW.
JUST NAIL HIM.
THAT'S WHAT I'D DO.
NO, NO, I CAN'T HIT
ANOTHER HUMAN BEING AT ALL.
OH, SURE.
PUNCH ME HERE,
PUNCH ME RIGHT NOW.
PUNCH ME IN THE STOMACH.
PUNCH ME RIGHT HERE.
COME ON.
NO! NO!
IT WON'T HURT ME.
IT WON'T HURT.
REALLY?
YEAH, PUNCH ME
RIGHT THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
LET HER FLY.
WE'LL BOTH
FEEL BETTER.
COME ON.
OKAY.
JUST GO AHEAD.
(LAUGHTER).
IT'S A GOOD SIZED
TARGET, ISN'T IT?
OH, THAT'S FUNNY.
LIKE THAT?
SEE, I DON'T
FEEL ANY BETTER.
DO YOU FEEL
ANY BETTER?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU WANT ME TO
HIT YOU AGAIN?
NOT RIGHT NOW.
NOW?
NO, NOT RIGHT NOW.
'CAUSE I DON'T EVER WANT
TO HAVE TO HIT YOU AGAIN.
THAT WAS AWFUL.
I DON'T WANT TO
HIT YOU EVER AGAIN.
WELL, FINE,
SUIT YOURSELF.
(COUGHS)
♪♪ OH, WHEN YOU FIND A GUY
LYING IN YOUR TRUNK ♪
♪ AND HE'S GAGGED,
AND HE'S ALL TIED UP ♪
♪ YOU PROBABLY SHOULD PHONE
THE COPS RIGHT AWAY ♪
♪ BECAUSE CHANCES ARE
HE'S NOT AN ESCAPE ARTIST ♪♪
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
(APPLAUSE)
AND THIS WEEK, Mr. MIKE HAMAR
WILL BE PLAYING FOR FOUR HOURS
OF UNLIMITED FUN AND HIGH JINKS
AT ETHEL'S HOUSE OF RUBBER.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET Mr. MIKE HAMAR TO
SAY THIS WORD.
BLAME.
AND GO.
OKAY, MIKE,
YOU DO SOMETHING BAD,
AND THE COPS HAVE
NABBED YOU.
YOU DON'T TRY TO GET AWAY
WITH IT BECAUSE YOU KNOW
YOU REALLY ARE TO...
DRUNK?
NO, OKAY, OKAY.
YOU DO SOMETHING
ELSE WRONG, OKAY,
AND THE THING IS YOU
KNOW YOU'RE THE ONE TO...
LIE.
NO.
SOMEONE ACCUSES YOU.
THEY ARE LAYING...
THEIR LIFE
ON THE LINE?
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
SAY SOMEBODY BREAKS INTO THE
LODGE AND STEALS SOMETHING,
YOU'RE GOING TO HELP
US FIND SOMEONE TO...
FRAME?
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT,
IT RHYMES WITH FRAME.
SHAME?
NO, NO, NO, C'MON.
OH, I KNOW, MAIM.
ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
UNCLE RED.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SAY I DO SOMETHING STUPID,
EVERYBODY KNOWS I DID IT.
I GO TO THE LODGE MEETING,
WHAT DO I DO?
BLAME HAROLD.
(FRANTIC BELL RINGING)
(CRASH!)
(COW MOOING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
Red Green:
MAN, DON'T YOU HATE THAT?
YOU COME HOME AFTER A
TOUGH DAY AT THE RACE TRACK,
AND YOUR WIFE HASN'T FOUND TIME
TO SHOVEL OFF THE DRIVEWAY.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE IN THE GARAGE,
AND SO IS THE DOOR.
YOU KNOW, MOST VEHICLES
ARE NOT DESIGNED TO BE
GARAGE DOOR OPENERS.
THE BEST SOLUTION, OF COURSE,
IS TO SPEND YOUR WINTERS
IN FLORIDA,
BUT FOR THOSE OF YOU
ON A FIXED INCOME,
OR MAYBE AN INCOME SO BROKE
IT CAN'T BE FIXED,
I THOUGHT I'D TAKE
THIS WEEK'S HANDYMAN CORNER
AND SHOW YOU HOW YOU COULD
MAKE YOUR OWN HEATED DRIVEWAY.
THE FIRST THING YOU
NEED IS A STOVE.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
WHEN YOU GET A HANDYMAN
THAT IS KIND OF SHORT ON
EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE
HE HAS TO TAKE
A CHANCE WITH LOGIC,
AND I'M THINKING,
IF YOU'VE GOT AN OVEN,
IT'S GOT THE CAPABILITY OF
TAKING A SPACE THIS SMALL
AND RAISING HER UP
TO ABOUT 500 DEGREES.
SO IT JUST MAKES SENSE THAT
THAT WOULD BE ENOUGH POWER
TO TAKE A SPACE THIS BIG
AND RAISE IT UP
TO ABOVE FREEZING.
NOW, I KNOW SCIENTISTS WOULD
PROBABLY SIT DOWN WITH
A COMPUTER
AND FIGURE OUT THE B.T.U.s
REQUIRED AND ALL THAT,
BUT BUT I SAY
LET'S JUST TRY IT,
AND IF IT WORKS,
WELL, THEN WE GOT IT RIGHT;
AND IF IT DOESN'T WORK,
WELL, AT THE VERY LEAST WE
GOT THROUGH A SATURDAY WITHOUT
BEING FORCED TO GO SHOPPING.
OKAY, THE FIRST THING
WE WANT TO UPGRADE
IS THE BURNER
BECAUSE WE NEED SOMETHING
THAT IS GOING TO COVER
A LOT MORE GROUND.
I'M THINKING
CHAIN LINK FENCE.
I FOUND THIS ROLL JUST
SITTING ON THE SIDE OF
THE MAIN ROAD THERE.
ACTUALLY THEY'RE BUILDING
A FENCE ALONG THE SIDE
OF THE FOREST.
HEY, THOSE TREES
AREN'T GOING ANYWHERE!
ALL RIGHT, WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS UNROLL THE FENCE
AND CUT IT, OR WHATEVER,
UNTIL IT COVERS THE WHOLE
SURFACE OF YOUR DRIVEWAY.
ALL RIGHT,
THERE WE GO.
GOT THE FENCE ALL HOOKED UP
THERE JUST LIKE A BURNER.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO NOW IS HOOK
THE OTHER END UP TO THE VARIOUS
ELEMENTS ON YOUR STOVE.
(EXPLOSION)
THAT'S GOT IT.
OKAY, NOW WE'RE READY TO TURN
OUR SNOW-COVERED DRIVEWAY
INTO A FRESH-COOKED DRIVEWAY;
ONE I CALL 'BAKED ALASKA.'
YOU SET YOUR OVEN TO
500 DEGREES BAKE,
SET YOUR TIMER FOR SPRING,
AND YOU'RE DONE.
MAN.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
(ELECTRIC SHOCKS)
I WANT TO TALK
TO YOU OLDER FELLOWS
WHO MAY NOT BE WHAT
YOU USED TO BE WAY BACK WHEN.
YOU KNOW, AFTER A CERTAIN
NUMBER OF YEARS OF MARRIAGE
YOU MAY FIND THAT THE ROMANCE
HAS GONE FROM RED HOT
DOWN INTO THE KIND OF
LUKEWARM AREA.
YOU KNOW, I READ ONE TIME,
IF YOU PUT A PENNY INTO A JAR
EVERY TIME YOU ANDYOUR WIFE
ARE INTIMATE WITHIN THE
FIRST YEAR OF MARRIAGE
AND THEN TAKE OUT A PENNY
EVERY TIME YOU AND YOUR WIFE
ARE INTIMATE AFTER THE FIRST
YEAR OF MARRIAGE,
YOU WILL NEVER
EMPTY THAT JAR.
TAKE A MOMENT NOW AND THINK
ABOUT ALL THE PENNY JARS
AT YOUR HOUSE.
BUT DON'T FEEL BAD.
I'M GUESSING YOUR FRIENDS HAVE
A FEW JARS OF THEIR OWN.
LOOK AT THE BRIGHT SIDE.
TAKE IT AS A SIGN OF THE
HOT TAMALE YOU WERE BACK THEN,
RATHER THAN FOCUSING ON THE
BURNT-OUT PICKLE YOU ARE NOW.
(LAUGHTER)
YOU KNOW, THE WAY I SEE IT,
YOU'RE PRETTY DARN SMART.
I THINK YOU SHOULD DISPLAY
THOSE PENNY JARS WITH PRIDE.
ANYBODY CAN BE A STUD,
BUT YOU'VE USED IT TO HELP
FINANCE YOUR RETIREMENT.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(APPLAUSE)
OH, YEAH?!
WELL, I'M GOING TO BE
THERE AT 7 O'CLOCK,
AND YOU BETTER BE READY.
YEAH!
OH, OKAY, YEAH.
I KNOW I AM,
BUT WHAT ARE YOU?
TRYING TO GET
A DATE, HAROLD?
NO, NO,
THAT WAS TUBBY.
I'M GOING OVER THERE, AND I'M
GOING TO STRAIGHTEN HIM OUT,
AND I AM TAKING THE
DUKES OF HAZARD WITH ME.
NOW YOU'RE TALKING.
YEAH, I'M GOING
TO CLEAN HIS CLOCK
AND THEN FIX HIS WAGON!
HE'S GOING DOWN.
OH, YEAH,
I'M READY.
I'M WILD TONIGHT.
OH, YEAH.
OH, WOW!
COULD HAVE BEEN --
COULD HAVE BEEN.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD, YOU'RE
STANDING UP FOR YOURSELF.
GOOD FOR YOU, HAROLD.
I'M DRAWING A LINE
IN THE SAND, UNCLE RED,
I'VE HAD IT.
OH, YEAH, TUBBY IS MESSING
WITH THE WRONG MAROON.
MARINE.
WHAT?
ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S GOOD.
I'M GOING TO GO OVER THERE,
AND I'M GOING TO SETTLE
THIS ONCE AND FOR ALL.
ALL RIGHT, DO YOU WANT
TO GIVE ME TUBBY'S ADDRESS,
SO I KNOW WHERE
TO SEND THE AMBULANCE?
DON'T WORRY, I'M NOT
GOING TO HIT HIM THAT HARD.
OH, I KNOW.
(LAUGHTER)
HA HA HA.
YOU DON'T WORRY.
I CAN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
ALL RIGHT.
(In W.W.F. announcer voice)
GET READY TO RUMBLE!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
Harold:
WELCOME TO THIS WEEK'S MEETING
OF MEN'S ANONYMOUS.
AND, AS ALWAYS, I WOULD LIKE TO
ASK MY UNCLE RED TO LEAD US ALL
IN THE MEN'S ANONYMOUS PLEDGE.
UNCLE RED.
Everyone:
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
Harold:
AT THIS POINT IN TIME,
AT THIS PARTICULAR JUNCTURE
AT WHICH WE FIND OURSELVES,
I'D LIKE TO ASK Mr. DALTON "H"
TO TELL US HIS STORY.
DALTON "H".
Dalton:
OKAY, LAST WEEK MY WIFE AND I
WENT TO SHOP AT PORT ASBESTOS,
AND OF COURSE, ALL THE WAY THERE
AND ALL THE WAY BACK SHE HAD
TO TELL ME WHERE TO DRIVE.
UH-OH.
AND I LET HER.
YES, YESIREE, I DID.
AND OF COURSE,
YOU'RE ON THE HIGHWAY,
AND THERE'S ALL THESE SIGNS
ALL THE WAY ALONG AND THEY SAY,
"PORT ASBESTOS TURN RIGHT,"
BUT YOU KNOW, SHE STILL
HAD TO SAY, "TURN RIGHT HERE."
I DIDN'T SAY A WORD.
NO, SIR.
AND I DIDN'T DO
THAT BIG SIGH THING,
YOU KNOW, THE ONE?
(SIGHING)
I DON'T SAY A WORD.
I DON'T ROLL MY EYES.
I DON'T DO THE HEAD THING.
NO, SIREE.
I JUST LET HER TELL ME,
AND I DON'T SAY A WORD.
BRAVO!
(APPLAUSE)
ALL RIGHT.
THERE YOU GO.
WE'RE VERY PROUD OF YOU.
I JUST NEED THE GROUP
TO HELP ME WITH ONE THING.
ANYTHING.
WHAT CAN WE DO?
CAN YOU HELP ME GET MY MY
FINGERS UNCLAMPED FROM
THIS STEERING WHEEL?
OH.
PULL!
(APPLAUSE)
Red Green:
REALLY EXCITED ABOUT THIS
WEEK'S ADVENTURE WITH BILL
BECAUSE I'M NOT IN IT.
IT'S HAROLD AND BILL
ARE OUT THERE.
THEY'RE GOING TO DO
A LITTLE ICE FISHING.
OH, BOY.
OH BOY.
SO MUCH FOR THAT AXE.
OH, OH, THAT'S A CRACK.
THAT ICE IS A LITTLE
THIN THERE BOYS.
COMPLETE OPPOSITE OF YOURSELVES.
YEAH, YEAH,
GOOD PLAN.
NO, NO, DON'T,
GET OUT.
GO, GO, GO!
ALL RIGHT, THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S BETTER.
THAT'S A LITTLE THICKER,
MUCH LIKE YOURSELF, HAROLD.
THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
JUST CHOP A HOLE THERE.
THERE, YOU GO.
OH-OH-OH.
YOU BETTER PUT ICE ON
THAT INJURY RIGHT AWAY.
OH, THERE WE GO.
NOW YOU'RE TALKING, BILL.
THAT'S A POWER AUGER.
THAT'LL CUT A HOLE
RIGHT THROUGH.
JUST GOT TO START THAT
LITTLE PUP UP THERE.
PROBLEM WITH THOSE THINGS,
ONCE THEY START CUTTING YOU'VE
GOT TO KEEP A FIRM GRIP
'CAUSE THEY'LL BIND ON YOU,
AND YOU DON'T ALWAYS --
YOU CAN'T ALWAYS GET
THE GOOD FIRM --
SHE'S BINDING.
SHE'LL SPIN YOU.
HANG ON.
OH, MAN!
LATER THAT WEEK,
WE GOT FISHING.
HAROLD, YOU'RE GETTING A BITE,
GETTING A BITE.
REEL HER IN.
YOU GET A LOT OF LITTLE SMELTS
THIS TIME OF YEAR,
SMELTS AND HERRING.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE GOT
A NORTHERN PIKE.
OH, NO, WHAT THE HECK.
HOLY COW!
THE HOLE GOT A LOT BIGGER.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW THAT WORKS.
WHAT IS THAT THING?
IT'S OUR ICE FISHING HUT
FROM LAST SEASON.
OH, FOR GOSH SAKE,
SHE'S IN PRETTY GOOD
SHAPE THERE TOO.
BETTER MOVE THAT OVER TO --
YEAH, MOVE THAT OVER TO ANOTHER
PLACE THERE WHERE YOU CAN --
THERE, THERE YOU GO.
NOW YOU'VE GOT YOUR
OWN SPOT IN THERE
AND HAROLD AND BILL --
BILL, I THINK YOU SHOULD --
I DON'T THINK THERE'S
ROOM IN THERE --
YOU CAN'T GET BOTH OF YOU
AND THE AUGER IN THERE.
I DON'T THINK YOU CAN GET
BOTH OF YOU AND THE AUGER --
BILL, BILL, BILL, BILL,
YOU CAN'T --
BILL, BILL, YOU CAN'T GET --
BILL YOU CAN'T --
TOLD YOU.
HAROLD, DON'T.
OH, YEAH, I WAS RIGHT.
OKAY, SO THEY GET
THAT IN THERE.
NOW, AGAIN BOYS,
BE CAREFUL.
'CAUSE IF SHE BINDS ON YOU,
THERE'S NOWHERE TO GO,
BOYS, IF SHE BINDS ON YOU.
BOYS, SHE'S BINDING.
SHE'S BINDING.
BOYS SHE'S BINDING.
SHUT HER DOWN.
YOU NEED A BIGGER ICE SHACK.
WELL, THAT'S ENOUGH
FROM THOSE ICE HOLES.
YOU KNOW, THIS IDEA OF HAVING
THE BIG DOGS AT THE BACK
LOOKED GOOD ON PAPER,
BUT ONCE THEY
STARTED RUNNING,
YOU KNOW, THE DOG THAT HAD A
BIGGER STRIDE THERE,
KIND OF ENDED UP GOING UP
AND OVER THE LITTLE DOGS.
SO INSTEAD OF TWO LINES OF DOGS,
WE HAD SORT OF TWO ROLLING
BALLS OF DOGS,
WHICH WOULD HAVE BEEN OKAY IF
THEY WERE EITHER ALL MALE
OR ALL FEMALE.
THE CO-ED THING JUST
DIDN'T WORK OUT AT ALL.
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
SO HOW DID IT GO?
I WENT UP TO TUBBY'S,
AND I WANTED TO HIT HIM.
I REALLY DID.
BUT YOU KNOW, I JUST REALIZED
AT THE LAST SECOND,
I CAN'T STRIKE
ANOTHER HUMAN BEING.
LOOKS LIKE TUBBY DIDN'T
HAVE THAT PROBLEM.
NO, NOT TUBBY,
HIS DAD!
YEAH, HE CAME OUT AND HE THREW
ME DOWN AND SAT ON MY HEAD.
MUST BE GENETIC
OR SOMETHING.
WELL, HAROLD, I WISH
I'D HAVE BEEN THERE.
I WOULD HAVE DECKED HIM.
I TELL YOU, HE WOULD HAVE
GONE DOWN LIKE BRI-EX SHARES.
YEAH, THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I TOLD HIM.
WHAT?
YEAH, I SAID YOU WAIT RIGHT
THERE BECAUSE MY UNCLE RED
IS GOING TO COME OVER HERE,
AND HE'S GOING
TO FIX YOUR WAGON.
WELL, HOW --
HOW DO YOU --
HOW DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, I SAID,
"JUST WAIT HERE,
"AND HE'S GOING TO COME OVER
HERE, AND HE'S GOING TO
CLEAN YOUR CLOCK."
C'MON, LET'S GO
CLEAN HIS CLOCK.
YOU KNOW I CAN'T;
I'D LOVED TO,
BUT I'VE GOT
THE DOGS AND I'VE --
WELL, TUBBY'S DAD SAYS
HE'S ONLY GOING TO WAIT
THERE TEN MINUTES.
THEN WHAT?
THEN HE SAID --
YOU KNOW WHAT HE SAID?
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT HE SAID.
HE SAID HE'S GOING
TO COME OVER HERE,
AND HE'S GOING TO BEAT YOU UP
RIGHT ON YOUR OWN TV SHOW.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO GO OVER
AND KICK SOME BUTT.
ALL RIGHT,
KICK HIS BUTT.
NO, NO, NO, NO,
I'M GOING TO
KICK YOUR BUTT.
COME ON.
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
"IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
JOINING ME THIS WEEK
IS EDGAR MONTROSE.
OH, HI, RED!
HI, MOM!
EDGAR IS KIND OF OUR LOCAL
EXPLOSIONS AND DEMOLITIONS
EXPERT HERE.
I WOULDN'T
SAY EXPERT, RED.
I'M MORE OF AN
EXPLOSIVES ENTHUSIAST.
SELF-TAUGHT,
FROM THE SCHOOL
OF HARD KNOCKS
AND SOFT APOLOGIES.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
GOT ANYTHING FOR US
TO FIX HERE TODAY?
OH, I AGREE.
YOU KNOW, RED, I'M HERE
BECAUSE I HAVE THIS HAMMER
THAT NEEDS REPAIRING.
IT'S MY GOOD HAMMER.
I USE IT FOR HAMMERING STICKS
OF DYNAMITE INTO TIGHT HOLES.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU JUST
DRILL BIGGER HOLES, EDGAR?
I DON'T LIKE DRILLING.
I LIKE HAMMERING.
IT REALLY SHARPENS
THE REFLEXES,
ESPECIALLY WHEN THE
HEAD COMES OFF...
LIKE THAT.
WELL, NOW, NORMALLY
WHAT I'D DO HERE
IS DRIVE A METAL WEDGE
IN THERE TO HOLD THAT ON,
BUT WE WANT TO
BE SAFE AND SECURE,
SO I RECOMMEND THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE ON THIS.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU THROW
A LITTLE DUCT TAPE ON THAT?
HOW ARE THE
EARDRUMS EDGAR?
OH, PROBABLY BY THURSDAY.
OKAY, EDGAR, I UNDERSTAND LAST
WEEK YOU BLEW UP THE OLD FLOUR
MILL UP AT PORT ASBESTOS.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
BOY, THAT BABY WENT
OFF LIKE A DRY SNEEZE.
A HUGE MUSHROOM CLOUD
OF DURUM SEMOLINA.
TALK ABOUT PRE-SIFTED.
HOW MUCH WOULD YOU GET PAID
FOR A DEMOLITION JOB LIKE THAT?
PAID?
YEAH.
OH, NO, RED.
JUST SEEING 300 TONS OF FLOUR
SUSPENDED OVER POSSUM LAKE
IS ALL THE PAYMENT I NEED.
I MEAN, TO FLATTEN THAT FLOUR
MILL AND NOT EVEN SCRATCH THE
GAS STATION RIGHT NEXT DOOR.
GAS STATION?
NO, NO, NEXT TO THE
FLOUR MILL YOU'VE GOT
THE OLD RAILWAY SHED THERE,
THEN THERE'S
THE BOWLING ALLEY,
AND YOU GOT
THE FOUNTAIN,
THEN THERE'S
THE GAS STATION.
IT'S NOT NEXT DOOR
TO THE FLOUR MILL.
IT IS NOW.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
OH, MAN.
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
LET ME IN!
AH, GEEZ.
GEEZ.
WELL, THAT
WAS INTERESTING.
TURNS OUT I WAS THE ONE WHO WAS
MESSING WITH THE WRONG MARINE.
YOU COULD HAVE WARNED ME ABOUT
THE SIZE OF THE GUY, HAROLD.
I DIDN'T THINK
IT MATTERED.
YOU SAID, "OH,
I'M GONNA NAIL HIM.
"YOU KNOW, A COUPLE
OF QUICK ONES,
"POP! POP!"
OH, YEAH.
I DIDN'T THINK HE WAS THAT
MUCH STRONGER THAN YOU.
HAROLD, I NEVER THOUGHT AN
18-YEAR-OLD KID WOULD HAVE
A FATHER WHO WAS ONLY 35.
I NEVER EXPECTED HIM TO BE
A HOMICIDAL MANIAC
AND A BODY BUILDER.
I'LL TELL YOU, YOU TAKE AWAY
HIS YOUTH, HIS ATTITUDE
AND HIS STEROIDS,
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
YOU.
HOW DID YOU KNOW?
I WAS THINKING IT,
BUT IT SHOULDN'T
HAVE COME OUT.
BUT --
REALLY --
BUT YOU'RE FAST.
YOU'RE IN GOOD SHAPE.
YOU'RE FAST.
BOY YOU WERE REALLY
RUNNING THERE.
DON'T BE DOING THAT.
NO, YOU WERE.
I NEVER WOULD HAVE CAUGHT YOU
IF I WASN'T IN THE VAN.
YOU'RE FAST.
I WASN'T RUNNING
OUT OF FEAR.
OH, NO, NO.
STANDING AND FIGHTING THAT GUY
WAS A WASTE OF MY VITAL TIME
AND ORGANS.
NO POINT COUGHING
UP A KIDNEY
IF THERE'S NO RECIPIENT
IN THE AREA.
I MEAN, I COULDN'T --
I COULDN'T REASON WITH THE GUY.
BUT YOU PROVED YOURSELF
TO BE A BIGGER MAN.
I THINK SO.
YOU TURNED
THE OTHER CHEEK.
AND HE NAILED ME WITH
THE CANOE PADDLE.
SORRY, I SHOULD HAVE
WARNED YOU ABOUT THAT.
(POSSUM CALL)
IT'S MEETING TIME.
ARE YOU GOING TO COME DOWNSTAIRS
AND TELL THE OTHER FELLOWS
ABOUT THE SENSELESSNESS
OF VIOLENCE NOW?
I WOULD
IF I HAD WON.
YEAH, OKAY,
NO, OKAY.
YOU GO AHEAD.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I'M THROUGH WITH FIGHTING,
BUT I HAVEN'T GIVEN UP ON
THE PHYSICAL INTERACTION
BETWEEN TWO ADULTS,
UNLESS YOUR DAD COMES OVER
TO WATCH THE GOLF CHANNEL,
IN WHICH CASE, THE PENDULUM
MAY SWING BACK TOWARDS
VIOLENCE AGAIN.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTER]
Harold:
HERE HE COMES.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE!
Everyone:
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red Green:
SIT DOWN.
Harold:
JUST GOT ONE QUICK
ANNOUNCEMENT THIS WEEK.
BUSTER HADFIELD LOST
HIS FAVOURITE KNIFE.
HE OVER SHARPENED IT,
AND IT CUT A HOLE IN
HIS PANTS' POCKET.
IT ESCAPED.
HE GOT OFF LUCKY
THAT TIME, HUH?