AS MEN PEOPLE ARE
ALWAYS ASKING US
TO DO THINGS
WE DON'T WANNA DO...
FEED THE DOG,
CHANGE THE CHANNEL,
HAVE KIDS.
SOMETIMES WE GET
ASKED TO DO THINGS
THAT ARE JUST
PLAIN DANGEROUS.
LIKE WASHING THE OUTSIDE
OF THE UPSTAIRS WINDOWS.
NOBODY WANTS TO BE CLIMBING
A $25 RICKETY LADDER
WITH A PAIL FULL
OF SOAPY WATER,
NOT TO MENTION THE SQUEEGIE,
WHICH GOT ITS NAME FROM
THE SOUND THE GUY MADE
WHEN HE LANDED ON ONE.
NATURALLY,
THERE'S A BETTER WAY.
ALL YOU NEED IS SOME
LIQUID SOAP IN A BALLOON,
A WET SUIT AND A
COUPLE OF HOCKEY STICKS.
OKAY, NOW I JUST
NEED TO RINSE.
I GOT WATER IN THIS ONE.
NOT POSSUM LAKE WATER,
BUT CLOSE ENOUGH.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
YEAH, OKAY.
WE HAD A LITTLE BIT
OF A BOATING ACCIDENT HERE.
A LITTLE TIP FOR YOU...
IF YOU'RE EVER DRIVING A BOAT,
DON'T TURN AROUND AND TALK TO
THE PEOPLE BEHIND YOU
FOR MORE THAN A COUPLE OF
MINUTES AT A TIME.
WHAT WAS THAT?!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
JUST RELAX, HAROLD.
YOU ALWAYS SAID YOU WANTED
TO TRY RUNNIN' THE RAPIDS.
YES, YES, I DID.
IN A KAYAK!
NOT IN A HOUSEBOAT.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA
TELL JUNIOR SINGLETON?
WELL, WHY WOULD WE
TELL HIM ANYTHING?
IT WAS HIS BOAT!
OKAY, YEAH, OKAY.
WELL, WE'LL JUST --
WE'LL TELL HIM
IT WAS STOLEN.
I MEAN, IF WE GET RID OF THE
STEERING WHEEL AND THE PADDLE,
THERE WON'T BE A
TRACE OF HER ANYWHERE.
THERE'S TRACES
OF JUNIOR'S HOUSEBOAT
SCATTERED ALONG THE ENTIRE
LENGTH OF THE LAKE,
UNCLE RED!
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
WE'LL TELL HIM IT
WAS AN ACT OF GOD.
WE CANNOT BLAME
THIS ON GOD.
HE'S STILL
APOLOGIZING FOR YOU.
RED! RED!
WHAT?
WHERE ARE ALL THE WOMEN?
WELL, I DON'T
HAVE 'EM,
AND I KNOW FOR SURE
HE DOESN'T HAVE 'EM.
WELL, THEY'RE
ALL MISSING.
YEAH, I KNOW WE GOT HOME
A COUPLE OF DAYS EARLY
FROM OUR BOAT CRUISE,
BUT I WAS EXPECTING
TO SEE ANN MARIE AT HOME.
AND BUSTER'S
SISTER'S MISSING.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S
MOTHER'S GONE.
WELL, MAYBE SHE GOT LOST
IN THE COUCH CUSHIONS AGAIN.
W-W-WELL,
JUST RELAX, OKAY?
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
THEY PROBABLY RENTED
A HALL SOMEWHERE
SO THEY COULD WATCH OPERA
TOGETHER OR SOMETHING.
I MEAN, YOU GOTTA GIVE WOMEN A
LITTLE SPACE SOMETIMES.
YOU KNOW, JUST LET
THEM ENJOY THEMSELVES.
OH! I FIND THAT ATTITUDE
REFRESHINGLY MATURE,
UNCLE RED.
YEAH, WELL, IT'S
NOT JUST MY WIFE.
BERNICE IS
MISSING TOO!
WELL, WHAT THE
HECK'S GOIN' ON?
YES, EXACTLY!
HOLY MACKEREL.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S PRIZE IS TWO TICKETS
TO THE HEARTWARMING NEW MOVIE
ABOUT A LITTLE LOST LAMB
WHO BECOMES HEAVYWEIGHT
CHAMPION OF THE WORLD.
DON'T MISS "RAGING WOOL."
OKAY, COVER YOUR ORIFICES,
MR. FARQUHARSON.
OKAY, MR. GREEN,
YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET CHARLIE FARQUHARSON
TO SAY THIS WORD...
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND... GO!
UH, ALL RIGHT, CHARLIE,
WHEN YOU WERE GROWING UP,
MOST THE PEOPLE IN YOUR
AREA LIVED ON THIS...
SOCIAL ASSISTANCE.
NO, NO, NO.
OKAY. OKAY.
THIS IS A PLACE WHERE
THEY HAVE DOMESTIC ANIMALS
IN AN ENCLOSED SPACE.
A SINGLES BAR.
NO, OKAY. OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT, IF YOU
WANNA PLAY IN THE N.H.L.,
FIRST YOU HAVE
TO PLAY ON THIS TEAM.
RUSSIANS.
NO, OKAY. OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHEN
SOMEBODY DIES,
YOU SAY THEY BOUGHT THE...
WRONG KIND OF
HEART MEDICINE.
ALMOST OUTTA TIME,
MR. GREEN.
YEAH, I KNOW.
CHARLIE, YOU INHERITED
THIS FROM YOUR FATHER.
FOOT ODOR!
FORTUNATELY,
I LIVE ON A FARM.
[ DOORBELL ]
[ CHEERS ON T.V. ]
announcer: WHEN THE GUYS
COME OVER FOR THE PLAYOFFS.
THERE'S ONE THING
YOU CAN'T FORGET...
YOU DON'T BUY 'EM,
YOU RENT 'EM.
ARE YOU PUMPED
FOR THE BIG GAME?
YOU KNOW, SOME DAY YOU'LL LOOK
BACK AT YOUR KIDS GROWING UP
AND YOU'LL THINK THOSE WERE
THE BEST TIMES OF YOUR LIVES.
THAT'S BECAUSE WE ONLY TEND
TO REMEMBER THE GOOD TIMES
AND BECAUSE OUR LIVES TEND
TO GET WORSE AND WORSE.
THE TRUTH IS, NOTHING RUINS
A DREAM VACATION WITH
YOUR KIDS FASTER
THAN TO ACTUALLY HAVE
TO TAKE YOUR KIDS ON IT.
LUCKILY, TODAY'S
NEW DELUXE MINI-VANS
HAVE ALL KINDS OF CONVENIENCES
TO MAKE TRAVELLING WITH KIDS
A LOT MORE ENJOYABLE.
THEY'VE GOT TVs
AND DVD PLAYERS
AND VIDEO GAMES,
THE WHOLE SHEBANG.
BUT WHAT CAR MAKERS
FORGET IS
THAT MOST PEOPLE
WHO HAVE KIDS
CAN'T AFFORD
A BRAND NEW MINI-VAN.
LUCKILY, THANKS
TO A MODERN MIRACLE
KNOWN AS THE
TEEN-AGED DRIVER,
VANS THAT START OUT
LOOKIN' LIKE THAT
END UP LOOKIN' LIKE THIS.
AND THEY'RE A
LOT MORE AFFORDABLE.
HECK, IF YOU CAN PICK UP
AN OLD MINI-VAN FOR
NEXT TO NOTHING,
YOU DON'T CARE
IF IT GETS WRECKED.
KIND OF LIKE WHEN
YOU RENT ONE.
NOW I'M GONNA SHOW
YOU HOW TO GIVE THIS VAN
ALL THE FAMILY
FRIENDLY FEATURES
THAT THE SUPER VANS HAVE
FOR A FRACTION
OF THE COST.
ASSUMING ZERO IS A FRACTION.
FIRST THING YOU WANNA DO IS GET
THE BENCH SEATS OUTTA THERE.
GOTTA KEEP THE KIDS APART.
EVERY WAR IN HISTORY
WAS STARTED BY IMMATURE PEOPLE
BEIN' TOO CLOSE TOGETHER.
SO WHAT YOU WANNA DO IS
MEASURE THE LENGTHS OF
YOUR KIDS' ARMS
AND THEN POSITION THESE CHAIRS
FARTHER APART THAN THAT.
THIS UNIT IS
DESIGNED FOR TWO KIDS.
IF YOU'RE CATHOLIC, YOU MAY
NEED TO GET A SCHOOL BUS.
AND FOR EXTRA SAFETY
I'VE INSTALLED THE FIVE-POINT
SEATBELTS ON EACH CHAIR.
THAT WAY THE
KIDS'LL BE PROTECTED
AGAINST THE NUMBER ONE
FAMILY ROAD HAZARD,
EACH OTHER.
WE EVEN HAVE A VIDEO GAME
FOR ONE OF THE KIDS.
SEE, THE LINE FROM
THIS FISHING ROD,
IT GOES OUT
THROUGH THE WINDOW.
AND DANGLING
FROM THE END...
IS AN ACTION
FIGURE THAT COMES FREE
WHENEVER YOU SUPER-SIZE YOUR
DOUBLE CHEESE FRIES AND
A SOFT DRINK,
I WOULD THINK.
AND THE KID CONTROLS THE
MOVEMENT OF OUR ACTION FIGURE
BY WINDING IN AND
LETTING OUT THE LINE.
YOU CAN EVEN SET
THE LEVEL OF DIFFICULTY
BY ADJUSTING THE
TENSION ON THE REEL.
AND OF COURSE THE OBSTACLES
YOU ARE TRYING TO AVOID
ARE THE DREADED
BUBBLES OF DEATH.
SEE, I'VE GOT THIS
JAR OF LIQUID SOAP
CONNECTED TO A SIPHON TUBE
TO THIS BUBBLE BLOWER.
SO AS YOU DRIVE ALONG,
THE WIND FIRES THE BUBBLES
TOWARDS THE ACTION HERO
AND THE KID USES THE
FISHING ROD TO DODGE THE SOAP.
PUT A LITTLE
DIRT ON THE GUY.
AS SOON AS HE'S CLEAN,
GAME'S OVER.
OKAY, NOW, TO KEEP
THE OTHER KID AMUSED,
I CUT A HOLE IN THE ROOF
AND HUNG AN AQUARIUM
FILLED WITH GOLDFISH.
THIS IS TO
SIMULATE A MOVIE.
YOU JUST SHOW 'EM THE BOX FROM
"20,000 LEAGUES UNDER THE SEA,"
AND HE'LL BE CONVINCED.
BY THE WAY, IF ONE
OF YOUR KIDS IS SMART,
YOU SHOULD DO THIS
WITH THE OTHER ONE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
AND FOR THAT LITTLE EXTRA
SOMETHING THAT EVERY
PARENT LOVES,
GET YOURSELF ONE
OF THESE TOY MICROPHONES
THAT COMES
OUT THE RADIO.
Hello, am I coming through?
Is this working?
THEY SELL THESE SO KIDS CAN
PRETEND THEY'RE FAMOUS SINGERS.
She was only a bird
in a girdle cage
THIS MICROPHONE IS NOT
FOR THE KIDS TO SING INTO.
IT'S FOR YOU TO TALK INTO.
Hey, you two,
settle down back there.
I saw that!
Don't make me
come back there.
I WANNA TALK TO YOU
OLDER GUYS A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT THE GENERATION GAP.
REMEMBER WHEN
IT WAS A GOOD THING?
BACK IN THE '60s WHEN WE WERE
COMIN' UP TO SPEED
ON THE ONRAMP OF
THE HIGHWAY OF LIFE.
PUT A FEW MILES ON US
SINCE THEN, HAVEN'T WE?
NOW WE'RE STOPPING
AT EVERY SERVICE CENTRE.
KIND OF WORRIED THAT MAYBE
THE NEXT EXIT WILL BE OURS.
WE WENT FROM CHANTING,
"MAKE LOVE NOT WAR,"
TO GETTING MARRIED
AND DOIN' BOTH.
AND NOW SOME OF US
EVEN HAVE KIDS --
OR AS THEY'RE ALSO KNOWN,
THE ULTIMATE PAYBACK.
SEE, NOBODY TALKS ABOUT THE
GENERATION GAP ANYMORE.
THAT'S BECAUSE MOST OF US
ARE ON THE WRONG SIDE OF IT.
BUT THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S OKAY TO BE ON THE WRONG
SIDE OF THE GENERATION GAP
OR THE WRONG SIDE
OF YOUR BOSS
OR EVEN ONCE IN A WHILE,
THE WRONG SIDE OF YOUR WIFE.
AS LONG AS WHEN
YOU GO TO THE CEMETERY
YOU'RE STILL ON THE RIGHT
SIDE OF THE GRASS,
YOU'RE DOIN' FINE.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
A MAN'S HOME
IS HIS CASTLE.
PROTECT THE THRONE.
WELL, WE SOLVED
THE MYSTERY,
BUT I'LL TELL YOU,
ALL THE WOMEN MISSING
ON A MONDAY AFTERNOON
IS SENDING SHOCKS
THROUGH THE WHOLE AREA.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT
LIKE WE HAVE A MALL
OR ANYTHING, YOU KNOW.
FOUND YOUR ARMY
SURPLUS BOX, UNCLE RED.
BOY, DO WE HAVE A LOT
OF SPIDERS DOWN THERE.
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
WE DON'T MIND
THEM REALLY.
WE USED TO HAVE A LOT
OF FLIES EVERYWHERE
IN THE LODGE,
BUT NOW WE GOT SPIDERS,
IT FEELS LIKE WE'RE
MOVING UP THE FOOD
CHAIN, YOU KNOW?
OH, GREAT.
AND WE FOUND OUT
WHERE THE WOMEN WERE.
OH, AT THE CHURCH.
AT THE CHURCH.
YEAH, THE WOMEN'S
CIRCLE MEETING.
THEY'RE AT THE WOMEN'S --
HOW'D YOU
KNOW ABOUT THAT?
WELL, THEY MEET
EVERY MONDAY AFTERNOON.
REALLY?
HOW LONG'S THAT
BEEN GOIN' ON?
A COUPLE YEARS.
YOU KNEW THAT,
AND YOU DIDN'T TELL ME?
YOU DIDN'T ASK.
SO ANYWAY, AT THE
WOMEN'S CIRCLE THERE,
THEY ALL GET TOGETHER AND
TALK ABOUT WHATEVER'S
ON THEIR MIND.
SO THOSE OF US WHO LIVE WITH
THESE WOMEN ARE THINKING,
YOU KNOW, THAT COULD
BE VALUABLE INFORMATION.
SO WITH THE HELP OF
THESE ARMY SURPLUS
WALKIE TALKIES
WE'RE GONNA MAKE
THAT HAPPEN.
GOT IT!
YES, YOU DO,
HAROLD.
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO
IS WE'RE GONNA USE
THIS FISHING LINE
AND DROP A WALKIE TALKIE
DOWN THROUGH THE
CHURCH CHIMNEY.
WE'RE GONNA BE ABLE HEAR
EVERYTHING THEY'RE
TALKIN' ABOUT.
THAT IS SO WRONG!
THAT'S AN INVASION
OF PRIVACY.
WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
YOU'VE GOT A FAIR SIZED
ARACHNID ON YOUR
FOREHEAD, HAROLD.
I KNOW.
I'VE BEEN EATING
TOO MUCH CHOCOLATE.
NO, IT'S A SPIDER,
HAROLD.
WHAT?!
YEAH. YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S BEEN THERE
A FEW MINUTES NOW.
[ SCREECHING ]
GET IT OFF!
OKAY. OKAY. OKAY.
WHY DIDN'T
YOU TELL ME?
YOU DIDN'T ASK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red: IT MUST'VE BEEN AUGUST,
'CAUSE I WAS WASHING
THE POSSUM VAN.
AND YOU KNOW, YOU JUST
GET DOIN' SOMETHING,
AND IT NEVER FAILS.
[ CELL PHONE RINGING ]
YOU KNOW, YOU'LL GET SOMETHING
THAT'LL INTERRUPT WHAT
YOU'RE TRYIN' --
MY CELL PHONE
STARTS RINGING.
I JUST THREW
THE HOSE OVER THERE.
I DON'T KNOW USE
THE CELL PHONE ENOUGH
TO EVER KNOW EXACTLY
WHERE IT IS, YOU KNOW?
I SHOULD REALLY TURN
THE RING UP ON THAT.
TRY THE GLOVE BOX.
NO, SHE'S NOT IN THERE.
IT'S IN THE
COFFEE MUG, I THINK.
THERE WE GO.
SO I GET ON THERE AND IT'S
WALTER ON THE OTHER END.
BUT DIDN'T HAVE
A GREAT CONNECTION.
YOU KNOW IT'S ALWAYS
WITH A CELL PHONE
YOU CAN HEAR THE ODD WORD,
BUT THERE'S NEVER A
VERB OR ANYTHING.
IT'S NOT CLEAR
WHAT HE WAS SAYIN'.
SO HE THOUGHT MAYBE
HE COULD MOVE AROUND.
SOMETIMES WHEN YOU'RE
OUT ON THE WATER
YOU'LL GET A
LITTLE BETTER SIGNAL.
UH, DON'T GO TOO FAR OUT
ONTO THE WATER.
OH, THAT WAS
AS GOOD IDEA.
MAYBE IN THE
BOAT IT'D BE --
BUT I'M STILL
NOT GETTIN' HIM,
SO I THOUGHT IF I
GOT UP A LITTLE HIGHER,
GO UP ON THE LADDER.
WHAT I DIDN'T REALISE
WAS THE HOSE
HAD SOAKED THE GROUND
UNDER THE LADDER.
THERE'S A LOT OF GRAVITY
AROUND THE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
YOU KNOW, MY PROBLEM THERE,
I NEEDED A LONGER LADDER.
BUT HE'S STILL
NOT GETTIN' --
HE FIGURES IF HE --
HOLD UP A FISHING --
NO, IT'S STILL NOT --
EVEN DOESN'T.
SO I'M THINKING
I NEED TO GET --
MAYBE I SHOULD
GET AWAY FROM THE BUILDING.
OR MAYBE THE POSSUM VAN
ITSELF IS THROWING IT OFF,
SO I'M GOIN' --
AND MEANWHILE HE'S GOIN'
THROUGH AN AREA THEY'RE
TRYING TO DEMOLISH.
FUNNY HE DIDN'T NOTICE
THAT WRECKING BALL,
BUT THAT ACTUALLY BROUGHT
HIM OVER TO THE VAN.
BUT OF COURSE, I WAS
GONE AT THAT POINT.
AND THEN WALTER GOT THE IDEA
THAT MAYBE HE COULD
GET ON TOP OF IT
WITH THE VAN BEING
SOMEWHAT METAL,
HE COULD CLIMB UP
THE SIDE THERE --
HOOKED HIS
FISHING LINE ON THERE,
JUST KIND OF
WIND HIMSELF UP,
RIGHT UP THE UNIT THERE.
MEANWHILE, I HAD FOUND
MY WAY BACK TO THE VAN,
BUT I DIDN'T NOTICE,
OF COURSE, THAT WALTER
WAS UP THERE.
STILL NOT REALLY
GETTING MUCH OF A SIGNAL,
AND SO I THOUGHT IF I COULD
TAKE HER UP TO THE POINT --
THIS WAS REALLY NOT
THE BEST THING TO DO.
DON'T TRY THIS
AT HOME, KIDS.
THEN I HEAR WALTER
UP ON THE ROOF,
SO I HIT THE BRAKES.
AND I COME OUT TO
SEE WHAT EXACTLY IT WAS
THAT HE WAS CALLING ABOUT,
AND HE WANTED TO SEE
IF I WANTED TO GO FISHING.
WELL, IT'S A
LITTLE LATE NOW.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD'VE
CALLED ME EARLIER.
[ DIAL TONE ]
YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS A KID,
MY MOTHER WOULD ALWAYS
COOK UP A TURKEY
FOR SPECIAL OCCASIONS.
SHE'D ROAST IT IN THE OVEN
WITH POTATOES ALL AROUND
THE OUTSIDE.
I MEAN, IT'S AN
EASY WAY TO COOK,
BUT IT DOESN'T REALLY
WORK UP HERE AT THE LODGE
BECAUSE WE'VE GOT
SO MANY BIG EATERS.
I'VE SEEN MOOSE THOMPSON PUT
A 25-POUND TURKEY ON A
ROOFING NAIL
AND CALL IT
AN HORS D'OEUVRE.
SO WE HAD TO TAKE
OUR COOKING TECHNIQUES
AND BIGGIE SIZE 'EM.
THE REAL PROBLEM HERE
IS THAT THE AVERAGE OVEN
ONLY HOLDS ABOUT
NINE CUBIC FEET OF FOOD,
WHICH IS THE SAME CAPACITY
AS MOOSE'S LEFT CHEEK --
THE ONE HE EATS WITH.
SO WE NEED A
BIGGER COOKER.
MEET THE POSSUM LODGE
V8 OVEN.
THE FLOOR BOARDS ARE ALL
ROTTED OUT ON THIS UNIT,
AND THE EXHAUST
SYSTEM LEAKS.
SO IT'S JUST LIKE
A GIFT FROM HEAVEN.
ALL'S I HAVE TO DO IS TAKE
A FEW SPARK PLUG WIRES OFF
TO GET RAW GAS
INTO THE TAIL PIPE.
WHO HASN'T BEEN THERE?
AND WE'VE GOT OURSELVES
A MAN-SIZED OVEN.
A LITTLE TRIAL AND ERROR
INVOLVED IN THE OVEN SETTINGS.
I FIND THAT IF YOU SET
THE IDLE TO 1200 rpm,
YOU CAN GET THE ENTIRE CARGO
AREA UP TO 350 DEGREES.
[ TIMER RINGING ]
YOU'LL HAVE TO EXCUSE ME.
DINNER'S READY.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, WE
INTERRUPT THE RED GREEN SHOW
SO THAT I MAY BRING YOU
THE FOLLOWING IMPORTANT
ENVIRONMENTAL MESSAGE.
GREETINGS, CAMPERS.
RANGER GORD HERE WITH
ANOTHER OF MY PATENTED
WELL, SAY NOW.
HERE'S A PLEASANT SCENE.
A COUPLE OF
VACANT-EYED GOOFBALLS
ENJOYING A CASUAL
SAIL TOGETHER.
UNFORTUNATELY, BEING OUT
ON THE WATER WITHOUT
PROPER TRAINING
CAN BE FATAL TO EVEN THE
SHARPEST TACK IN THE DRAWER.
OH, SURE.
WHEN THE WEATHER IS CALM,
NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
BUT WHAT HAPPENS
IF THE WIND PICKS UP
AND THE BOAT STARTS
TAKING ON WATER?
AND PERHAPS THE BAILER
GETS FLUNG OVERBOARD?
AND WHAT IF YOU DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH LIFE JACKETS, HM?
SO REMEMBER, KIDS,
NEVER SWIM IN
A GOOD FISHING SPOT.
IT'S JUST COMMON SENSE,
ISN'T IT?
[ HEARTY CHUCKLE ]
WELL, YET ANOTHER
REMINDER
THAT THERE IS ALMOST
NOTHING ABOUT WOMEN
THAT WE UNDERSTAND.
SO WE'RE UP THERE
ON THE CHURCH ROOF.
GOT THE WALKIE TALKIE
HANGING FROM THE
FISHING LINE
DOWN THROUGH
THE CHIMNEY
INTO THE ROOM WHERE
THEY'RE HAVING
THE MEETING.
YEAH, WE GOT THE OTHER
WALKIE TALKIE BESIDE US
SO WE CAN HEAR
WHAT THEY'RE SAYING.
NOW, I'M NOT SURE,
BUT I THINK WE WERE BREAKING
MAYBE FOUR OF THE TEN
COMMANDMENTS.
AND, YOU KNOW, BEING ON
THE ROOF OF A CHURCH,
THAT'S GOTTA BE
A NEW RECORD.
I WOULD SAY, YEAH.
AND IT WAS A WARM DAY,
WASN'T IT, DALTON?
OH! VERY WARM!
VERY WARM.
YEAH, BUT NOT MATTER
HOW WARM IT IS,
WOMAN CAN STILL
GET A CHILL.
OH, YEAH.
THEY CAN GET A CHILL.
SO IMAGINE OUR SURPRISE
WHEN IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE MEETING
THEY STARTED A FIRE
IN THE FIREPLACE.
HOW DID IT GO?
YOU HEAR
ANYTHING HOT?
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE WHAT
THEY SAID ABOUT US, HAROLD.
I DON'T THINK IT'S
FAIR TO CRITICIZE THEM
FOR SAYING THINGS YOU
WERE NEVER INTENDED
TO HEAR.
NO, HAROLD, NO!
THIS WAS
REALLY HURTFUL.
AND THERE'S NO
TAKING THIS BACK.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAID
ABOUT EACH AND EVERY
ONE OF US HUSBANDS?
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
ZERO. NADA.
TALKED ABOUT THEIR JOBS;
TALKED ABOUT THEIR
NEIGHBOURS;
TALKED ABOUT
THEIR KIDS.
NOT A WORD ABOUT US.
MAYBE THEY'VE
GIVEN UP.
NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS THEIR
WAY OF SAYING
THAT WE ARE SUCH A
SMALL PART OF THEIR LIVES
WE DON'T EVEN MAKE
IT ONTO THE RADAR.
WELL, TWO CAN
PLAY AT THAT GAME,
CAN'T THEY, DALTON?
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE ARE GOING TO START BEING A
HUGE PART OF THEIR LIVES.
AT HOME, ON TIME,
EVERY NIGHT.
TALK TO THEM.
WELL, THAT'LL
TEACH 'EM A LESSON.
WE'RE GONNA BUY
'EM GIFTS, HAROLD.
WE'RE GONNA BUY 'EM
FLOWERS, AREN'T WE,
DALTON?
UH, YEAH,
I GUESS, SURE.
AND WE'RE GONNA TAKE
'EM OUT ON DATES.
YEAH, BUT DOUBLE
DATES, RIGHT?
HEY, WHATEVER IT TAKES TO GET
'EM TALKIN' ABOUT US, RIGHT?
YOU'RE GONNA
TAKE 'EM SOMEWHERE
SPECIAL, THOUGH, HUH?
OH, YEAH.
SOMEWHERE SPECIAL?
YOU WANNA SEE
SOMETHING SPECIAL?
HOW ABOUT THE 10th ANNUAL
MONSTER TRUCK SHOWDOWN?!
WHERE YOU PAY
FOR THE WHOLE SEAT,
Both:
BUT YOU ONLY USE THE EDGE!
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M HOPING TO GIVE YOU
SOMETHING TO TALK
ABOUT TONIGHT.
WE PAID FOR
THE WHOLE BED,
BUT WE'LL ONLY USE THE EDGE!
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, EVERYBODY.
SIT DOWN IN THE BACK.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
YOU KNOW, SOMEBODY ONCE SAID
THAT THE ONLY THING WORSE
THAN HAVING PEOPLE
TALK ABOUT YOU,
WAS NOT HAVING
PEOPLE TALK ABOUT YOU.
YEAH, THAT WAS
OSCAR WILDE.
WHAT, THE HOT DOG GUY?
NO, THAT'S
OSCAR MAYER.
SEE, NOW, ONLY A
WIENER WOULD KNOW THAT.