And now it's the beginning of our show, the
part where the camera comes up the hallway at
great expense to us, but you know, that's
because the Dolly rental and things like
that. Of course, we're just, you know, an
indication to show you how much we're willing
to do to put on a good show.
And you know, that's why we're showing you
in the hallway.
Anyway, here's a man who pays for the dollar
in every way.
My uncle and the star of the Red Green Show,
Mr.
Red Green.
Harold, thank you and welcome to Possum
Lodge.
Harold produces and directs the show and
everything else that I don't feel like doing
or think is important or understand or care
about it.
I think it's very important to the look in
the pace of the show, especially, you know,
like the special effects.
Well, I think that's at least as helpful as
that Dolly is.
Oh, speaking of Dolly's, our head of security
is getting married.
What? Nor- North getting married?
Oh, I don't even know he was dating a girl.
Oh yeah. It all happened.
Last week, he and junior singleton were
skinny dipping down suicide rock, which is
pretty gutsy when you consider the amount of
carnivorous wildlife that hangs out down
there. Anyway, they're right in the middle
of a dip, skin wise, and a couple of women
came by and wow, the story gets a little
fuzzy here, but it ends up with Noel
proposing to one of them.
And the surprise is that what he proposed
was marriage.
That's a parallel
Fact. Sorry, miss that.
Sorry.
I just think Noel's engaged in what he
married Cheryl.
Noel is going to marry one of those women.
Oh, that means Junior's going to marry the
other one.
Well, he's going to check it with his present
wife.
I don't think it looks good. You know,
I was just thinking, you know what I mean?
Like, if Noel can find a woman, maybe
there's hope for me too.
You know what I mean? Noel Clayton, I
certainly could.
Well, maybe I should go skinny dipping for
Mrs.
Wright
Or Mr. Snapping
Turtle
And had dates before, you know, but that was
usually on dates with women.
This is this was totally different.
This one. Belinda Lind is her name.
Well, Linda actually didn't mind talking to
Noel for a few minutes, and as far as he's
concerned, that's love.
That's a little skeptical, you know, love at
first sight, especially if the first sight is
of Noel.
You really don't think you know you guys are
in any position to be judging relationships.
I mean, if you knew anything about women,
you wouldn't spend half of your life up at
this lodge
And the other half sleeping well.
Well, we know how to get along with women,
Harold.
It's just tiring. That's all.
Wow. Understanding and sensitivity.
All right. Yeah. Anyway, nobody's going to
tie the old Slipknot next week and everybody
at the lodge is invited. It's kind of
exciting.
So a bunch of us all went back for another
skinny dip and we decided that junior is the
best man. So we're going to have the wedding
put out by the sister there, where the
mosquitoes are real bad.
And that way the minister will keep
everything kind of goose in the long course.
Where have they decided to go like on their
honeymoon?
Are they going to Des Moines, Iowa, Harold?
Yeah, there's a Chuck Norris film festival
down there.
Kind of a lifelong dream for Noel.
They've to register the China pattern with
seven 11.
I wonder what I should get, Noel, for his
pre-nup nuptials.
Well, I think the doctors will take care of
that.
Harold, have you seen how long the grass is?
No, I've seen how green is my valley?
Is this like a sequel or something?
I'm talking about the grass out behind the
lodge.
We can't have an unkempt lawn with Noel's
wedding coming up.
It looks scrappy.
Why don't you go out there and cut that
lawn?
It's a field, yes, but it doesn't have to be
a messy field.
I could pay you.
I want a thousand dollars in a tractor.
Yes, I'm sure you would. But as large
treasurer, I'd have to say, get real.
And perhaps one of your school chums could
do it.
Oh no.
They hit me every time I asked them things
like that.
Well, I'm just I'm just going to have to go
out there and do it myself.
Is that what you want? I hadn't really
thought about it.
Yes, I do, I. But I'm having a little
trouble getting your nephew to help me out
here, read.
No kidding.
But. Ok, I got a little stag thing pretty
well set up.
We're having a stag for Noel.
This is the first time I've heard about it.
How come nobody told me anything?
Try coming to the lodge meetings, bob that
sometimes works.
No, not stags. No.
Stags are a pagan ritual and I will not be
involved.
You go right ahead if you like, but I will
not be there.
Of course, it looks like
I'm not invited either.
I made this list up of what we'll need for a
major party.
Ok, the flares are optional, but I thought
they'd be a nice touch and we're going to
have to get a couple more cases of beer.
My brother's coming. Is that wedding gift
coming
There, bill?
Great. Don't forget the salami.
Sorry. Figuring on holding his wing being in
the lodge helmet.
No, in the woods are more washrooms.
I mean, we'll have to come in for a while
because it's too dark to see the stripper
skipper.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Strippers. Strippers are sexist and archaic.
No, no, no. Do you honestly believe that the
bride is over there having a male stripper
and her shower? Oh, OK, yes, we know she is,
but the point is we should be setting an
example.
Well, we'll just turn the other cheek.
No, wait, Harold's, right?
Well, there's two words I never thought I'd
say together anyway.
We can do much better than that.
We can have a civilized stag, not a game of
golf, but a game of golf.
The No. Open a game of golf.
Thirty six pools of camaraderie, revelry,
jocularity.
Of course, all proceeds go to Noel, then
later will gather in the pro shop and sing
Scottish tunes.
Armstrong this stag is for members only.
Harry Lauder is not coming.
We have to do with members of Possum Lodge
have always done its tradition.
The party, the beer, the stripper, the fist
fight that drive to the hospital.
It's tradition. You see, maybe you don't
remember, but I work for the natural
resources. Oh, well, bunch of lodge members
are going to be caper in about in the in the
woods. Well, I've got a concern myself with
environmental damage.
The woods affair a hell of a lot better than
the golf course will tell you that.
Well, no stag.
Why don't we let him decide?
No, we're talking about.
No, no.
Yeah, you're right.
Who wants to spend the whole evening playing
ping pong and eating yogurt?
Let me know what you figure out anyway.
You know, the lodge is supposed to be a
democracy.
Why don't we let just the majority decide
we'll have a vote tonight at the Lodge
meeting?
But if it's a tie, we'll let the stripper
vote.
Fine. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Only lodge members can vote unless, of
course, one of the Lodge members is the
Stripper, and he takes his clothes off.
Oh, he's not, is he?
Oh, the cold, cold rain
Comes out of the sky.
It lands on things that were formerly dry.
It runs down the roof and drips from the air
and lets you know exactly where your bald
spots are.
This week on and back corner talk about
recycling.
If you're like me, I hate to throw things
away, you know, bits of string or newspapers
or our old engines and stuff, you know, and
what are you going to do with an old engine,
you know now? I suppose I could take this
down to the auto workers or scrap iron yard
or whatever and get a few dollars for it.
But you know the hassle of me driving down
there in the truck.
You know what? The cost of gas being what it
is.
And of course, I'd have to put this actually
install this back into the truck before I
could drive down there. And so.
So what am I going to do with this old
engine?
Well, I know that ordinarily what you do is
you dip down to a conservation area and just
dump it into a ravine or something.
I'd like to show you something kind of
interesting.
I'm going to show you how you can equip your
whole kitchen from one engine.
Now, everybody with the space between their
teeth likes corn on the cob.
And what an interesting way to hold the corn
on the cob and to take your valves out of
your engine and thrust them into the ends of
your crop.
And then you can take the the valve cover off
the motor, and this is a handy trait to hold
your your butter, just roll it in there or
you can make it 10 W30 if it's to go.
I don't care where you go, you're not going
to find a better frying pan than an air
cleaner. Get your bacon around the outside
there.
Do pancakes a little twisting them up in the
middle.
And then of course, you comes with a lid.
Pop that right on and what the wingnut on
her there.
You got yourself a pressure cooker.
Unbelievable. Other than kind of
interesting.
I don't care where you go, who you know
what?
You see what you do. You are not going to
find a better roasting pan than the sump pan
off of a motor. You ever try to ladle soup
in the kitchen?
It's a real problem.
Makes a big mess all over the place.
What you do is take your exhaust manifold,
line up the parts over the soup bowls, but
the soup into a pitcher of some kind.
And then you just pour the soup right up
your own tailpipe.
How about that, huh?
See, then you're going to throw this stuff
out.
So until next time, the women don't find you
handsome, least find your handy.
How about some more suit guys
Coming right up? Yes.
Oh, nuts, we got the junkie.
Typekit. It is autumn time to get the vote
out of the lake.
If only you can remember where it sank.
The. So anyway, everything's kind of coming
together for the wedding, you know, Junior
Sexton's wife, has accepted his apology.
Junior says, you know, he could make it a
double ring ceremony where Noel and Belinda,
we get married and then Junior and his wife,
who could renew their vows, but his wife's
not too keen on that.
She says she's not sorry that she married
him, but she's had 10 years to kind of think
it over and let's not push it.
I think weddings forced you into that sort of
thinking, you know, you reevaluate your
marriage in your life or what have you.
Yeah, and what have you, Harold?
Oh, I have my my hobbies in my work, you
know, like this?
Oh, you mean if I could find you a wife,
you'd quit.
Oh no, I'm not into those pre-arranged
marriage things.
I mean, love and destiny are the stars of
which I steer my life by.
I think you're like that.
Oh, yes, I do.
How did you now furnish me?
Go ahead.
Well, she was the only one who answered the
ad.
See, now I know that's a lie.
I know that. I know that deep down, you are
a happily married man.
Well, yeah, yeah.
You're right, Harold.
You know you're an Renesas made me what I am
today.
Don't ever say that to her uncle.
Read That could be oh, so hurtful.
I ask you a question here for a minute.
I'm a bit busy right here, Fred.
Well, that's OK. I don't mind.
It's about Noel Stagg.
I need to ask you about money.
It's always about money.
Isn't it red? Douglas, can we spare some
money?
Douglas, can I have some money?
Douglas How many quarters in a dollar?
But why do people always bother me with
money problems?
Well, probably because you're the lodge
treasurer.
Well, I'm a treasurer without a treasure.
I'm sorry. Read the men are just going to
have to pass the hat.
Oh, I don't think so, Douglas.
I mean, everybody likes Noel, you know, but
not enough to actually cough up some money
for him.
How much money are we wasting here anyway?
Well, it depends what kind of a stag you're
talking about right now.
It's either going to be a friendly game of
golf or a pagan ceremony in the jungle.
A golf tournament
Would be more
Expensive than a jungle orgy.
Yeah, that's what we figured, too.
Helmut says he can bring it in for under two
hundred bucks, and that would include a
mirror ball, fireworks, bricklayers trowel.
That's a gift. Seven cases of beer.
Half a dozen carrot sticks and a stripper.
Well, you can stop right there, Mr.
I'm not going to be any part of a sexist,
disgusting display of female flesh.
It's degrading.
Well, we weren't asking you to go, Douglas.
We just want you to pay for it.
Doesn't someone just go into town and rent
some movies, you know, like maybe Fellini's,
Amarcord or Bunuel's, the discreet charm of
the bourgeoisie, and then we can sit and
watch films and eat popcorn.
I like going to see, you know, we're talking
about some pretty modest attention spans the
I don't really think we've got the subtitles
crowd in there.
I'm sorry that I tried to help.
You know, I have to buy a new toilet seat
and you're asking me for stag money.
What would you
Do? Well, it depends when you ask me
What is wrong with this thing?
Why is it that the things all around here
always just break and fall apart?
Well, let me give it a try for those of you
who have watched our show more than once.
First of all, get help now and secondly this
year recognise this bit because this is
actually part two of an adventure of a bill
we did earlier where he cut his forehead with
a knife. But this is how to find food in the
woods.
What he's doing here and part two is he says
that in certain kinds of trees, you can just
peel the bark off and chew it.
It's got protein in there and it's got rival
rival.
It's got stuff in it. That's good for him
too, you know, by golly, he's just chewy.
I wouldn't say that it had a shortage of
taste.
It just had a shortage of good taste.
By golly, she was chewy and I thought, I
think I might have a better application for
this. And now
they'll locks up the tree there and sees a
nest was there.
What do you think is going to be a couple of
eggs in there?
So he needs a little boost up and bail is
put on a fair bit of weight since we used to
do this when we were six and seven years
old.
Now is aiming isn't any better either.
And this is taking far too long that you
don't want someone to come across you in the
woods. When you're doing that, I'll tell you
anyway, why don't we just get the ladder in
the first place? So now stands a ladder up
after hurting me, bad, and I'm going to hold
steady the ladder for him.
He's going to go up there and that's one of
them three legged cherry picking ladders.
I believe he's going to go up and do a
little cherry picking of his own.
There's an egg right there.
That's a big bird.
Two eggs, sunny side up and and a strip of
bacon may not be a bird's nest.
It might actually be a Denny's other egg.
There he's doing real close ups.
Oh no, I get mad and I pull a ladder over.
As a embarrassed about that, but not not too
bad a kind of gays are now in the nest cams
that could have got the exact way anyway and
funny, how life's fair sometimes.
But.
And. And.
Well, apparently a decision has been made
about Noel Stagg.
Whatever it is and wherever it is going to
happen, it's going to take place after the
Lodge meeting tonight. You know, the lodge
has quite a history of stags over the last
hundred years and actually the old man
Sedgwick has been to all of them, in fact,
that his own stag, he has such a good time.
He actually missed his wedding day and
luckily his bride ran off with the caterer.
I remember in Bill Smith's Stag, a whole
bunch of us got up in a tree and then and
then helmet cut it down,
You
Know? And what? What we thought was just a
social error turned out to be the chainsaw
backfiring. We set the tree on fire, burn us
all to the ground.
I got it. I do not know how you can associate
risking life and limb with a good time.
I mean, whatever happened to like, good
conversation, dancing, music, pop, you know,
stuff like that.
Well, Harold, it's not enough to enjoy a
party.
You know, you have to survive the party
after one of our stags 50 years of marriage
is a cakewalk.
Oh, OK, well, I guess we should bring this up
in the next meeting.
I'll see you down there, OK?
Don't worry, we're not going to let a hundred
years of tradition go down the drain just to
allow some common sense to get between us
and a little harmful fun
That ring ring ring.
Oh, you are great.
All right, guys.
I'm gonna get you down to the bank.
So is a lucky groom here?
No, no, no. This is perfect.
We're going to.
All right. All right. This helmet, Whittaker.
Good news, guys. The stag is on.
What did the beer and any city's going to
prepare some food so we can use it in the
food fight? Well, actually hang on a second
just a minute here, guys.
I've been checking the fire danger reports
and the forest is tinder dry.
The stag could turn into a huge inferno.
We're now on day on.
And what do you think about this while we
take this tag and move it right onto the golf
course?
What was the second look for the
Golf course is it's always watered, so
there's no possibility there will be a fire.
50 guys out there playing golf in the middle
of the night.
I could get those ah glow in the dark golf
balls from my friend at the atomic energy,
you know? I thought it would be fun.
You can bring bring all the beer you out
onto the course.
Know, maybe I could get one.
Why don't we use the balls that don't glow
in the dark?
That'll add a little edge to the game.
And then afterwards, we're going to have a
demolition derby with the golf cart.
Terror shovels, huh? Well, we're all the
Greens are not grass, I pay a million
Dollars a square inch for it. We just shovel
underneath it all over.
Well, I think probably having the party in
the forests would be fine
On a golf course is green because, you know,
I don't want to shut up travel tour because
we got what we do, right? We go skinny
dipping in the water hazards, right?
Yap, Yap, Yap. No. And then you know what
else we do?
We get out into dry off.
We roll around in the sand and the sand
traps rolling around to get dry in the set.
I'm not invited, so it's not like a point or
something.
But I understand there's going to be a
stripper.
The speed, Belinda Bettendorf.
I feel better he got so excited he burst into
tears, ran up the suicide rocket.
Well, he said waste that we. Belinda
Bettendorf.
That's the name of Noel's Bryant Knowles
marrying a stripper.
I know he thinks he seems to think that
she's a legal secretary.
Well, don't you see, that's why Noel is
crying.
He's probably calling off the wedding by
now.
She lost her job. No, I think Douglas is
right, guys.
We've all just been snookered out of
A stag party. Oh.
Oh, oh, god, no.
It's like
Business. Not just give us some entertainment
First, what us to be family first one.
Well, boys, I've got something special for
you.
I'm going to show you how to juggle.
Now, of course, we're all pretty disappointed
about there being no stag.
I guess we're going to have to come to terms
with that.
You know that our hopes and our dreams are
dashed and our plans for nothing.
And we've all been kind of betrayed on some
level.
I guess in time we'll be able to forgive
Noel, you know, time heals all wounds and all
that. But still, you know, as for Noah, I'm
sure that out there somewhere is a short,
bullheaded female correctional officer who
would like to be Mrs.
Noel Christmas. Noel Christmas.
Yeah, that's his name. Of course, the people
that gave him that name would be her in-laws.
Anyway, if my wife is watching, I'm going to
be coming straight home after the meeting,
and hopefully Noel will had a chance to
return our gift.
So until next time.
On behalf of myself and Harold and the whole
gang up here at Possum Lodge.
Keep your stick on the ice.
It looks harder than it is.
Well, you can even do this well, you know,
with other people, Bob, why don't you go out
there and show the boys how to juggle with
two people?
All right, I go, so let's go.
This is a great thing. It goes really well
at parties.