IF YOU'RE A
MARRIED MAN YOU KNOW
THERE ARE CERTAIN TIMES WHEN
YOUR WIFE WANTS YOU
TO FALL ASLEEP
AND CERTAIN TIMES
WHEN SHE DOESN'T.
FALLING ASLEEP IS
ALMOST ALWAYS ENCOURAGED.
BUT IN THE LIVING ROOM,
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU'RE
WATCHING OPRAH TOGETHER,
OR YOUR WIFE'S IN
THE MIDDLE OF DISCUSSING
YOUR MUCH-NEEDED
BEHAVIOR MODIFICATION,
FALLING ASLEEP
IS NOT SO GOOD.
SO WHAT I'VE DONE IS
CUSTOMIZED MY FAVOURITE CHAIR,
SO IT'S GONNA
HELP KEEP ME AWAKE
WHENEVER I'M BEING CRITICIZED
OR A RELATIVE DROPS OVER.
SEE, THIS HERE'S
A CAR BATTERY.
I'VE GOT THAT WIRED INTO
WHAT WAS LEFT OF MY
WINDSHIELD WIPER
AFTER THE CARWASH
GOT DONE WITH IT.
OKAY, SO NOW I JUST
HOOK UP THE BATTERY,
AND I'VE GOT THE WHOLE
SYSTEM WIRED THROUGH
THIS CLOTHES PEG,
KIND OF A DEADMAN SWITCH.
SO AS LONG AS I'M AWAKE,
I'M SQUEEZING THE PEG --
SO TO SPEAK --
AND THE WHOLE UNIT
IS SHUT OFF.
BUT AS SOON AS I FALL
ASLEEP AND START RELAXING,
THE WINDSHIELD
WIPER COMES ON,
AND STARTS POKING ME
IN THE BACK AND WAKES ME UP.
OKAY, LET'S HAVE A LITTLE
DEMONSTRATION HERE.
I'LL JUST SIT HERE
UNTIL I FALL ASLEEP.
LET'S SEE.
WHAT COULD MAKE ME DROWSY?
OH, I KNOW.
GET THE CAMERAMAN THERE
TO TALK ABOUT HAVING
HIS COLOURS DONE.
[snoring]
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
OH, I APPRECIATE THAT.
WELL, BIG, BIG WEEK AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
YEAH, WE ACTUALLY SUPPORT
A LOCAL CHARITY
THAT'S LOOKING FOR A CURE
FOR MALE PATTERN BALDNESS.
LAST NIGHT THEY HAD
THEIR ANNUAL CHARITY DANCE.
IT'S CALLED THE HAIR BALL.
I TELL YOU, PEOPLE
REALLY COUGH UP THE CASH.
UNCLE RED.
OKAY, DID YOU NOTICE
LAST NIGHT AT THE PARTY
I WAS THE ONLY
PERSON WITHOUT A DATE?
NO, MIKE DIDN'T
HAVE A DATE.
THAT WOMAN WAS
HIS PAROLE OFFICER.
EVEN STILL, YOU KNOW,
EVERYONE AROUND HERE
EITHER HAS A GIRLFRIEND
OR A WIFE OR SOMETHING.
EXCEPT ME.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
IT'S ONLY A HALF-HOUR
SHOW, HAROLD.
WELL, HAVE YOU ASKED
ANY OF THE GIRLS OUT
AROUND HERE?
THERE'S PLENTY OF
THEM IN THE AREA.
YES!
I ASKED EVERYONE.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT'S WEIRD?
ON FRIDAY NIGHTS
EVERY GIRL IN THIS AREA
EITHER WASHES HER HAIR
OR DOES HER LAUNDRY.
I'M VERY CONCERNED
WHAT ALL THAT SOAP RUN-OFF
IS GOING TO DO
TO THE ECOSYSTEM.
WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
GO TO WHERE YOU CAN
MEET GIRLS,
LIKE GO TO THE
LAUNDROMAT OR THE
SHAMPOO STORE.
YEAH, I'VE EVEN GOT
A BETTER IDEA THAN THAT.
IS THAT OUR LOCAL
YELLOW PAGES?
YEAH, BOTH OF 'EM.
LOOK AT THIS...
VIDEO DATING SERVICE.
YEAH, YOU MAKE A
VIDEO TAPE OF YOURSELF,
TALKING ABOUT YOURSELF,
AND THEN YOU SEND IT TO THIS
COMPANY, RIGHT, VIDEOMATE.
AND THAT WAY,
YOUR PROSPECTIVE DATE,
SHE GETS TO HEAR AND SEE ME
BEFORE SHE MEETS ME.
OKAY, BUT YOU'RE SAYING THAT
LIKE IT'S A GOOD THING.
[laughter]
DON'T BE SO NEGATIVE.
YOUR GENERATION DIDN'T
HAVE VIDEO DATING,
AND LOOK AT ALL THE HORRIBLE
MISTAKES THEY MADE.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
WHO TOLD YOU THAT?
AUNT BERNICE.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
UH, TONIGHT'S WINNER WILL
RECEIVE THIS COUPON
FOR TWO HOURS ALONE
WITH A FINICKY LAWN MOWER
AND A 10-POUND
SLEDGE HAMMER.
NO QUESTIONS ASKED.
OKAY, COVER YOUR EARS.
AND NOW MR. GREEN
YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH,
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND... GO!
OKAY, DALTON,
YOUR CLOTHES, YOUR SHOES,
THE CAR YOU DRIVE ARE ALL
PART OF YOUR PERSONAL...
COMMITMENT
TO RECYCLING.
NO, NO, NO.
I'M TALKING ABOUT --
WELL, LIKE YOUR HAIR.
IT LOOKS THAT WAY BECAUSE
OF YOUR SPECIAL...
UH, UH, VACUUM
CLEANER ATTACHMENT!
NO, OKAY.
OKAY, OKAY.
LET'S SAY YOU WERE GONNA
TAKE ANN MARIE ON A
WORLD CRUISE.
SO YOU BOUGHT A WHOLE NEW
WARDROBE OF CRUISE WEAR.
YOU'VE GOT THE BEST
STATE ROOM ON THE
WHOLE SHIP,
AND YOU DID EVERYTHING
FIRST CLASS ALL THE WAY.
PEOPLE WOULD SAY, DALTON,
YOU'RE REALLY GOING IN...
SANE!
ALMOST OUTTA
TIME, MR. GREEN.
YEAH, OKAY.
DALTON, ANN MARIE LIKES
TO GO SHOPPING ALL THE TIME
BECAUSE SHE WANTS
TO STAY IN...
DEBT.
THE WOMAN SPENDS MONEY LIKE
IT'S GOIN' OUTTA STYLE.
THERE WE GO!
[quirky upbeat music]
HEY! RED GREEN!
WHAT A BIG SURPRISE!
YOU ASKED ME TO
COME HERE, GORD.
I KNOW, BUT I LIKE
MAKING A BIG FUSS
OVER MY VISITORS.
THAT WAY THEY
MIGHT STAY LONGER.
WHAT DO YOU LIKE
HAVING FOR BREAKFAST?
A CONVERSATION
WITH MY WIFE.
RIGHT. OKAY.
MESSAGE TAKEN.
ABSOLUTELY.
WITH RANGER GORD THERE'S
NO STRINGS ATTACHED.
YOU'RE FREE TO COME
AND GO AS YOU PLEASE.
OH, PLEASE DON'T GO!
[weeping]
OKAY. OKAY.
YEAH, PLEASE.
LET'S SIT DOWN.
WHAT DID YOU WANT TO
TALK TO ME ABOUT, GORD?
YEAH, RIGHT.
ABOUT MY NEW CAREER.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
RED, WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT ME AND MY LIFE,
WHAT'S THE BIGGEST MISTAKE
YOU THINK I'VE MADE?
WELL, THERE'S SO MANY
TO CHOOSE FROM, GORD.
NO, BEING AN
EMPLOYEE.
OKAY, THAT'S THE BIG ONE,
BUT NO MORE.
I'VE DECIDED
TO GO FREELANCE.
A FREELANCE
FOREST RANGER?
OH, SURE, SURE.
ABSOLUTELY.
FOREST FIRES CAN SPOIL
ALMOST ANY SOCIAL EVENT,
WEDDINGS,
BAR MITZVAHs,
EVER BEEN A FOREST FIRE
AT A BAR MITZVAH?
NOT YET,
BUT WHY TAKE THE CHANCE?
AND THERE'S PLENTY
OF OTHER OPPORTUNITIES...
STRIP MALLS,
RETIREMENT VILLAGES.
I MEAN, COME ON, RED,
OLD PEOPLE WITH BARBECUES?
WHOO!
HERE'S MY NEW
BUSINESS CARD.
"RANGER GORD,
FREELANCE FOREST RANGER.
"WHERE THERE'S
SMOKE THERE'S GORD."
I WAS HOPING YOU COULD
PASS THAT OUT TO EVERYBODY.
WELL, DO YOU HAVE
ANY MORE OF THEM?
I DID,
BUT THEY BURNED.
YEAH, I WAS HOPING YOU
COULD READ THE INFORMATION
AND THEN PASS IT ON, KIND OF
LIKE A CHAIN BUSINESS CARD.
BUT THERE'S NO PHONE
NUMBER ON HERE, GORD.
YEAH, RED, I DON'T
HAVE A PHONE.
OKAY, UH, YOU KNOW,
YOU MAY NEED TO RETHINK
THIS WHOLE THING.
LIKE, WHAT IS YOUR
INCOME RIGHT NOW?
OH, GEE, DO YOU NEED
AN EXACT AMOUNT?
NO, JUST
BALLPARK IT.
OKAY, UH...
ZERO.
UH-HUH. OKAY.
SO ANY ADDITIONAL FREELANCE
INCOME THAT YOU MAKE
IS GONNA PUT YOU IN
A HIGHER TAX BRACKET.
RIGHT.
OKAY, SO I'M
GETTING FROM YOU
THAT YOU THINK I'M BETTER OFF
IF I STAY IN THE TOWER.
GORD, YOU STAY IN THE TOWER,
EVERYBODY'S BETTER OFF.
YOU KNOW, AROUND HERE WE GET
OUR DRINKING WATER FROM
POSSUM LAKE.
YEARS AGO THAT
NEVER BOTHERED ME.
BUT OF COURSE, BACK THEN YOU
COULD GET A SIX-PACK
FOR ONLY $1.79.
SO THIS TIME ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
YOU CAN MAKE YOUR OWN WATER.
OKAY, WE'RE GONNA
START WITH RAIN WATER
COMING RIGHT OFF THE ROOF.
THIS IS PURE,
UNPOLLUTED WATER
COMING STRAIGHT
FROM HEAVEN.
ALL WE GOTTA DO IS
FILTER OUT THE LEAVES
AND THE BIRD FEATHERS
AND THE MOLDY CHESTNUTS.
AND BOIL HER ALL UP,
AND WE'RE BEATIN' THE SYSTEM.
OKAY, FIRST THING YOU WANNA
DO IS TAKE OFF YOUR DOWNSPOUT.
CUT A SLOT IN HER,
DOWN AT THE ONE END.
THAT'S YOUR FIRST STAGE
FILTRATION RIGHT THERE.
TO CATCH THE
FINER STUFF...
PANTYHOSE.
NOT JUST FOR
HOLD-UPS ANYMORE.
OH, I GOT A RUN.
OKAY, NOW YOU WOULD
JUST RUN YOUR DOWNPIPE
JUST RIGHT OFF THE END
OF THE BUILDING THERE,
BUT I PUT THIS
EXTENSION ON OURS,
BECAUSE THERE'S A
WET SPOT OVER THERE
AND WHAT LOOKS LIKE MOOSE
THOMPSON'S FOOTPRINTS.
I JUST --
OKAY, WHAT I'M GONNA
DO NOW THEN
IS JUST JAM THIS UP IN HERE.
AND THAT TAKES CARE
OF OUR FILTRATION UNIT.
NOW WE NEED SOMETHING THAT
WILL CATCH THE WATER AND
THEN DISTILL IT.
I WANTED SOMETHING
SMALL AND PORTABLE
THAT HAD THE SAME
ENGINEERING SOPHISTICATION
AS THOSE HIGH END WATER
PURIFICATION PLANTS
THEY USE IN THE LARGER
METROPOLIS AREAS.
AND I THINK I'VE DONE IT.
[chuckles]
OH, YEAH, METAL CONTAINER HERE
GONNA CATCH MY FILTERED
RAIN WATER;
BARBECUE MAKES IT BOIL;
AND THE WAGON
MAKES IT PORTABLE.
NOW I JUST NEED
IT TO RAIN.
[thunder crashes]
OKAY SO I'M STANDING OUT IN
FRONT OF THE LODGE
WAITING FOR THE
RAIN TO STOP
SO I CAN TEST MY
DRINKING WATER,
AND THIS SMART GUY DROPPED
50 CENTS IN MY TIN CUP.
[change jingling]
PEOPLE ARE SO CHEAP.
OKAY, LET'S SEE WHAT
WE'VE GOT HERE.
[searing sound]
OH, IT'S HOT.
IT'S LIKE A FLAVOURED TEA.
KIND OF A SHINGLE/PEKOE.
I'M SURE YOU CAN
GET USED TO IT.
BUT THE MAIN POINT IS THAT
YOU'RE PROVIDING SOMETHING
FOR YOURSELF
AND YOUR FAMILY
THAT YOU KNOW
IS COMPLETELY SAFE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME --
(discouraged)
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[applause]
[quirky upbeat music]
ANY OF YOU GUYS WITH A FULL
HEALTHY HEAD OF HAIR
MIGHT WANT TO IGNORE
THIS PART.
BUT FOR THE REST OF US,
I WANNA TALK A LITTLE
BIT ABOUT BALD SPOTS.
YOU CAN NEVER BE FULLY
PREPARED FOR A BALD SPOT.
THEY KINDA CREEP
UP ON YOU.
AND THEY COME
UP FROM BEHIND,
SO YOU'RE USUALLY THE
LAST ONE TO EVEN FIND OUT.
AND I BELIEVE
THAT A BALD SPOT
IS SOME ALIEN LIFE FORM
OF SOME TYPE.
IT'S A LOT MORE SENSITIVE
THAN THE REST OF YOUR SKIN.
I MEAN, IT SUNBURNS
REAL EASY.
IT'S THE FIRST THING
THAT FEELS COLD OR RAIN.
IT'S THE FIRST THING TO
SWEAT IF YOU'RE IN TROUBLE
OR EATING MEXICAN FOOD
OR BOTH.
I THINK IT'S BECAUSE IT'S A
LOT YOUNGER THAN THE REST
OF YOUR SKIN.
I MEAN, EVERYTHING ELSE
IS MAYBE 50 YEARS OLD,
BUT YOUR BALD SPOT'S ONLY BEEN
AROUND FOR THE LAST THREE.
THAT'S WHY IT'S
SO SMOOTH AND PERKY.
SO INSTEAD OF THINKING
OF A BALD SPOT
AS AN EMBARRASSING
SIGN OF
OLD AGE AND
RAMPANT DECAY.
WHY DON'T YOU
THINK OF IT AS SEXY?
THEY SAY HAIR LOSS IS FROM
HAVING TOO MUCH TESTOSTERONE,
SO THAT'S A
PRETTY GOOD START.
I'VE ALREADY ESTABLISHED
THAT IT'S SMOOTH AND
REAL SENSITIVE.
SO I'M SUGGESTING
THAT A BALD SPOT
IS THE ULTIMATE
EROGENOUS ZONE,
A POWERFUL LOVE BADGE
THAT'S ONLY GIVEN
TO THE MOST MANLY OF MEN.
THERE.
NOW DO YOU FEEL
BETTER ABOUT YOUR BALD SPOT?
ME NEITHER.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
WHEN THE AIR AT YOUR
PLACE GIVES YOU THE BENDS;
WHEN YOU'VE LOST ALL CONTACT
WITH FAMILY AND FRIENDS;
I HAVE A TRUCK THAT
PUMPS AS IT MENDS.
'CAUSE THIS IS WHERE
THE FOOD CHAIN ENDS.
OKAY, I'M READY FOR
MY CLOSE-UP, PEOPLE.
LET'S GO!
THIS IS THE ONLY TAPE
I COULD FIND, HAROLD.
THAT CAMERA'S SOME KIND OF
DISCONTINUED, ONE-OFF FORMAT.
"THETA-MAX
VIDEOTAPE.
"MADE IN
PORTUGUESE MACAU."
OKAY, WELL,
ALL YOU'VE GOTTA DO
IS PROVIDE THE
LIGHTS AND THE CAMERA,
AND I'LL PROVIDE
THE ACT-SHUN!
HERE WE GO.
Red: OKAY.
AND... CAMERA'S ON.
ACTION, HAROLD.
I SAID,
ACTION, HAROLD. GO!
I AM GOING.
THIS PAUSE IS PART
OF MY VIDEO.
NOT A GOOD
IDEA, HAROLD.
YOU'RE GIVING HER
TIME TO CHANGE HER MIND.
[affected British accent]
OH, I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T HEAR
YOU COME IN.
WELL, I JUST CAME IN.
I WAS JUST TALKING TO YOU.
I JUST CAME UPSTAIRS --
NOT YOU!
MY DATE!
[affected British accent]
PLEASE, PLEASE FORGIVE MY
TECHNICAL ASSISTANT.
NON-UNION.
ALLOW ME TO
INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I'M HAROLD GREEN.
AND MIGHT I SAY YOU LOOK
LOVELY THIS EVENING
AND/OR DAY.
THAT IT?
Harold: NO! SHH!
I'M LISTENING TO WHAT
THE YOUNG, LOVELY,
FUN-LOVING, NON-SMOKING
LADY HAS TO SAY.
[affected British accent]
HM, OH, YOU WANT
TO COME CLOSER?
UH, GOT A BAD
WHEEL HERE, HAROLD.
HANG ON.
OKAY,
THERE WE GO.
[affected accent]
OH, CLOSER? WELL!
CERTAINLY, COME CLOSER.
OH, I DON'T KNOW,
HAROLD.
I'M NOT SURE THE CAMERA
CAN GRAB ALL THOSE TEETH.
CLOSER! CLOSER!
HAROLD, WE'RE GETTING A LOT
OF LIGHT OFF THOSE MOLARS.
WE'RE PINNING
THE NEEDLE HERE.
CALL ME! CALL ME!
CALL ME!
CALL 911 !
Red: NEEDED TO PUT A
SIGNPOST UP BEHIND THE LODGE.
SO WE AGREED TO ALL
MEET AROUND THERE.
A FEW EXTRA
THINGS IN THE VAN.
BUT THEN THE SIGNPOST
WAS IN THERE.
DALTON, HE GRABBED
HE PICKAXE.
WE NEEDED THAT TO
KIND OF DIG THE HOLE.
AND I GRABBED THE POST, AND
SHE WAS SNAGGED ON SOMETHING,
SO I ASKED DALTON TO
MAYBE GIVE ME A HAND THERE.
LET'S HORSE HER OUTTA THERE.
SO I'M NOT SURE WHAT IT WAS
CAUGHT ON AT THAT POINT.
THEN I REALISED IT WAS
ACTUALLY CAUGHT ON WALTER.
AND WINSTON WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE --
BUT HE HAD FALLEN ASLEEP AT
THE SWITCH, SO TO SPEAK,
SO WINSTON'S JUST GOT A --
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF
WAKING HIM UP.
YOU DON'T GET MUCH SLEEP
IN THE SEWAGE BUSINESS.
SO HE JUST CLIPS THAT ON.
AND THEN YOU KNOW THE GROUND
AROUND THE LODGE IS VERY ODD.
THERE'S HARD SPOTS,
AND THERE'S SOFT SPOTS,
AND THERE'S KIND OF IN
BETWEEN KIND OF CLAY STUFF.
SO YOU KNOW, YOU JUST
KIND OF TAKE YOUR CHANCES.
SO WINSTON PICKED A SPOT,
AND HE GOT INTO IT,
BUT HE'D GET IT DOWN
TO A CERTAIN POINT,
BUT HE COULDN'T GET
IT ALL THE WAY IN,
SO WALTER GAVE HIM
A LITTLE HAND ON THAT.
SO I'M THINKING,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S JUST TRY
ANOTHER SPOT.
MAYBE THERE'S A
SOFTER SPOT HERE.
OKAY, THAT'S A
LITTLE TOO HARD.
THEN DALTON FIGURES HE
WOULD TRY A PICKAXE.
THE TROUBLE WITH THAT IS YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT'S DOWN THERE.
AND I'M GUESSING SOME
KIND OF BURIED CABLE.
AND, YEAH.
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
SO THEN WE'VE GOTTA
GET THAT OUTTA THERE.
I'M TELLING WINSTON,
GO BACK AND GET
THE POSSUM VAN.
WE'LL PULL IT
OUT WITH THAT.
SO WINSTON NOTICED
THE BREAKER HAD TRIPPED,
SO HE JUST --
UH, NOT THE BEST IDEA.
BUT HE DID GET
THE VAN THERE,
AND WE HOOKED THAT UP
TO THE END OF THE CABLE.
AND THE IDEA IS WE WERE
JUST GONNA PULL HER
RIGHT OUT OF THE GROUND THAT
WAY, USING THE POSSUM VAN.
SO, UH, I WENT AND GOT IN THE
VAN THERE, AND JUST --
I DON'T LIKE TO
LOOK BACK IN LIFE.
THAT WAS UNFORTUNATE.
SO THEN I THOUGHT,
IF I BACK UP AND TAKE
A RUN AT IT,
AS I DO WITH MOST
THINGS IN MY LIFE,
I THOUGHT PERHAPS THAT
WOULD WORK A LITTLE BETTER.
BUT WHAT HAPPENED THERE
WAS ALL I WAS DOING THERE
WAS ACTUALLY PULLING ON THE
CABLE INSTEAD OF --
AND IT WAS PULLING THE HYDRO
POLE DOWN INTO THE GROUND
AND THEN UP THROUGH HOLE THAT
THE CABLE COME UP THROUGH.
AND OF COURSE THE GUYS WERE
NOTICING AND TRYING
TO STOP ME
BEFORE WE GOT INTO
ANY REAL KIND OF TROUBLE.
NOW, I SAY YOU CAN ALWAYS
FIND A POSITIVE SIDE
TO EVERYTHING.
I'M THINKING,
WAIT A SECOND.
WE DON'T NEED
TO PUT UP A SIGNPOST.
WE'VE ALREADY GOT THE POST.
JUST TAKE THE SIGN
OFF THAT ONE,
STICK HER ON THE HYDRO POLE,
AND IT REALLY SERVES
THE PURPOSE WHICH IS...
"CALL BEFORE YOU DIG."
[quirky upbeat music]
WE'VE ALL SEEN THESE
MOTION DETECTOR UNITS
THAT TURN THE LIGHTS
ON WHEN YOU COME HOME
AFTER DARK SO YOU CAN SEE
WHERE YOUR KID LEFT HIS BIKE.
THE PROBLEM IS THEY DO THE
SAME THING FOR BURGLARS.
THEY TURN THE LIGHTS ON
WHEN THEY'RE SNEAKING
AROUND AFTER DARK.
SO THEY GET TO SEE WHERE
YOUR KID LEFT HIS BIKE.
THEN OF COURSE,
SOME PEOPLE OVERREACT
BY GETTING BEAR
TRAPS OR LAND MINES
OR SOME KIND OF
HOMEMADE NUCLEAR DEVICE.
I GUESS THE SENSIBLE THING
WOULD BE TO GET A GUARD DOG.
BUT THEN YOU GOTTA FEED IT
AND TAKE CARE OF IT
AND MAKE SURE IT
KNOWS WHO YOU ARE.
WELL, I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
I GOT ONE OF THESE
HIGH-PITCHED WHISTLES
THAT CAN ONLY BE HEARD BY
DOGS AND UNMARRIED LIBRARIANS,
AND I ATTACHED IT
TO AN AIR COMPRESSOR.
NOW, INSTEAD OF JUST
THE LIGHT COMING ON, SEE,
EVERY TIME A
BURGLAR GOES BY,
THIS IS GONNA KICK
ON THE COMPRESSOR,
WHICH WILL WAKE UP EVERY DOG
IN THE TRI-COUNTY AREA.
HUH? SEE?
YOU DON'T NEED MONEY,
AS LONG AS YOU HAVE --
[dogs barking]
WHEN THE GRASS IN THE BACK'S
GROWING HIGHER AND HIGHER;
WHEN THE SMOKE ALARM'S
SCREAMING,
BUT THERE'S NOTHING ON FIRE;
SEND ME AN E-MAIL,
A CARD OR A WIRE.
I'M QUICK
AND I'M DIRTY,
BUT I'M ALWAYS FOR HIRE.
WELL, I DIDN'T HAVE MUCH
LUCK FIXING HAROLD'S TAPE
FOR THE VIDEO TAPE
DATING SER --
I THINK HE SHOULD
JUST SUBMIT IT LIKE THAT.
IT PRETTY MUCH REPRESENTS
HIS PERSONALITY.
HELLO, UNCLE RED.
I HOPE THOSE FLOWERS
AREN'T FOR ME, HAROLD.
NO, THEY'RE
FOR MY DATE.
I WENT WITH A COMPUTER
DATING SERVICE INSTEAD.
YEAH, IT'S CALLED
LOVE IS BLIND.
YEAH. YEAH.
SO YOU JUST GIVE A
SHORT BIO OF YOURSELF,
AND THEN THEY MATCH YOU UP
WITH SOMEONE WITH SIMILAR
INTERESTS.
I THINK IT'S
WAY BETTER.
VIDEO DOESN'T
FLATTER ME.
NO, LIFE DOESN'T
FLATTER YOU, HAROLD.
SO SHOULDN'T YOU
BE LEAVING?
NO, NO, NO.
THEY'RE SENDING MY
DATE HERE TO THE LODGE.
GET THIS DESCRIPTION.
LISTEN TO THIS.
"ATTRACTIVE,
"SELF-EMPLOYED,
AMBITIOUS, CREATIVE..."
[knock at door]
EARLY.
OH! OH! OH! OH!
TAKE IT EASY.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
DON'T FREAK OUT,
HAROLD, OKAY?
FREAK OUT, HAROLD.
[cheers and applause]
WINSTON?
HAROLD?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THAT COMPUTER WAS SUPPOSED
TO SET ME UP WITH MY
PERFECT MATCH.
[together]
"MY IDEAL DATE...
"NICE DINNER,
"A GOOD MOVIE,
"AND A LITTLE STIMULATING
CONVERSATION."
WELL, YOU GUYS
BETTER GET GOING,
IF YOU'RE HOPING TO
CATCH THE EARLY MOVIE.
YOU ARE SO
BUYING THE POPCORN.
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
YEAH, THANKS,
HAROLD.
YOU GO
HAVE FUN, EH?
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND HAROLD IS RIGHT.
LOVE IS BLIND.
BY THE TIME HE
GETS FINISHED WITH IT,
IT WILL HAVE LOST
ALL ITS FACULTIES.
SPEAKING OF WHICH I DON'T
THINK I'VE EVER FELT
SO WIDE AWAKE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheers and applause]
SIT DOWN, EVERYBODY.
SIT DOWN, EVERYONE.
HAVE A SEAT THERE.
THAT'S THE WAY.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
THAT WAS KIND OF
A SHORT DATE.
YEAH, WINSTON HAD TO LEAVE
FOR AN EMERGENCY CALL.
SO HE LEFT YOU FOR
A YOUNGER LOAD.