YOU MAY NOT REALIZE IT, BUT IF
YOU HAVE INDOOR PLUMBING,
YOU'VE GOT ONE OF
THESE BREATHER PIPES
SOMEWHERE ON YOUR ROOF.
IT LETS THE AIR
INTO THE SYSTEM,
WHICH ALLOWS THE WASTE
WATER TO ESCAPE DOWN
THE DRAIN,
BUT IT ALSO ALLOWS THE SEWER
GASES TO ESCAPE UP INTO
THE ATMOSPHERE,
WHICH POLLUTES OUR AIR,
KILLS THE SURROUNDING TREES
AND DISORIENTS
PASSING BIRDS.
THE SOLUTION IS PRETTY SIMPLE
BECAUSE FORTUNATELY
THESE GASES ARE FLAMMABLE.
SO ALL IT TAKES IS A
FLICK OF YOUR BIC
TO TURN AN
ENVIRONMENTAL HAZARD
INTO AN OLYMPIC TORCH.
BLAZING FORTH IN THE NIGHT
TO REMIND US OF WHAT
HAS GONE BEFORE.
AND WHAT BETTER TRIBUTE TO THE
CONTINUUM OF THE HUMAN SPIRIT
THAN AN ELEVATED STACK OF
FLAMING METHANE?
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
KIND OF AN ODD SITUATION UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
THERE'S A GREAT BIG CHICKEN
ON THE LOOSE UP HERE.
IT STANDS ABOUT FOUR FEET TALL
AND, MAN, VERY, VERY VICIOUS.
I'LL TELL YOU, IF COLONEL
SAUNDERS HAD TANGOED
WITH THIS BABY,
HE'D BE THE ONE WHO ENDED UP
FINGER LICKIN' GOOD.
RED, I'VE GOT SOMEONE REAL
SPECIAL OUTSIDE I WANT TO
INTRODUCE YOU TO.
NO, COME ON, I'VE MET
ANNE MARIE 100 TIMES.
NOT ANNE MARIE.
SHE WOULDN'T COME
DOWN TO THE LODGE.
I'M TALKING
ABOUT MY EMU.
IS THAT WHAT THE
BIG CHICKEN IS?
IT'S YOURS?
IT'S AN EMU, RED,
AND IT AIN'T NO CHICKEN.
OKAY, WE'LL BE
RIGHT THERE.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE
NEAR THAT THING.
NOW, WHAT DID YOU
GET AN EMU FOR ANYWAY?
BECAUSE I'M GETTING
INTO THE EMU BUSINESS.
OKAY, RIGHT NOW
I'VE JUST GOT ONE.
BUT I'M GOING TO
MATE HER RIGHT AWAY.
YOU KNOW, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO GET ANOTHER EMU TO
DO THAT FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW, RED, I WAS
KINDA HOPING WE COULD WORK
TOGETHER ON THIS, YOU KNOW.
IF YOU GOT A MALE,
THEN WE COULD BE PARTNERS,
AND WE COULD SPLIT THE
CHICKS AND SPLIT THE MONEY.
YOU'D BE MAKING MONEY
WITHIN THREE MONTHS.
YEAH, OH, YEAH.
APPARENTLY THEY
MATE VERY QUICKLY.
I NEVER REALIZED THAT
WAS A GOOD THING, DALTON.
I TELL YOU WHAT.
I'LL TRY IT ONCE,
BUT IF IT DOESN'T WORK OUT
I'M SELLING MY EMU TO THE
CIRCUS OR SOMETHING.
OH, GEEZ, I THINK
SHE HEARD YOU THERE.
OKAY! I'LL BE RIGHT --
I GOTTA GO, RED --
OH, LISTEN, I'VE GOT TO
COME UP WITH A NAME FOR HER.
YOU GOT ANY
SUGGESTIONS?
SHE LOOKS A BIT LIKE
AN ANNE MARIE TO ME.
Dalton: OH! OW! OW! OW!
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER WILL RECEIVE
THIS GIFT CERTIFICATE
TO BIG AL'S
PODIATRY CLINIC.
THIS WEEK, GET ONE BUNYAN
REMOVED AT THE REGULAR PRICE,
AND GET THE
SECOND ONE HALF OFF.
OKAY, EDGAR, YOU GOT TO
COVER YOUR EARS, OKAY?
OH, I'LL HAVE A
TALL ONE WITH ICE.
OKAY, Mr GREEN,
YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET EDGAR
TO SAY THIS WORD...
ALRIGHT, MIKE.
AND GO!
EDGAR, WHAT DO YOU CALL THE
THING THAT CATCHES ON FIRE
JUST BEFORE THE
DYNAMITE EXPLODES?
MY TRUCK.
OKAY, YOU CAN ALWAYS TELL WHEN
SOMEBODY HAS A QUICK TEMPER
BECAUSE THEY
HAVE A VERY SHORT...
BROTHER?
NO, EDGAR.
OKAY. CANDLES HAVE WICKS, BUT
WITH DYNAMITE IT'S DIFFERENT.
OH, YEAH.
WITH DYNAMITE
YOU DON'T HAVE TO CUT
THE BIRTHDAY CAKE AFTER.
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT
OF TIME, Mr GREEN.
YEAH, OKAY, MIKE.
EDGAR, IF I WAS GOING TO
LIGHT A STICK OF DYNAMITE,
WHAT WOULD I
BE LOOKING FOR?
YOUR RUNNING SHOES.
OKAY, LET'S TRY A
SCIENTIFIC THING.
IF YOU FORCIBLY JOIN
TWO THINGS TOGETHER
THAT'S CALLED...
A SHOTGUN WEDDING.
WELL, IT'S KIND OF LIKE
AN OFFER YOU CAN'T REFUSE.
THERE WE GO.
[ RINGING BELL ]
I'M ON MY WAY.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WALK OUT
OF THEIR HOUSES EACH
AND EVERY MORNING
WITH NO REAL DIRECTION.
THEY GET UP, GET READY
AND GO TO WORK
WITHOUT EVER
REALLY KNOWING WHY.
IT'S JUST SOMETHING THEY
THINK THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO DO.
SO LIKE SHEEP THEY DO IT
WITHOUT QUESTIONING
THE REASONS.
IT'S AN AIMLESS
PURSUIT OF NOTHING.
A ROBOTIC EXISTENCE THAT DOES
LITTLE MORE THAN PUT FOOD
ON THE TABLE.
THAT'S WHERE I'M DIFFERENT.
EVERY MORNING
I WAKE UP WITH PURPOSE.
I KNOW WHERE I'M GOING
AND HOW TO GET THERE,
AND I KNOW, AS AN INDIVIDUAL,
I CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
WHEN YOU CALL ME, YOU KNOW
YOU'RE GETTING A MAN WHO
KNOWS HIS BUSINESS
AS WELL AS HE KNOWS YOURS.
QUALITY WORKMANSHIP.
IT'S WHAT I DO.
ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
WHEN DUTY CALLS.
[ TOILET FLUSHING ]
WELL, WINTER'S COMING.
THE DAYS ARE GETTING COLDER;
THE NIGHTS ARE GETTING LONGER.
YOU GOT TO GET ONE
OF THESE UNITS OUT
BECAUSE YOU GOT A WHOLE SEASON
OF SCRAPING SNOW AND
ICE OFF YOUR CAR,
AND YOU THINK TO YOURSELF,
IS THIS THE WAY
RICH PEOPLE LIVE?
WELL, NO, SIR,
THEY DON'T.
THEY HAVE ONE OF THOSE FANCY
REMOTE CAR STARTER UNITS
WHERE THEY CAN START THE CAR
FROM INSIDE THE HOUSE,
AND THEY DON'T EVEN GO NEAR
UNTIL SHE'S ALL WARMED UP
AND ALL THE ICE AND SNOW IS
MELTED RIGHT OFF HER.
WHY CAN'T YOU HAVE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT, HUH?
YOU HAVE TO BE RICH
OR KNOW SOMEBODY?
NO, YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE RICH,
AND YOU DO KNOW SOMEBODY.
ME!
ALL YOU NEED IS AN
ELECTRIC DRILL, A TIRE IRON
AND A BROOM.
I CAN SHOW YOU
HOW IT ALL WORKS,
BUT I'M SURE YOU'VE
ALREADY FIGURED IT OUT.
ALL RIGHT, I'VE GOT ONE
END OF THE TIRE IRON
TIGHTENED INTO
THE CHUCK OF MY DRILL,
AND THEN I GOT THE WHOLE
UNIT DUCT TAPED INTO THE
IGNITION KEY HERE.
AND THEN WHAT I DO IS DUCT
TAPE THE BROOM ON TO THE
TIRE IRON ITSELF.
GOT THE BUTT END OF THE HANDLE
RESTING ON THE GAS PEDAL
SO I CAN START THE CAR
FROM INSIDE MY HOME
WITH THE BUTT END OF MYSELF
RESTING ON THE RECLINER.
[ IGNITION DOESN'T START ]
OKAY, RAN INTO A BIT
OF A SNAG HERE.
THE CHOKE STICKS
ON THIS CAR.
I NEED SOME WAY OF OPENING
UP THIS BUTTERFLY VALVE
ON THE CARBURATOR,
OR THIS UNIT
WILL NEVER START.
NOW, I HOPE YOU YOUNG PEOPLE
ARE NOTICING OUT THERE
THAT I'M NOT GOING TO QUIT
ON SOMETHING JUST BECAUSE
IT GOT DIFFICULT.
YOU'LL LEARN THAT
AS YOU GET OLDER,
THAT AS SOON AS YOU QUIT
ON WHAT YOU SET OUT
TO ACCOMPLISH,
YOUR WIFE WILL COME UP WITH
100 OTHER WAYS TO WRECK
YOUR WEEKEND.
SO INSTEAD, I'M RUNNING THIS
LITTLE CHAIN DOWN FROM THE
INSIDE OF THE HOOD.
GONNA HOOK THAT ON TO THE
BUTTERFLY VALVE,
AND THAT WAY AS SOON
AS THE HOOD OPENS THAT
WILL UNSTICK MY CHOKE.
HOW AM I GONNA
OPEN THE HOOD?
CAN YOU SAY
GARAGE DOOR OPENER?
SEE WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU DOUBT A PERSON?
ALL RIGHT, STEP ONE,
YOU WANT TO PUMP THE
GAS A COUPLE OF TIMES.
STEP TWO, UNSTICK THE CHOKE.
AND STEP THREE, THE EASIEST
ONE OF ALL, START THE CAR.
YOU KNOW, GUYS DON'T LIKE TO
ASK ANYBODY FOR HELP.
WOMEN THINK IT'S BECAUSE IT
MAKES US LOOK WEAK.
BUT THAT'S NOT IT.
OH, NO, GUYS HATE ASKING
FRIENDS FOR HELP ON A PROJECT
BECAUSE IT MEANS SELLING
YOURSELF INTO SLAVERY.
IT'S CALLED, PAYBACK WORK.
IF I ASK A FRIEND TO DO
SOMETHING SMART,
LIKE BUILD A WINTERIZED
GARAGE FOR MY SNOWMOBILE,
THEN I HAVE TO GO HELP
HIM DO SOMETHING STUPID,
LIKE GO POUR A CEMENT PAD
FOR HIS ROCKET LAUNCHER.
NOW, WHY WOULD
I WANT TO DO THAT?
IF I'VE ALREADY
FINISHED MY PROJECT,
I DON'T WANT TO
DO ANY MORE WORK?
BUT THAT PAYBACK WORK THING
IS NAGGING AWAY AT THE
BACK OF YOUR MIND.
IT'S LIKE THE RELATIVE
STAYING IN THE GUEST ROOM.
NO MATTER WHAT YOU SAY,
OR WHAT YOU DO,
IT WILL NOT LEAVE.
SO YOU WANT MY ADVICE?
IF YOU GOT SOMETHING AT YOUR
HOUSE THAT NEEDS FIXING,
HIRE A PROFESSIONAL.
IF IT'S NOT BAD ENOUGH
TO NEED A PROFESSIONAL,
FIX IT YOURSELF
AND IT WILL BE.
BUT BELIEVE ME, YOU'RE BETTER
OFF PAYING IN CASH ONCE,
THEN PAYING IN PAYBACK WORK
THE REST OF THE YOUR LIFE.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, IT'S BEEN THREE WEEKS
SINCE DALTON AND I
GOT OUR EMUS.
I DON'T KNOW IF THEY'VE
MATED YET OR NOT,
BUT JUDGING BY THE WAY THEY'RE
FIGHTING WITH EACH OTHER
ALL THE TIME,
I WOULD SAY YES.
Dalton: OKAY, OKAY. BACK OFF.
BACK OFF! NO! OW! BACK OFF!
GO ON! BACK! BACK! BACK!
Red: YEAH, YEAH, LITTLE
HENPECKED ARE YOU, DALTON?
NO, NO. I'M FINE.
HEY, RED!
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
WHAT DOES THAT
LOOK LIKE TO YOU?
THE BIG BOY BREAKFAST.
IT'S NOT A MEAL, RED.
IT'S A MEAL TICKET.
YEAH?
MONEY FROM THIS.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE SOME REAL
HOW MANY EMUS DO
YOU FIGURE ARE IN THERE?
YOU KNOW I WAS GOING TO
TALK TO YOU ABOUT THAT,
BECAUSE I THINK WE
GOT TO BE A LITTLE MORE
AGGRESSIVE IN OUR APPROACH.
I THINK WE HAVE TO
GET OURSELVES SOME
MORE EMUS.
MORE EMUS?
YOU KNOW, ONLY A MARRIED
PERSON WOULD HAVE
AN APPETITE
FOR THAT MUCH
ABUSE, DALTON.
NO PAIN,
NO GAIN, RED.
WELL, AN EMU'S ONLY FUNNY
UNTIL SOMEONE LOSES AN EYE.
THAT'S THE WAY
I FEEL ABOUT IT.
ANYWAY, WHO'S GONNA
PAY FOR MORE EMUS?
I GOT THAT COVERED, OKAY?
THERE ARE A BUNCH OF
EMUS IN PORT ASBESTOS,
AND THE OWNERS HAVE OFFERED TO
GIVE US THOSE EMUS FOR A SHARE
OF THE UPSIDE, HUH?
SO IT'S GONNA
COST US NOTHING.
THAT SOUNDS HIGH TO ME.
RED, I'M NOT ASKING
YOU FOR MORE MONEY.
I'M GONNA DO THE WORK.
NOW, COME ON,
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
OH, ALL RIGHT, GO AHEAD.
I DON'T WANT TO SPOIL
YOUR FUN, DALTON.
OKAY!
YOU WON'T REGRET IT.
IT'S A GREAT
OPPORTUNITY.
I THINK I HEAR
OPPORTUNITY KNOCKING
THERE ON THE WINDOW.
Red: LOOK OUT! LOOK OUT!
GET BACK! GET BACK! BACK!
GO ON, BACK!
WHEN YOU GET THE NEWS THAT
YOUR SEPTICS HAVE THE OOZE,
AND IT'S GIVING YOU THE BLUES
AND GETTING ON YOUR SHOES.
CALL ME, WINSTON,
AND I'LL PUT HER
BACK IN CRUISE.
HI, FOLKS.
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN WORKING IN
FILM FOR QUITE SOME TIME NOW,
AND I FUNCTION
COMPLETELY ON MY OWN,
WITHOUT ANY OUTSIDE
INFLUENCE WHATSOEVER.
OH, SURE,
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE
I'LL PICK UP AND READ MY
PSYCHOLOGICAL EVALUATION THE
HEADQUARTERS DID ON ME,
BUT IT'S COMPLETE GARBAGE.
IT'S ENTITLED,
"SOCIOPATH OF THE FOREST."
IT'S NONSENSE.
I'VE BEEN ON EVERY TRAIL
AND PATH IN THIS WOODS,
AND THERE'S NO SUCH THING.
YOU KNOW, WORKING AS I DO,
ALONE, WITH ONLY LIMITED
RESOURCES,
MY FILMS ARE, BY NECESSITY,
AVANT-GARDE,
AND AS SUCH, I'VE NEVER BEEN
REVIEWED BY ANY MAINSTREAM
FILM CRITIC.
IF THEY DID, I CAN JUST
IMAGINE WHAT THEY'D SAY...
"YES, BEARS DO GO IN
THE WOODS, AND THIS IS
WHAT THEY LEAVE."
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE THEY
DON'T UNDERSTAND THE
SUBTLETIES
THAT ARE SO MUCH
A PART OF THIS MEDIUM.
AND THAT'S WHY I'D RATHER
JUST LET YOU SEE THEM.
AND IF YOU DON'T LIKE THEM,
WELL, FINE,
THAT'S THE END OF IT.
BUT IF YOU LIKE THEM,
WELL, HECK,
WHY DON'T YOU COME UP HERE
AND STAY FOR A YEAR OR TWO,
AND WE COULD WATCH THEM OVER
AND OVER AND OVER
AND OVER AND OVER AND.....
OH, THAT'D BE GREAT.
ANYWAY, HERE'S THIS
WEEK'S FILM.
I HOPE YOU LOVE IT.
FOLKS, I HOPE EVERYONE
OUT THERE REALIZES
THAT THE BEST WAY
TO PREVENT FOREST FIRES
IS TO PREVENT THEM FROM
HAPPENING IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THAT'S HOW I PLAN
TO SAVE THIS FOREST.
THIS FOREST IS ALREADY
BURNT TO THE GROUND,
RANGER GORD.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN'T SAVE IT NOW.
NOT UNLESS YOU'VE GOT A TIME
MACHINE OR SOMETHING.
WELL, YOU'VE
CONVINCED ME, RED.
IN THE FUTURE, I'M WORKING ON
A TIME MACHINE AND WILL
BRING IT BACK HERE
TO THE PRESENT.
HELLO, EVERYONE.
I'M FUTURE GORD.
I FINISHED THE TIME MACHINE,
SO LET'S TAKE A
TRIP INTO THE PAST
AND PREVENT THIS DISASTER
FROM EVER HAPPENING.
FWAAAH,
TWO RANGER GORDS.
OH, JUST WHAT
THE WORLD NEEDS.
WELL, COME ON YOU TWO.
DO YOU WANT TO
MAKE HISTORY OR NOT?
WHAT'S THIS?
IT LOOKS LIKE SOME KIND OF
MACHINE FROM THE FUTURE.
HELLO, RANGER GORD
OF THE PAST.
I'M GORD OF THE PRESENT,
AND THIS IS GORD
OF THE FUTURE.
WE'VE COME BACK IN TIME
TO PREVENT THIS MAGNIFICENT
FOREST FROM BURNING TO
THE GROUND.
I SEE.
WELL, I HOPE
I CAN BE OF ASSISTANCE.
ACCORDING TO
MY CALCULATIONS,
THIS FOREST WILL BE
IGNITED BY A BOLT
OF LIGHTNING
THAT WILL STRIKE SOMEWHERE IN
THIS VICINITY VERY SHORTLY.
I DOUBT IT,
FUTURE GORD.
THERE ISN'T A
CLOUD IN THE SKY.
AH, HA.
THERE'S THE TROUBLE SPOT.
WE'VE DONE IT.
WE'VE SAVED THE TREES.
LET'S ALL TRAVEL INTO
THE FUTURE AND CELEBRATE.
WAIT.
WHAT ABOUT THOSE TWO?
HM, WELL, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THEM.
THEY NEVER HAD
MUCH OF A FUTURE ANYWAY.
( laughing )
THIS IS A BRAINWAVE
I HAD LAST FALL,
BUT I HAD TO WAIT 'TIL
NOW TO SHOW IT TO YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT A PAIN IT IS
TO GET RID OF THE LEAVES
IN THE AUTUMN?
WELL, WHAT I DID IS I JUST
RAKE THEM UP INTO A BIG
PILE LIKE THIS,
SPRAY THEM WITH WATER
'TIL THEY FROZE SOLID.
OH, THAT'S THE BARBECUE.
HERE. HERE'S THE LEAVES.
THIS IS THE
LEAF PILE RIGHT HERE.
MAYBE A BIGGER PILE
THAN I THOUGHT.
THESE ARE THE
LEAVES FOR SURE.
( dog barking )
NO, HERE WE ARE.
THESE ARE THE LEAVES.
YEAH, THIS IS THEM.
OH, YEAH, 'CAUSE I LEFT THE
CHAIN SAW HERE TO REMIND ME.
'CAUSE WHAT I DO NOW,
I TAKE THE FROZEN LEAVES,
CUT THEM INTO A LOG
SHAPE AND SIZE
AND I CAN BURN THEM
IN THE FIREPLACE.
OKAY, THAT'S THE
MANURE PILE.
YOU KNOW, THESE UP CLOSE
AND PERSONAL DEALS
ARE VERY POPULAR WITH THE
TELEVISION AUDIENCE
AND, OF COURSE, WE'RE
ALWAYS LOOKING FOR FILLER.
SO, RIGHT NOW, WE'RE GOING
TO FIND A LITTLE BIT MORE
ABOUT THE MAN WE'VE COME
TO KNOW AS MIKE HAMAR.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MAKE
ME CRY, YOU KNOW THAT.
NO. NO.
I'M FINE WITH THAT.
MIKE, YOU'VE HAD
A COLOURFUL LIFE.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL US
ABOUT THE EARLY YEARS
OF YOUR CHILDHOOD?
OKAY, WELL, WE HAD A
PRETTY NORMAL FAMILY.
MOM WAS AN EXOTIC
DANCER AND,
UH, I HAD SOMEWHERE BETWEEN
THREE AND SEVEN DADS,
DEPENDING UPON HOW MUCH BAIL
MONEY WE COULD COME UP WITH.
AND WHICH ONE OF THOSE GUYS
WAS YOUR BIOLOGICAL FATHER?
WELL, MOM WAS NEVER
SURE ABOUT THAT.
SEE, SHE'S A
HEAVY SLEEPER.
NOW, WAS THERE
JUST YOU, MIKE,
OR DID YOU HAVE
BROTHERS AND SISTERS?
OH, SURE.
THERE WERE SEVEN OF US,
ALL UNDER SEVEN.
I WAS THE YOUNGEST.
MOM USED TO BLAME ME FOR
LOSING HER JOB
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, LIKE,
WHEN SHE WAS CARRYING ME,
SHE GAINED A LOT OF WEIGHT,
AND SHE GOT BIGGER THAN
SOME OF THE TABLES SHE
WAS DANCING ON.
SO -- BUT, ACTUALLY,
IT WAS QUITE A HAPPY
FAMILY ENVIRONMENT.
OH, YEAH, SO WOULD
YOU SAY YOUR HOUSE WAS
FULL OF LOVE, THEN?
IT WAS ON SATURDAY
NIGHTS, YEAH.
NO. NO, I MEAN YOU WEREN'T
LACKING IN ANYTHING, YOU KNOW.
YOU HAD THE NORMAL STUFF,
TOYS AND BIKES AND THAT
KIND OF THING.
OH, SURE, YEAH, I HAD ALL THE
SAME KIND OF TOYS AS THE
NEIGHBOURHOOD KIDS.
IN FACT, I HAD THEIRS.
SEE, MY FAMILY ALWAYS
BELIEVED IN SHARING.
SO IF A STRANGER
HAD SOMETHING,
WE THOUGHT THEY SHOULD
SHARE IT WITH US.
YOU HAD KIND OF A COMMUNAL
ATTITUDE TOWARD POSSESSIONS?
YEAH, SEE, WE WEREN'T HUNG UP
ABOUT POSSESSIONS, RIGHT.
BUT, OH, BOY,
THOSE COPS SURE WERE.
OH, MAN.
THAT'S ALL THEY'D EVER
TALK ABOUT, RIGHT,
POSSESSION, TRAFFICKING.
OH, I SEE. ALL RIGHT.
I SEE WHERE WE'RE
GOING WITH THIS.
WELL, MIKE, YOU KNOW,
I'D LIKE TO TALK TO YOU MORE,
BUT SO MUCH OF THIS IS
STILL BEFORE THE COURTS,
AND WE'RE RUNNING A
LITTLE SHORT OF TIME,
SO MAYBE WHAT YOU COULD DO,
IN THE LAST FEW SECONDS,
IS SUM UP, YOU KNOW,
LOOK RIGHT OUT THERE
INTO THE AUDIENCE
AND, UH, GIVE THE
YOUNGSTERS OUT THERE
A LITTLE BIT OF ADVICE
ON LIFE, IF YOU WOULD.
OKAY, OKAY.
LIFE, YEAH, SURE.
OKAY.
IT'S NOT THAT BAD, YOU KNOW?
THEY CALL IT LIFE,
BUT REALLY IT'S ONLY 25 YEARS.
HI, I'M WINSTON.
LOVE MEANS NEVER HAVING
TO SEE YOUR SEWAGE.
CALL ROTHSCHILD'S.
OH, THIS IS
GOING WELL.
AND THANK YOU, DALTON,
FOR AN EXCITING BUSINESS
OPPORTUNITY.
WELL, I DIDN'T KNOW EMUS
WOULD BE THIS HOSTILE.
WELL, LOOK AT THEM,
FOR GOSH SAKE.
THE LONG NECK,
THE BEADY EYES,
IT LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE CROSSED
A BUDGIE WITH A GIRAFFE.
CAN'T EVEN FLY.
OH, NO,
THAT'S A GOOD THING.
YOU DON'T WANT ANY ANIMAL
OVER 150 POUNDS TO
BE AIRBORNE.
RED, I-I'M AFRAID TO
GO OUT THERE AGAIN.
I MEAN, WHAT ARE
WE GOING TO DO?
WE'RE GOING TO GET RID OF
THEM, THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO DO.
WE'RE GOING
TO GIVE THEM AWAY.
TO WHO?
WHO'S GONNA TAKE THEM?
SOMEBODY WHO WOULD TAKE
ANYTHING YOU GIVE
THEM, DALTON.
SOMEBODY WHO'S MORE
PATHETIC THAN YOU AND I.
HELLO, RANGER GORD.
YEAH.
NO, I'M GOOD.
LISTEN, UH, HOW WOULD YOU
LIKE TO HAVE EIGHT CHICKS
UP AT THE FIRE TOWER?
OH, YEAH, THEY GOT LONG LEGS
AND THEY GOT THE BIG EYES.
I TELL YEAH, GORD,
THEY'RE PRETTY WILD.
ALL RIGHT,
HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
BLAST OFF ONE SHOT ON YOUR
FOREST FIRE SIREN.
JUST DO THAT FOR ME, GORD,
WOULD YOU?
[ SIREN SCREAMING ]
OKAY, IT'S WORKING.
ANOTHER ONE.
A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
[ SIREN SCREAMING ]
( possum squealing )
OH, MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD, DALTON.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
MAN, OH, MAN.
OKAY, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I WAS ALL BACKWARDS ON
THIS EMU THING, YOU KNOW.
IF YOU TAKE A LOOK
AT THE WORD "EMU,"
IF YOU SHOOK IT AROUND
YOU GET "U-ME."
THAT'S WHERE I SHOULD
HAVE BEEN SPENDING MY
TIME AND MONEY.
NOW, WAS THAT SAPPY ENOUGH,
OR DO I STILL HAVE TO
BUY FLOWERS?
AND TO REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND THE
WHOLE GANG UP HERE AT
POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN, GUYS. SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN PLEASE.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
BOW YOUR HEADS FOR
THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
KEEP YOUR HEADS BOWED, MEN.
I'D LIKE TO HAVE A COUPLE OF
MINUTES OF SILENT PRAYER
FOR RANGER GORD.