♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN
IN TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD'S
GOING TO DIRECT,
BILL'S GOING TO DO
SOME TRAPPING,
AND I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO USE A PROPANE
TORCH SAFELY.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: NOW HERE'S A MAN
WHOSE HEART IS BIG AS ALL
OUTDOORS AND HIS OTHER INTERNAL
ORGANS ARE JUST AS ENORMOUS,
THE STAR OF OUR SHOW
MR. RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
CERTAINLY HOPE YOU WEREN'T
EATING DINNER DURING THAT INTRO.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED
THAT'S SHOCK TELEVISION
THAT GRABS THE
AUDIENCE'S ATTENTION,
YOU SEE THAT'S
WHAT THIS SHOW NEEDS IS PACE,
ACTION, AND MOVEMENT,
VISUAL DYNAMICS, PAN IN,
PAN OUT, DOLLY TRUCKING,
TRUCKING WOO HOO HOO!
>>RED: HAROLD!
SPEAKING OF ACTION AND TRUCKING
MOOSE THOMPSON DECIDED TO
WASH HIS TRUCK THIS WEEK
AND HE LIKES TO USE
POSSUM LAKE WATER 'CAUSE WE
GOT SO MUCH SOAP RESIDUE IN
THERE IT MAKES IT'S OWN SUDS.
>>HAROLD: SOMETIMES YOU KNOW IT
EVEN LEAVES A NICE LAYER
OF WAX ON YOUR FENDERS
YOU CAN OIL YOUR DOOR HINGES
TOO IT'S REALLY GOOD.
>>RED: YEAH IF IT WOULD WRAP
THINGS IN A LAYER OF DUCT TAPE
I'D THROW YOU IN THERE HAROLD.
SO ANYWAY MOOSE PUT HIS TRUCK
RIGHT DOWN ON THE DOCK WHICH
I THOUGHT WAS A LITTLE FOOLISH
BECAUSE THAT DOCK'S NOT
VERY LEVEL.
>>HAROLD: I'VE SEEN
FLATTER ROLLER COASTERS.
>>RED: YEAH WELL MOOSE THOUGHT
ABOUT IT SO HE GOT SOME LOGS
TO PUT YOU KNOW IN FRONT OF
THE WHEELS SO SHE WOULDN'T ROLL
UNFORTUNATELY HE TOOK THE LOGS
OUT OF THE DOCK CRIBBING
SO THE WHOLE THING KIND
OF COLLAPSED ON HIM.
WELL YOU KNOW LIFE'S
LIKE THAT ISN'T IT?
>>HAROLD: WELL YOURS IS.
SO WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO NOW?
WE HAVE TO HAVE A DOCK.
>>RED: WELL WE'RE GOING TO
BUILD A NEW DOCK HAROLD
WE'VE ALREADY GOT A BRAND NEW
CRIB FOUNDATION FORMERLY KNOWN
AS MOOSE'S TRUCK AND I WOULD SAY
BY SUNDOWN TONIGHT THE GUYS
ARE GOING TO GO OUT AND SCAVENGE
LUMBER AND WE'LL HAVE ENOUGH
FOR A BRAND NEW WOODEN DOCK.
>>HAROLD: AND EVERYONE ELSE WHO
LIVES AROUND THE LAKE IS GOING
TO BE MISSING WOOD FROM
THEIR DOCK.
>>RED: WELL THAT'S JUST PART
OF THE PRICE OF HAVING
A COTTAGE UP HERE.
♪ WHEN THE NIGHT GETS LONELY ♪
♪ AND THE ROAD SEEMS LONG ♪
♪ IT IS GOOD FOR YOUR SOUL ♪
♪ TO JUST BURST OUT IN SONG ♪
♪ AND THE LOUSIER THE SINGER ♪
♪ THE LOUDER THE SONG ♪
♪ 'CAUSE IF YOU SING ♪
♪ LOUD ENOUGH MAYBE ♪
♪ THE AUDIENCE WILL THINK ♪
♪ IT'S THE BAND THAT'S WRONG ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE GOING
TO SHOW YOU WHAT YOU CAN DO
WITH ALL THAT COPPER PIPE
AND STUFF YOU GOT LEANING
UP AGAINST THE HOUSE SINCE
THAT TIME THE BATHROOM BLEW UP
WHEN WE SHOWED YOU HOW TO
CLEAN CERAMIC TILES WITH
NITRO GLYCERINE.
NOW WITH MOST OF THE PROJECTS
UP HERE AT THE LODGE THE KEY
IS NEVER THROW ANYTHING OUT
WHICH IS ALSO A PHILOSOPHY
THAT SAVES A LOT OF MARRIAGES.
IF YOU DON'T HAPPEN TO HAVE
ANY COPPER PIPE AT YOUR PLACE
SURELY THERE MUST BE
A CONSTRUCTION SITE NEARBY
AND REMEMBER THE MOON DOESN'T
SHINE EVERY NIGHT.
TALK IS CHEAP, LET'S BUILD!
STEP ONE IS YOU GOT TO TAKE
ALL THE PIPES APART AND GET
ALL THE FITTINGS OFF THEM
AND SO ON SO YOU GOT TO HEAT
'EM UP TO DO THAT AND I SUGGEST
YOU USE ONE OF THESE HOUSEHOLD
PROPANE UNITS, TURN HER ON FULL
AND GET THE FLAME REALLY GOING
OUT OF THERE BUT I'M GOING TO
USE THE SLOW WAY AND HEAT THIS
ALL UP THE IDEA IS YOU'RE GOING
TO MELT ALL THE SOLDER IN
THERE AND SHE'LL JUST
POP APART ON YOU.
(CRACKLING OF FLAMES)
>>RED: OH BOY, NO, NO,
OKAY NO PROBLEM,
NO PROBLEM.
HAROLD CALL THE FIRE DEPARTMENT!
HOPEFULLY BY THE TIME THEY GET
HERE IT'LL BE WORTH COMING,
ALL RIGHT SO NOW WE JUST
TAKE THE PIPE
(LOUD HISSING)
OH I SHOULD SAY THE RED HOT PIPE
AND WE DROP THAT INTO WATER
BUT WHEN THAT THING HITS
THE WATER THOSE JOINTS
WILL JUST POP RIGHT OPEN
LIKE SUNFISH ON A TENNIS RACKET.
(LOUD HISSING)
OH BOY OKAY MAYBE WE SHOULD
HAVE LET THAT COOL DOWN A TAD
BEFORE WE POPPED IT IN THERE.
(FIRE TRUCK SIRENS WAILING)
ALL RIGHT THIS IS GOING
TO TAKE A LITTLE WHILE
WHY DON'T WE JUST GET ON
WITH THE SHOW AND I'M GOING
TO COME BACK A LITTLE BIT LATER
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW TO
MAKE ALL OF THIS PIPE INTO
A REALLY UNUSUAL CHAIR
AND DON'T WORRY I'LL GET
THESE FITTINGS APART.
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S THAT
PART OF THE SHOW WHERE WE
EXPOSE THE 3 LITTLE WORDS THAT
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT
ON THE EXPERT PORTION OF
THE SHOW IS OF COURSE
MY UNCLE RED AND HIS
GOOD FRIEND, MR. GLEN BRAXTON.
>>HAROLD: ALL RIGHTY HERE
WE GO LETTER NUMBER ONE.
'DEAR EXPERTS I'M A BIT
OVERWEIGHT BUT THEN
WHO ISN'T?'
>>RED: WELL I'M NOT.
>>GLEN: NOT ME, I GOT BIG BONES.
>>HAROLD: THAT'S ALL THAT IS.
YEAH IT GOES ON,
'I'M INTERESTED IN SHEDDING
A FEW POUNDS WHAT WOULD YOU
SAY IS THE FASTEST, EASIEST
WAY TO LOSE WEIGHT?'
GOOD QUESTION.
>>GLEN: OH OKAY, YEAH, YEAH,
ACTUALLY MY 3 OLDEST GIRLS
ARE ALWAYS ON SOME SORT OF DIET
OR SOMETHING AND I DON'T KNOW
WHY THOUGH I MEAN WELL YOU'VE
SEEN THEM THEY'RE NOT REALLY
OVERWEIGHT AT ALL ARE THEY?
>>RED: NO, NO.
>>HAROLD: NO, NO, NO.
>>RED: THEY'RE SLENDER,
THEY'RE SLENDER.
>>HAROLD: SVELTE,
THEY'RE SVELTE YEAH.
>>GLEN: YEAH?
>>HAROLD: YOUR OLDEST DAUGHTER
SHE'S LIKE CHRISTINA APPLEGATE
AND MICHELLE PFEIFFER AND
CINDY CRAWFORD ALL
JUST ROLLED INTO ONE.
>>GLEN: WELL YOU KNOW HAROLD
I COULD INTRODUCE YOU TWO.
>>HAROLD: NO THANKS.
THOUGH I MEAN YOU KNOW,
SHE'S RIGHT OUT OF MY LEAGUE
YOU KNOW SHE'S MUCH BIGGER,
OLDER... THAN
IT'S NOT JUST RIGHT.
>>GLEN: WELL SHE DID SAY
THAT SHE HAD A LITTLE
CRUSH ON YOU.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH?
>>GLEN: YEAH.
>>RED: A CRUSH HAROLD
THINK ABOUT IT.
>>HAROLD: ALL RIGHT MR. BRAXTON
WHAT ABOUT THE DIETS
YOU WERE SAYING?
>>GLEN: OH YEAH RIGHT
WELL MY MOTTO IS
'WATCH WHAT YOU EAT'
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN IS WELL
YOU GOT TO CUT OUT THINGS
YOU GOT TO CUT OUT COOKIES,
YOU GOT TO CUT OUT ICE CREAM,
YOU GOT TO CUT OUT DANISH,
PASTRY, PIES.
PIES YOU KNOW THOSE YOU KNOW
THOSE PUMPKIN PIES YOU KNOW
RIGHT AROUND THANKSGIVING
THEY'RE LOADED UP WITH
WHIPPED CREAM YOU KNOW THEY'RE
JUST NICE ONES THEY'RE JUST
RIGHT THERE AT THE DINNER TABLE
AND THEY GOT A CHERRY IN THEM
YOU KNOW AND CHERRY CRUMBLE PIE
MY OLDEST DAUGHTER LISA MAKES
THIS CHERRY CRUMBLE PIE
I SWEAR IT'S THAT THICK
AND IT'S GOT JUST STUFF FALLIN'
OFF THE TOP AND YOU'RE JUST
LOOKING AT IT AND MAN
IT'S JUST WOO!
>>HAROLD: HOO HOO!
>>GLEN: THAT'S TOUGH.
>>HAROLD: OH BOY
I HOPE THAT ANSWERS
YOUR QUESTION VIEWER.
>>GLEN: I'M HUNGRY.
>>HAROLD: YEAH.
>>RED: IT IS AUTUMN,
HUNTING SEASON IN THE SCRUB
A NERVOUS CREATURE COWERS
EYES WIDE WITH FEAR
TREMBLING, LOST, AFRAID
JUMPING AT EVERY SOUND
BUT MOTHER IS ALWAYS
TWITCHY ON OPENING DAY.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: AND THERE WE GO
NOW SHE'S PROBABLY GOING TO
LEAK A LITTLE BIT YOU KNOW
BUT IT'S A LAWN CHAIR
SO IT JUST BECOMES A
LAWN CHAIR/SPRINKLER
THEN YOU HOOK YOUR GARDEN
HOSE UP THERE TO THE INLET
UP IN THE TOP CORNER AND
OH DON'T FORGET YOUR WATER
SAFETY AND THEN WHAT YOU DO
IS YOU USE THIS VALVE HERE TO
BLEED ALL THE AIR OUT OF HER
AND ONCE SHE'S FULL OF COLD
WATER BY GOLLY YOU'RE GOING
TO BE COOL AS A CUCUMBER
ALL SUMMER LONG.
OR YOU KNOW IF YOU LIVE NEXT
DOOR TO A BREWERY YOU COULD
JUST RUN THE HOSE INTO ONE
OF THEM BIG BEER VATS
OF THEIRS, EIN PROSIT!
THIS IS LIVING!
(HISS OF WATER)
YEAH BEER WILL DO THAT TO YOU.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>BUZZ: OOPS!
>>RED: BUZZ! BUZZ!
>>BUZZ: OH RED MAN
HOW'S IT GOING?
>>RED: OH NOT BAD.
I NEED SOME 6 INCH SPIKES
FOR BUILDING THE NEW DOCK
AND HAROLD HERE HAS RUN
THE POSSUM VAN RIGHT OUT OF GAS
WHICH MEANS I CAN'T GET
ANY TILL I HAVE SOME WHEN
IS SOMEBODY AROUND HERE GOING
TO HAVE THE BRAINS TO PUT
THE GAS STATION AT THE BOTTOM
OF THE HILL?
>>BUZZ: WELL THAT'S NO SWEAT
MAN 'CAUSE I CAN FLY
YOU INTO TOWN.
>>RED: WOULD YOU DO
THAT FOR ME BUZZ?
>>BUZZ: OH RED YOU KNOW ME ALL
I NEED TO FLY IS A GOOD EXCUSE.
>>RED: YEAH AND YOU NEED
A PILOT'S LICENSE TOO RIGHT?
>>BUZZ: NOT IF YOU'VE GOT
A REALLY GOOD EXCUSE LIKE IF
THE COPS PULL US OVER WE'LL JUST
TELL HIM LIKE YOUR WIFE'S GOING
INTO LABOUR OR SOMETHING AND
SHE'S HAVING LIKE TRIPLETS
OR SOMETHING BUT BEFORE WE GO
YOU GOT TO HELP ME INSTALL
MY NEW CONTROL PANEL
OKAY SO HERE HOLD THIS.
>>RED: YEAH ALL RIGHT.
>>BUZZ: I NEED 4 HOLES
HERE YOU SEE.
WHOA MAN!
>>RED: WHOA, WHOA, BUZZ, BUZZ.
>>BUZZ: I NEED ONE
FOR THE COMPASS.
>>RED: OH!
>>BUZZ: I NEED ONE
FOR THE ALTIMETER.
>>RED: OH!
>>BUZZ: AND ONE
FOR THE TACHOMETER.
>>RED: OH!
>>BUZZ: AND THIS
ONE'S FOR THE ASHTRAY.
>>RED: OH!
>>BUZZ: GREAT.
NOW INSTRUMENTS
WE NEED INSTRUMENTS
CAN'T GO FLYING
WITHOUT INSTRUMENTS.
>>RED: NO.
>>BUZZ: LET'S ROCK AND ROLL.
>>RED: OH BUZZ BUZZ SHOULDN'T
THOSE BE HOOKED UP TO SOMETHING?
>>BUZZ: NO YOU SEE YOU ONLY
NEED THESE IN THE PLANE RIGHT
IN CASE THE COPS PULL YOU OVER.
>>RED: OH BUZZ, BUZZ?
>>BUZZ: YEAH?
>>RED: HOW DO COPS PULL
YOU OVER WHEN YOU'RE
FLYING IN A PLANE?
>>BUZZ: WITH GUNS.
>>RED: YOU KNOW WHAT I JUST HAD
AN IDEA INSTEAD OF ME GOING
TO TOWN WHAT ABOUT HAROLD HERE
YOU KNOW CAN GO WITH YOU AND I
CAN STAY AND SUPERVISE THE NEW
CRIBBING FOR THE DOCK YOU KNOW.
>>BUZZ: YEAH OKAY BUT I DON'T
WANT HIM THROWING UP ON MY
WINDSHIELD LIKE HE DID
LAST TIME.
>>RED: WELL JUST FLY LOW
AND IF HE HAS HIS HELMET ON
BACKWARDS I THINK HE'LL BE FINE.
>>BUZZ: OH OKAY ALL RIGHT
LET'S GO, HAROLD?
>>RED: HAROLD, HAROLD?
>>BUZZ: WHERE DID
THE DOOFUS GO?
>>RED: HAROLD?
>>BUZZ: (YELLING) HAROLD!
>>RED: COME ON HAROLD
GO WITH THE NICE MAN.
>>RED: WELL OUR NEW DOCK IS UP
AND WE GOT A WHOLE LOT OF WOOD
LEFT OVER, MIND YOU THERE ISN'T
A TELEPHONE POLE OR A RAILWAY
TIE WITHIN 20 MILES OF THE LODGE
AND STINKY PETERSON WAS GOING
OVER TO THAT CONSTRUCTION SITE
ACROSS THE STREET YOU KNOW
WHILE THE GUYS WERE ON LUNCH
HE WAS GOING TO TRY AND GET SOME
PLANKS YOU KNOW FOR THE TOP OF
THE DOCK I THINK THE FOREMAN
KIND OF KNEW HE WAS COMING
'CAUSE HE PUT UP AN 8 FOOT
FENCE AROUND THE WHOLE YARD
SO NOW THE DOCK IS 8 FEET WIDE
AND WE GOT ENOUGH WOOD LEFT
OVER TO BUILD OURSELVES A PIER,
A WHARF AND A JETTY.
>>HAROLD: 'SCUSE ME UNCLE RED
BUT AREN'T THOSE JUST FANCY
NAMES FOR YOU KNOW DOCK?
>>RED: YEAH BUT WE ALREADY HAVE
A DOCK ACTUALLY THAT'S KIND
OF DUMB WE DON'T NEED ANY
MORE DOCK WE ONLY HAVE
3 AND A HALF BOATS.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED I KNOW WHAT
WE CAN DO WITH THE EXTRA WOOD
I KNOW WHAT WE CAN DO
YOU KNOW WHAT WE CAN DO,
WE CAN BUILD A BRAND NEW
TELEVISION STUDIO THAT'S WHAT
WE COULD DO WE COULD BUILD
A BRAND NEW TELEVISION
STUDIO AND THAT WAY WE COULD
DO THE SHOW PROPERLY, RIGHT?
>>RED: YEAH THAT'S A GOOD IDEA
HAROLD THEN WE COULD HIRE
A PROPER PRODUCER AND DIRECTOR.
>>HAROLD: YOU KNOW WHAT
I WAS SAYING, FORGET IT
JUST FORGET WHAT I SAID BECAUSE
THAT'D BE SILLY TO DO THAT
FORGET IT COMPLETELY NO
A WOODEN STUDIO YOU KNOW
HELLO NOBODY'S THERE.
THE ACOUSTICS WOULD BE TERRIBLE
YOU KNOW AND THE TERMITES
YOU KNOW AND THE SAP DRIPPING
OFF FORGET IT YOU KNOW.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
>>HAROLD: I'M SURE YOU COULD
THINK OF SOMETHING ELSE
TO MAKE WITH THE WOOD.
>>RED: WE HAVE HAROLD, SMOKE.
>>HAROLD: YOU'RE GOING
TO BURN IT?
THAT'S SUCH A WASTE UNCLE
RED WASTE NOT, WANT NOT.
>>RED: HAROLD WANT NOT YOU NOT.
WITH ALL THIS TALK THESE DAYS
ABOUT YOU KNOW CONVERTING
TO ALTERNATE FUELS AND BEING
CONSCIOUS OF THE ENVIRONMENT
AND EVERYTHING WHAT WE'RE GOING
TO DO IS WE'RE GOING TO CONVERT
ALL OUR VEHICLES TO RUN
ON FIREWOOD.
>>HAROLD: WOOD BURNING CARS.
>>RED: YES SIRREE PAPA COCKTAILS
PICTURE THIS ONE HAROLD
DUAL OVERHEAD POTBELLIED STOVES
DOUGIE FRANKLIN SAYS WE'RE
PROBABLY LOOKING AT 50 MILES
TO A LOG AND WITH THE RAILWAYS
TIES IN THERE YOU GOT THE
CREOSOTE GOING TO LUBRICATE
YOUR TRANSMISSION.
>>HAROLD: I DON'T THINK THAT'S
GOING TO WORK UNCLE RED REALLY.
>>RED: YOU WANT TO BET HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: NO I DON'T
WANT TO BET.
>>RED: $10 BUCKS HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: IT'S NOT
GOING TO WORK NO, NO.
>>RED: HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: WHAT?
>>RED: PUT YOUR MONEY WHERE
YOUR MOUTH IS, NOT THAT YOU
HAVE THAT MUCH MONEY.
>>HAROLD: ALL RIGHT I'M IN
$10 BUCKS, OKAY ALL RIGHT.
>>RED: YOU KNOW IF THIS WOOD
BURNING THING WORKS OUT I THINK
WE CAN BE EXPECTING A CALL FROM
THE GAS COMPANIES AND THE
OIL COMPANIES ON THIS BABY.
>>HAROLD: IF IT DOESN'T
I THINK YOU CAN EXPECT A
CALL FROM THE FIRE DEPARTMENT.
♪ THE MOON HAS MAGICAL POWERS ♪
♪ TO MAKE THINGS CHANGE ♪
♪ IN THEIR APPEARANCE ♪
♪ AND PERSONALITY ♪
♪ WHEN THE MOON SHINES THROUGH ♪
♪ THE LIMBS OF THE MAPLE TREE ♪
♪ IT CAN TURN AN ADMIRER INTO ♪
♪ A WEREWOLF AND VICE VERSA ♪
♪ OH THE MOON IS A MYSTERY ♪
♪ WITH MAGICAL POWERS ♪
♪ THAT'S FOR SURE ♪
♪ WE KNOW THAT THAT'S TRUE ♪
♪ WE KNOW THAT, BUT HANGING ♪
♪ A MOON OUT OF THE REAR ♪
♪ WINDOW OF A '74 CHEV ♪
♪ DOESN'T TURN IT INTO ♪
♪ A LUNAR MODULE ♪
>>RED: WELL I WAS OUT THE
BACK OF THE LODGE JUST WORKING
ON AN OLD PADDLE AND IT'S TIME
FOR 'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'
ANYWAYS HANDED DOWN TO ME BY
MY GREAT GREAT GRANDFATHER
OH BOY BILL...
OH YEAH BILL HAS BROUGHT
SOME TRAPS, THESE THINGS I'LL
TELL YOU SCARE THE HECK OUT
OF ME BUT HE WANTED TO SHOW US
HOW YOU GO TRAPPING WITH THESE
AND THEN HE BILL, BILL, BILL,
THAT'S AN HEIRLOOM,
IT IS NOW KINDLING THANK YOU.
ANYWAY HE GOES OUT THERE
AND HE SAYS YOU KNOW YOU GOT
A TRAP LIKE THAT YOU GOT TO DIG
A LITTLE HOLE FOR IT BECAUSE IF
IT'S JUST ON TOP OF THE GROUND
OH, OH, OH, IF IT'S JUST
SITTING ON TOP OF THE GROUND
OF COURSE THE ANIMALS ARE
GOING TO SEE IT.
YOU MARK THAT THERE WELL
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA
USE THAT AS A MARKER TO
TELL US WHERE WE'RE
GOING TO BURY THE TRAP.
SEE SO HE DIGS A HOLE DEEP
ENOUGH THAT THE TRAP WILL GO
IN THERE AND ACTUALLY BE
BELOW GROUND LEVEL SO YOU
CAN'T EVEN SEE EVEN IF YOU'RE
LYING DOWN ON YOUR SIDE
YOU COULDN'T EVEN SEE THIS THING
OH BOY THAT'S A SCARY ITEM THERE
NOW HE PUTS ALL THE LITTLE BITS
OF TWIGS SO I'M HELPING HIM OUT
HERE BEST I CAN AND WE'RE
COVERING IT UP SO YOU'D NEVER
EVER KNOW AND I THINK THE POLE
IS A TERRIFIC IDEA THERE
'CAUSE IT KIND OF MARKS,
AT LEAST TO ME
TO BILL IT WASN'T YOU KNOW
BUT TO ME I WAS USING THAT AS
KIND OF A MARKER.
BUT BILL FOUND A CARROT
THERE WHICH WAS AN IDEA
I WAS GOING TO KIND OF USE
THAT TO BAIT ANOTHER TYPE
OF TRAP COURSE AGAIN WITH
THE POLE I WAS STILL
OH! OH! OH! OH! OH!
NOW I'M QUESTIONING WHY WOULD
YOU MOVE WHY WOULD YOU MOVE?
HE SAID OKAY WELL IF YOU'RE
UPSET ABOUT IT I'LL MOVE IT
BACK THAT'S NOT GOOD
ENOUGH BILL.
>>BILL: AAAHHHH!
>>RED: SO NOW IT'S A
DIFFERENT TYPE OF TRAP HERE
THIS IS WHEN YOU JUST HAVE
A BOX LEANING ON A BOARD
THAT'S ABOUT IT AND
THEN OH YEAH YOU GOT TO PUT
SOME BAIT IN THERE SO HE'S GOT
SOME CELERY AND SOME OF THOSE
CARROTS AND PUT THAT IN THERE
NOW HE'S GOT A STRING ATTACHED
TO THE BOARD YOU SEE SO THAT
THE IDEA NOW THIS IS NOT
THE BEST VIEW OF BILL THAT
YOU'LL EVER GET BUT...
>>BILL: WHOAAA!
>>RED: FUNNY HOW
THINGS WORK OUT.
SO ANYWAY NOW WE'RE JUST
SITTING THERE WAITING FOR
SOMETHING TO COME ALONG TO GET
THE CARROTS AND CELERY AND WHAT
HAVE YOU WE GOT TO BE VERY
QUIET NOW SIT VERY STILL.
>>BILL: SHHHHH!
>>RED: YEAH ALL RIGHT BILL
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
(BILL CRUNCHING CARROT)
>>RED: OH OH OH LOOK OH OH
MUST BE GETTING CLOSE TO EASTER
HE'S GOING IN THERE,
HE GETS INSIDE AND BILL GIVES
IT A YANK.
(THUD OF BOARD HITTING BILL)
AND OFF HE GOES WITH A CARROT.
WOW, SO WE GOT TO GO CHECK THIS
OUT AND TRY TO FIGURE OUT
EXACTLY HOW IS THIS BOX
DEFYING THE LAW OF GRAVITY.
SO BILL GOES JUST TO CLUB
THE DARN THING BEFORE IT
GETS TOO FAR.
(SNAPPING OF METAL TRAP)
>>RED: OH.
(BILL MOANING & GROANING)
>>RED: YEAH THAT'S RIGHT
THAT'S WHERE THAT SNARE WAS BILL
OH MY GOSH, OH LOOK WHAT
I CAUGHT HERE,
I DON'T WANT TO CLEAN THIS ONE.
>>RED: AND NOW HERE IS HAROLD
REACHING OUT TO TODAY'S YOUTH
WHILE TODAY'S YOUTH REACHES
OUT TO THE CHANNEL CHANGER.
>>HAROLD: WELCOME TO A BRAND
NEW FEATURE ON THE RED GREEN
SHOW ENTITLED
I'M HAROLD GREEN,
FILM AFICIONADO AND CINEMAHOLIC
AND BY HAPPY CHANCE
A DIRECTOR MYSELF.
OKAY CUT THE MUSIC
AND CUT THE CREDIT CUES
ZOOM IN!
WHEN FILM HISTORIANS NAME
DROP GREAT FILM DIRECTORS
OF THE 20TH CENTURY
THEY OFTENTIMES MENTION PEOPLE
LIKE JOHN FORD, WILLIAM WYLER,
DAVID LEE AND ONE YOUNG PRODIGY
WHO HAS REDEFINED THE CINEMATIC
MEDIUM EVEN THOUGH YOU KNOW
HE HASN'T REALLY DIRECTED
A FEATURE FILM OR PEOPLE
WON'T EVEN LET HIM LIKE
NEAR A CAMERA...
BUT ANYWAY LIKE STANLEY KUBRICK
HE'S ABLE TO FIND THOSE
INTERESTING ANGLES.
CUT TO CAMERA 2!
WHERE'S THE CAMERA 2?
OH AND LIKE CAPRA HE'S ABLE
TO GET THE MOST EXCITING
AND ELECTRIFYING PERFORMANCE
OUT OF EACH AND EVERY
PLAYER AND LIKE TRUPHEAU
HE'S ABLE TO EMBELLISH
EACH SCENE WITH ONLY HIS
SPECIAL TOUCHES.
(CRUNCHING SUCKER)
AND LIKE PRESTON STURGESS
HE'S ABLE TO LET A SCENE
PLAY ON.
>>RED: HAROLD YOU'LL NEVER
WORK IN THIS TOWN AGAIN.
>>HAROLD: AND LIKE HITCHCOCK
HE'S KNOWS EXACTLY WHEN
TO YELL CUT! CUT!
>>RED: HAP CAN YOU GIVE
ME A LIFT INTO TOWN?
>>HAP: YOUR VAN NOT WORKING RED
LET ME GUESS DOUGIE FRANKLIN'S
REPLACED THE MOTOR
WITH A WOODSTOVE.
>>RED: NO, THE VAN'S OUT OF
COMMISSION BECAUSE SOMEBODY
STOLE THE RIGHT FRONT TIRE.
>>HAP: YOU DON'T SAY?
>>RED: OH YEAH GOODYEAR,
WHITEWALL 75R-14 GOOD TIRE.
>>HAP: WELL I GUESS I CAN SEE
MY WAY CLEAR TO GIVING YOU
A LIFT MAYBE.
YOU'LL DO SOMETHING
FOR ME LATER ON.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
INTO TOWN FOR?
>>RED: WELL A TIRE AND SOME
MATCHES FOR OUR ALTERNATE
FUEL WOODSTOVE PROJECT THING.
>>HAP: OH TRICKY THINGS
ALTERNATIVE FUELS
I REMEMBER THE PROBLEMS WE HAD
BACK IN THE 50'S WHEN I WORKED
ON THE ATOMIC BUICK.
>>RED: HEY HAP DID YOU
SAY ATOMIC BUICK?
>>HAP: A PROTON POWERED 4-DOOR
SEDAN WITH A NUCLEAR FAMILY
NO PISTONS, NO POLLUTION
NO OIL TO CHANGE.
I DESIGNED THE TRANSMISSION
EINSTEIN DESIGNED THE ENGINE
AND A WOMAN NAMED ENOLA GAY
DESIGNED THE EXHAUST SYSTEM.
>>RED: I NEVER HEARD OF
AN ATOMIC BUICK.
>>HAP: WELL WHY WOULD YOU?
WE DIDN'T GET IT PAST
THE PROTOTYPE STAGE
IN SECOND GEAR THE ATOMIC
REACTOR OR WHAT WE CALLED
THE ATOMIC PILE WOULD
OVERHEAT AND BACKFIRE
A MUSHROOM CLOUD THAT'LL
FLATTEN A CITY BLOCK.
>>RED: BOY I GUESS THAT
WOULD PUT AN END TO TAILGATERS.
>>HAP: YES SIR, BUT IT WAS A
SAFE CAR, SOLID LEAD AND INSTEAD
OF HEADLIGHTS RED I DESIGNED IT
SO THE WHOLE FRONT OF THE CAR
GLOWED AND FAST ZERO TO THE
SPEED OF LIGHT IN 14 SECONDS.
>>RED: WOW THAT IS HARD
TO BELIEVE ACTUALLY
IS WHAT THAT IS.
>>HAP: IT'S TOO BAD IT DIDN'T
WORK OUT BECAUSE THAT CAR GOT
800 MILLION MILES TO THE GALLON.
BUT THE BIG OIL COMPANIES
BOUGHT UP ALL THE PATENTS AND
DISBANDED MY DESIGN TEAM
AND MELTED DOWN THE LEAD
AND SCRAPPED THE ATOMIC PILE
TO THIS DAY NO ONE KNOWS
WHERE THAT PILE IS.
>>RED: WELL I WOULD THINK YOU'D
BE SITTING IN IT ABOUT NOW.
>>RED: WELL THAT WAS A GOOD DAY
YOU KNOW GOT OURSELVES
A NEW DOCK AND HAD ENOUGH WOOD
LEFTOVER TO BUILD AN OUTHOUSE
OR A GARDEN SHED OR A COUPLE
OF CATHEDRALS.
AND BIT OF LATE BREAKING NEWS
APPARENTLY A COUPLE OF RAILWAY
TANK CARS FULL OF PROPANE
GOT A LITTLE DERAILED
JUST DOWN THE ROAD HERE
APPARENTLY THERE WAS NO
RAILWAY TIES UNDER THE TRACK.
>>HAROLD: OH REALLY?
>>RED: OH YEAH THE CARPENTER
ANTS BEEN BRUTAL THIS
YEAR HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OH HAVEN'T
THEY THOUGH UNCLE RED.
YOUR HAT'S SMOKING
THERE UNCLE RED.
>>RED: (BLOWING)
THANKS A LOT HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: NO PROBLEM
OH THE 10 DOLLARS!
I FORGOT THAT YOU OWED ME
$10 I FORGOT BECAUSE YOU WERE
WRONG AND THUSLY YOU OWED ME
$10 FOR BEING WRONG
YOU HAD TO PAY ME BUT I FORGOT
THAT THAT YOU WERE WRONG.
I WAS RIGHT, YOU WERE WRONG
SLIPPED MY MIND BUT NOW
I'M REMINDED BY THE $10
THAT YOU GAVE ME HOW WRONG
YOU ACTUALLY WERE
IT'S CLEAR AS A BELL HOW
WRONG HE ACTUALLY WAS.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
OH THERE'S THE SQUEAL
OF THE POSSUM I HAVE TO GO TO
THE MEETING AND SHOW THEM HOW
I HAVE THE $10 FROM
YOU BEING WRONG.
>>RED: I WOULD SUGGEST YOU
DON'T GO TO SLEEP BEFORE
ME TONIGHT HAROLD.
WELL WE'RE NOT DEAD UP
HERE AT THE LODGE
APPARENTLY THE RAILWAY COMPANY
IS NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO
GET ALL THOSE PROPANE CARS
OUT OF THERE SO WE'RE GOING TO
CONVERT ALL OUR VEHICLES
TO RUN ON THAT STUFF.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
I'LL BE COMING HOME STRAIGHT
AFTER THE MEETING
MAYBE YOU COULD DRAW ME A BATH
SO I CAN RINSE THE ASHES OUT
OF MY HAIR AND POSSIBLY
EXTINGUISH MY UNDERSHORTS HERE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU
ON BEHALF OF, OH TO HECK
WITH HIM ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND EVERYBODY EXCEPT HAROLD
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING
AND KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(POSSUM SQEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>ALL: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: COUPLE OF QUICK ONES
BEFORE WE START THE MEETING.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca