AWNINGS.
YOU KNOW THAT THING THAT WOULD
HANG DOWN OVER YOUR WINDOW?
I DON'T MEAN THE CREEPY GUY
IN THE TRENCH COAT.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE CANOPIES THAT WOULD
KEEP THE DIRECT SUNLIGHT
OFF YOUR PARENTS'
GOOD FURNITURE;
YOU KNOW, THE STUFF
YOUR SISTER GOT.
WELL, HERE'S YOUR CHANCE TO
GET IN ON THE LATEST HOME
DECORATING TREND...
AWNINGS MADE FROM CAR HOODS.
CHEAP, EASY TO INSTALL,
AND THEY PROTECT THE HOUSE
AGAINST HURRICANES
AND TORNADOES
AND DRIVE-BY SHOOTINGS --
IF THINGS GET TOO
HOT IN THE 'HOOD.
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU. THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
YOU KNOW OUR LOCAL PAPER,
"THE POSSUM LAKE DAILY
MOVEMENT,"
THEY GOT A CONTEST GOING ON.
THEY'RE LOOKING TO NAME
A MAN OF THE YEAR
FROM THE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
NOMINATIONS ARE OPEN NOW,
AND THE WINNING CONTESTANT GETS
A BRAND NEW FISHING BOAT,
AND I'M THINKING YOURS TRULY
MIGHT ACTUALLY HAVE A SHOT
AT THIS ONE.
HEY, Mr GREEN, DID YOU SEE
THIS MAN OF THE YEAR CONTEST?
I ALREADY GOT
A PAPER, MIKE.
YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO BUY ONE.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
I GET 'EM FOR FREE.
[laughter]
HOW DO YOU DO THAT?
I DON'T REMEMBER.
I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT THIS CONTEST.
I THINK THE LODGE SHOULD
NOMINATE SOMEBODY.
YEAH, OKAY, I KNOW
WHERE YOU'RE GOING,
BUT DO YOU REALLY
THINK I HAVE A CHANCE?
[ CHUCKLING ]
NO, I'M TRYING TO BE
SERIOUS HERE, Mr GREEN.
I THOUGHT I'D HAD
A PRETTY GOOD YEAR.
YEAH, COMPARED TO THE OTHER
LODGE MEMBERS, MAYBE.
BUT THE REAL WORLD HAS A
WHOLE OTHER SENSE OF SCALE.
I MEAN, THIS CONTEST IS OPEN
TO THE WHOLE COMMUNITY...
POLICEMEN, DOCTORS,
FIREMEN,
BAIL BONDSMEN.
YOU KNOW, AS A GROUP,
WE'RE SUCKING
CANAL WATER.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
WHAT'S YOUR BIG IDEA?
I MADE UP A GUY.
WHAT?
I NAMED HIM
AFTER THE TIRE FIRE.
I CALL HIM
BERNIE GOODYEAR.
I MADE HIM A
RETIRED GENERAL.
SAYS HE DOES
VOLUNTEER WORK;
AND HE DONATES
TO AN ORPHANAGE.
AND I ALSO GAVE HIM
THE ORDER OF CANADA.
NO, THERE'S ANOTHER "R."
YOU'VE GOT THE 'ODOR'
OF CANADA.
OKAY, I'LL CHANGE THAT.
BUT I NEED YOU TO SIGN
THIS AS A NOMINATOR,
BECAUSE, LIKE, IF I SIGN IT,
THEY'LL THINK IT'S A SCAM.
IT'S DISCRIMINATION
BUT --
WELL, IT'S KIND
OF CROOKED.
MAYBE DALTON
WILL SIGN IT.
AH, COME ON, Mr GREEN,
BE A SPORT.
I MEAN, NOBODY AT THE LODGE
HERE IS GOOD ENOUGH TO BE
MAN OF THE YEAR.
BUT BERNIE GOODYEAR CAN SET AN
EXAMPLE FOR US ALL TO FOLLOW.
PLUS HERE'S
THE GOOD BIT.
"IF HE WINS, HE'S
INSTRUCTED THE JUDGES
"TO GIVE THE FISHING
BOAT TO THE POSSUM LODGE."
OH, MAN, THIS BERNIE
SOUNDS LIKE A GREAT GUY.
[applause]
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
JOINING Mr GREEN TODAY IS
EXPLOSIVES ENTHUSIAST,
EDGAR MONTROSE.
[applause]
EDGAR WILL BE PLAYING
FOR A FULL BODY MASSAGE
FROM SIX-FINGER LOUIS
AT RUB-A-DUB-DUB
MASSAGE PARLOUR.
AND OIL CHANGE.
DON'T LET THE DIRTY
FINGERNAILS SCARE YOU OFF.
OKAY, Mr GREEN,
YOU'VE 30 SECONDS
TO GET Mr MONTROSE
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT, EDGAR,
YOU USE YOUR
NOSE FOR SMELLING;
YOUR HANDS FOR FEELING;
WHAT DO YOU USE
YOUR EARS FOR?
SEEING.
YOU USE YOUR EARS TO SEE?
YEAH, MY GLASSES SIT ON 'EM.
OKAY, NO.
THERE'S AN EXPRESSION...
"IF A TREE FALLS IN THE FOREST
AND NO ONE IS THERE,
"DOES ANYBODY BLANK IT?"
WHAT KIND OF BLANKET?
WE'RE ALMOST
OUTTA TIME, Mr GREEN.
REMEMBER A
FEW YEARS AGO,
YOU USED REAL DYNAMITE
IN YOUR FIREWORKS DISPLAY?
YOU BLEW UP CITY HALL.
THAT WAS A CROWD PLEASER.
I KNOW THAT, BUT THAT WAS ALSO
THE DAY YOU LOST YOUR...
DEMOLITION LICENSE.
AT LEAST THAT'S WHAT
THEY TOLD ME AT
THE HEARING.
[cheering and applause]
[van chugging,
brakes squealing]
YOU PLANNING
ON GOING IN ANY
TIME SOON, DALTON?
WHAT TIME IS IT?
Red: I HAVE NO IDEA.
IT'S EITHER 1:17, 1:19,
OR SEPTEMBER 6th.
ANNE MARIE'S
GONNA KILL ME.
WELL, YOU COULD
FAKE AN INJURY,
PRETEND YOU WERE
IN AN ACCIDENT.
NO FAKE INJURY IS
GOING TO FOOL ANNE MARIE.
OH, WE COULD HELP
YOU OUT WITH THAT PART.
NO, THANK YOU.
OH, WAIT A MINUTE.
I GOT BUSTER HADFIELD'S PYJAMAS
IN THE BACK OF THE VAN.
YOU KNOW, THIS MAY NOT
BE A NEED TO KNOW.
NO, HE GAVE 'EM TO ME.
HE SAID THEY WERE BAD LUCK.
I WAS GONNA USE
'EM AS OIL RAGS,
BUT YOU COULD PUT
THEM ON, DALTON.
NOW, WHY WOULD I
WANNA DO THAT?
WELL, THEN YOU JUST STAND
ON THE PORCH AND PRETEND
YOU GOT LOCKED OUT.
YEAH, LIKE FRED FLINTSTONE.
"WILMA-A-A-A!"
GO ON UP THERE
AND KNOCK ON THE DOOR.
SHHH!
TURN YOUR LIGHTS OFF.
ANNE MARIE!
ANNE MARIE,
I'VE LOCKED MYSELF OUT.
Anne Marie:
WHO IS THAT?
IT'S ME, HONEY,
IT'S DALTON.
I HEARD A NOISE ON THE PORCH
AND IT WOKE ME UP,
AND WHEN I CAME OUT
TO INVESTIGATE,
THE DOOR LOCKED BEHIND ME.
YOU ARE SUCH A MORON,
YOU KNOW THAT?
YES, I AM.
DALTON?
YES, DEAR.
COMING, DEAR.
HOW COME YOU'RE WEARING BUSTE
HADFIELD'S PAJAMAS?
YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS A BOY
I ALWAYS DREAMED
ABOUT BEING
A RIVERBOAT GAMBLER.
I'VE TAKEN SOME CHANCES
IN A BOAT A FEW TIMES
BUT, YOU KNOW,
THAT'S NOT THE SAME THING.
SO TODAY ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'VE COME ALL THE WAY UP
TO THE PORT ASBESTOS SHIPYARD,
AND I'M GONNA TURN THIS VAN
INTO A RIVERBOAT
PADDLE WHEELER.
I MIGHT EVEN TRY IT
WITH MY OWN VAN.
NOW, THE FIRST CONSIDERATION
HAS TO BE GETTING THE VAN
TO FLOAT,
ESPECIALLY FOR
YOU NON-SWIMMERS.
TAKE A BUNCH OF THESE PALLETS,
WHICH YOU CAN GET ANYWHERE
THAT THEY HAVE PALLETS
RATHER THAN FENCES.
THEN WHAT YOU WANNA DO IS FILL
THEM WITH FLOATATION.
NOW, YOU COULD USE THAT
STYROFOAM STUFF
IF YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY
MADE OF MONEY.
BUT I PREFER TO RECYCLE.
IF YOU'RE LIKE ME,
YOU GENERATE TWO OR THREE
HUNDRED OF THESE PLASTIC
MOTOR OIL BOTTLES
EVERY MONTH OR SO.
NOW INSTEAD OF HAVING TO
THROW THEM OUT THE WINDOW
OR LEAVE THEM IN THE CANADIAN
TIRE PARKING LOT,
YOU CAN HANG ONTO THEM,
PLUS ANY OTHER BOTTLES
YOU'VE GOT
BECAUSE YOU'RE GONNA USE
'EM AS FLOATATIONS ON
YOUR RIVER BOAT.
OKAY, THAT'S OUR HULL.
LOOKS LIKE HULL, DOESN'T IT?
NOW ALL I HAVE TO DO IS ADD THE
PADDLE WHEEL TO THE VAN ITSELF.
YOU KNOW, THE OLD WOOLWORTH
STORE IN TOWN
HAS HAD DECLINING
REVENUES SINCE 1957.
FINALLY CLOSED IT LAST YEAR.
WHEN THEY TORE IT DOWN,
I MANAGED TO GET MY HANDS
ON THIS OLD REVOLVING DOOR.
I WAS GONNA INSTALL IT
IN THE LODGE
TO SPEED UP THE EXIT TIME
ON MEXICAN NIGHT.
BUT INSTEAD I'M GOING TO TAKE
ALL THE WINDOWS OUT OF HER
AND USE THIS AS
MY PADDLE WHEEL.
WELL, THOSE EXTENSION LADDERS
SURE CAME IN HANDY
TO MOUNT THE UNIT TO.
AND YOU MAY NOTICE I'VE
ADDED A WHEEL RIM
TO THE OUTSIDE OF
MY PADDLE WHEEL.
AND THEN A
CORRESPONDING WHEEL RIM,
I'VE PUT ON THE OUTSIDE OF
ONE OF MY DRIVE WHEELS HERE.
NOW I JUST CONNECT THE TWO
TOGETHER, USING A SEAT BELT.
BUCKLE UP FOR SAFETY.
I ACTUALLY TOOK THE SEAT BELTS
OUT OF THE VAN.
I FIGURE WHEN YOU'RE
OUT ON THE WATER,
YOU REALLY DON'T WANT
TO HAVE A SEAT BELT ON.
OH, BY THE WAY,
I JACKED UP THE WHOLE
BACK END HERE.
THAT WAY WHEN
I PUT HER IN GEAR,
THERE GOES MY PADDLE WHEEL.
ACTUALLY WE TAPED ME PUTTING THE
VAN ONTO MY FLOATATION RAFT,
BUT WE'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO SHOW IT ON TELEVISION,
DUE TO A FEW
ENVIRONMENTAL INFRACTIONS
AND SOME INAPPROPRIATE LANGUAGE.
HERE'S SOMETHING YOU MIGHT
THINK ABOUT FOR YOUR
RIVER BOAT.
IT'S ACTUALLY JUST
A PIECE OF STOVE PIPE.
RAN THE EXHAUST SYSTEM
UP THROUGH IT.
AND HERE'S A TRICK TO GIVE IT
THAT BLACK RIVER BOAT SMOKE...
INSTEAD OF PUTTING
GASOLINE IN HER
I FILLED UP THE TANK
WITH DIESEL.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
THEY'LL FIND ME
ROLLING DOWN THE RIVER.
[foghorn blasting]
[applause]
YOU KNOW THE BEST
TIME TO FIND OUT WHAT
YOUR FRIENDS ARE REALLY LIKE
IS WHEN YOU'RE IN SOME KIND
OF A GROUP ENDEAVOR;
LIKE WHEN THEY'RE ALL
OVER HELPING YOU MOVE
SOMETHING HEAVY,
SAY, THE BEER FRIDGE --
SAY, THE BEER FRIDGE
ON PAY DAY.
THAT'S WHEN YOU
FIND OUT WHO'S WHO.
FIRST OF ALL YOU
GET THE QUITTERS.
THE ONES WHO JUST STEP BACK FROM
THE FRIDGE AND SAY,
"HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT,
"I FEEL LIKE I'M JUST
IN THE WAY HERE."
THEN YOU GET THE HISTORIAN.
STEPS BACK FROM THE FRIDGE,
PULLS OUT A CAMERA.
WANTS TO GET A PICTURE
OF YOU AND YOUR HERNIA.
NEXT YOU GET THE SUPERVISOR.
THEY STEP BACK AND THEY TURN
INTO SOME KIND OF A CHEERLEADER.
"ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY,
HEAVE!"
I ALMOST DID.
THEN YOU GET THE FAKERS.
THEY'RE THE TRICKIEST ONES.
YEAH, SURE, THEY BELLY
UP TO THE FRIDGE.
THEY SPIT ON THEIR HANDS.
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO
THE GRAB AND LIFT,
YOU HEAR THE TELL-TALE
TINKLING OF POCKET CHANGE.
YOU GOTTA KNOW WHO'S WHO
BECAUSE THESE GUYS ARE GONNA BE
YOUR PALLBEARERS ONE DAY.
THE LAST THING YOU WANT IS A
SUPERVISOR THERE GOING,
"EASY, EASY."
WHILE TWO FAKERS DROP YOU
HEAD FIRST INTO YOUR
FINAL RESTING PLACE.
YOU GOTTA WALK AROUND HEAVEN
LOOKING LIKE THE RCA DOG.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
HI, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
IF THERE'S SOMETHING IN THE AIR
THAT KNOCKS YOU OFF YOUR CHAIR,
JUST CALL ME,
AND I'LL BE THERE.
OR SEND UP A FLARE,
IF YOU DARE.
WELL, I GOT THE LODGE
MEMBERS TOGETHER.
TOLD THEM ABOUT THIS BERNIE
GOODYEAR THAT WE MADE UP
AND HOW WE WANT HIM TO WIN THE
MAN OF THE YEAR AWARD.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK SAID HE
ACTUALLY REMEMBERED THE GUY.
I REMINDED HIM THAT
BERNIE DOESN'T EXIST.
SOMETIMES I WONDER IF
OLD MAN SEDGWICK EXISTS.
BUT WHEN THEY HEARD
ABOUT THE FISHING BOAT,
THEY ALL LIKE THE IDEA
OF SHARING THAT,
SO WE'RE ALL GOING AROUND
TALKING UP BERNIE GOODYEAR
AS THE MAN OF THE YEAR.
HEY, Mr GREEN,
DID YOU SEE TODAY'S PAPER?
NO, I DIDN'T.
THE BOX WAS MISSING
FOR SOME REASON.
OH, SORRY.
IT'S BEHIND
THE LIQUOR STORE.
UH, THERE'S THIS BIG
ARTICLE ON BERNIE GOODYEAR.
"TOO GOOD TO BE TRUE."
OH, MAN, THEY'RE
ON TO US.
NO, NO, THEY'RE SAYING
HE'S A CHEAT AND A LIAR.
SOME WOMAN IN PORT ASBESTOS
SAID SHE HAD HIS BABY.
WELL, THAT DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE THE BERNIE I KNOW.
EXACTLY.
AND NOW THE TOWN COUNCIL
IS DEMANDING
THAT BERNIE COME FORWARD
AND FACE HIS ACCUSERS.
UNTIL HE DOES,
THEY'VE SUSPENDED
THE MAN OF THE YEAR
COMPETITION.
WELL, WE GOTTA GO DOWN
THERE AND STAND UP FOR HIM.
YOU KNOW WHO'S
BEHIND THIS?
THOSE GUYS FROM CARIBOU LODGE.
I HEARD THEY WANT ONE OF THEIR
MEMBERS TO WIN THE CONTEST.
YEAH, IT'S A SMEAR CAMPAIGN,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A
SHAME THAT THEY
HAVE TO RESORT
TO LIES AND TRICKERY
JUST TO GET
WHAT THEY WANT!
WELL, MIKE,
THAT'S HUMAN NATURE.
[applause]
OH, HELLO, BOYS AND GIRLS.
RANGER GORD HERE WITH
ANOTHER HOMEMADE ANIMATED
EDUCATIONAL FILM
YOU ALL SEEM TO ENJOY SO MUCH.
WELL, JUDGING BY
THE MAIL, THAT IS.
WHAT I MEAN, IS JUDGING BY THE
LACK OF ANY NEGATIVE MAIL,
[wailing]
OR ANY MAIL, REALLY!
[sobbing]
BUT THAT'S NOT YOUR PROBLEM.
ANYWAY, TODAY'S FILM IS
ABOUT PEOPLE WHO THINK
THEY KNOW THINGS
BUT THEY REALLY DON'T.
NOW, LET'S SEE IF YOU CAN GUESS
WHO I'M TALKING ABOUT HERE,
AND I'LL GIVE YOU A HINT...
IT'S RED AND HAROLD.
OKAY?
GOOD LUCK.
HERE WE GO.
[quirky upbeat music]
[thunder and rain]
RANGER GORD,
UNCLE RED,
LOOK AT THE
BEAUTIFUL RAINBOW.
IT WAS ALMOST WORTH
GETTING SOAKING WET.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL
THING TO BEHOLD.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT'S MORE
BEAUTIFUL THAN THAT, THOUGH.
IT'S WHAT YOU CAN
FIND AT THE END OF IT.
WHAT'S AT THE END
OF A RAINBOW,
RANGER GORD?
AT THEN END OF EVERY
RAINBOW IS A DUFFEL BAG
STUFFED WITH
UNMARKED BILLS.
OH, THAT'S NOT TRUE!
OH, I THINK MAYBE YOU SHOULD GO
AND CHECK IT OUT,
BECAUSE MAYBE WE
COULD GO AND SEE
BECAUSE, LIKE -- MONEY --
WE COULD ALL GET SOME OF IT.
HA HA, IF ONLY IT
WERE THAT EASY, HAROLD.
THE PROBLEM IS THE DUFFEL BAG
AT THE END OF THE RAINBOW
IS GUARDED BY
A MAGIC ANVIL.
WAH, A MAGIC ANVIL?
IT'S A MYTH, HAROLD.
AND GORD DOESN'T
EVEN HAVE IT RIGHT.
THERE'S A POT OF GOLD
AT THE END OF THE RAINBOW,
AND IT'S GUARDED
BY A LEPRECHAUN,
NOT A MAGIC ANVIL.
WOW! GORD WAS RIGHT.
UNBELIEVABLE!
WOW!
WAH!
AREN'T YOU TWO
FORGETTING SOMETHING?
WELL, I THINK YOU TWO HAVE HAD
ENOUGH FUN FOR ONE DAY.
SO DON'T BE LIKE
HAROLD AND RED, FOLKS.
THE MONEY AT THE END OF THE
RAINBOW CAN'T BUY YOU HAPPINESS.
IT CAN ONLY DROP A
MAGIC ANVIL ON YOUR HEAD.
[laughing heartily]
[applause]
[telephone ringing]
IF YOU'RE LIKE ME, YOU GET
A LOT OF ANNOYING PHONE CALLS,
USUALLY AROUND
THE DINNER HOUR.
SOME GUY TRYING TO SELL
YOU USED ALUMINUM SIDING
OR A VACUUM CLEANER THAT
CAN SUCK UP A BOWLING BALL.
[telephone ringing]
I FIGURE THERE'S A LIST OUT
THERE SOMEWHERE WITH ALL
OUR PHONE NUMBERS ON IT.
WE GOTTA FIND A WAY TO GET OUR
NUMBERS OFF OF THAT LIST.
SO HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
[telephone ringing]
Good evening, could I speak
to the head of the --
USE SOMEBODY'S BUSINESS CARD
AND DIAL UP THEIR FAX NUMBER.
THEN WHAT YOU WANNA DO IS GET
YOURSELF ONE OF THOSE TAPE
RECORDER UNITS THERE
AND RECORD THE SOUND THAT THEIR
FAX MACHINE MAKES WHEN IT
ANSWERS THE PHONE.
[ ELECTRONIC BEEPING
OF FAX MACHINE ]
THEN YOU JUST REWIND THE TAPE,
TURN THE VOLUME UP FULL,
AND WAIT FOR THE
NEXT SALESMAN TO CALL.
[telephone ringing]
Good evening, could I speak --
[electronic beeping
of fax machine]
[applause]
WELCOME TO THE EXPERTS PORTION
OF THE SHOW,
WHERE WE ADDRESS THOSE THREE
LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
Audience: I DON'T KNOW.
TODAY'S LETTER READS...
"DEAR EXPERTS, LAST NIGHT I
CELEBRATED A LITTLE TOO MUCH,
"WAS ARRESTED IN A HOTEL ROOM
WITH TWO STRANGE WOMEN,
"AND LOST MY WIFE'S CAR IN A
HIGH STAKES GAMBLING MATCH.
"AND NOW SHE'S REALLY
MAD AT ME.
"HOWEVER, I'VE FIGURED A WAY
TO GET OUT OF THIS TROUBLE
SCOT FREE.
"IN ORDER FOR MY PLAN TO
SUCCEED, HOWEVER,
"I NEED YOUR
EXPERT OPINION.
"IS TIME TRAVEL POSSIBLE?"
SIGNED "READY TO
LEAVE YESTERDAY."
GENTLEMEN?
WELL, IN THEORY,
YOU KNOW, IT IS.
MAYBE NOT NOW,
BUT IN THE FUTURE,
CERTAINLY.
WELL, JUST A
SECO NOW.
I WOULD THINK THAT IF
TIME TRAVEL IS GOING TO
BE POSSIBLE IN THE FUTURE,
THEN BY NOW, SOMEBODY FROM
THE FUTURE WOULD HAVE COME
BACK TO SEE US.
WELL, THEY DO.
THAT'S WHAT UFOs ARE,
PEOPLE COMING BACK
FROM THE FUTURE.
GEE WHIZ.
IT'S IN ALL THE PAPERS.
OH, YEAH?
WHAT PAPERS
ARE THOSE, DALTON?
THE ONES YOU PUT
UNDER THE PUPPY?
YOU ARE SO SKEPTICAL.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT I'M NOT A
SUPER-INTELLIGENT ALIEN
THAT'S COME BACK
FROM THE FUTURE?
BECAUSE I WENT TO
SCHOOL WITH YOU.
UH, COULD WE ANSWER
THIS GUY'S LETTER, PLEASE?
ALL RIGHT, I'M SORRY,
BUT TIME TRAVEL MAKES
NO SENSE TO ME AT ALL.
EVEN IF IT WAS POSSIBLE,
I WOULDN'T WANNA GO
BACK IN THE PAST.
MY TIME MACHINE WOULD BREAK,
AND I GOTTA TRY AND FIX IT
WITH EDSEL PARTS.
AND I SURE AS HECK DON'T
WANNA GO INTO THE FUTURE.
I CAN'T OPERATE THE
APPLIANCES I GOT NOW.
SO YOU WOULD ADVISE
OUR VIEWER TO ABANDON THE
WHOLE TIME TRAVEL CONCEPT?
OH, COMPLETELY ABANDON THAT.
THIS GUY JUST NEEDS
TO GET AWAY AND LIE LOW.
HE DOESN'T NEED TIME TRAVEL,
HE NEEDS TRAVEL TIME.
[laughter]
YEAH, BUT WHAT IF
TIME TRAVEL WAS POSSIBLE?
WHEN WOULD YOU
GUYS GO BACK TO?
OH, BOY.
I'D PROBABLY GO BACK
TO THE DATE OF MY BIRTH.
I'D PROBABLY GO BACK TO NINE
MONTHS BEFORE THAT.
THEN I COULD MEET MY DAD.
[laughter]
WHAT ABOUT YOU,
Mr GREEN?
I THINK I'D GO
BACK TEN MINUTES
AND BURN THAT LETTER.
[laughter and applause]
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD OF
ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
COVER ME.
I'M GOING IN.
[applause and laughter]
WELL, I'M NOT EXACTLY
SURE WHAT HAPPENED,
BUT I DO KNOW WE DON'T
HAVE A NEW FISHING BOAT.
YEAH, BUT THE GUYS FROM
THE CARIBOU LODGE DO.
UNBELIEVABLE.
THEY GOT UP IN FRONT
OF THE TOWN COUNCIL.
THEY ACCUSED BERNIE GOODYEAR
OF EVERY SIN KNOWN TO MAN
AND A COUPLE OF NEW ONES
THEY MADE UP THEMSELVES.
THEN Mr GREEN, HE GOT UP AND
DENIED ALL THE ACCUSATIONS,
AND THEN HE PRESENTED
Mr GOODYEAR AS THAT
WONDERFUL GUY
THAT WE ALL CAME
TO KNOW AND LOVE.
YOU WERE GREAT, Mr GREEN.
I WAS MOVED.
I WISH THE TOWN COUNCIL
HAD SEEN IT THAT WAY, MIKE.
WELL, YOU WERE LYING.
SO WERE THEY.
YES, BUT HERE AGAIN,
PEOPLE WOULD RATHER
BELIEVE A HURTFUL LIE
THAN A HELPFUL ONE.
AND I'VE GOT THE
RAP SHEET TO PROVE IT.
SO THEN THE CARIBOU LODGE
GUYS CUT THEMSELVES A DEAL.
THEY TOLD TOWN COUNCIL THEY'D
GET RID OF BERNIE GOODYEAR
IN A PEACEFUL,
NON-VIOLENT WAY,
AND THEY GUARANTEED
THEM THAT BERNIE
WOULD NEVER SHOW HIS
FACE IN THE POSSUM
LAKE AREA AGAIN.
AND ALL THEY WANTED IN RETURN
WAS THE PRIZE FISHING BOAT.
WITH THE PROVISO
THEY'D GIVE THE BOAT BACK
IF BERNIE EVER
SHOWED UP IN TOWN.
THAT'S WHEN I KNEW THE
SCAM HAD GONE TOO FAR.
WELL, YOU TRIED TO DO THE
RIGHT THING, Mr GREEN.
YOU REALLY DID.
YEP, I TOLD 'EM BERNIE
GOODYEAR DIDN'T EXIST.
I TOLD 'EM
WE MADE HIM UP.
THEY DIDN'T BELIEVE IT.
DIDN'T BELIEVE IT.
I FOUND THAT IRONIC.
OH, WELL, I'M JUST SORRY
YOU DIDN'T WIN MAN OF
THE YEAR, Mr GREEN.
WELL, MIKE, I LIED,
I CHEATED,
AND I TRIED TO GET SOMETHING
UNDER FALSE PRETENSES.
FORGET MAN OF THE YEAR,
I SHOULD'VE RUN FOR
PRESIDENT.
[laughter and applause]
[possum squealing]
OH, MEETING TIME, Mr GREEN.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD, MIKE.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I DID LEARN SOMETHING TODAY.
I LEARNED THAT IF YOU'RE HONEST,
YOU CAN STOP TALKING ANY TIME
YOU WANT,
BUT WHEN YOU LIE, YOU GOTTA JUST
KEEP HER ROLLING AND ROLLING...
BOY, YOUR SISTER TALKS A LOT,
DOESN'T SHE?
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND BERNIE GOODYEAR
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause and cheering]
SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY, SIT DOWN.
SIT, SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
BOW YOUR HEADS FOR
THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
Red: YES, DALTON?
Dalton: OKAY, I HAVE AN
IMPORTANT ANNOUNCEMENT.
CARIBOU LODGE IS SAYING THEIR
FISHING BOAT IS MISSING,
AND THEY'RE CLAIMING THAT
MAYBE ONE OR MORE MEMBERS
OF THIS LODGE
HAD SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT.
AND THEY'RE ASKING FOR OUR
COOPERATION.
Red: OKAY, DALTON, I THINK I
KNOW WHO TOOK THE FISHING BOAT.
BERNIE GOODYEAR!