IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE MAN WITH THE SPRING
IN HIS STEP
SINCE HIS POCKETWATCH EXPLODED
IN HIS PANTS,
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
WHOOOO!
THANKS, APPRECIATE IT.
(Howling)
OOH, RED, OOOH!
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GONNA GET THE SHOW GOING
'CAUSE I'M ALREADY LATE FOR
THE MONTHLY POKER GAME.
A BUNCH OF OVERWEIGHT GUYS,
DRINKIN' BEER, SMOKIN' CIGARS.
HOW IS
THAT FUN?
WELL, YOU WON'T BE THERE.
YOU'RE ALL A BUNCH OF SHIRKERS.
YOU'RE SHIRKING
YOUR RESPONSIBILITY
BY PLAYING POKER.
SHIRKER, SHIRKER,
SHIRKER, SHIRKER!
SHA-A-A-A-AMELESS SHIRKER!
SHIRKING YOUR RESPONSIBILITIES,
GO PLAY AT CARDS,
INDULGE IN STUPID STORIES FULL
OF EXAGGERATION AND INNUENDO.
YOU'RE AN AWFUL GOOD GUESSER.
IF THAT'S WHAT BEING AN ADULT
IS ABOUT,
I HOPE
I NEVER GROW UP.
THAT COULD BE ARRANGED.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MAIN MESSAGE BEING,
FOR GOSH SAKES,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
(Laughing)
THE POKER GAME BREAK UP EARLY?
YOU STILL HAVE
YOUR SHIRT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT, HAROLD.
I WAS WINNING ALL NIGHT.
THE LAST HAND, I PUT
THE WHOLE WORKS ON THE LINE.
I'M SENSING IT DIDN'T GO WELL.
IT WAS MY FAVOURITE GAME:
"ODD MAN OUT".
THREES, FIVES, SEVENS,
AND NINES ARE WILD,
PLUS ONE-EYED JACKS
AND THE MAN WITH THE AXE.
SO I'M SITTING THERE
WITH 11 QUEENS.
I'M NOT GONNA LET ON.
JUST KINDA PLAY IT COOL.
SO STINKY BETS, I RAISE,
BUSTER RAISES, MOOSE FOLDS.
SO DOES THE CHAIR
HE'S SITTIN' ON.
THEN STINKY RAISES AGAIN,
I RAISE AGAIN, BUSTER CALLS.
I LAY DOWN MY 11 QUEENS.
BUSTER HAD A FULL HOUSE --
FIVE EIGHTS AND SIX NINES.
AND, UH...
I'M REACHING FOR THE POT...
STINKY LAYS DOWN 12 ACES!
CLEANED ME RIGHT OUT!
YOU KNOW, UNCLE RED,
IF YOU PLAYED
WITH FEWER WILD CARDS,
YOU'D HAVE LESS CHANCE
OF SOMEONE GETTING 12 ACES.
THERE WERE 12
NATURAL ACES.
(Audience laughing)
UNCLE RED, THERE'S ONLY
FOUR NATURAL ACES IN A DECK,
AREN'T THERE?
WELL, AROUND THAT.
I LIKE TO TAKE AN EXTRA ONE,
JUST IN CASE, YOU KNOW.
SOME OF THE OTHER GUYS,
MAYBE...
BUT THERE'S NEVER MORE
THAN FIVE OR SIX EXTRA ACES.
IF STINKY HAD 12 AND THERE'S
ONLY 4, THEN HE BROUGHT 8.
SOMEBODY'S CHEATING!
(Red): LATER ON
WE'LL BE DOING
A LITTLE FRUIT-PICKING
WITH TWO GUYS
WHO ARE PERFECT FOR THE JOB,
BILL AND HAROLD.
THAT'S A PRETTY CLASSY-LOOKING
LADDER THERE, BUT...
THE OPERATOR IS AT ABOUT
THE SAME LEVEL AS USUAL.
THIS IS ONE OF
THE OLD TRADTIONS--
THERE'S NO BOTTOM IN THAT.
ONE OF THE TRADTIONS
AROUND THE LODGE IS TO
FORGET ABOUT
THE MECHANIZED-- OH.
THE MECHANIZED-- HA, HA, HA.
THE MECHANICAL EQUIPMENT
AND SO ON.
'CAUSE IT'S JUST
MORE FUN
PICKING FRUIT BY HAND.
IT WILL TAKE A LONG TIME
TO FILL THAT BASKET.
IT'S REVENGE OF THE NERDS.
THERE WE GO.
(Laughing)
BY GOLLY, EH.
AND THEY SAY
FRUIT'S NOT GOOD FOR YA.
OH MY GOSH,
IT'S WATERMELON MAN.
OH, THE MOON IS
A STRANGE SHADE OF YELLOW
WITH STRIPES
OF MAGENTA AND BLUE
THE CLOUDS ARE PURPLE
AND ORANGE
AND THE MIST SMELLS
LIKE AN OLD SHOE
OH, I HAVE
A HORRIBLE HEADACHE
AND I PASS OUT
EVERY MINUTE OR TWO
IT'S OK TO HAVE
A BONFIRE
BUT NOT IN
A FIBREGLASS CANOE
THIS IS FOR THE BIG ONE --
A BENCH-STOP SIGN
AND A COUPON FOR
A FREE DRIVING LESSON!
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET DOUGIE FRANKLIN
TO SAY THIS WORD...
(Quietly): "PET".
"PET".
OHHHH...
AND GO.
ALL RIGHT --
DOUGIE?
YEAH!
A DOG.
FRIEND.
NO, IT'S MORE THAN A FRIEND.
FAMILY MEMBER.
THAT MAY VERY WELL BE.
OK, HOW ABOUT THIS -- CAT.
BULLDOZER!
(Audience laughing)
NO, NO, NO,
LET'S GO ANOTHER WAY.
WHEN WE WERE YOUNG, WE WOULDN'T
MAKE OUT
WITH GIRLS.
WE WOULDN'T NECK WITH GIRLS.
WE WOULD...
... CRY.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
THE WORD WE USED
INSTEAD OF
"MAKE OUT" WAS...
... LIE.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
YOU GET SENIOR CITIZENS,
YOU KNOW?
AND THEY GET LONELY --
MANY DOCTORS WILL RECOMMEND
THEY GET A...
... LOBOTOMY.
WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
I'M HAPPY TO REPORT.
ALL RIGHT,
BUDGIES AND PARAKEETS.
THESE ARE COMMON HOUSEHOLD...
... PE-- PESTS.
OHHH!
OK, YOU TAKE A PEST,
YOU TAKE THE "SSS" OUT.
AND WHAT YOU
HAVE IS A...
YOU GOT A BLADDER PROBLEM.
(Audience laughing)
YOU KNOW, WITH MONSTER-TRUCK
DRIVERS,
THAT'S ONE OF OUR PET PEEVES.
OHHH!
WHAT? WHAT?
CONGRATULATIONS, MR. FRANKLIN!
LAST WEEK, FOR OUR ANNIVERSARY,
I GAVE MY WIFE, BERNICE,
THE ENTIRE JAMES BOND FILM
LIBRARY ON VIDEOCASSETTE.
SHOULD HAVE SEEN HER FACE.
SHAKEN, NOT STIRRED.
LATER ON THAT EVENING,
BERNICE WAS SLEEPING UPSTAIRS,
SNORING LIKE A BANSHEE,
AND I WAS ABOUT HALFWAY THROUGH
MY THIRD... UH, BIG FILM
AND I NOTICED AGENT 007
STRAPPED ON
ONE OF THEM ROCKET JET-PACKS
AND JUST TOOK OFF -- WHOOSH! --
LIKE THAT.
JUST LIKE THE TIME MOOSE
THOMPSON FELL OFF THE ROOF...
EXCEPT BACKWARDS, YOU KNOW?
WHEN I SAW THAT JET-PACK,
I KNEW WHAT I HAD TO BUILD
FOR "HANDYMAN CORNER".
FORGET ABOUT TRAFFIC JAMS,
PARKING SPACES, AND STOP SIGNS.
GET YOURSELF A ROCKET JET-PACK.
HERE'S ALL YOU NEED.
GET A FUEL TANK --
GET SOME ROCKET FUEL IN THERE.
GET A FUEL CONTROL VALVE.
YOU'LL NEED A FUEL IGNITER AND
SOME KIND OF A ROCKET NOZZLE,
SOME SORT OF METAL FRAME
TO HOLD 'ER ALL TOGETHER,
AND, OF COURSE, A CRASH HELMET.
YOU CAN GET THIS FROM FORMER
SOVIET UNION ROCKET SCIENTISTS.
THEY'LL SMUGGLE IT OUT
FOR A FEW THOUSAND DOLLARS.
OR YOU COULD JUST LOOK
IN YOUR GARAGE.
PERSONALLY, I'M LEANIN'
TOWARDS THE GARAGE.
ACTUALLY, THE GARAGE
IS LEANIN' TOWARDS
ME.
(Grunting)
AHHH...
THERE WE GO, OR, AS THE FRENCH
WOULD SAY, "VIOLA".
ALL RIGHT, FIRST THING
YOU LOOK AT IS YOUR FUEL TANK.
I'M GONNA GO WITH
THE DOUBLE TANK ON THIS.
I TELL YA, ME FLYING UP THERE
17,000 FEET,
HAVING TO STOP FOR FUEL,
THAT WOULD BE... INCONVENIENT.
YOU DON'T SEE JAMES BOND
RUNNIN' OUT OF GAS
EVERY HALF HOUR,
WHICH IS PROBABLY HOW
HE GETS ALL THOSE WOMEN.
FOR YOUR HOSES
AND YOUR ROCKET NOZZLE,
JUST USE EVERYTHING
THAT COMES IN THE BARBECUE.
YOUR 3-2-1 IGNITION...
YOU GOT THE BARBECUE STARTER
RIGHT THERE.
FOR YOUR VERTICAL THRUST, YOU
GOT YOUR BURNER CONTROL KNOBS.
I GUESS... COME OFF
WITH A WRENCH OF SOME KIND.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED
A METAL FRAMEWORK
TO HOLD THE WHOLE THING
TOGETHER.
I WOULD USE THIS PART
OF THE UNIT.
WHAT YOU WANNA DO IS
FORM THAT TOGETHER
AND STRAP 'ER ON YOUR BACK.
YOU COULD USE SEATBELTS
FOR THAT OR HEAVY ROPE
OR IF YOU WANTED
TO BE
REAL
SAFE...
I RECOMMEND THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
JUST RELAX -- TAKE IT EASY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
A ROCKET SCIENTIST.
JUST LIKE THAT.
YOU'RE READY TO TAKE
YOUR EQUIPMENT AND PUT IT ON.
YOU GOT YOUR FUEL LINES
ATTACHED TO YOUR FUEL TANKS.
THEY GO UP, ATTACHED IN
THROUGH YOUR FUEL REGULATORS,
AND THEN ON
TO YOUR ROCKET NOZZLES.
WHAT YOU WANNA DO THERE
IS JUST HOOK THEM ON...
HOOK THEM ON THE BACK
OF THE...
I FEEL LIKE THAT GUY THAT MAKES
ALL JAMES BOND'S EQUIPMENT.
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
"Q" -- YEAH,
AND HIS LETTER'S "Q", TOO.
I FEEL LIKE "Q".
I LOOK LIKE "L".
A LITTLE SPY HUMOUR.
HERE WE GO.
THERE I HAVE MY VERY OWN
PERSONALIZED
JAMES BOND JET-PACK.
NOW ALL I NEED IS
A FLYING HELMET,
OR A CRASH HELMET,
AS PESSIMISTS CALL IT.
FOR THAT, I'M GONNA USE
THIS UNIT RIGHT HERE.
EH? LOOK AT THAT.
DOESN'T THAT JUST SCREAM
"SAFETY" AND "SECRET AGENT"
AND "SPYING" AND "DANGER"?
JUST POP THAT BABY ON.
EH? PERFECT, ISN'T IT?
I'M THE SPY WHO CAME IN
FROM THE COALS.
NOW WE JUST TURN ON
OUR ROCKET POWER.
LOST ONE OF MY KNOBS, THERE.
HERE WE GO.
WHEN I WANT TO TAKE OFF,
I HIT THE IGNITION BUTTON.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I GOTTA FLY!
(Explosion)
(Grunting)
AHHH...
I SEE WHY THEY HAVE TO
KEEP GETTIN' NEW ACTORS
TO PLAY JAMES BOND.
(Coughing)
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT MORE.
WANT TO TALK TO YOU GUYS ABOUT
WHAT YOU SHOULD TELL YOUR KIDS
ABOUT LIFE.
IN MY DAY, FATHERS DIDN'T TALK
THAT MUCH TO THEIR KIDS.
THE ONLY ADVICE MY DAD GAVE ME
WAS, "DON'T SLOUCH LIKE THAT!"
IT WASN'T MUCH,
BUT IT MEANT A LOT.
(Audience laughing)
YOU KNOW, I THINK NOW
I KINDA WISH MY DAD
HAD GIVEN ME MORE ADVICE.
NOT THAT THE SLOUCHING THING
WASN'T REALLY TERRIFIC,
BUT MAYBE HE COULD HAVE
TAUGHT ME ABOUT CAREER
OR MONEY OR MARRIAGE
OR WOMEN OR RELATIONSHIPS,
SOMETHING ALONG THAT LINE.
'COURSE, NOW IT'S TOO LATE
'CAUSE DAD HAS LEFT US.
HE'S GONE TO LIVE IN FLORIDA.
(Laughing)
I WAS SITTIN' HERE, THINKING,
"WHAT COULD I TELL PEOPLE
TO TELL THEIR YOUNGSTERS?"
SOMETHING THAT WOULD
HELP THEM OUT.
I THINK OF THE ONE THING,
THE ONE PIECE OF ADVICE,
THAT WOULD HAVE SAVED ME A LOT
OF GRIEF AND TIME AND MONEY.
I KNOW WHAT IT IS.
TAKE CARE OF YOUR TEETH.
(Audience laughing)
YEAH, FRIENDS COME AND GO,
FAMILIES COME AND GO,
JOBS COME AND GO,
BUT WHEN YOU'RE BUILT
LIKE I AM,
YOU'LL USE THESE BABIES
FIVE, SIX TIMES A DAY.
YOU FELLAS OUT THERE,
TAKE YOUR YOUNGSTERS ASIDE,
SIT THEM DOWN AND SAY,
"TAKE CARE OF YOUR TEETH."
WHAT THE HECK -- THEY'RE NOT
GONNA LISTEN TO YOU ANYWAY.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Laughing and applause)
HAROLD, LOOK AT THIS.
HOW MANY CARDS IN A DECK?
LIKE, A NORMAL DECK?
A NORMAL DECK OF CARDS.
IT DEPENDS,
'CAUSE IN A EUCHRE DECK,
THERE'S LESS CARDS, RIGHT,
THAN IN A NORMAL DECK.
CANASTA, THERE'S MORE CARDS
THAT'S WEIRD, TOO, HUH?
"OLD MAID", THEY'RE BIZARRE!
THEY GOT, LIKE,
THE SEVEN OF DONKEYS
AND THE ACE OF DRAGONS.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON THERE!
REGULAR DECKS SOMETIMES
HAVE TWO MORE CARDS.
THERE'S, LIKE,
AN INSTRUCTION CARD
AND A WARRANTY CARD
AND A BLANK CARD.
"IT'S A BLANK -- AHHHH!"
FIFTY-TWO!
FIFTY-TWO CARDS.
REGULAR DECK, SURE, 52, YEAH.
I COUNTED THE CARDS
WE PLAYED WITH.
COMES TO 94.
NINETY-FOUR?!
THAT'S A LOT
OF EXTRA JOKERS.
YEAH, 18 EXTRA.
MORE OR LESS,
YEAH.
THAT'S NOT COUNTING
THESE, HAROLD.
WHOA!
DID THE CARD TABLE
COME LIKE THAT?
YOU CAME LIKE THAT,
SO I GUESS ANYTHING'S POSSIBLE.
HAROLD, HERE'S SOMETHING ELSE.
STINKY HAPPENED TO BE SITTING
ON THIS SIDE.
STINKY HAPPENED TO WIN
THE ENTIRE POT.
IT'S MORE THAN A COINCIDENCE.
HERE'S ANOTHER CLUE,
UNCLE RED.
THESE CARDS ARE STUCK ON WITH
THAT WEIRD GUM STINKY CHEWS.
NO, THAT'S
HIS SALIVA.
WHOA-AH-OH!
OHHHH!
(Siren)
OHHH... POSSUM 9-1-1!
STATE YOUR NAME
AND MEMBERSHIP NUMBER, PLEASE!
IT'S BUZZ SHERWOOD.
UM, I LOST MY MEMBERSHIP CARD
BUT I GOT A CARD
FROM THE VIDEO STORE.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH.
WHERE YOU CALLIN' FROM?
THAT'S JUST IT, RED-MAN.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE I AM --
I'M LOST.
ARE YOU IN YOUR CAR
OR IN YOUR PLANE?
LET ME CHECK.
OHHH...
UH... DINGLE BALLS...
GROUND'S SORT OF CLOSE...
THAT MEANS HE'S IN HIS PLANE.
I'M IN A CAR!
HE'S IN A CAR?! WOW!
WHAT DO YOU SEE AROUND THERE?
UM... OH! TREES AND A HILL.
IS THAT FAMILIAR TO YOU GUYS?
IT'S HILLY AND TREE-Y.
ARE THERE ANY PEOPLE AROUND?
I SEE A GUY UP AHEAD.
HE'S FIXING HIS MAILBOX.
OH, MAN, THAT'S THE ONE
I HIT EARLIER!
I'M GOING AROUND
IN CIRCLES, RED.
BUZZ, KEEP CALM, NOW.
YOU'LL HAVE TO GO UP
TO THAT GUY
AND ASK HIM FOR DIRECTIONS.
ASK... FOR DIRECTIONS?
HOW DOES THAT WORK, MAN?
DON'T PANIC, BUZZ,
DO NOT PANIC.
WE'LL COACH YOU THROUGH THIS.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN, BUZZ.
THE DIRECTIONS WILL BE
TOO COMPLICATED TO REMEMBER.
LISTEN TO THE FIRST
FEW THINGS HE SAYS
AND GET AN IDEA OF
THE DIRECTION HE'S POINTING IN.
KEEP NODDING YOUR HEAD UNTIL
HE SAYS, "YOU CAN'T MISS IT."
THEN JUST SAY, "SO I WAS RIGHT"
AND TAKE OFF.
(Red): HERE WE ARE WITH
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL".
I SAID WE WEREN'T GOING TO GO
WITH THE MECHANIZED,
BUT LOOK WHAT WE GOT.
LOOK AT THAT THING.
THIS IS SOMETHING
YOU YOUNGSTERS
MIGHT BE INTERESTED IN.
BILL STARTED AS A YOUNGSTER,
I BELIEVE HE HAD THE MACHANO
AND THE LEGO
AND THE VARIOUS OTHER "O's".
AND NOW HE'S GRADUATED
UP THE LADDER--
WE'LL NOT A LADDER.
IT'S A STICK BOOM.
WHAT THEY FIND WITH THAT IS,
AS IN SO MANY EXAMPLES
OF LIFE,
YOU MECHANIZE THINGS
AND GET A MACHINE
THAT CAN DO THE WORK
OF FOUR OR FIVE MEN.
I DON'T KNOW WHO THE MEN ARE
IN THIS CASE --
NOT RIGHT MEN.
BUT YOU CAN PICK THE FRUIT
NOT JUST FROM THE UNDERNEATH,
BUT FROM THE SIDES
AND ALSO THE TOP OF THE TREE.
JUST GRAB THAT
AND... ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
NOW, IN THE MANUAL IT SAYS
DON'T GRAB THAT LEVER TOO HARD
BECAUSE IT HAS A TENDENCY
TO COME OUT, AND
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO DO
A LOT OF FRUIT-PICKING
UP IN THAT AREA.
TRY OVER BY THE BARN.
OH!
CAN YOU CLIMB--
NO HE CAN'T.
THERE WE GO!
HAROLD, THERE'S NO BOTTOM
IN THAT.
OH BOY, HE'S UP THERE.
WELL, THIS IS ANOTHER EXAMPLE
OF MACHINERY
HELPING US THROUGH LIFE.
I GUESS IT'S THE END
OF HIS SHIFT.
GOT HIM, HAROLD?
OH, LOST HIM IN THE SUN.
OH BOY.
OW!
HERE'S A STUFFED CAT FROM
WTVP-47 IN PEORIA.
(Audience laughing)
(Laughing)
GOT TOO MUCH STARCH
IN YOUR SHIRT?
GOT THE CHEATING PROBLEM
ALL STRAIGHTENED OUT
AND I'M ALL SET
FOR THE REMATCH WITH STINKY.
JUST THE TWO OF US,
EYEBALL TO EYEBALL,
WINNER TAKE ALL.
AWW, COOL!
YEAH, LIKE BRETT MAVERICK,
FRONTIER GAMBLER, HUH?
OR PAUL NEWMAN IN "THE STING"?
REMEMBER? HE PLAYED POKER
AGAINST ROBERT SHAW
IN THE TRAIN.
HE WAS HENRY GONDORF
AND HE BURPED REALLY LOUD.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU NEED?
A GOOD POKER FACE.
I DON'T HAVE ONE.
BRING IT HERE AND
LET ME POKE IT FOR YOU.
HOW ARE YOU GONNA BEAT STINKY?
YOU BEEN TAKING
POKER LESSONS?
I DON'T NEED LESSONS.
YOU DO,
BECAUSE--
OH, MAN!
YOU WERE
GONNA CHEAT!
NO, HAROLD.
HE WAS GONNA CHEAT!
IT'S NO WONDER
MY GENERATION'S SO CYNICAL.
I HOPE YOU ARE VERY PROUD
OF YOURSELF, YOUNG MAN.
GOTTA GO,
HAROLD.
YOU GOT CARDS IN YOUR PANTS!
(Audience laughing)
LOOKS LIKE A STRAIGHT FLUSH.
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO.
NO, HAROLD, NO!
FULL HOUSE.
(Audience laughing)
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW,
WHERE WE EXAMINE THOSE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO DIFFICULT.
(Audience):
"I DON'T KNOW!"
OK, JOINING MY UNCLE RED
THIS WEEK
IS HIS BEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE ROOM, LOCAL ROOFER
ARNIE DOGAN!
(Howling)
THIS WEEK'S
LETTER
GOES
AS FOLLOWS.
"DEAR EXPERTS, I HAVE A STRING
OF UNSUCCESSFUL CAREERS.
"I WAS A UREA FORMALDEHYDE
SALESMAN.
"I INVESTED MY SAVINGS IN POGS,
"THINKING THEY COULD ONLY
INCREASE IN VALUE.
"CURRENTLY, I'M A TRAVEL AGENT
FOR VALUJET.
"IS THE WHOLE WORLD
AGAINST ME OR WHAT?"
BEFORE THE WORLD'S
GONNA BE AGAINST YOU,
YOU MUST MEET MORE PEOPLE.
JUST ASK HAROLD.
HEY!
(Audience laughing)
IN MY EXPERIENCE,
THE WORLD IS NEVER AGAINST YA.
IN THE ROOFING BUSINESS,
YOU ONLY GOT
THREE NATURAL ENEMIES --
WIND, GRAVITY,
AND WET SHINGLES.
HOW IS THE LEG,
MR. DOGAN?
THEY WERE GONNA PUT
A STEEL PIN IN,
BUT I ALREADY GOT ALUMINUM
IN THERE
FROM WHEN I LANDED ON BUSTER
HADFIELD'S T.V. ANTENNA.
OHHH.
NOBODY AT DOGAN
AND SONS ROOFING
COMPLAINS THAT
THE WORLD'S AGAINST US.
WHEN MY DAD DROPPED 60 FEET
ONTO THAT FORD FAIRLANE,
HE WAS JUST GLAD
IT WAS A CONVERTIBLE.
THE DRIVER WASN'T
TOO THRILLED ABOUT IT.
NO.
NEITHER WAS HIS WIDOW.
YEAH.
IT'S A HEALTHY ATTITUDE.
YOU'RE TAKING RESPONSIBILITY
FOR LIFE.
THAT'S IT, YEAH.
I WROTE A SONG ABOUT THAT
FOR MY NEXT C.D.
YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO!
ON THE DOGAN LABEL
FROM DOGAN DISTRIBUTING.
THE ALBUM COMES OUT
WHEN WE GET
THAT ROOFING CONTRACT
AT THE COMMUNITY CENTRE.
(Clearing throat)
GOES LIKE THIS...
NO, I'VE HEARD IT.
YOU HAVEN'T HEARD THIS ONE.
THIS IS A SPECIAL NEW ONE.
WHEN YOU FEEL LIKE A TOAD
ON THE HIGHWAY OF LIFE
AND EVERYONE SEEMS LIKE
A STEEL-BELTED RADIAL
WHEN YOU'RE LYIN' THERE
SQUISHED
IN AN ASSORTMENT
OF BODY FLUIDS
HEY, AT LEAST
YOU LEFT YOUR MARK
(Laughing and applause)
THANK YOU.
(Applause)
WELL, I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE
THAT
VIDEO.
OOOH!
(Harold singing
quietly)
(Audience laughing)
THE GOOD NEWS
IS, WHATEVER GOES AROUND,
COMES AROUND.
I WON BACK EVERYTHING I LOST
IN THE POKER GAME.
SHAME, SHAME --
HOW ABOUT YOUR HONOUR?
YOU LOST THAT
WHEN YOU DECIDED TO CHEAT.
I WAS FIGHTING FIRE WITH FIRE.
NO, YOU WERE FIGHTING FIRE
WITH ACES IN
YOUR UNDERWEAR.
SHAME, SHAME!
YOU PROFITED
BY DECEIT.
I DIDN'T PROFIT, HAROLD.
I JUST BROKE EVEN,
PLUS A LITTLE BIT.
WE GOT A NEW AGREEMENT
ON CHEATING.
YOU CAN ONLY BRING
FIVE EXTRA CARDS
AND YOU GOTTA USE THEM
IN ONE HAND.
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
TOO BAD YOU FEEL BAD
ABOUT CHEATING.
I WAS GONNA GIVE YOU 10%
OF MY WINNINGS.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT, I UNDERSTAND.
NO, I'M FROWNING
ON IT.
I'M FROWNING --
THIS IS A FROWN.
10% IS VERY GENEROUS OF YOU.
REALLY?
YEAH, SO I DON'T WANT
TO BE RUDE.
HERE YOU GO.
ENJOY.
TOOTHPICKS!
YEAH, TOOTHPICKS, YEAH.
YOU'RE PLAYING
FOR TOOTHPICKS!
I THOUGHT YOU
PLAYED FOR MONEY.
YOU GOTTA HAVE MONEY
TO PLAY FOR MONEY.
TOOTHPICKS IN YOUR POCKET'S
A REAL KILLER.
OOH, THEY'RE ALL USED!
MAN, I WAS ROLLIN'.
I COULD HAVE WON
STINKY'S MATCHES, TOO,
BUT HE'S GOT THE WOOD STOVE.
DIDN'T WANT HIM TO FREEZE.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
TOOTHPICKS!
DON'T SPEND THEM ALL
ON ONE MOUTH!
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME.
IF YOU HEAR I WAS CHEATING,
IT WAS DURING POKER
SO DON'T THINK ABOUT THINGS
TO DO TO A SLEEPING MAN
WITH 12,000 TOOTHPICKS.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): ALL RISE!
UP! UP AND AT 'EM!
(Red): OK.
ALL RIGHT.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN.
I HAVE A HAPPY ANNOUNCEMENT
FOR YOU.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK, WHO WON
THE FOUR CASES OF WHISKEY
AT CHRISTMAS, IS NOW
UP AND AROUND AGAIN.