ALMOST HAD A LITTLE DOMESTIC
SITUATION A FEW MINUTES AGO.
SEE, I WANTED TO WASH
ONE OF MY VEHICLES,
BUT MY WIFE SEEMED TO FEEL
THAT WASHING THE DISHES
WAS A BETTER USE OF MY
AVAILABLE TIME AND TALENT.
IT REALLY WASN'T
MUCH OF AN ARGUMENT,
BECAUSE I GAVE IN RIGHT AWAY.
THAT'S ACTUALLY
AN OLD TRICK
THAT EVERY HIGH MILEAGE
MARRIED MAN KNOWS.
BUT THE BEAUTY
OF THE SOLUTION IS
THANKS TO THIS POWER WASHER
AND A MESH LAUNDRY BAG,
I CAN ACTUALLY WASH
THE CAR AND THE DISHES
AT THE SAME TIME.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANKS VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
WELL, THIS WEEKEND
IT'S THE BIG POSSUM LAKE
MARSH GAS FESTIVAL.
I'LL TELL YOU THE PARADE
AND THE DINNER AND THE DANCE
ARE KIND OF BORING,
BUT THE FIREWORKS
CAN BLOW THE ROOF OFF --
AT LEAST THEY DID LAST YEAR.
UNCLE RED! UNCLE RED!
UNCLE RED!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
GUESS WHAT! GUESS WHAT!
WHAT?!
I MET A GIRL!
WOW! FIRST THE MARS
SIGHTING, NOW THIS.
I'VE ASKED HER TO ACCOMPANY ME
TO THE MARSH GAS BLOWOUT.
WELL, WHAT DOES
SHE LOOK?
I MEAN, WHAT'S HER --
HOW DID YOU FOOL HER?
I MET HER ON
THE INTERNET.
I DON'T KNOW
A LOT ABOUT HER,
BUT I KNOW SHE'S
VERY PRETTY,
AND SHE'S A
VERY FAST TYPIST.
OH! AND GET THIS.
SHE JUST LIVES UP
NEAR PORT ASBESTOS.
OH, HAROLD, SHE'S
GOT THE MONEY, HUH?
HAROLD, THERE'S SOMEBODY
HERE TO SEE YOU.
[ HYSTERICAL LAUGH ]
GIRL. GIRL. GIRL!
CAN YOU TALK TO HER
FOR A MINUTE, PLEASE,
BECAUSE I HAVE TO GO
MAKE MYSELF LOOK GOOD.
WE DON'T HAVE THAT
KINDA TIME, HAROLD.
ALL RIGHT, DALTON,
LET HER IN.
[ DALTON CHUCKLING ]
MAN, OH, MAN.
C'MON IN.
GOOD LUCK.
YEAH, THANKS,
DALTON.
HELLO.
HELLO, HAROLD.
PARDON ME?
YOU'RE EVEN HANDSOMER
THAN YOUR PICTURE.
HAROLD!
OKAY, I'M ALL SET.
HELLO.
WHO'S SHE?
WHO'S HE?
RIGHT, I KNOW WHAT'S
HAPPENED HERE.
HAROLD, DID YOU PUT
A PICTURE OF ME ON
YOUR WEB PAGE?
HA! HA -- YES.
AND DID YOU PUT A
PICTURE OF SOMEBODY
ELSE ON YOUR WEB PAGE?
MMM --
YES!
I-I-I USED
MY NIECE'S PICTURE.
ALL RIGHT, HERE'S
WHAT WE GOTTA DO...
WE GOTTA GET YOUR NIECE
TOGETHER WITH HAROLD --
THE REAL HAROLD,
NOT THIS HAROLD.
AND THAT'LL SOLVE
THE PROBLEM.
WHAT'LL YOU AND I DO?
WELL,
YOU'LL GO HOME,
AND I'LL PRAY MY WIFE IS
NOT SURFIN' THE INTERNET.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S PRIZE IS A COUPON
FOR A FREE STRAY ANIMAL
AND WALL CLOCK
FROM THE POSSUM LAKE
FLEA AND TICK MARKET.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
EARS THERE, MIKE.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS TO
GET MIKE TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, MIKE, THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT KEEPS YOU IN A JAIL CELL.
CRUMMY LAWYERS.
NO, OKAY,
BUT CRUMMY OR NOT,
THE LAWYERS
ALL PASSED THE...
BUCK.
OKAY, OKAY,
IF YOU KNOW A
WOMAN DANCER,
SHE PRACTISES HER LEG
EXERCISES WITH ONE OF THESE.
OH, FIRE POLE.
OKAY, NO.
OKAY, OKAY.
A PERSON WHO MIXES
DRINKS ALL NIGHT TENDS...
TO GET A HANGOVER.
NO, OKAY. OKAY.
UM, THIS IS THE GREATEST
SURPRISE YOU'LL GET
IN A HOTEL ROOM,
IT HAS A MINI...
SKIRT.
UH, ALMOST
OUTTA TIME, RED.
YEAH, OKAY, OKAY.
OKAY, MIKE, IF SOMEBODY
WANTED TO MAKE SOMETHING
MORE DIFFICULT,
THEY RAISE THE...
BAIL.
$10,000 FOR A B&E.
WHICH I DIDN'T DO.
ONLY I FORGOT TO WIPE
MY PRINTS OFF THE CROWBAR.
THERE WE GO!
TODAY ON TALKING
ANIMALS,
LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER, ED FRID,
IS GOING TO TELL US
ALL ABOUT SCORPIONS.
NOT SCORPIONS, RED,
DEADLY SCORPIONS.
GIANT SCORPIONS!
GIANT, DEADLY,
DESERT, DEADLY SCORPIONS.
THEY'RE BIG
AND THEY'RE DEADLY
AND THEY KILL YOU.
OKAY, ED, I THINK
WE'RE GETTIN' THAT.
UH, BUT SCORPIONS AREN'T
NATIVE TO THIS PART OF
THE COUNTRY, ARE THEY?
IF THEY WERE,
WOULD I LIVE HERE?
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, GOOD.
UM, I UNDERSTAND SCORPIONS
ARE QUITE CLEAN CREATURES.
OH, GOOD FOR THEM.
UH, YEAH, OH --
SO, UM, WHAT DO
SCORPIONS EAT, ED?
EACH OTHER.
AND, UH, TERMITES,
YOU KNOW,
LITTLE TERMITES.
SO YOU DROP
TERMITES IN THERE?
YEAH.
WELL, ED, THIS IS
A WOODEN BOX.
IT'S A WOODEN --
A WOODEN -- A WOODEN --
AHHHH! WE'RE ALL
GONNA DIE!
HAROLD!
YOU KNOW, USUALLY WHEN A GUY
COMES UP TO ME AND SAYS,
"YOU'RE THE MOST CREATIVE
HANDYMAN I'VE EVER SEEN,
"HOW DO YOU COME UP
WITH ALL THE GREAT IDEAS?"
I GIVE 'EM MY
STOCK ANSWER...
STEP AWAY FROM THE VEHICLE.
BUT THIS TIME
ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW YOU CAN COME UP WITH
AN ENDLESS LIST
OF CREATIVE PROJECTS,
BECAUSE WHEN YOU'VE BEEN
MARRIED AS LONG AS I HAVE,
YOU'RE PRETTY MUCH
OUT OF IDEAS.
SO I'M ACTUALLY GOING
TO CONVERT THESE OLD BIKES
INTO A MACHINE THAT WILL
GENERATE PROJECT IDEAS,
USING ONLY THE LAWS
OF RANDOM CHANCE.
AND IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE
YOU CAN MAKE SOMETHING
BY ACCIDENT,
JUST ASK HAROLD'S PARENTS.
NOW, WHAT YOU WANNA DO IS
REPLACE THE FRONT WHEELS
WITH BACK WHEELS.
THAT WAY YOU CAN
RUN ALL FOUR TIRES
FROM THE ONE
SET OF PEDALS.
SADLY, THIS IS THE CLOSEST
MOST OF US WILL EVER GET
TO OWNING AN
ALL-WHEEL-DRIVE VEHICLE.
THE IMPORTANT THING IS TO PICK
WHEELS WITH DIFFERENT SIZED
SPROCKETS ON 'EM.
THAT'S WHAT GIVES
YOU THE RANDOM RESULTS.
IT'S KINDA LIKE BUYING
A GIFT FOR YOUR WIFE.
YOU PAY YOUR MONEY;
YOU TAKE YOUR CHANCES.
OKAY, ONCE WE GET
THE CHAIN ALL ON THERE,
OUR BIKE WHEELS
ARE READY TO BECOME
OUR WHEELS OF FORTUNE.
AND TO DO THAT, WE NEED
SOMETHING THICK AND STICKY
THAT EVERYBODY
HAS IN THEIR HOME...
NO, NOT PAT SAJAK.
NOW, ON THE FIRST WHEEL,
I PUT ALL THE DAYS OF
THE COMING WEEK
WHEN I MIGHT WANNA BUSY
MYSELF WITH A PROJECT.
BERNICE'S MOTHER
IS IN TOWN,
SO I'M GOIN' WITH ALL SEVEN.
NEXT, I WENT
THROUGH THE GARAGE,
LOOKIN' AT ALL THE DIFFERENT
COLOURS OF PAINT I HAD
IN THE HALF-EMPTY PAINT TINS,
MARGARINE TUBS AND
SAMPLE BOTTLES.
THEN I WROTE DOWN THE
NAMES OF ALL THOSE COLOURS
AND MOUNTED THEM
ON MY SECOND WHEEL.
OKAY, ON THIS ONE I WROTE
ALL THE RAW MATERIAL
I FOUND LYING AROUND MY YARD
AND THE YARDS OF MY
NEIGHBOURS WHO AREN'T HOME.
OH, BY THE WAY.
I FIND IF YOU WRITE DOWN
TWO OR MORE PIECES OF JUNK
ON EACH STRIP OF TAPE,
IT REALLY INCREASES
THE CHALLENGE LEVEL.
AND FINALLY ON
THE FOURTH WHEEL,
I WROTE DOWN THE NAMES OF A
FEW THINGS THAT NEEDED DOING,
FIXING, IMPROVING
AROUND THE HOUSE.
I GOT THEM FROM A LIST
MY WIFE HAD GIVEN ME.
I COULDN'T GET ALL OF HER
SUGGESTIONS ON THERE.
OH, AND I ALMOST FORGOT.
ON EACH HUB,
I'VE TAPED A POINTER.
THIS IS HOW WE READ THE
RESULTS FROM EACH WHEEL.
PUT THEM ALL TOGETHER,
AND WHAT YOU HAVE
IS THE HANDYMAN'S
RANDOM PROJECT PLANNER.
LET'S GIVE THIS
BABY A SPIN.
OKAY, LET'S SEE
WHAT WE GOT HERE.
ON TUESDAY, I'M GOING TO BUILD
A YELLOW, SHAG-CARPETED
BIRDFEEDER
OUT OF A MILK CRATE;
AND ON WEDNESDAY I'M INSTALLING
PURPLE KEVLAR STORM SHUTTERS
INTO THE TOOL SHED;
AND ON THURSDAY,
IT'S A TURQUOISE SPICE RACK
MADE FROM HOCKEY STICKS
AND A GARDEN HOSE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO WAX MY CAR,
USING SCUBA FLIPPERS AND A
BUNCH OF OLD KETCHUP PACKETS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
REMEMBER, WHEN YOU
MAKE ENOUGH DEPOSITS,
IT'S TIME FOR A WITHDRAWAL.
SHE'S INCREDIBLE!
SHE'S AWESOME!
SHE'S FANTASTIC!
IT'S LIKE SHE'S MADE FOR ME
OR SOMETHING, YOU KNOW?
SHE EVEN KNOWS WHAT
I'M THINKIN'.
SHE EVEN FINISHES MY --
YOUR SENTENCES?
YEAH!
AND NO ONE DOES THAT.
NO.
DOES SHE HAVE A
NAME AT ALL, HAROLD?
BONNIE.
IS THAT SHORT
FOR SOMETHING?
YEAH, BONNEVILLE.
PROBABLY CONCEIVED
IN A PONTIAC.
WELL, I ASKED HER
TO THE MARSH GAS BLOWOUT.
YOU'LL NEVER BELIEVE
WHAT SHE SAID TO ME.
LEAVE OUT THE
SWEAR WORDS, HAROLD.
SHE SAID YES!
[ APPLAUSE ]
I'M GOING WITH
A GIRL TO A DANCE.
I STILL GOT PROBLEMS.
WOULD YOU RELAX?
WOULD YOU PLEASE
JUST SETTLE DOWN,
BECAUSE I GOT PROBLEMS.
I TOLD HER I'D PICK
HER UP AT 7 O'CLOCK,
BUT I DON'T HAVE A CAR
OR A DRIVER'S LICENSE.
WELL, THAT'S
NOT A PROBLEM.
I MEAN, YOUR BICYCLE
HAS A CROSSBAR, RIGHT?
YES, BUT NO, C'MON,
DRIVE US, PLEASE.
PLEASE JUST DRIVE US
TO THE POSSUM DANCE.
PLEASE. PLEASE. PLEASE.
IN THE POSSUM VAN?
AFTER YOU'VE SAID THOSE
HURTFUL THINGS TO US
FOR SO MANY YEARS?
YES.
WELL, OKAY, HAROLD,
BUT THERE'S ONLY
TWO SEATS.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO SIT ON THE ENGINE.
OH, NO PROBLEM.
EVER SINCE PUBERTY, I FEEL
LIKE I'VE BEEN SITTING
ON THE ENGINE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red: WE WENT OUT
BEHIND THE LODGE THERE
BECAUSE WALTER HAD A
LITTLE PHOTO THING SET UP,
AND WE WANTED TO --
IT LOOKS LIKE HE
STARTED AT 20 BUCKS,
AND HE'S DOWN TO --
SO I SAID, HOW'S BUSINESS?
HE'S GOT NO
SENSE OF HUMOUR, YOU KNOW,
SO I THOUGHT,
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
SO I GOT A LOONIE
OUT THERE
AND OKAY, TAKE OUR PICTURES.
BUT HE SAYS, NO, THESE
ARE NOVELTY PICTURES.
YOU GOTTA PUT COSTUMES ON.
AW, COME ON.
HE SAYS, YOU CAN BE
LIKE A SOLDIER
OR A MARCHING GUY
OR A FOOTBALL -- YOU KNOW.
AND THEN DALTON
DOESN'T WANNA.
I SAID, COME ON.
GIVE THE GUY A BREAK.
GET IN THERE.
IT'S GONNA BE A NICE
COSTUME OF SOME KIND.
SO HE DIDN'T HAVE A LOT OF
SELECTION ON THE COSTUMES.
I GOT THE KIND OF
AN AIRLINE CAPTAIN THING.
BUT I THINK WINSTON
WAS THE REAL WINNER.
AND HE DIDN'T WANNA TAKE
THE PICTURE RIGHT THERE.
HE WANTED TO GO OVER
TO ANOTHER FIELD.
I GUESS THE LIGHT WAS
BETTER OR SOMETHING.
SO WE GO ACROSS THE STREET.
SO WHAT HE'S SAYIN' IS,
IF YOU CAN'T SEE THE CAMERA,
THE CAMERA CAN'T SEE YOU.
SO WINSTON WAS THE ONE HAVING
THE REAL PROBLEM THERE,
SO HE'S SORT OF
JUMPING UP AND --
MEANWHILE, BILL WAS
HUNTING RABBIT,
AND, UH, --
THOUGHT HE SPOTTED
THE MOTHER LODE.
WELL, THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
BILL, BILL, COME ON!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THAT'S NOT A RABBIT, BILL.
IT'S NOT A RABBIT.
HI, BILL.
I -- IT -- OH.
BILL, IT'S NOT A RABBIT.
STOP SHOOTING.
BILL, STOP IT.
BILL, NO!
OKAY, GREAT, YEAH.
NO, BILL, BILL, BILL.
IT'S WINSTON.
IT'S WINSTON
IN A RABBIT SUIT.
AND HE'S NOT
IN THE BEST MOOD EVER.
SO THEN WE FIGURE, WELL,
LET'S GET BILL TO JOIN US
FOR THE GROUP PHOTO.
WE HAVE ONE MORE COSTUME.
WE THINK IT'D BE
A PERFECT COSTUME FOR BILL.
SO WE GET HIM ALL --
AND I THINK HE'S LOOKIN'
PRETTY SPECTACULAR,
DON'T YOU?
SO NOW WE'RE ALL SET.
BUT THIS IS TAKIN'
SO DARNED LONG
THAT WALTER SAYS
HE'S LOSIN' LIGHT.
HE NEEDS TO GET SOME KIND OF A
FLASH UNIT FOR THE CAMERA.
HE'S GOT AN OLDER CAMERA,
SO IT'S GOT THE
OLDER STYLE OF FLASH.
YOU KNOW, THEY'VE GOT
THE MAGNESIUM FLASH
POWDER ON THERE.
SO HE PUTS THAT
INTO THE TRAY.
MEANWHILE, HE'S LEFT US
A LITTLE TOO LONG IN THE SUN,
AND TEMPERS ARE STARTIN'
TO FLARE A LITTLE BIT.
SO WALTER COMES OUT
TO SORT THAT OUT.
AND WINSTON FIGURES,
YOU KNOW, IT'D BE KINDA FUNNY
TO PUT A LITTLE MORE FLASH
POWDER INTO THE TRAY.
SO HE GOES BACK AND
THINGS ARE SETTLING DOWN.
SO YOU KNOW,
DALTON GOES BACK,
AND DALTON'S FIGURING,
YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD BE FUNNY?
IF I PUT A LITTLE MORE FLASH
POWDER INTO THE TRAY.
AND THEN DALTON
COMES BACK TO JOIN.
NOW WE'RE ALL SET,
BUT THEN WOULDN'T YOU KNOW IT,
BILL SLIPS OFF.
AND BILL'S THINKIN',
YEAH, YOU GUESSED IT.
THE WHOLE JAR.
OKAY, SO THEN BILL
GETS BACK INTO THE --
WHY DON'T YOU SKIP?
THERE YOU GO.
AND NOW WE'RE ALL SET.
PROBABLY SOME OF YOU AMATEUR
PHOTOGRAPHERS HAVE ALWAYS
WONDERED WHAT IT'D BE LIKE
IF YOU USED WAY TOO MUCH
FLASH POWDER.
WELL, WE'RE GOING TO
SOLVE THAT MYSTERY
FOR YOU RIGHT NOW.
[ APPLAUSE ]
LET ROTHSCHILD'S TAKE CARE
OF YOUR SEPTIC SYSTEM,
BECAUSE YOUR WASTE IS
A TERRIBLE THING TO MIND.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, WE
INTERRUPT THE RED GREEN SHOW
SO THAT I MAY BRING YOU
THE FOLLOWING IMPORTANT
ENVIRONMENTAL MESSAGE.
GREETINGS CAMPERS.
RANGER GORD HERE WITH ANOTHER
ONE OF MY PATENTED...
HOW MANY TIMES HAVE YOU BEEN
OUT ON A ONE-HORSE OPEN SLEIGH
WITH A LOAD OF PROPS FROM
YOUR OLD ANIMATED CARTOON
WHEN THIS HAPPENS?
AH! GORD! GORD! GORD!
LOOK! GORD! GORD! GORD!
WELL, I DON'T REALLY
HAVE TO LOOK, LITLE RED.
I KNOW THAT WE ARE BEING
PURSUED BY A PACK OF
RAVENOUS WOLVES.
AND UNLESS WE
LIGHTEN THE SLEIGH,
THEY'RE GOING TO BE ALL
OVER US LIKE COUGARS
AT CLOSING TIME.
AH! HURRY UP,
RANGER GORD!
THEY'RE GAINING ON US.
HM. I DON'T KNOW.
I'M GOING TO NEED
ALL THIS STUFF.
HM. I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I CAN SPARE.
AH, GEE,
I DON'T KNOW.
HOW ABOUT THESE
FOR STARTERS?
THOSE? THOSE WERE
MY MOM'S, LITTLE RED.
LISTEN,
BOYS AND GIRLS,
IT'S NEVER A GOOD IDEA
TO MAKE IMPORTANT DECISIONS
WHEN YOU'RE UNDER
A LOT OF STRESS.
LUCKILY, I EARLIER MADE
A LIST OF ALL THE CARGO
IN ORDER OF IMPORTANCE,
FROM MOST TO LEAST.
[ LITTLE HAROLD AND
LITTLE RED SCREAMING ]
SO REMEMBER, KIDS,
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO OUTRUN A WOLF.
JUST DROP SOMETHING THE WOLF
WILL FIND INTERESTING ENOUGH
TO STOP AND SMELL.
Little Harold: AH, UNCLE RED,
HE'S NOT GOING TO EAT ME.
OR SIMPLY MARK
AS THEIR TERRITORY.
[ WOLVES HOWLING
AND URINATING ]
Little Harold:
HEY! CUT THAT OUT!
[ HEARTY CHUCKLE ]
COME ON, HAROLD.
WE'RE READY TO GO HERE.
Harold: COMING!
MAN, I GAVE UP WAITING
FOR HAROLD THERE.
HE'S BEEN IN THE
SHOWER FOR SEVEN HOURS.
WE EITHER NEED A SECOND
BATHROOM OR A CLOSER TREE.
SO I SAID
THE HECK WITH IT.
I WENT UP IN THE POSSUM VAN AND
PICKED UP BONNIE ON MY OWN.
SO AS SOON AS HAROLD'S READY,
WE'RE GOOD TO GO.
OH, BOY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, I'M ALL SET.
SHOULD WE GO PICK UP BONNIE?
I'VE ALREADY
DONE THAT, HAROLD.
I CAN CERTAINLY SEE
WHAT YOU LIKE ABOUT HER.
SHE'S OUT THERE WAITING
IN THE POSSUM VAN RIGHT NOW.
WHAT?!
YEAH.
HOW RUDE IS THAT?
WE HAVE SOMETHING WE
WOULD LIKE TO ASK
YOU TOGETHER.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
OH, BONNIE, SWEETHEART!
CAN YOU COME
IN HERE A MINUTE, PLEASE?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW
TO TREAT A LADY, DO YOU?
THIS IS A MISTAKE,
HAROLD.
[ APPLAUSE ]
SO, UH,
HOW DO WE LOOK?
LIKE A PERFECT
COUPLE.
YOU'RE GOING TO SAVE
A FORTUNE ON MIRRORS,
HAROLD.
I'M PRETTY EXCITED.
KNOW WHY? KNOW WHY? KNOW WHY?
JUST HAD YOUR
FIRST COFFEE?
NO!
THIS IS MY FIRST DATE.
UM, BONNIE.
UH, THIS IS FOR YOU.
OH, HAROLD,
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
YOU PIN IT ON ME.
UH, PERHAPS, BONNIE,
YOU WOULD LIKE TO
DO IT FOR YOURSELF.
OKAY,
WE'RE GOOD TO GO.
WHAT TIME DO YOU WANT
ME TO PICK YOU GUYS UP?
I USUALLY AM
ASLEEP BY TEN.
MR. GREEN.
YEAH?
HAROLD AND I WERE WONDERING
IF MAYBE WE COULD DRIVE
OURSELVES?
I'VE GOT MY LICENSE.
WELL, I DUNNO.
THE POSSUM VAN IS
A PRETTY BIG RIG.
UNCLE RED, BONNIE IS
A LICENSED COMMERCIAL
TRUCK DRIVER.
YEAH, SHE DRIVES AN
18-WHEELER FOR PORT
ASBESTOS CARTAGE.
WELL, HEY, GREAT.
HEY, GO FOR IT.
I ALMOST SAW UP
YOUR SKIRT.
[ TALKING AT ONCE ]
OKAY?
ALL RIGHT,
YOU GO HAVE FUN.
DON'T DO ANYTHING
I WOULDN'T DO.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, IF MY
WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
HAROLD HAS A GIRLFRIEND.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
SERIOUS THEY ARE,
BUT IF THEY EVER
GET MARRIED AND HAVE KIDS,
IT'S THE END OF
THE WORLD AS WE KNOW IT.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND LOVER BOY,
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
MEETING'S COMING TO ORDER.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
WELL, MEN, WE'VE ALL
HEARD THE STORY
THAT THERE'S A MAN FOR
EVERY WOMAN IN THIS WORLD
AND VICE VERSA.
AND TODAY WE HAVE PROVED THAT
BEYOND A SHADOW OF A DOUBT.
I DON'T MISS HIM EITHER.