[quirky upbeat music]
[gunshots]
>> WE ARE ROLLING AND RECORDING.
HIT THE LIGHTS AND TURN ON YOUR
VCRs AND SIT BACK.
IT'S THE SHOW THE CRITICS SAID
COULDN'T BE DONE.
WOULDN'T BE DONE.
AND SHOULDN'T BE DONE.
WHICH HURT US, I JUST WANT YOU
TO KNOW THAT, WHEN YOU SAID
THINGS LIKE THAT.
BUT WE'RE HERE TO PROVE THEM
CRITICS WRONG.
AND THAT'S TOUGH TO DO.
GRANTED.
AND HERE'S THE PROOF HIMSELF.
THE MAN OF THE HALF-HOUR.
MY UNCLE, THE STAR OF
THE RED GREEN SHOW, RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU, HAROLD.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANKS FOR TUNING IN.
HAROLD'S RIGHT, I'M THE PROOF,
AND HE'S THE PUDDING.
WE'VE GOT A HECK OF A SHOW
FOR YOU TODAY.
WE'VE GOT A LIST OF GUESTS AS
LONG AS YOUR ARM AND TWICE
AS MUCH FUN.
YOU'VE ALREADY MET HAROLD, AND
YOU'VE PROBABLY MADE SOME KIND
OF A JUDGMENT ON HIM, AND MY
GUESS IS THAT YOU'RE RIGHT.
ANYWAY, WE HAD A HECK OF A TIME
AT THE LODGE YESTERDAY.
STINKY PETERSON DECIDED THAT
WE'RE USING WAY TOO MUCH
GASOLINE, WHICH IS EXPENSIVE,
IN THE BOAT, AND THAT WE SHOULD
SWITCH TO AN ALTERNATE KIND
OF FUEL AND PUT A WASHROOM
IN THE RIG, ALL AT THE
SAME TIME.
BUT BUSTER HADFIELD WANTED TO GO
WITH THE SOLAR-POWERED...
>> EXCUSE ME, UNCLE RED, UNCLE
RED, IS THIS GONNA BE ANOTHER
ONE OF YOUR STRANGE STORIES
ABOUT WHAT YOU AND YOUR BUDDIES
DID?
IT ALWAYS ENDS UP WITH PERSONAL
INJURY AND PRIVATE PROPERTY
AND WILDLIFE DAMAGE.
>> WELL, THIS IS A VIGNETTE
OF WHAT HAPPENS AT THE LODGE,
HAROLD.
THAT'S ALL.
>> WELL, YEAH, OKAY, OAKY, YES,
WE COULD GO THAT ROUTE.
OR WE COULD JUST GO, LIKE,
RIGHT INTO THE NEXT SEGMENT,
RIGHT?
BECAUSE THAT WOULD BE GOOD.
YOU KNOW, WE CAN JUST DO THAT,
BE AN ELECTRONIC TRANSITION.
LIKE THAT.
HA-HA-HA.
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT THE VIEWERS
WANT.
I MEAN, THAT'S, YOU KNOW,
WHAT THEY PREFER.
>> THAT THING MAKES ME CARSICK,
HAROLD.
I WANT TO JUST TELL MY STORY.
>> OKAY, JUST SAYING IT'S TV,
YOU KNOW, AND PEOPLE LIKE TV.
IT'S BASED ON MOVING.
YOU KNOW, MOVING IMAGES,
MOVING PICTURES.
>> MOVING BOWELS, OKAY?
>> MESSAGES IN THE MEDIUM.
THAT'S WHAT MARSHAL DILLON SAID.
NOW, IS THERE ANY REASON WE
CAN'T GO TO THE NEXT SEGMENT?
>> I WANT TO TELL MY STORY ABOUT
THE BOAT.
>> OH, THAT'S A GOOD REASON.
[folksy guitar and spoons music plays]
>>  STRONG MAN JACK
WAS A HELL OF A MAN
IF ANYONE CAN LIFT SOMETHING
STRONG MAN CAN
I REMEMBER ONE DAY
JUST FOR A PRANK
JACK TRIED TO LIFT
THE HOLDING TANK
HE STRAINED AND HE PULLED
WITH ALL HIS MIGHT
AND THEN THERE WAS A LOUD POP
AND HIS SPLEEN COME OUT
THROUGH ONE OF HIS BODY ORIFICES
AND DAMN NEAR KILLED THE GUY.
THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
GONNA SHOW YOU HOW TO CHANGE
A HEADLIGHT.
AND I KNOW--I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING.
EVERYBODY KNOWS HOW TO CHANGE.
WELL, THEY DON'T.
THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE DON'T
KNOW HOW TO CHANGE A HEADLIGHT,
AND IT'S SOMETHING YOU CAN DO
YOURSELF.
AND NOT ONLY DO YOU SAVE MONEY,
BUT IT GIVES YOU A FEELING OF
SELF-RELIANCE, 'CAUSE, YOU
KNOW, YOU CAN'T TRUST ANYONE.
NOW, THIS HERE IS BILL SMITH'S
CAR, AND HE TOLD ME HE'S GOT A
HEADLIGHT BURNT OUT,
AND SO, I THOUGHT I'D JUST,
YOU KNOW, KIND OF DO HIM
A FAVOR AND CHANGE
THE HEADLIGHT.
I MIGHT CHARGE HIM FIVE BUCKS,
YOU KNOW.
SO...
THE SCREWDRIVER'S NOT BIG
ENOUGH.
THE SCREWDRIVERS ON THESE, I
SHOULD SAY, THE SCREWS ON THESE
ARE WAY BACK IN THERE.
BUT, YOU KNOW...
WHO THE HECK DESIGNS
THESE THINGS?
PROBABLY MECHANICS.
I CAN'T SEE IF THE SCREW IS A
FLATHEAD OR A ROBERTSON, OR A--
I CAN'T SEE WHAT KIND IT IS.
SO--OKAY.
WE'LL JUST TRY ANOTHER METHOD
HERE.
I THINK THIS WILL JUST POP
RIGHT OFF HERE.
GET THAT IN THERE.
TAKE THE OTHER SIDE.
UH...
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO NOW IS,
IT'S THE WIRING I GUESS,
THAT'S CATCHING THAT IN THERE,
AND WE'LL JUST USE THE SPECIAL
TOOL THAT I KEEP IN MY CLOSET.
SOME METAL OR SOMETHING CAUGHT
BACK IN HERE.
OH, THAT'S--ALL RIGHT.
I THINK, YOU KNOW, THE WIRING IS
THE THING THAT'S MESSING
THIS UP, SO WE'LL JUST CLIP
THAT OUT OF THERE.
YOU KNOW, THESE NEW CARS, THEY
GOT SO MUCH WIRING IN THEM.
IT'S JUST MORE THINGS
TO GO WRONG.
YOU KNOW, WHAT'S JUST OCCURRING
TO ME, I THINK ONE OF THESE
MODERN CARS, THIS IS THE TYPE
WHERE THE HOOD--THE HEADLIGHT
COMES OUT FROM BEHIND,
FROM OUT IN THE BACK,
AND SO WHAT YOU NEED TO DO IS,
YOU NEED TO OPEN THE HOOD.
[buzzing]
UH, I'LL TRY THIS.
crash!
NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, NOW I THINK THINGS ARE
GONNA GO A LITTLE BETTER NOW.
FOR GOD'S SAKE.
UH, OH--SAFETY.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, YEAH, I CAN GET HER
OUT FROM THE INSIDE HERE,
BUT I'M GONNA HAVE TO TAKE A FEW
THINGS OUT TO GET OUT OF THERE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK MORE WITH A
LOT MORE FUN AND THE REST OF
THE STORY ABOUT MY
WIND-POWERED BOAT.
>> OH, GREAT, SO NOW YOU GOT
LIKE A CHOICE OF FUN
OR THE STORY.
>> "IT IS SUMMER.
YOU RUN DOWN THE BEACH
AND EMBRACE THE SURF.
THE OCEAN RESPONDS WITH A HUGE
WAVE THAT REMOVES YOUR TRUNKS.
THE FIRST BRUSH WITH
SUMMER LOVE.
AND CRAYFISH."
NOW, AS I WAS SAYING BEFORE I
WAS ELECTRONICALLY ASSAULTED, WE
WANTED TO BUILD A SOLAR-POWERED
BOAT, SO WE GOT A FEW OF THEM
SOLAR PANELS, AND WE WENT AROUND
THE LODGE HERE AND COLLECTED UP
ALL THE OLD CAR BATTERIES--
IT CAME TO ABOUT 95--
AND WE HOOKED THEM UP TO ONE
OF THEM LITTLE ELECTRIC
TROLLING MOTORS.
AND THEN WE WENT OUT, A BUNCH OF
US, FOR SOME NIGHT FISHING,
BUT IT DIDN'T WORK OUT ALL
THAT WELL.
AND WE SUDDENLY REALIZED THAT--
AND I GUESS THE SOLAR THING HAS
GOT, YOU KNOW, SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE SUN.
SO AS WE WERE PADDLING BACK,
WE THOUGHT MAYBE WE SHOULD
SWITCH OVER TO
A TIDAL-POWERED BOAT.
BUT THEN THE LAKE IS REALLY NOT
ALL THAT BIG, AND BESIDES, NONE
OF US HAS REALLY ANY IDEA WHAT
TIDAL-POWER IS.
SO WE DECIDED TO GO WITH
WIND POWER.
IT SEEMED LIKE A HECK OF A GOOD
IDEA, AND THE FIRST STEP WOULD
BE TO GET OURSELVES A WINDMILL.
>> A WINDMILL?
I MEAN, YOU JUST WANT, LIKE,
A WIND-POWERED BOAT.
YOU GET A WINDMILL?
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GET, LIKE,
A SAIL.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, A SAIL?
>> NO, WE HAD TO HAVE
A WINDMILL, BECAUSE A BOAT
HAS TO HAVE A MOTOR--
FOR A MAN, OKAY, HAROLD?
I MEAN, SAILING IS FOR WIMPS.
YOU KNOW, A BUNCH OF GUYS IN
THOSE LITTLE WHITE SHORTS AND
SNEAKERS, YOU KNOW.
>> I DON'T KNOW, UNCLE RED,
THAT'S NOT A VERY NICE THING TO
SAY, TO CLASSIFY PEOPLE
LIKE THAT.
I'M SURE THERE'S SOME VERY NICE
PEOPLE WHO HAVE SAILBOATS.
>> NAME THREE, HAROLD.
>> UM, SIR FRANCIS DRAKE,
MAGELLAN, AND MY HERO,
TED TURNER, THE MAN
WHO COLORIZED AMERICA.
TED, THIS ONE'S FOR YOU.
[laughs]
>> WHAT ABOUT MY BOAT STORY?
>> WE SAILED AWAY FROM IT.
[laughs]
>> YEAH, AND I'LL TELL YOU
SOMETHING, HAP.
FISHING HAS GOT TO BE THE MOST
RELAXING THING THERE IS.
>> YEAH, THAT'S FOR SURE.
I USED TO DO A LOT OF FISHING
WHEN I WORKED ON THE RANCH.
JUST ON THE LINES, YOU KNOW.
>> WHAT RANCH WAS THAT?
>> OH, THE CIRCLE "K" BAR,
DOUBLE "R," INVERTED AMPERSAND.
>> AROUND HERE, HAP?
>> NO, NO.
NO, THAT WAS KENYA.
THAT WAS YEARS AGO.
I CAN'T REMEMBER THE OWNER'S
NAME NOW.
BIG FELLA.
AUSTRALIAN.
NO.
AUSTRIAN.
OR AFGHANI OR SOMETHING.
>> WHAT KIND OF CATTLES YOU HAVE
DOWN THERE?
DID YOU REMEMBER?
>> NO CATTLE.
COWS ARE CONSIDERED HOLY ANIMALS
OVER IN KENYA.
>> NO, NO, I THINK THAT'S INDIA,
HAP.
>> OH, KENYA WAS THE SAME WAY
FOR A WHILE.
A BIG INDIAN POPULATION
OVER THERE.
ANYWAY, WE RAISED TIGERS.
THAT WAS TOUGH WORK.
>> YOU'RE TELLING ME THAT YOU
LOOKED AFTER A HERD OF TIGERS?
>> IT WASN'T A BIG HERD,
200 OR 300 HEAD,
BUT IT WAS A HANDFUL,
ROPING AND BRANDING THEM.
IT WAS VIOLENT WORK.
RODEOS WERE NOTHING BUT
A BLOODBATH.
>> WELL, HAP, THAT SOUNDS LIKE A
TERRIBLE WAY TO MAKE A LIVING.
>> YEAH, I HAD THE WORST OF IT.
I HAD TO TRAIN TIGERS FOR
THE CIRCUS.
I HAD TO TEACH THEM TO TAKE
A MAN'S HEAD IN THEIR MOUTH
WITHOUT BITING IT OFF.
YOU KNOW, I COVERED MY FACE
WITH HORSERADISH.
WORKED LIKE A CHARM.
ALTHOUGH MY EYES WERE BLOODSHOT
FOR TWO YEARS.
>> HAP, WHERE EXACTLY WAS THIS
RANCH IN KENYA?
>> OH, IT'S ALL CLOSED DOWN NOW.
YOU KNOW, SAME OLD STORY.
RANCHERS AGAINST THE FARMERS,
YOU KNOW.
THAT'S A NYLON FARM NOW.
>> OH, NO, NO, NO, NYLON DOESN'T
COME FROM A FARM.
IT'S FROM OIL.
>> WELL, YOU COULD BE RIGHT.
MAYBE I'M THINKING NACRON
OR ORLON OR SOMETHING.
>> WELL, YOU'RE THINKING
OF SOMETHING, THAT'S FOR SURE,
HAP.
[grunting]
ALL RIGHT, GET THAT OUT
OF THE WAY.
WINDSHIELD WASHER.
[grunting]
OKAY, NOW, AS LONG AS WE
REMEMBER WHAT ORDER THIS STUFF
COME OUT, WE'LL BE FINE.
NO, I STILL CAN'T GET HER.
HMM.
[clears throat]
YEAH, YOU KNOW THE SAYING WE GOT
AT THE LODGE: IF AT FIRST YOU
DON'T SUCCEED,
SWITCH TO POWER TOOLS.
[mechanical whirring]
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING,
I'M GONNA CHARGE BILL TEN BUCKS.
SHE'S COMING. SHE'S COMING.
YEAH, SHE'S COMING.
SHE'S COMING!
OH, YEAH.
ALMOST GOT HER THERE.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
SHE'S COMING.
SHE'S COMING, ALL RIGHT.
NO PROBLEM.
[groaning]
ALL RIGHT, NOW, WHAT WE'VE DONE
HERE IS, WE'VE FREED UP
THE PLUG, SO I'LL JUST GET
A REPLACEMENT BULB.
POP THAT IN.
WE'RE ALL SET.
NOW, JUST GIVE THAT A TRY
AND SEE HOW IT LOOKS.
PERFECT.
OH.
WELL, I GUESS THIS WAS
THE BURNED OUT HEADLIGHT.
WELL, IT WON'T TAKE AS LONG NOW,
'CAUSE WE KNOW HOW TO DO IT.
AND I CHARGED BILL, I THINK.
200 TO 300 BUCKS FOR THIS.
ANYWAY, TILL NEXT TIME,
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
>> OH, GEE, UNCLE RED, GREAT.
UM, JUST IN THE NICK OF TIME.
'CAUSE--OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
SPEAKING OF NICKS, I GOT THIS
LETTER FRO A VIEWER HERE,
AND HE WANTS TO KNOW ABOUT
YOUR NEW NICKNAME.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD A NEW
NICKNAME.
NOBODY TELLS ME ANYTHING
AROUND HERE.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD A NEW
NICKNAME.
YOU GOT A NEW NICKNAME?
WHAT'S YOUR NEW NICKNAME?
>> I TOLD YOU ALL ABOUT IT,
HAROLD.
I'VE HAD IT FOR MONTHS NOW.
IT'S ON THE INSIDE OF THE TRUCK.
>> BIRD DROPPINGS?
HEY, THAT IS A GOOD NICKNAME.
>> HAROLD, I GOT THE TRUCK
PAINTED LIKE A POSSUM.
WE HAVE POSSUM ON ALL
OUR STATIONARY.
HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED THAT?
WE'VE EVEN GOT A POSSUM RIGHT
HERE ON OUR SHOW CRESTS.
SO WHAT DO YOU SUPPOSE MY NEW
NICKNAME IS?
>> STUPID?
>> IT'S "POSSUM," HAROLD.
>> STUPID'S BETTER.
I MEAN, IF YOU WANT A NAME THAT
PEOPLE ARE GONNA USE.
AND WHAT'S SO GREAT ABOUT
A POSSUM ANYWAY?
>> I LIKE POSSUMS, HAROLD.
THEY MOVE SLOW, AND WHEN THEY'RE
PROVOKED OR DISTURBED OR ANNOYED
OR ANYTHING,
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY DO?
>> STING?
NO, THEY BITE?
NO, NO, THEY CLAW, RIGHT?
THEY CLAW.
NO, NO, THEY SPIT.
THEY SPIT POISON LIKE A COBRA
OR SOMETHING.
YOU SPIT A LOT, UNCLE RED.
THAT'D BE A GREAT NICKNAME
FOR YOU.
SPITTIN' POSSUM GREEN.
>> I DON'T SPIT, HAROLD.
>> NO, I THOUGHT YOU...
>> POSSUMS ARE WAY TOO SMART
FOR THAT.
YEAH, WHEN THEY'RE CORNERED,
WHEN THEY'RE THREATENED,
WHEN THEIR LIFE'S ON THE LINE,
THEY JUST LIE PERFECTLY STILL.
THEY PRETEND THEY'RE DEAD.
THE OTHER ANIMAL THINKS THEY'RE
DEAD AND LEAVES THEM ALONE,
'CAUSE AN ANIMAL WILL NOT TOUCH
A DEAD ANIMAL.
I THINK IT'S THE SMELL
OR SOMETHING.
>> GEEZ, UNCLE RED, POSSUM
SOUNDS A BIT LIKE A COWARD.
I MEAN, HE GETS PARALYZED WITH
TERROR AND FEAR IN THE EVENT
OF AN ATTACK,
INCAPABLE OF MAKING A DECISION
WHEN HE NEEDS IT MOST.
BOY, IF YOU ASK ME, LIKE, OKAY,
I'M NOT A ZOOLOGIST OR
ANYTHING--
GRANTED, I FAILED SCIENCE TWICE.
GOOD POINT.
BUT AGAIN, IF YOU ASK ME,
I THINK IT'S A PRETTY WUSSY
ANIMAL.
THAT'S A DUMB NICKNAME, POSSUM.
BOY, FREEZES OFTEN IN THE EVENT
OF EMERGENCY.
WHEN HE NEEDS A DECISION MOST,
HE CAN'T DO IT.
[laughs]
THAT'S A PRETTY STUPID CHOICE.
WELL, LET'S GO TO OUR NEXT
SEGMENT.
PRETTY STUPID CHOICE, THE WHOLE
POSSUM THING, RIGHT?
UNCLE RED, WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT THE WHOLE POSSUM THING,
THE NICKNAME?
UNCLE RED?
YOO-HOO?
YOU OKAY?
IS HE DEAD OR SOMETHING?
>> BILL'S ACTUALLY TRYING TO
HELP ME OUT WITH A PROBLEM.
I'D LOST MY WATCH, AND HE
BROUGHT A METAL DETECTOR TO...
YEAH, THAT'S ABOUT AS MUCH
HELP AS BILL USUALLY IS,
BUT THIS UNIT HERE, HE'S GOT THE
HEADPHONES AND THE BATTERY PACK.
AND HE FLIPS HER ON.
AND IT FINDS PIECES OF METAL
IN THE GROUND.
LIKE, THERE, YOU SEE THAT
TIN CAN WAS PICKING IT UP.
AND BILL HAD TO PICK UP
THE CAN--OH, MY GOD.
OH.
>> OOH!
>> THAT WOULD GET YOUR
ATTENTION, WOULDN'T IT?
THE THING I HAVE AGAINST THE
METAL DETECTORS IS THAT PEOPLE
WALK AROUND WITH THEM, THEY LOOK
A LITTLE ON THE DORKY SIDE,
AND I REALLY DIDN'T WANT TO BE
WITH BILL, BUT I WANTED TO GET
MY WATCH BACK TOO.
OH, I'M GETTING A LITTLE
IMPATIENT WITH HIM.
I GOT TO ADMIT.
I REALLY DIDN'T FEEL LIKE
SPENDING THE REST OF THE SUMMER
DOING THIS.
BUT HE WAS GETTING SOMETHING.
HE WAS GETTING CLOSE.
YOU COULD HEAR IT.
OH, FOR GOD'S SAKE.
YEAH.
UH-HUH.
I'D AGREE WITH THAT, BILL.
ANYWAY, BACK AT IT AGAIN.
HE'S STARTING TO PICK UP
A LITTLE SOMETHING,
SO HE SAYS ANYWAY.
IT SEEMS TO BE AROUND ME
SOMEWHERE.
OH, OH, OH, OH--
IT WAS HIS BATTERY BELT.
SO WHAT HE DOES IS, HE TELLS ME
TO AND GET AN EXTENSION CORD.
HE UNPLUGS THE BATTERY PACK.
HE'S GONNA DROP THAT.
AND WE'RE GONNA RUN IT RIGHT OFF
OF THE NORMAL LODGE CURRENT,
WHICH IS I THINK 98 VOLTS
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
BUT IT'S WAY TOO MUCH FOR A--
OH, AND THEN SHE JUST STARTED
TO HUM, YOU KNOW, AND IT JUST
DIDN'T SOUND RIGHT TO ME,
BUT HE FELT IT WOULD WORK.
I HAD A METAL FLY IN MY PANTS.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED THERE.
BUT IT WAS GETTING BILL
OUT OF CONTROL.
AND SUDDENLY IT WAS--
BILL, BILL, BILL, BILL, BILL.
STILL QUITE A BIT OF METAL LEFT
IN THE VAN, SO I SAVED HIS LIFE
RIGHT THERE.
>> OH.
>> HE'S ALL RIGHT.
HE'S ALL RIGHT.
SO I FIGURED HE GOT HIMSELF
BACK TOGETHER AGAIN.
I SHOULD BE ABLE TO, YOU KNOW,
TO PLUG IT BACK IN.
I DIDN'T SEE HIM--SORRY, BILL.
SO THIS TIME HE DECIDES HE'S
GONNA--HE'S JUST GONNA HOLD
HIS GROUND.
HE'S GONNA DIG IN.
IT'S TOUGH.
IT'S TOUGH FOR AN OLDER
GENTLEMAN, AND HE'S GONNA DIG
RIGHT IN, AND NOW STUFF STARTS
MOVING ACROSS THE...
WELL, HE HAD A LOT OF METAL
THINGS AROUND THE LODGE.
WELL, MAYBE THINGS THAT WE DON'T
HAVE A SPECIFIC USE FOR TODAY,
YOU KNOW, OR NECESSARILY
TOMORROW.
BUT CERTAINLY WITHIN THE NEXT
200 TO 300 YEARS, WE'D HAVE
USE FOR ALL OF THIS STUFF.
INTERESTING THING HERE WAS THAT,
YOU KNOW, I'D FORGOTTEN WHERE
THAT BIKE WAS.
AND THAT MAY AFFECT TRAFFIC,
THAT ONE.
BUT WHAT HE WAS DOING WAS REALLY
COLLECTING ALL OF THE STUFF INTO
ONE AREA, AND THAT WAS DONE.
THAT WAS ENOUGH.
AND HE'S OKAY.
AND THEN THE GREAT NEWS IS,
SON OF A GUN, HE ACTUALLY FOUND
MY WATCH.
SO, YOU KNOW, JUST WHEN YOU
LEAST EXPECT IT.
SO, COME ON, BILL.
LUNCHTIME.
THIS WAS MORE OF A CHALLENGE
THAN FINDING THE WATCH, I THINK.
IT KIND OF LOOKS A BIT LIKE
THE C.N. TOWER.
OH, OH, OH, BILL.
NO, HE'S ALL RIGHT.
"IT IS SUMMER.
YOU'VE EATEN SO MANY SALADS,
YOU'RE TURNING INTO A RABBIT.
IT WAS YOUR WIFE'S IDEA."
HOW ARE THINGS GOING IN SCHOOL
THESE DAYS, HAROLD?
>> OH, NOT TOO BAD.
I'M HAVING A LITTLE BIT OF
TROUBLE WITH MY DRIVER EDUCATION
COURSE.
[cow moos]
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS IN
SCHOOL, WE DIDN'T EVEN HAVE
DRIVER EDUCATION.
>> WELL, I WOULD HAVE ASSUMED
THAT.
I JUST THINK THOUGH, IF YOU HAVE
TO TAKE ONE OF THESE PRO-DRIVING
COURSES TO GET A REDUCED
INSURANCE RATE OF LESS THAN
$4,000 A YEAR,
YOU SHOULDN'T BE FORCED
TO HAVE THREE OTHER STUDENTS
IN THE CAR WITH YOU.
[water splashes]
>> YOU JUST CAN'T TAKE THE
PRESSURE FROM THE OTHER
PASSENGERS, THAT'S ALL.
>> YEAH, BUT STILL, I MEAN, THE
BIGGEST PROBLEM IS I CAN'T HEAR
THE INSTRUCTOR OVER ALL THE
SCREAMING.
TEENAGERS CAN REALLY SCREAM
WHEN THEY'RE TERRIFIED.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
SCREAMING ABOUT.
NO, I'M NOT GONNA KILL ANYBODY
UNLESS THEY START HITTING THINGS
A LOT HARDER THAN I HAVE BEEN
SO FAR.
[glass shatters]
>> DOES THE SCHOOL SUPPLY THE
CAR FOR THE DRIVER'S LICENSE?
>> NOT ANYMORE.
>> SO YOU'RE USING YOUR DAD'S
CAR NOW?
>> NOT ANYMORE.
>> FORGET IT.
>> PLEASE.
>> NO.
>> PLEASE, COME ON.
>> PLEASE.
>> NO.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK
WITH LOTS MORE.
>> AND THE MORE, THE MERRIER.
[laughs]
THEY SAY THAT SOMETIMES ABOUT
THINGS WHEN THERE'S MORE OF IT.
>> "IT IS SUMMER.
IN THE SHADE OF AN APPLE TREE,
YOU RELAX WITH A MINT JULEP
OR NINE.
SUMMER IS NO TIME FOR STRESS.
YOU CASUALLY FORGET YOUR
AUNT'S BIRTHDAY.
SHE THANKS YOU."
SO I WANTED TO TELL YOU HOW THE
WIND-POWERED BOAT TURNED OUT.
WE MANAGED TO FIND AN OLD
WINDMILL AT A MINIATURE GOLF
COURSE THAT WAS GOING OUT OF
BUSINESS, AND IT HAS A NICE
BIG BLADE ON HERE THERE
AND A SMOOTH AXLE,
AND ONCE WE DUMPED THE 400
GOLF BALLS OUT OF HER,
SHE WASN'T THAT HARD TO CARRY.
SO WE BOLTED IT RIGHT ONTO
THE BOAT, AND THEN WE PATCHED
ALL THE SCREW HOLES AND THE
MISTAKES, AND THEN WE RAN
A CHAIN FROM THE WINDMILL
DOWN TO THE GENERATOR
WE RIPPED OUT OF MY STUDEBAKER,
AND THEN WE HAD THAT GENERATOR
HOOKED UP TO AN ELECTROPLATE
THAT WENT RIGHT INTO A BIG TANK
OF DISTILLED WATER,
AND SO THAT WOULD GET
HYDROGEN THERE.
AND THEN WE HAD A SECOND
WINDMILL TO BLOW THE HYDROGEN
INTO THE OUTBOARD MOTOR,
BUT THEN WITH ALL THAT STUFF IN
THERE WAS REALLY JUST ROOM FOR
ABOUT ONE PERSON, BUT, HEY,
IT WAS A PROTOTYPE.
YOU KNOW, AND NONE OF THE GUYS
HAD MUCH FAITH IN THE
MECHANISM WORK, BUT IT
SURPRISED EVERYONE BY SINKING.
ANYWAY, I GUESS THE WIND-POWERED
BOAT JUST STAYS AS A DREAM FOR
A WHILE, BUT, HEY, IT KILLED OFF
A DAY, SO IT WASN'T ALL BAD.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
THE SHOW TONIGHT, I'M GONNA BE
COMING STRAIGHT HOME.
IF YOU WANT ME TO WAKE YOU, JUST
TIE A RIBBON AROUND THE BEDROOM
DOORKNOB.
SO TILL NEXT TIME, ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD AND THE WHOLE
GANG UP HERE AT THE LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]