WOMEN ARE USUALLY
SMARTER THAN MEN,
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO
ORGANIZING THEIR CLOTHES,
WE COULD TEACH THEM A THING
OR TWO ABOUT HOW TO STORE
YOUR WARDROBE...
BY JUST THROWING
IT ON THE FLOOR.
YOU ALWAYS KNOW
WHERE EVERYTHING IS
AND IT SAVES WEAR AND TEAR
ON THE LINOLEUM.
BUT, EVEN THE MOST ORGANIZED GUY
COULD USE A LITTLE HELP.
SO, HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
TAKE SOME DUCT TAPE AND
WIND IT ONTO A RAKE HANDLE.
SO, YOU'VE GOT
THE STICKY SIDE OUT.
GO DOWN THE RAKE AND
THROW IT ON THE FLOOR.
NOW, WHEN YOU TAKE
OFF YOUR CLOTHES,
YOU THROW THEM ONTO
THE RAKE HANDLE.
AND, WHEN YOU'RE READY TO PUT ON
A SHIRT OR A PAIR OF PANTS,
YOU JUST STEP ON
THE END OF THE RAKE.
[laughter]
THEY USED TO CALL THIS
"DRESSING LIKE A RAKE."
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW!!!
HERE'S THE MAN
WHO'S BEHIND
THE MESSAGE,
BEHIND THE EIGHT BALL,
AND THE PAYMENTS.
YOUR HOST AND HERO:
RED GREEN!!!
[applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
THE TOWN COUNCIL HAS DECIDED
THEY NEED A NEW MONUMENT
IN FRONT OF CITY HALL.
I'M GLAD THEY DECIDED
TO GET RID OF THAT OLD,
RUSTY TANK FROM THE WAR.
THAT THING SMELLS.
HAROLD, IF YOU
HAVE A PROBLEM WITH
RUSTY TANKS THAT SMELL,
THIS MAY NOT BE
THE TOWN FOR YOU.
THEY PUT OUT FOR TENDERS
ON THIS NEW MONUMENT.
I THINK WE'VE GOT A CHANCE
OF GETTING A NOD ON THIS DEAL.
THEY'RE HEARING THE PROPOSALS
IN THE NEXT HALF HOUR.
MAYBE WE SHOULD GET DOWN THERE.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE I'VE GOT
A PROPOSAL, TOO.
OH, REALLY?
THEY WANT THE NEW MONUMENT
TO SIGNIFY THE LIFESTYLE
UP HERE.
THAT'S MY DRAWING.
I'VE GOT AN
ENTIRE FAMILY
IN A CANOE
AND THE SUNSHINE
SHINING ON THEM,
THE ANIMALS FROLICKING
ABOUT IN THE WOODS
AND A BABBLING BROOK.
HA! HA! HA!
WHAT'S YOUR DESIGN OF?
WE'RE DESIGNING
A 70-FOOT FLAGPOLE
MADE OUT OF BEER CANS
WITH A HUGE
UNEMPLOYMENT CHEQUE
FLYING OFF THE TOP.
[applause and laughter]
IN FACT, I'M GOING
TO MAKE THEM A DEAL.
IF THEY GIVE US
AN EXTRA WEEK,
WE CAN MAKE IT AN
80-FOOT FLAGPOLE.
IT'S TIME TO PLAY
"THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME."
TODAY'S PRIZE IS FOR ANYONE
WHO'S EVER DREAMT OF WAKING
UP A MILLIONAIRE:
AN ALARM CLOCK.
[laughter and applause]
PLAYING FOR THIS
WONDERFUL PRIZE
IS CITY SLICKER,
TURNED POSSUM LICKER:
MR. KEVIN BLACK.
MR. BLACK, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MY UNCLE RED TO SAY
THE FOLLOWING WORD:
GO!!!
OKAY, PIECE OF CAKE.
BIRTHDAY.
I HAVEN'T
STARTED YET.
AH... MMM...MUMBLY BUMBLY,
FISH.
CHIPS.
RAW FISH.
BAIT.
NO, OKAY.
WHAT DO YOU CALL IT
WHEN YOU EAT RAW FISH?
INSANE.
[loud laughter]
A KIND OF BAR.
OPEN.
NO, A KIND OF BAR
YOU DON'T LIKE.
OH, CASH!
[laughter and applause]
WHEN YOU GO TO
A JAPANESE RESTAURANT,
WHAT DO YOU EAT?
I DON'T GO TO
A JAPANESE RESTAURANT.
I KNOW YOU DON'T,
BUT IF YOU DID,
WHAT WOULD YOU EAT?
PIZZA.
THEY DON'T
SERVE PIZZA.
NO, I BRING
IT WITH ME.
THEY DON'T LET YOU DO THAT.
THAT'S WHY I DON'T GO.
[applause]
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT
OF TIME, MR. BLACK.
REMEMBER THE TIME YOU WERE
FISHING IN MERCURY CREEK
AND YOU GOT THAT SOAKER?
OH, YEAH.
REMEMBER THE SOUND YOUR BOOT
MADE WHEN YOU WERE WALKING?
"SHOO-SHE!"
[ring! ring! ring!]
[applause]
YOU GUYS ARE
SO EMBARRASSING
WHEN YOU'RE YELLING AND
SCREAMING LIKE THAT.
I TOLD YOU THAT
THE TOWN COUNCIL
WASN'T GOING TO GO FOR
YOUR BEER CAN SCULPTURE.
MAN, I CAN'T BELIEVE
THE ONE THEY WENT WITH.
FROM THOSE TWO GOOFBALLS.
THEY'RE NOT GOOFBALLS.
THEY'RE HEAD OF THEIR CLASS
AT THE ART COLLEGE.
OH BOY, OH BOY,
ART COLLEGE, EH?
THAT REALLY PREPARES YOU
FOR LIFE'S EMERGENCIES.
IMAGINE THE CAPTAIN OF A SHIP
GETTING EVERYBODY TOGETHER
AND SAYING: SHE'S
TAKING ON WATER,
THE ENGINES AREN'T RUNNING,
WE'VE LOST THE RADIO.
IS THERE
AN ART COLLEGE
GRADUATE HERE?
MAYBE YOU COULD DO SOME
CHARCOAL SKETCHES FOR US?
HA! HA! HA!
I HAPPEN TO LIKE ART
AND I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT
AND I LIKE
THEIR DESIGN, TOO.
IT WAS A STAINED
GLASS ABSTRACT WORK
AND IT WAS ALL FRAMED
IN WOOD AND COPPER.
IT WAS SIGNIFYING
THE ELEMENTAL OPENNESS
OF POSSUM LAKE.
NO, IT WAS SIGNIFYING
THE ELEMENTAL OPENNESS
OF THE TOWN COUNCIL WALLET.
NO, IT WASN'T.
YES, SIR!
THEY WON THAT TENDER
FAIR AND SQUARE.
ALL YOUR YELLING
AND SCREAMING
DIDN'T MAKE A BIT OF
A DIFFERENCE, DID IT?
ACTUALLY, IT DID.
OUR DEMONSTRATION
FORCED THEM TO GIVE US
COMPENSATION FOR LOSING.
WHAT KIND OF COMPENSATION?
HAROLD, THEY GAVE US
THE OLD ARMY TANK.
NO!
THEY GAVE IT TO US.
THE WHOLE TANK.
WE GOT THE TANK.
WHAT DO YOU
WANT THAT FOR?
THAT TANK DOESN'T RUN.
IT DOESN'T EVEN MOVE.
IT'S RUSTY AND
FULL OF HOLES
AND RODENTS.
IT'S A PIECE OF JUNK.
YOU JUST DON'T GET IT.
THIS IS ALL ABOUT
PRIDE OF OWNERSHIP.
IF SOMEBODY
SAYS TO ME:
"DO YOU HAVE A TANK?"
I CAN SAY YES.
[laughter]
OKAY, BUT WHAT IF
THEY SAY TO YOU:
"WHY DO YOU HAVE A TANK?"
THE GUYS I HANG WITH
WOULD NEVER SAY WHY.
[laughter and applause]
YOU NEVER SEE A VAMPIRE
WITH A FULL-GROWN BEARD
YET, A VAMPIRE CAN'T
SEE HIS REFLECTION
SO, A LACK OF FACIAL HAIR
IS UNBELIEVABLY WEIRD
'CAUSE SHAVING WOULD BE
OUT OF THE QUESTION
IF YOU HAVE A TEENAGER
WHO HAS A DRIVER'S LICENSE,
THERE'S TWO THINGS THAT YOU
NEVER WANT YOUR KID TO
HAVE IN THE CAR
AND THEY'RE BOTH
CALLED ACCIDENTS.
SO, THIS WEEK ON
"HANDYMAN CORNER,"
WE'RE GOING TO
TEEN-PROOF THE CAR,
NOBODY IS GOING TO BE CALLING
YOU GRANDPA FOR AWHILE.
LET'S ADDRESS THE MAIN PROBLEM
RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
FROM NOW ON,
THIS BACK SEAT IS OUT OF BOUNDS.
OH, WAIT A MINUTE NOW.
A COMFORTABLE FRONT SEAT IS
JUST ASKING FOR TROUBLE.
IT'S GOT TO GO.
I THINK I'LL GO WITH SOMETHING
THAT'S PURELY FUNCTIONAL,
NOT COMFORTABLE AT ALL.
[laughter]
I'M THINKING CHURCH PEW.
I NEVER HAD ANY FUN
SITTING IN ONE OF THESE
AND I'M PRAYING THAT
NO ONE ELSE DOES EITHER.
GO WITH SOMETHING KIND OF
SPARTAN AND HARD.
MAYBE PRESBYTERIAN OR LUTHERAN.
IF YOUR KID COMPLAINS
ABOUT SLIVERS,
WELL, I'D SAY THERE'S
BEEN A SIN INVOLVED.
I'VE INSTALLED THESE METAL BARS
TO BLOCK THE ALTERNATE ROUTE
TO THE BACK SEAT.
I'M GOING TO BE TAKING OUT
THIS INTERIOR LIGHT
AND REPLACING IT WITH
A FLUORESCENT UNIT.
YOU KNOW HOW ATTRACTIVE EVERYONE
LOOKS UNDER A FLUORESCENT LIGHT.
AND ONE LAST THING.
I'VE TURNED THE RADIO ON
TO THE PUBLICLY FUNDED
"ALL NEWS STATION."
NOW, I'VE JUST GOT TO MAKE SURE
THAT NOBODY CAN EVER CHANGE
THE STATION.
THIS IS THE ONE MODIFICATION
THAT I'M MOST PROUD OF.
REMEMBER THAT CHEESY EXCUSE?
"SORRY DAD, WE RAN OUT OF GAS."
REMEMBER THAT, BERNICE?
BUT, NOT WITH THIS BABY.
NO WAY!
I'VE GOT 438 GALLONS
OF GAS IN THERE.
THOSE TEENS ARE GOING TO BE
DRIVING AROUND FOR SO LONG,
THEY'RE GOING TO FORGET WHAT
THEY'RE DRIVING AROUND FOR.
IF THIS PUT YOUR TEEN OFF ANY
KIND OF TRANSPORTATION FOREVER.
CONGRATULATIONS!
YOU'VE EXCEEDED
YOUR EXPECTATIONS.
SO, REMEMBER...
"IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY."
WELL, I HOPE YOU'RE READY
FOR THE WORLD YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO LIVE IN.
I LOST THE COIN TOSS
LAST NIGHT AT THE LODGE.
HAD TO GO FOR COFFEE.
I DON'T MIND THAT.
I ENDED UP AT ONE OF THEM
"FANCY COFFEE PLACES."
"SUFFICIENT GROUNDS" WAS
THE NAME OF THE PLACE.
OR "HAS BEAN."
I'M NOT SURE.
I WALKED UP TO
"THE COFFEE SPECIALIST"
AND SAID TO HER:
GIVE ME SIX REGULAR,
THREE DOUBLE-DOUBLE,
AND ONE BLACK
WITH EIGHT SUGARS.
TO GO.
WELL, SHE LOOKS AT ME LIKE
A GOAT STARING AT A NEW FENCE.
"WHAT'S A REGULAR?" SHE SAYS.
WHAT'S A REGULAR, EH?
THIS AIN'T A GAS STATION.
WELL, EXCUSE ME.
I SAID: "WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?"
SHE GIVES ME THIS LIST:
LATTES, MOCHAS, CAPPUCCINOS.
SOUNDS LIKE THE GUEST LIST
AT AN ITALIAN WEDDING.
GIVE ME 10 CUPS OF SOMETHING
THAT'S SORT OF LIKE COFFEE.
SO, 30 MINUTES AND THE ENTIRE
ANNUAL COFFEE BUDGET LATER,
SHE HANDS ME TEN LITTLE CUPS,
LIKE, ABOUT THAT SIZE.
HOW CAN ANYTHING THAT SMALL
BE THAT EXPENSIVE?
AND HOW CAN ANYTHING CALLED
ESPRESSO TAKE A HALF HOUR?
WHEN I GOT BACK TO THE LODGE,
THE GUYS SAID TO ME:
"WHAT KEPT YOU?"
YOU KNOW WHAT I SAID?
"PROGRESS."
WE GOT THE OLD ARMY TANK
TOWED UP TO THE LODGE.
THAT WAS A JOB AND A HALF.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD HAVE
HIRED A GUY WITH A CRANE.
HE COULD HAVE LIFTED IT
ONTO A FLATBED TRUCK
AND DROVE IT RIGHT UP HERE.
AND MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE
BEEN BORN A MILLIONAIRE.
IT'S ALWAYS MONEY WITH YOU.
YOU NEED A TANK MOVED,
YOU PAY SOMEONE.
YOU NEED A ROOF RESHINGLED,
YOU NEED UNDERWEAR,
YOU PAY SOMEONE.
[laughter]
I JUST DON'T WORK THAT WAY.
AND WE GOT THE TANK HERE.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN EASIER IF
THE TREADS WEREN'T SEIZED UP.
OR, IF SHE DIDN'T WEIGH 30 TON.
BUT, A FEW BLOWN TRANSMISSIONS
AND A COUPLE OF
BROKEN CHAINS LATER,
WE GOT 'ER DONE.
SO, YOU JUST DRAGGED IT
LIKE A BIG ROCK?
WOW! THAT'S NOT EASY.
THERE'S NO DIRECT PATH
FROM CITY HALL TO THE LODGE.
THERE IS NOW.
[laughter]
OKAY, OKAY.
YOU GOT YOURSELF A TANK.
NOW WHAT?
WELL, WE'VE GOT
A LAWN ORNAMENT THAT
NO ONE WILL EVER STEAL.
WE COULD USE IT
AS A STORAGE SHED.
OR MAYBE A CROCK POT.
[laughter]
A COUPLE OF THE GUYS WANT
TO SLEEP OVERNIGHT IN IT.
THAT SCARES ME A LITTLE.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
MAYBE, WE CAN USE IT
AS A TOURIST ATTRACTION.
THE BUSINESS CAN
BE USED UP HERE
AT THE LODGE.
BUT, WHAT KIND OF TOURIST
WOULD COME ALL THE WAY
TO SEE A TANK?
HEY, HEY, HEY!
GUYS LIKE ME.
[laughter]
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
FORGET IT.
ALL RIGHT, SETTLE DOWN.
AS YOU KNOW, IT'S
NEW MEMBER NIGHT.
HAP SHAUGHNESSEY HAS BROUGHT
IN A GUY TO SHOW US.
CAN'T WAIT TO
HEAR THIS ONE.
[laughter]
I'M GLAD TO SEE SO MANY
OF YOU CAME HERE TONIGHT.
NO DOUBT, YOU HEARD THAT
I WAS GOING TO NOMINATE
JACK BATTERSBY, HERE.
AND YOU HAD TO COME
SEE HIM IN PERSON.
WELL, I CAN'T SAY
AS I BLAME YA.
TO BE THIS CLOSE
TO GREATNESS.
OF COURSE,
I'M USED TO IT.
BEEN AROUND HIM SO LONG,
YOU COULD SAY I'M JADED.
IN CASE YOU'VE BEEN
HIDING UNDER A ROCK
THESE PAST 20 YEARS.
LET ME TELL YOU
ABOUT THIS MAN.
40 YEARS AGO,
WE WERE BARTENDERS
AT THIS CLUB IN LIVERPOOL
AND WE TOLD
THE CLUB'S MANAGER
TO HIRE THIS BAND,
THE BEATLES.
AFTER THAT "THE FAB FOUR"
WANTED US TO MANAGE THEM,
BUT I DIDN'T WANT TO GET
TIED DOWN TO ONE JOB
AND JACK HERE,
HE GOT AN OFFER TO
BE IN THE MOVIES.
HE WOULD HAVE BEEN GREAT,
BUT ALL THE HANDSOME MEN
IN HOLLYWOOD GOT TOGETHER
AND THEY BLACKLISTED HIM.
SO, HE'S BEEN
SPENDING HIS LIFE
BOUNCING AROUND THE WORLD
AS A FREELANCE GIGOLO
AND A PART-TIME SPY.
LIKE ME.
UNFORTUNATELY,
JACK DEVELOPED
SO MUCH CHARISMA,
THE LADIES WON'T
LEAVE HIM ALONE.
NOW YOU SEE,
I CAN TURN MY CHARISMA
OFF AND ON, LIKE THIS.
BUT, JACK HERE,
HE NEVER MASTERED THE ART.
SO, HE'S ALWAYS
ATTRACTIVE TO WOMEN.
THAT'S WHY HE WANTS TO
JOIN A LODGE FULL OF MEN,
SO THE WOMEN WILL
LEAVE HIM ALONE
AND HE CAN HAVE
SOME PEACE AND QUIET.
RIGHT, JACK?
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
OKAY GUYS, JACK IS
A FRIEND OF HAPS
AND SUPPOSED TO HAVE
DONE A LOT OF STUFF,
JUST LIKE HAP.
DO YOU WANT TO ADD
ANYTHING TO THIS, JACK?
NOT MUCH OF A TALKER?
UNLIKE HAP, HE'S NOT
MUCH OF A TALKER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
( Lodge members ):
AYE!!!
( Narrated by Red ):
THIS LOOKS LIKE TROUBLE.
OH BOY, YOU GOT
THE WHOLE SET UP.
GOOD LUCK.
[glass smashing]
INTERESTING START.
KEEP IT DOWN A BIT.
OH, GEEZ.
NO.
BILL, NO, NO, NO.
LET ME GIVE IT A SHOT.
DEAD CENTRE.
[glass smashing]
I DIDN'T KNOW THERE WAS
A WINDOW BACK THERE.
BILL, YOU NEED SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU NEED?
SOME STRAW.
WE'VE GOT A FEW BAILS OF STRAW.
GO GET SOME STRAW.
THAT'S NOT STRAW.
IS THERE STRAW IN
THE BACK OF THE VAN?
IS THAT WHAT'S HE DOING?
GETTING STRAW FROM
THE BACK OF THE VAN?
NO, NO, BILL, BILL.
BILL, NO, BILL.
EASY DOES IT.
YOU CANNOT THROW AN AXE
INTO A VAN, ESPECIALLY MINE.
NO, BILL.
I JUST WANT TO MOVE
ONE LITTLE THING.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE
ONE LITTLE CHANGE.
AN AXE WON'T STICK INTO A VAN.
THAT'S ONE OF THE LAWS
THAT I KEEP UP WITH.
NO, BILL, IT WON'T WORK.
OH, MY GOSH.
YOU KNOW, I STAND
CORRECTED ON THAT.
NOW, COME ON.
COME ON, NOW.
SURE, NOW HE GETS GOOD.
LOT OF TENSION THERE, BILL.
CAREFUL, CAREFUL.
I'M GOING TO OPEN THE DOOR.
I'M OPENING THE DOOR.
OH BOY, OH BOY.
I HOPE HE'S OKAY.
OH, HE'S FINE.
UNBELIEVABLE,
TOTALLY UNBELIEVABLE.
WE'VE GOT THE TANK RUNNING.
LISTEN TO THIS, HAROLD.
[loud sound of machinery]
Harold:
UNCLE RED, WHY CAN'T
YOU LEAVE THINGS ALONE?
THAT TANK WAS A PASSIVE,
DORMANT ORNAMENT.
NOW, IT'S LIKE A LOUD,
THREATENING EYESORE.
ACTUALLY, IT FITS
RIGHT IN, DOESN'T IT?
JUST OUR IDEA OF FUN.
WHO'S GOING TO GET HURT?
YOU ARE.
WELL, THEN IT'S NOT FUN.
BUT, IF ONE OF
THE OTHER GUYS GETS HURT
AND IT'S NOT TOO SERIOUS
THAT'S WHAT MAKES
LIFE WORTH LIVING.
THAT'S WHY MY GENERATION
IS MORE MATURE THAN
YOUR GENERATION,
CONCERNING COMMON
SENSE AND SAFETY.
YOUR GENERATION HAS
TATTOOS ON THEIR BUTTS
AND STOVE BOLTS
THROUGH THEIR NOSES.
COME ON, HAROLD.
GO GRAB YOUR VIDEO CAMERA
AND WE'RE GOING TO
CAPTURE A SPECIAL MOMENT.
WHAT SPECIAL MOMENT?
49 LODGE MEMBERS
IN A TANK?
THERE WILL BE
A SPECIAL MOMENT.
WELCOME TO
"THE EXPERTS."
THE PART OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE EXAMINE
THE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY:
[studio audience]:
I DON'T KNOW!!!
THAT'S A TRUISM,
ISN'T IT?
JOINING MY UNCLE RED
IS HIS BEST FRIEND IN
THE WHOLE WIDE ROOM:
THE OWNER AND PROPRIETOR
OF THE LIVE BAIT SHOP
MR. EARL BATTERSBY.
[applause]
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
AND MAY I ADD,
WE HAVE A NEW
"DRIVE-THRU WINDOW"
TO HELP US SERVE
ALL YOUR LIVE BAIT NEEDS.
[laughter]
IS THAT WORKING OUT
FOR YOU, EARL?
OH, YEAH.
BUT, WE HAD TO GO TO CONTAINERS.
PEOPLE FEEL A LITTLE UNEASY
DRIVING THROUGH A SCHOOL ZONE
WITH A LAPFUL OF FROGS.
REALLY?
THE LETTER GOES:
"DEAR EXPERTS:"
"I HAVE A TWIN BROTHER AND
WE SEEM TO ALWAYS KNOW WHAT
THE OTHER IS THINKING."
"ESPECIALLY,
WHEN WE'RE AROUND
GOOD LOOKING WOMEN."
IS THIS A MENTAL CONDITION
BECAUSE WE'RE TWINS?
P.S., MY BROTHER
WANTS TO KNOW, TOO.
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH TWINS.
MENTAL TELEPATHY IS A POWER
THAT EVERYONE HAS,
BUT FEW PEOPLE EXERCISE IT.
I NEVER KNOW WHAT
PEOPLE ARE THINKING.
I NEVER CARE WHAT
THEY DID A STUDY THAT
FOUND 30% OF PEOPLE
CAN READ MINDS.
CAN I SEE THIS
STUDY, EARL?
NO, I DON'T HAVE THE STUDY.
BUT, I HEARD IT FROM A GUY,
WHO HEARD IT FROM A GUY,
WHO HEARD IT FROM A GUY.
NO, IT'S TRUE.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN ABLE
TO READ PEOPLE'S MINDS.
I WANT YOU TO
READ HAROLD'S MIND.
IT SHOULDN'T TAKE LONG.
[laughter]
OKAY, HAROLD.
I WANT YOU TO THINK OF A NUMBER
BETWEEN ONE AND TEN.
I WILL WRITE SOMETHING
ON THIS PIECE OF PAPER
AND WE'LL SEE IF IT'S CORRECT.
[laughter]
Earl:
ALL RIGHT, I GOT IT.
( Groaning in pain )
[laughter]
HAROLD, WHAT NUMBER
WERE YOU THINKING OF?
THE NUMBER THREE.
I WAS GOING TO PICK SEVEN,
BUT I THOUGHT HE'LL
GET ME ON SEVEN.
SO, I WENT TO SIX,
BUT I THOUGHT,
I'M GOING TO GO BIG
AT A TIME LIKE THIS.
BUT, TEN'S NOT BETWEEN
ONE AND TEN.
SO, YOU PICKED THREE?
RED, WHAT'S ON THE PAPER?
THIS SHOULD BE GOOD.
[laughter]
WOW!
[applause]
( Shouting )
I THINK WE'RE BACK
TO THE WAY WE WERE
AT THE START OF THE SHOW.
[laughter]
( Shouting )
TANKS ARE LOUD!!!
[laughter]
YOU KNOW WHAT HAROLD,
TANKS ARE LOUD!!!
LOUD!
WHY WERE YOU
INSIDE THE TANK?
I WANTED TO GET
A "P.O.V. SHOT."
WHAT IT LOOKED LIKE
FROM INSIDE THE TANK.
BUT YOU'RE A JOURNALIST,
YOU'RE AN OBSERVER.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO TOUCH THINGS.
WELL, I ASKED SOMEBODY:
"WHAT'S THIS BUTTON FOR?"
BUT, NOBODY ANSWERED.
WE COULDN'T HEAR YOU.
WHEN YOU'RE KNOCKING
BUILDINGS OVER,
THERE'S A LOT OF
RACKET GOING ON.
I WOULDN'T HAVE TOUCHED IT
IF I KNEW IT WAS LOADED.
I MEAN, WHY
WAS IT LOADED?
WELL, IT WASN'T
REALLY LOADED.
EDGAR THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE MORE AUTHENTIC
IF WE HAD A THERMOS
FULL OF DYNAMITE DROPPED
INTO THE CHAMBER, THERE.
I MEAN, WHAT ARE THE ODDS?
WHAT ARE THE ODDS?
THAT THE CANNON
WOULD ACTUALLY FIRE?
WHAT ARE THE ODDS
THAT IT WOULD BE AIMED
AT THE "NEW" TOWN MONUMENT?
[loud laughter]
I TELL YA...
GLASS AND COPPER IS NO MATCH
FOR AN EXPLODING THERMOS.
I JUST FEEL FOR
THOSE STUDENTS.
THEY WORKED SO HARD
ON THAT THING.
HAROLD, THEY'RE
IN ART COLLEGE.
THEY LOVE REJECTION.
BUT, THERE'S LEGAL
RAMIFICATIONS.
WE LOST THEM THEIR
NEW MONUMENT.
NO, NO, NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT I DID?
I GAVE THEM BACK
THE TANK, HAROLD.
THEY WON'T SUE US BECAUSE
WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
I LOVE THAT ABOUT US.
[squeal of the Possum]
IT'S MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN
IN A MINUTE.
YOU GO AHEAD.
TANKS ARE LOUD!
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED
WITH THE TANK THING.
SO, WE HAD A BIT OF A D-DAY
AND I'M HOPING TONIGHT
IS THE "DE NIGHT."
AND TO THE REST OF YOU:
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE GANG UP AT THE LODGE.
"KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE."
[applause]
ALL RISE.
[lodge members]:
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
I WAS ASKED TO MAKE
ONE ANNOUNCEMENT.
I'D JUST LIKE TO SAY,
I'M FORMALLY APOLOGIZING
FOR FIRING THE CANNON
ON THE TANK.
I AM VERY ASHAMED.
I HAD NO IDEA WHAT I WAS DOING
AND I TAKE NO PLEASURE IN
THE AMOUNT OF PROPERTY DAMAGE
THAT I CAUSED.
I WOULD ALSO LIKE TO
EXTEND MY CONDOLENCES
TO THE ART STUDENTS
WHO BUILT THE MONUMENT
THAT I, AND I ALONE, DESTROYED.
BUT, DID YOU SEE
THAT BABY GO DOWN?
BUT, I AM SORRY.