You know it once in a while, it's nice to dip
back into the past to find something useful
for the present. Like, for example, this
mood ring, remember these from the sixties?
No. Do you remember anything from the 60s?
Yeah, some kind of weird chemical on here
that makes it change color with the mood of
the person who's wearing it came in real
handy when you're on a date kind of gave you
a signal of wanting to make your move.
But after you get married, you need more of
a distant early warning system.
I taped a bunch of these mood rings to the
door knob on the front of my house and the
door knob and brass, so it actually conducts
the mood from inside the house.
That way, when I get home, I can get a sense
of what kind of mood my wife's in without
even having to step through the door.
The caller tells me whether I need to get
maybe flowers, chocolates or a place to stay.
Got this invitation from the government for
the town of Possum Lake, they're going to
have a spelling contest with a thousand
first prize.
It's part of a big plan to smarten us all
up.
Apparently, they had some survey and the
average Canadian is stupider than ever.
I think of all these politicians better be
careful.
If we get too smart, none of them will get
elected.
Good morning, G.O.O.D, and thank you.
I'm sorry, Harold, that's incorrect.
It's quarter after three.
It's a spelling exercise.
I want to be spelling rep for the town, you
know, over the big spelling bee.
Yes, I'm using a dictionary to practice,
right?
Well, you have to earn that job here.
Let's see the rules here.
You've got to have an open competition with
at least three people in it and then the
winner of that represents the town.
Yeah, that's OK. I'm fine with that because I
am a very good speller.
All right. Are you a good speller?
I don't really know. You know, my handwriting
is so bad I never been able to tell.
Well, I'm a very good speller.
You can pick any word on this dictionary and
I can spell it.
Go ahead, pick any word, pick a word, pick a
word, pick a word, pick a word, pick a word.
All right, I'll pick a word. Ok.
Obnoxious. Alfie A.
No. H a r OLB.
Hey, there's a picture of you.
It's time for the Possum Lodge word game.
Today's price is a coupon for a free session
at the House of Hammers and Phrenology.
Where we give you a bump on the head, then
read it.
Ok, here I'm coming to your ears.
Ok, read you got 30 seconds to get Harold to
say this word.
Car car.
All right, Mr. And go.
All right. Harold, this is something that
you've got to have if you want to go parking
on lover's lane. A girl.
Ok, no, no. But this is something that you
need to attract girls.
Wow. Fluency in Klingon.
No, no, no.
Ok. This is something you don't ever want to
have an accident in a rented tax.
Most of us at the
Lodge have these, OK?
Winston says a Hemi daltons as a hatchback,
mine's about 15 years old.
Bad haircuts. Almost out of time, ran, you
know, I know, I know, I know.
Ok, Harold. This is something that will take
you anywhere you want to go at any speed, day
or night at any one high
Speed wireless connection.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh, it's great for
shopping on the internet.
That's where I bought my cargo pants.
There we go. That's the repair
shop, part of the show we call, if it ain't
broke, you're not trying.
Joining me today is local water taxi
operator Hypersonics.
You've got a pair of boxing gloves there,
huh?
Yeah, I'm in training thinking about going
back in the ring again.
Yeah, but my old gloves are coming apart at
the seams.
Well, they're in good company.
I didn't know you were a boxer, huh?
Oh, I didn't fight under the name HAP.
Back then I was kid unbelievable.
Nineteen sixty four, I was making ends meet
by working as a limo driver in New York City.
It was my job to drive a young Sonny Liston
to his fateful bout with Cassius Clay at
Madison Square Garden.
My grandfather built that place with his
bare hands.
One at a time now. Come on.
Anyway, Liston and I got into a squabble
about the validity of my quantum physics
theorem and the next thing I know the cars
pulled over and Liston and I are throwing
punches at each other in an alley hall 40
Seventh Street.
I led with the right.
He crossed with the left and suddenly bam.
Tremendous blow to the head.
Well, you know, that explains so much.
Main Liston went down like a sack of hammers
right there at that moment, I was the champ
and I got nothing for it.
Anyway, I folded Sonny up, threw him in the
limo, took him to the fight, and the rest is
history.
Yeah, well, your boxing gloves are all done
there.
I think you'll find they're as good as new.
Yeah.
Great. Great. Great. Thanks, Ray.
All right. No problem. I sure hope the
Boxing Commission grants me my license.
Yeah, that's a part of my life.
I want to get back.
I feel the same way about this conversation.
A lot of people have these ceiling fans in
their houses.
They're supposed to help with the air
movement so that instead of your house having
a couple of cold spots, it's cold all over.
I don't really like the ceiling fans all
that much at the low speed.
They cool off your soup and at the high
speed they blow your toupee right into it.
Mind you, they are handy for slice and
fruit.
And I believe I have a better use for
ceiling fans instead of using energy.
My idea has these ceiling fans saving
energy.
Now some of you may already be ahead of me
on this.
That just means you probably shouldn't be
watching my show.
I believe Lawrence Welk is on what I'm going
to do is mount these ceiling fans on to this
car one on each corner.
And then as they spin around, that's going
to give me lift.
Lift is very important, as any woman will
tell you.
But in this case, see, the lift is actually
going to reduce the weight of this pig by
about a thousand pounds, going to give it
the same gas mileage as those little puddle
jumpers they sell to old ladies and college
professors.
Now we just need some way to spin the
ceiling, fans can't just plug them in and
drive away. I mean, even if you did have a
long enough extension cord, you'd have to
worry about pedestrians and lift bridges,
and you always have to come back the same way
you went. Someone said, We're going to take
the wheels off.
This baby carriage shouldn't be too tough.
If you have my kind of medical history, the
wheels fell off your baby carriage years ago.
Oh oh, oh, oh
Oh, it's a doll. Now, here's where the real
genius comes in.
No, I'm wrong. Ok, I'm going to use the car
itself to power these fancy.
I got them out of the ceiling fan over each
of the wheel wells and then when the carriage
wheel rubs up against the tire, that'll make
the fan spin even on the front wheel.
And even though it turns like that, it's
still the center of the top stays in the same
place. Hey, how brilliant is that?
You know, no wonder my parents questioned
why I found great.
Seven So hard every year.
The only other tricky part is you've got to
take a look at the angle of the fan blades,
make sure you mount them on the right side
of the car because one side is going to go
one way and the other side is going to go
the other way.
And if you do it wrong, the fans will push
down instead of lift and that's going to kill
your gas mileage. It'll be like driving
around with Moose Thompson on your roof rack.
I think we're good to go here, and this is
way better than the EPA solutions to gas
mileage, they just want you to go slow.
They got the walking's far.
But my system, the faster you go, the faster
the fans go, the lighter the car gets, the
better gas mileage you get.
I don't see a downside.
You let's take it for a spin pack.
Let's take her for four spins.
So remember, if the women don't find you
handsome, they should at least find your
handy. Oh, here's another bonus hitchhikers
won't come near you.
I think I have a sensible explanation as to
why men do so many crazy things.
Now I don't care what species you look at,
the male is forced to attract the females
attention. Peacock spread their tails, Ram's
butt heads.
Men drive monster trucks.
Now, I know when you see a guy peel away
from a stoplight or a crushed beer cans with
his forehead.
Most women just roll their eyes.
But the truth is men are programmed to
choose behavior that doesn't interfere with
mating. You know what that means?
That means that somewhere there are other
women who are actually impressed with male
stupidity. We call these women girlfriends.
Then later, when they come to their senses
and see the idiotic behavior for what it
really is, we call them wives.
So whenever you see a guy belching the
national anthem while he accompanies himself
with an armpit? Wish him luck.
He's either not married or about to be that
way.
Remember, I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
On my way, Rothschild sewage.
When you can't take it anymore, we'll come
over and take it for you.
Now, we're not quite ready to fill the entry
form yet, but we thought we'd have a little
trial run between Dalton and Harold there,
so might want to check the spelling on the.
All right. Harold, are you ready for your
first word there?
Ok, let's see indices,
Indices, AI and the AI.
I see it
S wasn't really asking you, Mike.
What's your guess,
What he said?
Ok, Dalton, quadrennial quadrennial,
What does that mean,
Something that only happens every four years?
Oh, like Anne-Marie, getting romantic?
No, no, it's more like the Olympics.
You don't know it, Marie.
All right, just take your guess, William
Dalton.
Ok, OK,
Hugh, you? D, D, e and An.
A hell look to your mind.
Oh, oh, oh, sorry, Don.
I don't know what came over me.
Well, it's the chainsaw, the sound of the
chainsaw.
Every time he hears it, he goes into that
trance to start spelling.
But why would that be here?
Oh, I know it was a cell mate I had in jail
who used to punch me every time I spelled my
graffiti. Wrong chainsaw working.
So you learn to show a little r-e-s-p-e-c-t,
huh?
I found out what it means to me, you've got
to be stuck it to me, sock it to me, sucking.
We're putting a little campfire tent thing
together behind the lines, Walter was
bringing the cooler and Bill and I were
putting on a photo.
I guess it wasn't much. Ok.
Ok. You know. Well, you've got to be
responsible for yourself.
You've got to watch. No, no, no.
No, no, no. No need for temper now.
You're not hurt. You're fine. So Bill and I
tried to get the tent together and Walter's
trying to clean things up.
Ok. Ok, now that probably hurt.
Ok, that's probably. But again, you're going
to want you always when you're camping, this
is for your youngsters out there.
You got to watch what the other guy is
doing, you know, like, don't do this, and we
didn't know what was pulling on me again.
Mean that that way lies madness.
So we got the tent up and Bill's going to
get the campfire going and we're going to
just split the log. So he's got you just
just going to just hit it.
Walter, Walter, Walter, Walter Lowery hit
the log.
And you know, this happens sometimes you get
a green log or what have you, or maybe the ax
isn't wide enough at the one end that the
bill is going to get the.
Not too many. Oh, no, not don't, you know,
don't use all the matches bill.
Not. Yeah.
All right. So meanwhile, a second axe into
the roughly into the same split, we'll just
open that baby right up.
Just hit it. Walter. Hit it, hit it.
Walter hit it now. Walter hit it now.
Ok, I was wrong. Ok, OK.
No. Hmm.
Yeah, well, let's try by this point, we
tried a few axes.
And that unbelievable that a lie would take
that.
I spend lots of nuts in that.
I got an idea, though. Let's flip it over.
Just flip it over. Meanwhile, Bill is going
back to the old style of lighting a fire with
a string and the I don't even know what they
call this, but it's nothing good.
And then. All right.
I should know. It's unbelievable, isn't it?
Boy, oh boy. We're going to run out of
access here.
This is we got the double ender.
I used to call it when we were younger.
And oh.
Hmm. Ok.
Ok. Ok. Ok, so now, Bill, starting to get
some small kids getting some heat going,
they're gonna take her up a notch there,
bill and.
Actually running out of space is to put an
axe into the log, so yeah, I got another
idea. I think that that's.
On fire, it's on fire.
Get it down. Ok, now, just move the camp,
yeah.
Move the Camp Fire over to where the fire is
there.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
If not, don't blow too hard.
Easy. Easy. Oh boy, oh boy.
Oh boy. So I think if he uses the hatchet
just in the right spot, we still got room for
that. Now, Walter's not good at taking
direction, and he just misinterpreted my
instructions. No. Like, how is that helping,
I don't I don't understand that.
Meanwhile, bills, he's got enough of it
stamped out.
He's all set. He's ready to bring the two
bring the log over.
But OK, well, you know what?
I got an idea, OK?
And we're all. Don't watch Bill.
Eat it. Don't watch. Not not if you're
eating it all yourself.
You can't use the log to burn or use it as a
holder.
No men have always had hobbies like fishing
or building things or just winging acorns and
squirrels. Unfortunately, men have also had
chores like cleaning out the eavesdrops.
The difference is hobbies are fun.
Chores are work now.
On the surface, it may be kind of hard to
tell them apart.
What's the difference, you might say between
collecting screws in a jar and picking up
your laundry and put it in the hamper?
Or what's the difference between the policy
in your car and polishing your silverware?
Simple one is a job, the other one is a
hobby.
The trick is to be able to combine the two,
and I'm a tricky guy.
Here we have a hobby.
This model train and a job to do, clean out
those these troughs, you have attached a
snowplow onto the front of the train.
And gets to do all the work I get to have
all the fun.
You get to watch.
Well, we're almost ready to fill out our
entry form.
We got Mike and Dalton from the Lodge and
then the town is sending up some lame entrant
Sam, something or other so that we'll have
three and that'll make it legal and we're
going to help Mike out a little bit.
We got Harold outside with a chainsaw.
He's going to rev it up, you know, just at
the right moment.
All good to go there, Harold.
That OK, let's get started.
I'm ready to SPL and my alphabets for
breakfast.
Now we just just got to wait for the token
entrant from the town there, you know?
Sam Sumner, You know what?
That's probably him right now.
I. Hello, there.
We'd like four boxes of cookies if you'll
take a check.
Far for
A spelling contest,
This is Sam. Well, you know, we have some
pretty big words in this thing.
That's OK. I'll help you print out some.
All right, well, all right, I guess we're
ready to go.
Are we all are we ready to go?
Yeah. All right. Great. Ok.
All right, well, ladies, first and.
Rhythm h y t, h m.
Yeah, right,
Yeah, right. Ok, Dalton, your word is
tchotchke.
I give up.
Well, that's a little embarrassing, isn't it?
Not nearly as embarrassing as it would have
been.
All right, Mike, Tchotchke charge cap.
T C, h, o t, c, h k e.
Mike, you go first this time.
Oh, you're where it is.
Pick a Lily.
Well, we didn't use the word peculiarly in
prison.
Oh, man. Time's up peculiarly.
P i cc a l i l l i.
I went got to go.
Oh, that's little time, and
Oh, no, no, no, no.
We. I'll be down in the minute.
My wife is watching.
I'll be coming straight home after the
meeting.
Real tense day and I'm hoping for a little
relief and I don't smell it.
Our old lady and the president.
Thanks for watching on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole gang up here for some
lunch. Keep your stick on the ice.
Down down.
All right. Know.
More now, Eric Bamberger heads for the man's
PR.
I'm a man, but I can change if I have to.
Yes. Okay, man, we're out of the running for
the spelling bee in the thousand dollar
prize. I was looking in the large cash box
and I was just wondering how many of you know
how to spell IOU, OK?
And how many of you know what it means?
That's what I thought. But.