THIS GUY IS MY NEIGHBOR
BOB DINKINS FROM UP THE ROAD
NOW, I'VE JUST
GIVEN HIM A WATCH.
HE'S PRETTY
HAPPY ABOUT THAT.
HE THINKS IT'S
REAL NICE TO GET A GIFT.
I GUESS HE DOESN'T KNOW
MUCH ABOUT THE TROJAN WAR.
REMEMBER, BOB, DON'T PUT
IT ON UNTIL YOU GET HOME.
IF YOU HAVE A
NEIGHBOUR OR A RELATIVE
WHO KEEPS DROPPING IN
UNANNOUNCED
AND IS ALWAYS QUICK TO TELL
YOU WHAT YOU'RE DOING WRONG
OR YOU'RE AN IDIOT,
OR HE'S GONNA CALL THE COPS
UNLESS YOU GIVE HIM A BEER,
WELL, HERE'S WHAT YOU DO...
GET YOURSELF ONE OF THOSE
INVISIBLE FENCE UNITS
THAT YOU USE TO KEEP
YOUR DOG INSIDE YOUR YARD,
AND YOU BURY THE WIRE AROUND
THE WHOLE PERIMETER OF
YOUR PROPERTY.
THEN YOU PUT A SPECIAL COLLAR
ONTO YOUR DOG,
AND EVERY TIME HE GETS
NEAR THE BURIED WIRE,
HE GETS ZAPPED.
NOW, YOU MAY NOTICE THAT 'VE
TAKEN THE ZAPPER OUT OF
THIS COLLAR.
THAT'S BECAUSE I INSTALLED
IT INTO THAT WATCH
I JUST GAVE TO MY
ANNOYING NEIGHBOUR.
I FIGURE ANY SYSTEM
THAT CAN KEEP A DOG IN
SHOULD BE ABLE TO
KEEP A GOOF OUT.
BESIDES, THIS IS WAY TOO CRUEL
TO USE ON AN ANIMAL.
OKAY, HE'S OFF THE PROPERTY.
I THINK WE SHOULD ARM
THE PERIMETER.
OH, LOOK,
HE'S COMING BACK.
PROBABLY WANTS TO TELL ME
SOMETHING ELSE I DON'T
NEED TO KNOW.
[zapping sounds]
HEY, BOB!
CHECK YOUR WATCH.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S
PAYBACK TIME.
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WELL, I APPRECIATE THAT.
I GOTTA TELL YOU,
WE'VE HAD A REAL HOT ONE
GOIN' ON HERE TODAY.
I DON'T KNOW THE
EXACT TEMPERATURE,
BUT THE BASEMENT OF
THE LODGE IS DRY.
THAT HASN'T HAPPENED SINCE --
WELL, THAT'S NEVER HAPPENED.
[sniffing]
OKAY, I THINK I KNOW WHICH
BUILDING THIS SHINGLE
CAME OFF OF.
MERRY CHRISTMAS,
UNCLE RED!
MERRY CHRISTMAS!
CHRISTMAS MERRY!
I HOPE THAT'S
SUN STROKE, HAROLD.
OH, NO, I'M JUST TRYING
TO GET YOU IN THE SPIRIT
FOR OUR FIRST ANNUAL CHRISTMAS
IN JULY CELEBRATION!
OH, AND WHY WOULD
THIS BE A GOOD THING?
WELL, BECAUSE IT
BRINGS CROWDS.
IT BRINGS VISITORS
UP TO THE LODGE.
THEY'LL THINK, "POSSUM LAKE IS
HAVING CHRISTMAS IN JULY?
"THAT'S CRAZY.
LET'S GO!"
WHAT IF THEY THINK,
"THAT'S CRAZY.
"LET'S STAY AWAY IN DROVES"?
WELL, WE JUST GOTTA
KEEP PUTTING OUT THAT
CHRISTMAS CHEER, DON'T WE?
WE'LL HAVE TO GET EVERY CYNIC
TO JOIN HAND IN HAND AND SAY,
"I DON'T CARE
IF IT IS JULY.
"I WISH EVERYONE THE BEST,
MERRIEST CHRISTMAS EVER!"
BOY, I HOPE YOUR MEDICAL
INSURANCE IS PAID UP.
I NEED YOUR HELP --
I NEED YOUR HELP BECAUSE THE
LODGE IS A BIG PART OF
CHRISTMAS AROUND HERE.
SO YOU KNOW HOW YOU PUT THOSE
LIGHTS AROUND THE LODGE
AS CHRISTMAS TIME?
I NEED YOU TO DO
THAT AGAIN, RIGHT NOW.
GET THE FESTIVE
MOOD STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, SURE.
SURE, THAT'S FINE.
NO COMPLAINING?
NO ARGUING?
THAT'S IT?
I ASKED YOU TO PUT
LIGHTS ALL AROUND THE LODGE.
AND YOU'RE GONNA
GO ALONG WITH IT?
THAT'S SO GREAT.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
WELL, IT IS A LOT OF
WORK FOR ME,
BUT I FIGURE IF
I HELP YOU NOW,
YOU'RE GONNA OWE ME.
ABSOLUTELY.
ANYTHING, ANY TIME.
DONE.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
TODAY'S CONTESTANT WILL
BE PLAYING FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE
WORD GAME HOME VERSION!
OKAY, RED, YOU HAVE 30
SECONDS TO GET MIKE HAMAR --
COVER YOUR EARS --
TO SAY THIS WORD...
RESPECT
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, MIKE,
WHEN YOUR WERE A KID,
YOU WERE TAUGHT TO ALWAYS
GIVE THIS TO YOUR PARENTS.
MY TAKE.
OKAY, IF YOU WANNA HAVE A
LASTING RELATIONSHIP
WITH A WOMAN,
YOU HAVE TO TREAT HER WITH...
ANTI-DEPRESSANTS.
OKAY, YOUR MOTHER PROBABLY
TOLD YOU THAT IF YOU WANNA
GET AHEAD IN LIFE,
YOU GOTTA SHOW A LITTLE...
THIGH.
RED, YOU'RE
ALMOST OUTTA TIME
I GOT IT!
THIS WAS BIG HIT FOR ARETHA
FRANKLIN IN THE '60s.
YOU CAN REMEMBER SOMETHING
FROM THE '60s?
BOY, YOU GOTTA
RESPECT THAT.
THERE WE GO!
[applause]
I GOT A LETTER FROM OUR
LOCAL ENVIRONMENTAL AGENCY.
APPARENTLY ONE OF
OUR NEIGHBOURS HAS
REGISTERED A COMPLAINT
ABOUT ALL THE JUNK WE
HAVE LYING AROUND THE LODGE,
ESPECIALLY OUR
UNFINISHED PROJECTS.
I KNOW WHO IT IS TOO.
IT'S THAT NEW GUY
WITH THE FANCY A-FRAME.
HE'S BEEN GIVING US GRIEF
EVER SINCE HE SAW US
COOKING WIENIES
OVER A TIRE FIRE.
HE SAYS THE LODGE IS KEEPING
HIS PROPERTY VALUE DOWN.
WELL, SURE IT IS.
IT ALWAYS HAS.
IF IT DIDN'T,
HE WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO AFFORD THE PLACE.
BUT NOW HE'S GONE AND GOT
THE GOVERNMENT INVOLVED,
AND I GOTTA GET
THE CAR OUTTA HERE.
ACTUALLY, THEY SAY IF I CAN
JUST REMOVE THE ENGINE
AND GAS TANK,
THEY'RE THE BIGGEST
ENVIRONMENTAL HAZARDS.
I GUESS THEY NEVER
SMELLED THE UPHOLSTERY.
NOW, AS ALWAYS, I LIKE
TO DO TWO THINGS AT ONCE,
BECAUSE THAT MEANS
I CAN WORK SLOWER.
SO I HAVE AN IDEA THAT'LL
SATISFY THE GOVERNMENT
AND INCREASE THE PROPERTY
VALUE ALL AT THE SAME TIME.
CAN YOU GUESS WHAT IT IS?
I'M GONNA TAKE OUT THE
ENGINE AND THE GAS TANK,
AND WHAT DO YOU SUPPOSE
I'M GONNA DO WITH 'EM?
EXACTLY RIGHT: AN AUTOMATIC
LAWN SPRINKLER SYSTEM.
YOU'RE GOOD.
OKAY, NOW, TO TAKE OUT THE
ENGINE AND THE GAS TANK,
ALL YOU DO IS TAKE OUT THE
ENGINE AND THE GAS TANK.
[laughter and applause]
OKAY, THE REST OF THE
JOB IS PRETTY EASY HERE.
I'VE GOT EVERYTHING I NEED
TO MAKE THE ENGINE GO
MOUNTED TO THE INSIDE
OF THE BOAT HERE.
NOW, I HAD TO MAKE A
FEW MINOR ALTERATIONS
TO THE WATER PUMP
TO TURN IT INTO A SPRINKLER.
FIRST OF ALL, I QUADRUPLED
THE SIZE OF THE INTAKE HOSE.
SO THIS BABY'LL PASS
SOME SERIOUS WATER.
NOW I JUST DROP
THAT INTO THE LAKE.
OKAY, NOW, TO GET
THE BIG SPRAY,
I TOOK THE NOZZLE
OFF THE LODGE FIRE HOSE
AND ATTACHED THAT TO THE
OUTPUT SIDE OF THE WATER PUMP.
I'M NOT REALLY WORRIED ABOUT
THE LODGE CATCHING FIRE.
WE KEEP IT PRETTY DAMP.
AND HERE'S A LITTLE
EXTRA PIECE OF INGENUITY...
I ATTACHED THE ROPE JUST
TO THE ONE SIDE OF THE BOAT.
THAT WAY SHE'LL KIND
OF SWING AND SWAY
WITH THE WIND AND THE WAVES,
AND I'LL END UP GETTING
MAXIMUM COVERAGE WITH
MY WATER SPRAY.
OH, YEAH.
AND FOR SAFETY SAKE,
I ADDED A REMOTE STARTER.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I WANNA TALK TO ALL YOU GUYS
ABOUT SUCCEEDING AND FAILING.
NOW, WHEN YOU WERE GROWING UP
AND GOING TO SCHOOL,
THEY PUT A LOT OF
EMPHASIS ON SUCCESS.
I DON'T AGREE WITH THAT.
I DON'T THINK SUCCESS IS
NEARLY AS IMPORTANT
AS FAILURE.
I'M NOT TALKIN' ABOUT
TOTAL FAILURE,
WHERE YOU LOSE EVERYTHING AND
LIVE IN A CARDBOARD BOX
UNDER A BRIDGE.
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT
MANAGEABLE FAILURE,
YOU KNOW, LIKE BEING
TEMPORARILY UNEMPLOYED
OR LOSING YOUR CAR KEYS
OR BUYING SOMETHING ON
TELEVISION THAT'S
"NOT AVAILABLE IN STORES."
NOW, DON'T GET ME WRONG.
SUCCESS IS GOOD, BUT IT
DOESN'T HAPPEN TO MOST OF US.
AND IF IT DID,
THEY'D CHANGE IT, BELIEVE ME.
SO I FIGURE, RATHER THAN
SPENDING YOUR WHOLE LIFE
FEELING BAD BECAUSE
YOU'VE NEVER SUCCEEDED,
I THINK FOR US NORMAL PEOPLE,
IT'S BETTER TO SPEND YOUR
WHOLE LIFE FEELING CONFIDENT
THAT YOU CAN HANDLE FAILURE.
SO HERE'S WHAT YOU DO...
TAKE SOME LITTLE HARMLESS
CHALLENGE AND JUST FAIL AT IT.
JUST FLUNK RIGHT
OUT AT IT.
THEN GET OVER IT
AND GET ON WITH YOUR LIFE.
AND JUST KEEP DOING THAT OVER
AND OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
WHAT'LL HAPPEN IS YOU'LL STOP
BEING AFRAID OF FAILING.
YOU MIGHT EVEN
FLUKE A SUCCESS.
AT THE VERY LEAST,
YOU'LL BE A HAPPY FAILURE,
AND YOUR FRIENDS'LL HAVE A LOT
OF LAUGHS AT YOUR EXPENSE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLIN'
FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
WELCOME TO THE EXPERTS'
PORTION OF THE SHOW,
WHERE WE EXPLORE THOSE
THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
YES, THOSE ARE
THE WORDS.
TODAY'S LETTER
READS AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"A GUY AT WORK HAS OWED ME
$100 FOR OVER A YEAR.
"YESTERDAY I FOUND HIS
WALLET IN THE LOCKER ROOM.
"THE WALLET HAD APPROXIMATELY
$187.13 IN IT.
"SHOULD I KEEP SOME
OF IT, ALL OF IT
"OR NONE OF IT?"
RED?
WELL, I HAVE AN ANSWER,
BUT I JUST CAN'T WAIT TO
HEAR WHAT MIKE HAS TO SAY.
OH, OKAY, SURE.
WELL, UH, I WOULD RETURN THE
WALLET TO ITS PROPER OWNER
COMPLETE WITH ALL
THE PERSON'S MONEY.
AND THAT'S
YOUR ANSWER?
THAT'S MY ANSWER
FOR TELEVISION.
YEAH, I AGREE.
I'D RETURN THE WALLET,
BUT I'D TAKE OUT THE
100 BUCKS THE GUY OWED ME.
OKAY, I KINDA AGREE
WITH BOTH OF YOU HERE.
I CERTAINLY WOULDN'T
KEEP THE WALLET.
I WOULD CHUCK IT
INTO A DUMPSTER
AFTER I HOISTED THE
180 BUCKS OUTTA HER.
THAT IS VERY
DISAPPOINTING.
YOU NOTICE A DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN OUR ANSWER
AND YOURS?
YEAH, I DIDN'T LIE.
RED, YOU CAN'T
STEAL A MAN'S WALLET.
WELL, HE DIDN'T
STEAL THE WALLET.
THE GUY JUST LEFT IT
LYING AROUND.
I MEAN, IT WAS FAIR GAME.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
MR. GREEN MIGHT
BE RIGHT.
NO, HE'S NOT RIGHT.
WELL, SURE I AM.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU
THE PROBLEM, BAGGY PANTS...
BAGGY PANTS.
I LIKE TO WEAR MINE
A LITTLE BIT TIGHT.
THAT WAY I CAN ALWAYS FEEL MY
WALLET RIGHT WHERE --
YOU LOOKIN'
FOR THIS?
HOW'D YOU GET
MY WALLET?
MAYBE YOU JUST
LEFT IT LYING AROUND.
GIVE ME THE
WALLET BACK.
OKAY, BUT FIRST
I'LL TAKE OUT THE
20 BUCKS YOU OWE ME.
I DON'T OWE YOU 20 BUCKS;
YOU OWE ME 20 BUCKS.
OKAY, HERE YOU GO.
NOW WE'RE EVEN.
WE'RE NOT EVEN, MIKE.
THIS IS MY MONEY.
OKAY, OKAY, FINE.
UH, HERE'S THE
20 BUCKS I OWE YOU.
GREAT, THANK YOU
HEY, THAT'S
MY WALLET!
UH, MR. GREEN, YOU OWE
WINSTON 20 BUCKS.
[train whistling]
Red: HAVE YOU SEEN
THESE TOY TRAINS,
WHEN THEY RUN INTO SOMETHING,
THEY JUST TURN AROUND
AND HEAD OFF IN
ANOTHER DIRECTION,
KIND OF LIKE A POLITICIAN
AT A PRESS CONFERENCE?
I BET IF I LET THIS THING GO,
IT'D COVER THE WHOLE FLOOR.
IN FACT, I'M COUNTIN' ON IT.
NOW, YOU'RE PROBABLY
WONDERING WHY I WOULD
HAVE A TOY LIKE THIS.
I DON'T HAVE ANY KIDS.
I DON'T REALLY ENJOY A TOY
RUNNING UNDERFOOT MAKING
ANNOYING NOISES.
YOU PROBABLY COULDN'T GUESS
WHY I HAVE THIS TOY,
IF I GAVE YOU
A MONTH OF SUNDAYS.
BUT THEN AGAIN, YOU DON'T KNOW
THAT I PROMISED BERNICE
THAT I'D VACUUM THIS ROOM.
[vacuum humming,
toy train whistling]
[applause]
WELL, HAROLD'S STILL TRYING
TO CONVINCE EVERYBODY
TO CELEBRATE
CHRISTMAS IN JULY.
HE'S ALL DRESSED UP
LIKE A CHRISTMAS ANGEL.
HE'S GOT THIS
BOOTH DOWNTOWN,
WHERE HE'S SELLING CHRISTMAS
COOKIES AND PUMPKIN PIES.
AND HE'S SINGING
CHRISTMAS CAROLS.
WHAT IS IT WITH
SINGING VOICES?
YOU EVER NOTICE HOW THE
BAD ONES ARE ALWAYS LOUD?
NOBODY WANTS TO HARK WHEN THEY
HEAR THIS "HAROLD" ANGEL SING.
[laughter and applause]
MAN, HAROLD.
YOU OKAY?
YOU LOOK A
LITTLE PIE-EYED.
MAY I HAVE A
TOWEL, PLEASE?
HERE'S A CURTAIN.
WELL, THIS WAS
A LEARNING EXPERIENCE.
NEVER TO SING WHEN
THERE'S PIES AROUND?
NO, THAT THIS TOWN NEEDS A
LITTLE CHRISTMAS
RIGHT THIS VERY MINUTE!
THERE'S HARDLY ANY SPIRIT
OF HUMAN KINDNESS OUT
THERE AT ALL.
HAROLD,
GIVE IT UP, OKAY?
A PUMPKIN PIE IN THE
FACE IS NO HARM DONE.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET OFF
SO LUCKY WHEN THE CORN
COBS COME OUT.
I DO NOT QUIT,
UNCLE RED!
I'VE ALREADY SPOKEN TO SOME
OF THE LODGE MEMBERS.
THEY'VE AGREED
TO JOIN ME IN A VERY
SPECIAL CHRISTMAS PARADE.
OH, NO.
HAROLD, THIS FROSTY THE
SNOWMAN COSTUME IS RIDICULOUS.
IT'S HOT.
IT'S ITCHY.
I'M MELTING IN HERE.
WELL, NOW, THERE'S
A JOLLY, HAPPY SOUL.
HOW DO YOU LIKE
MY RED NOSE, MR. GREEN?
YOU WEARING
A RED NOSE?
I THINK YOU GUYS
LOOK GREAT.
I NEED YOUR HELP
TOO, UNCLE RED.
YEAH, I NEED YOU
TO DRIVE THE FLOAT.
SURE.
WHAT IS IT, ANYWAY?
IT'S SOFT DRINK
DELIVERY TRUCK.
WHAT KIND OF
SOFT DRINK?
ROOT BEER.
OH, SO IT'S A
ROOT BEER FLOAT.
AM I SUPPOSED TO
LAUGH AT THAT?
WELL, IT'S
CHRISTMAS, HAROLD.
IT'S PARADE TIME,
UNCLE RED.
HEY, WHAT COSTUME ARE
YOU WEARING, MR. GREEN?
I'M GOING LIKE THIS.
I'M GOING AS THE SMART ONE.
I CAN PULL THAT OFF.
SHOULD WORK
IF HE DOESN'T TALK.
Red: I WANTED TO REPLACE THE
TIRE SWING OUT THE BACK,
BUT WALTER SEEMED TO THINK
THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH IT.
HE'S THE ONE WHO USES IT,
SO I DIDN'T WANNA ARGUE.
SEE, I THINK IT NEEDS --
YEAH.
I THINK IT NEEDS
TO BE REPLACED.
OF COURSE, WHAT WE NEED TO
DO THAT IS ANOTHER TIRE.
WE USUALLY HAVE TIRES
AROUND THE LODGE.
WE KINDA -- WE KEEP LOTS OF
STUFF AROUND THE LODGE.
SO WE LET WALTER PICK 'CAUSE
HE'S THE ONE WHO USES
THE TIRE SWING.
HE'S GOT ONE RIGHT THERE.
GIVE HER A BOUNCE, WALTER,
TO MAKE SURE SHE'S OKAY.
NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
SO MOVING ON.
ACTUALLY WE HAVE
A LOT OF JUNK.
FUNNY HOW THINGS JUST PILE UP
IF YOU DON'T GET THINGS
PUT AWAY PROPERLY.
I DON'T EXACTLY WHAT
WE HAD IN MIND
WHEN WE CREATED
THIS LITTLE DISPLAY.
PROBABLY NOTHING.
WE KEEP MOVING ON.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S TIRES
BEHIND ONE OF THE
OUT BUILDINGS.
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
LOOK AT ALL THE TIRES.
WE LIKE ANY OF THESE
DOWN ON THE GROUND.
OF COURSE, WALTER SEES ONE
UP ON THE ROOF THAT HE WANTS.
SO THE BIG QUESTION IS:
HOW DOES A TIRE GET
UP ON THE ROOF?
WALTER HAS NO IDEA.
HE WANTS US TO PILE
THE TIRES UP ON TOP THERE,
AND HE'LL JUST CLIMB UP
AND GET DOWN
WHAT HE SEES
AS HIS FAVOURITE TIRE.
WALTER IS KIND OF ATHLETIC,
AND UP HE GOES.
IT LOOKS A LITTLE
SHAKY TO ME,
BUT HE'S FINE WITH IT.
SO HE GETS UP THERE,
AND HE'S JUST GONNA
GRAB THE TIRE.
KEEP HER BALANCED.
NICE -- YOU'RE GOOD.
YOU'RE GOOD.
OKAY, COME ON DOWN.
COME ON DOWN.
OH!
SO NOW WE GOTTA
GET HIM OUTTA THERE.
NOW, THE FIRST FEW
COME OFF NO PROBLEM.
BUT NOW WE'RE GETTIN'
DOWN INTO THE RADIALS
WITH THE SMALL RIM,
AND IT JUST WON'T FIT
AROUND HIS WAIST.
SO RATHER THAN TAKE THE TIRE
OFF, I FIGURE WHY DON'T WE
JUST USE THAT TIRE,
GET WALTER OVER TO THE SWING
AND JUST ATTACH THE ROPE
RIGHT DIRECTLY TO THE TIRE
THAT WALTER IS WEARING?
IT'S A LITTLE BIT EASIER.
SO WE GET THAT
HOOKED ON THERE,
SO WE GIVE HIM
A NICE LITTLE --
IT'S NOT EXCITING ENOUGH,
HE'S COMPLAINING.
HE WANTS A REAL GOOD --
SO I GET AN IDEA.
GET HIM TO LIE DOWN.
LIE DOWN, WALTER.
NOW, WINSTON, LET'S GIVE
HIM A REAL GOOD --
AND I THINK, OF COURSE,
WE PUSHED A LITTLE TOO HARD.
THE ROPE BROKE OFF THERE.
AND THEN DOWN SHE COMES,
AND THEN UP THE SLIDE,
AND THEN INTO THE TUB.
BUT HE'S ALL RIGHT.
HE'S FINE.
HE'S ALL GOOD.
OKAY, THAT'S HOW THE
TIRE ENDED UP ON THE
ROOF, I GUESS.
[applause]
NOW, HERE'S AN IDEA THAT'S
EITHER GONNA CHANGE WHAT
YOU THINK OF ME,
OR CONFIRM WHAT
YOU ALREADY SUSPECTED.
YOU KNOW WHEN THE ROADS ARE
COVERED WITH SNOW AND ICE?
INSTEAD OF GOING OUT AND
BUYING SNOW TIRES LIKE
YOU'RE MADE OF MONEY,
OR STAYING HOME,
LIKE YOU'RE FUN TO BE WITH,
WHY DON'T YOU TRY THIS?
HOOK UP A COUPLE
OF OLD SHOWER HEADS
IN FRONT OF EACH
OF YOUR WHEELS, POINTING
STRAIGHT DOWN AT THE ROAD.
THEN YOU CONNECT THEM ALL
TOGETHER WITH THIS
FLEXIBLE HOSE,
WHICH YOU CAN GET FROM
ANY CONSTRUCTION SITE
DURING A STRIKE.
AND YOU RUN THE HOSES ALL
THE WAY DOWN TO THE BACK,
AND HOOK THEM UP TO THE
EXHAUST PIPE OF YOUR VEHICLE.
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
YOU DON'T NEED SNOW TIRES,
BECAUSE THE HEAT FROM
THE EXHAUST
WILL MELT THE SNOW LONG BEFORE
YOUR TIRES EVER GET THERE.
GIVE IT A TRY.
YOU'LL HAVE PEOPLE IN YOUR
TOWN WONDERING WHERE YOU
GOT THE HOT WHEELS,
RATHER THAN WHERE
YOU GOT THE HOT CAR.
[applause]
THAT WAS THE MOST DISGUSTING,
EMBARRASSING THING THAT'S
EVER HAPPENED TO ME
IN MY LIFE.
AND BELIEVE ME,
I'VE HAD SOME DANDIES.
IT WAS TERRIBLE.
OH, MAN!
THANKS, HAROLD.
THAT WAS A HOOT.
THAT HAD TO BE THE
MOST FUN PARADE EVER.
THAT WASN'T FUN.
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
WERE GONNA GET KILLED.
RED GOT HER GOING
PRETTY QUICK, HUH?
WE'RE GOING TO
THE MEETING.
ARE YOU COMING?
NO, I'M GONNA WAIT RIGHT
HERE FOR THE GRINCH.
WHERE IS HE
ANYWAY?
HE'S PARKING THE POP TRUCK
AND APOLOGIZING TO
THE POLICE.
HO HO HO.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
WHAT WAS THAT
ALL ABOUT?
THE ENTIRE CHRISTMAS
PARADE ONLY TOOK
45 SECONDS.
HOW FAST WERE
YOU GOING?
I DON'T KNOW.
MY STOMACH WAS
BLOCKING THE DASHBOARD.
WE WERE HOT, AND THAT
BREEZE WAS VERY REFRESHING.
A CHRISTMAS PARADE IS NOT
SUPPOSED TO PEEL RUBBER.
CHRISTMAS SYMBOLIZES
PEACE ON EARTH,
NOT HELL ON WHEELS.
SO YOU'RE NOT
HAPPY WITH SANTA?
NOT WHEN SANTA
TURNS A PARADE INTO
A DEMOLITION DERBY.
NO ONE WAS
EVER AT RISK.
I DON'T THINK EITHER OF THE
SPECTATORS WERE INJURED.
OKAY. OKAY.
OKAY.
YOU ARE THE WORST SANTA
THERE HAS EVER BEEN.
OH, I THINK
YOU'VE FORGOTTEN
I'M MAKIN' A LIST
AND CHECKIN'
IT TWICE.
AND THAT WAS A LITTLE
NAUGHTY AND NOT
VERY NICE.
DID YOU GET WHAT YOU
WANTED FOR CHRISTMAS?
NO WONDER.
NO.
'CAUSE YOU CRIED
AND YOU POUTED.
BUT LET ME LOOK
IN MY SACK, LITTLE BOY.
I THINK I MAY HAVE
SOMETHING FOR YOU.
I GOT SOMETHING.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
I'VE GOT SOMETHING.
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
HOW'S THAT, EH?
WHAT?
OH! OH!
WHAT IS THAT?
WELL, THAT'S A
CAN OF ROOT BEER.
BUT YOU KNOW, IT ROLLED
AROUND A BIT IN THE TRUCK,
SO I WOULD SAY DON'T OPEN
THAT UNTIL CHRISTMAS.
[possum squealing]
IT'S MEETING TIME.
NO, YOU'RE GOOD.
YOU'RE GOOD.
WATCH THE DOOR.
ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
OKAY. SO IF MRS. CLAUS IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I'M REALLY HOPING THERE'S
SOMETHING FOR ME UNDER
THE TREE TONIGHT.
OR EVEN BETTER, I'M HOPING
I CAN ACTUALLY COME INTO
THE HOUSE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND THE
WHOLE GANG UP HERE AT
POSSUM LODGE,
MERRY CHRISTMAS, AND KEEP
YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
OKAY, GUYS,
COME AND SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
COME ON, GUYS.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
OKAY, GUYS, THIS CHRISTMAS
IN JULY THING
WAS NOT A BIG SUCCESS.
WE'RE CANCELING
THE WHOLE DEAL,
WHICH I THINK IS GOOD,
BECAUSE THAT WOULD HAVE LET TO
NEW YEAR'S ON FIRECRACKER DAY,
AND THAT WOULD COST LIVES.