IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW!"
AND HERE HE IS NOW,
A MAN WHO ONCE YELLED...
"WAITER, THERE'S A
FLY IN MY PANTS."
YOUR HOST,
MY HERO,
UNCLE RED,
UNCLE RED GREEN.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
BOY, I HAD A ROUGH DAY
AT THE LODGE YESTERDAY.
BUSTER AND I WERE DRAGGED UP
TO THIS NEW MALL BY OUR WIVES.
NEW MALL?
YEAH.
YOU WERE UP AT
THE NEW MALL?
YEAH.
YOU WENT TO THE NEW MALL?
THE ONE AT PORT ASBESTOS?
THAT NEW MALL?
THAT IS SUPPOSED TO BE
SO COOL UP THERE.
THEY'VE GOT, LIKE,
A MUSIC STORE.
THEY'VE EVEN GOT A GAP.
WELL, HAROLD, EVERYBODY
AT POSSUM LODGE HAS
A GAP SOMEWHERE.
I TELL YOU, EVERY MALL HAS
THREE THINGS THE SAME...
CLOTHES, STORES
AND BENCHES FOR
THE HUSBANDS TO SIT ON.
I WISH I KNEW YOU
WERE GOING TO THE MALL.
I REALLY  WISH --
CAN I GO WITH YOU
NEXT TIME YOU GO?
WELL, THERE'S NOT GOING
TO BE A NEXT TIME, HAROLD.
YEAH, BUSTER AND I
WERE BANNED FROM THE MALL.
WHAT DID HE
DO THIS TIME?
WELL, I DON'T BLAME
HIM SO MUCH.
WE WERE BORED,
WE WERE TIRED,
AND THEY SHOULD NEVER SERVE BEER
ANYWHERE THERE'S A FOUNTAIN.
I'LL TELL YOU THOUGH, HAROLD,
I DON'T EVEN CARE ABOUT THAT
BECAUSE THAT MALL HAS
NO HARDWARE STORE,
NO CAR DEALERSHIP.
THERE'S NOTHING
I WANT THERE.
WELL, YOU CAN BUY
THAT KIND OF STUFF
DOWNTOWN POSSUM LAKE.
BUT DOWNTOWN POSSUM LAKE
DOESN'T HAVE A MALL.
SEE, THE LADIES LIKE
TO GO TO A MALL.
WAIT A SEC.
WHAT?
WE CAN TURN DOWNTOWN
POSSUM LAKE INTO A MALL.
WELL...
YEAH, YEAH.
IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S
ALREADY BEEN MAULED SO --
HOW ARE YOU GOING TO TAKE
A BUNCH OF RANDOMLY LOCATED
SHOPS AND STORES AND HOVELS
AND TURN THEM INTO
A HI-TECH ENCLOSED MALL?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW, HAROLD,
BUT THAT DOESN'T STOP
ME FROM TRYING.
NO, BUT IT STOPS YOU
FROM SUCCEEDING.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
Red Green:
ON THIS WEEK'S SHOW BILL
IS GOING TO TRY SKATING,
GOING TO GO WELL I'M GUESSING.
I'M GOING TO CONVERT THE
POSSUM VAN TO RUN ON PROPANE,
FOR A WHILE.
HAROLD'S GOT A DOUBLE-BARRELED
SLINGSHOT THERE BY THE
LOOK OF 'ER,
AND ARNIE HAS
A MEDICAL PROBLEM.
MERCHANTS ARE ALL
EXCITED ABOUT IT.
I GUESS THEY
HAVE WIVES TOO.
UNCLE RED, WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO, LIKE, PUT A DOME OVER
THE ENTIRE DOWNTOWN AREA?
YOU'VE GOT TO REMEMBER, LIKE,
YOU GUYS AREN'T ARCHITECTS OR
BUILDERS OR ENGINEERS.
YOU'RE MORE LIKE THE --
YOU GUYS ARE MORE LIKE THE
PEOPLE WHO HOLD THINGS...
FOR THE GUY WHO
KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
AND THIS GUY
AIN'T COMING.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
DON'T WORRY, HAROLD,
THIS PLAN IS FOOL PROOF.
TELL ME THIS.
WHAT IS THE MOST APPEALING
PART OF AN INDOOR MALL?
THE STORES.
NO, FLAVOURED POPCORN.
NO, BABES.
BABES,
NO.
OH, YEAH!
NO, NO.
YES, YES.
THE CONVENIENCE, HAROLD,
THE ABILITY TO GO FROM STORE TO
STORE WITHOUT GOING OUTSIDE.
YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE A FOUNTAIN.
'CAUSE THAT'S WHERE ALL
THE TEENAGERS HANG OUT
WHERE THERE'S BABES.
I'LL BE GETTING
RIGHT ON THAT, HAROLD.
SO THE QUESTION IS HOW DO YOU
ATTACH THE STORES TOGETHER
WHEN YOU'RE WORKING WITH A
LIMITED BUDGET?
DUCT TAPE?
NO, NO.
OH, GOOD.
HAROLD, YOU'RE GOING
TO LOVE THIS.
THE STORES ARE ALREADY
ATTACHED TOGETHER.
HUH?
THROUGH THE STORM SEWERS.
STORM SEWERS.
I KNEW YOU'D LIKE IT.
OH, YEAH, I'M LOVING IT.
I'M LOVING IT.
YOU GO INTO A STORE,
YOU GO DOWN INTO THE BASEMENT,
YOU DROP INTO THE SEWER AND YOU
STROLL ALONG IN CONCRETE-LINED
COMFORT TO THE NEXT SHOP.
THE MALL IS PRE-BUILT.
THAT'S THE BEAUTY OF IT.
WELL, IF THAT'S
THE BEAUTY OF IT,
I DON'T WANT TO
KNOW THE UGLY PART.
OH, HAVE YOU EVER HAD A
DREAM YOU WERE FALLING
FALLING
WELL CHANCES ARE YOU
WEREN'T REALLY FALLING
FALLING
UNLESS YOU FELL
ASLEEP SKYDIVIING
SKYDIVING
AND THAT'S NOT REALLY
RECOMMENDED
IF YOU'D READ
THE INSTRUCTIONS
YOU'D KNOW THAT
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S TIME TO PLAY THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
AND THIS WEEK THE GRAND PRIZE IS
FOR ANYONE WHO HAS EVER DREAMED
OF VISITING THE EIFFEL TOWER,
THE LEANING TOWER OF PISA,
THE TOWER OF LONDON.
THIS WEEK'S GRAND PRIZE,
A ROAD MAP OF EUROPE!
YOU CAN FIND ANYTHING.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET Mr. DALTON HUMPHREY
TO SAY THIS WORD.
"ACCIDENT."
OKAY, GO!
OKAY, DALTON,
MISTAKE...?
MARRYING YOUNG.
DISASTER...?
MARRYING LATER
IN LIFE.
ALL RIGHT, REMEMBER A
COUPLE OF DAYS AGO,
YOUR DAUGHTER BUMPED
INTO YOUR PIGGY BANK,
SMASHED IT
ON THE FLOOR.
THAT WAS AN...?
OMEN.
OKAY, TWO YEARS BACK NOW,
REMEMBER YOUR DAUGHTER'S IN
THE BACK SEAT OF THAT CAR.
SHE HAD THAT TERRIBLE...?
MARRIAGE PROPOSAL.
NO, FIVE YEARS --
FIVE YEARS BACK.
REMEMBER SHE
CRASHED YOUR PINTO.
INSURANCE FRAUD.
THEY NEVER PROVED THAT!
ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
JUST KEEP GOING
TO SAVE YOURSELF.
ALL RIGHT YOUR DAUGHTER
24 YEARS AGO...?
OH, AN ACCIDENT.
(FRANTIC BELL RINGING)
THERE WAS NOTHING
ON TV LAST NIGHT,
AT LEAST NOTHING
THAT I WANTED TO WATCH,
SO I ENDED UP AT THE
KITCHEN TABLE TRYING
TO PAY A FEW BILLS.
I'M LOOKING AT MY
CREDIT CARD STATEMENT.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE HOW
MUCH I SPEND ON GASOLINE.
I BLAME IT ON TWO THINGS...
THE GAS MILEAGE
OF THE POSSUM VAN,
AND THE FACT THAT ALL THE
OTHER LODGE MEMBERS HAVE
LOCKING GAS CAPS.
SO THIS WEEK ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO CONVERT
THE POSSUM VAN
(CRASH!)
TO RUN ON PROPANE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S CHEAPER,
IT'S CLEANER,
AND IT'S MUCH MORE
READILY AVAILABLE
BECAUSE SO FAR, THEY
HAVEN'T FIGURED OUT HOW TO PUT
A LOCKING GAS CAP ON A BARBEQUE.
FIRST THING YOU WANT TO DO
IS MOUNT THE PROPANE TANKS
ON YOUR VEHICLE.
I SAY JUST PUT THEM ON
THERE LIKE SADDLEBAGS.
I MEAN, THIS HERE IS MY HORSE,
200 HORSE ACTUALLY.
YOU'LL NEED
A LOT OF SADDLEBAGS,
SORT OF LIKE MOOSE THOMPSON.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS GET A
HUNK OF CHAIN, PUT A PROPANE
TANK ON EACH END
AND THEN JUST DRAPE
THAT OVER YOUR VEHICLE.
(EXPLOSION)
EASY, BIG FELLA.
YOU MIGHT WANT
TO GET A FEW TANKS.
YOU MAY GO THROUGH SOME.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE YOU GET
THE TANKS ON THERE,
YOU COULD CONNECT THE PROPANE TO
THE ENGINE USING THE PROPER
FITTINGS AND COUPLINGS,
IF YOU'RE MADE OF MONEY...
BUT, HECK, IF YOU'RE THAT RICH
YOU MIGHT AS WELL BE RUNNING
ON GASOLINE AND FORGET
THE WHOLE DEAL.
SO I RECOMMEND YOU GO
WITH REGULAR GARDEN HOSE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, PROBABLY SOME OF
YOU MIGHT BE GETTING A LITTLE
SKEPTICAL AT THIS POINT.
LIKE, MY DAD USED TO SAY,
"YOU KNOW, YOU CAN'T MIX
RIGHT-HAND AND LEFT-HAND
THREAD CONNECTORS."
HE NEVER KNEW ABOUT
THE HANDYMAN SECRET ADAPTOR!
SO JUST TAKE OFF AS MUCH OF
GARDEN HOSE AS YOU NEED
TO CONNECT --
OH, GEEZ, FROZEN HERE.
THAT'S A START I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, WE'RE HMM --
OKAY, WE'RE ABOUT
READY TO GO HERE.
GOT ALL THE HOSES RUNNING RIGHT
DOWN INTO THE CARBURETOR.
AND THEN I TAKE THIS
BARBEQUE STARTER,
JAM THAT IN THROUGH THE GRILL,
AND WHEN I FIRE THAT UP
THE WHOLE UNIT SHOULD GO.
OKAY, ALL I'VE GOT TO DO NOW
IS OPEN ALL THE VALVES ON
THE PROPANE TANKS,
AND WE SHOULD BE READY
TO HIT THE ROAD.
RUSTY HERE.
YOU KNOW, FOR SAFETY SAKE THERE,
YOU MIGHT WANT TO LEAVE ONE
OF THE VALVES CLOSED.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU RUN OUT
OF PROPANE YOU'LL HAVE
A LITTLE EXTRA,
YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE
CONSERVATIVE.
MIND YOU, IF YOU'RE
THAT CONSERVATIVE,
PROBABLY DON'T WANT TO DO
THIS PROJECT IN THE FIRST PLACE.
DAMN, SMELL THAT PROPANE.
IF YOU'RE A SMOKER NOW YOU MIGHT
WANT TO EXTINGUISH YOUR BUTT
WHILE YOU STILL HAVE ONE.
OKAY, THEY'RE ALL WIDE OPEN.
LET'S JUST FIRE IT UP.
MAN, I MUST HAVE
LEFT 'ER IN GEAR.
SO REMEMBER, IF WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
(EXPLOSION)
I WANT TO TAKE A MINUTE AND TALK
TO YOU OLDER FELLOWS OUT THERE.
THERE IS A NEW TREND
GOING ON NOW FOR MEN.
IT'S CALLED
"SHARE YOUR FEELINGS."
ESPECIALLY "SHARE YOUR FEELINGS
WITH YOUR PARTNER FOR LIFE,"
AND I DON'T MEAN
YOUR BEER GUT.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A
GREAT IDEA, DOESN'T IT?
SHARING YOUR FEELINGS,
MAKE YOUR
RELATIONSHIP STRONGER,
MAYBE MAKE THE TWO OF
YOU GET CLOSER TOGETHER.
BUT I'D JUST LIKE TO PUT
THE BRAKES ON THAT
RIGHT HERE,
RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT CERTAIN THINGS
SHE SAYS AND DOES,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'D
LIKE TO TELL HER.
OKAY, THESE ARE FEELINGS
THAT SHOULD NOT BE SHARED.
WHEN SHE ASKS YOU
WHAT YOU'RE FEELING,
FOR GOSH SAKE,
DON'T LISTEN TO YOURSELF.
JUST PUT YOUR HEAD DOWN,
TELL HER WHAT SHE NEEDS TO HEAR.
IF YOU HAVE OTHER FEELINGS THAT
NEED TO BE EXPRESSED TO SOME
LIVING CREATURE,
HEY, THAT'S WHAT
DOGS ARE FOR.
NOW, I'M NOT ASKING
YOU TO LIE,
JUST PICK AND CHOOSE.
'CAUSE IF YOU TELL HER HOW YOU
FEEL ABOUT WHAT SHE DOES,
THERE'S A REAL DANGER SHE'S
GOING TO DO THE SAME
THING BACK TO YOU,
AND YOU'RE JUST NOT
STRONG ENOUGH FOR THAT.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, OPERATION INDOOR MALL
IS REALLY PICKING UP SPEED.
WE DID HAVE THE ONE SETBACK.
MOOSE THOMPSON GOT WEDGED
DOWN IN THE SEWER THERE
HALFWAY BETWEEN THE BAGEL SHOP
AND THE KIELBASA COTTAGE.
AND WE WENT DOWN TO
LOOK FOR HIM THERE,
AND HE LIT A MATCH
TO SHOW US WHERE HE WAS,
AND THE METHANE WENT OFF
LIKE AN A-BOMB DOWN THERE.
METHANE IN
A STORM SEWER?
HOW DID THAT
GET DOWN THERE?
MOOSE PANICKED.
ANYWAY, I'LL TELL YOU,
BY GOSH, THE SEWER REALLY
OPENED UP THERE.
YOU CAN ACTUALLY STAND UP IN IT,
AND THAT'S GOT TO BE A BIG
APPEAL FOR A LOT OF SHOPPERS.
AND WE'VE GOT A
BRAND NEW SLOGAN.
WE'VE GOT ONE OF THE FEW
MALLS THAT'S RAT-FREE NOW TOO.
I CAN HELP OUT TOO.
KNOW WHAT I CAN DO?
I CAN DO LIKE DISPLAYS
BECAUSE DISPLAYS DOWNTOWN,
THEY'VE GOT --
OUT OF IT, RIGHT?
BUT I CAN MAKE UP THESE
MODERN COOL ONES, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE I'LL BE
HONEST WITH YOU,
LEISURE SUITS SOLD BY THE POUND
IS NOT A DRAWING CARD.
I'M JUST SAYING --
WELL, YOU KNOW, IT MIGHT BE
GOOD TO HAVE A YOUNGER
PERSPECTIVE, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW, OUR MARKET
RESEARCH HAS TOLD US
THAT IT'S THE YOUNG PEOPLE
THAT HAVE THE DISPOSABLE INCOME.
YOU DID MARKET RESEARCH?
WELL, SOMEBODY SAW
FLINTY McCLINTOCK'S
DAUGHTER WITH A 20.
I'M HOPIN' IT WASN'
YOUR 20, HAROLD.
I'M KIDDING.
I'M JUST KIDDING YOU.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
SENSITIVE ABOUT EVERYTHING.
THIS MALL THING IS
A BIG OPPORTUNITY,
WAVING RIGHT IN
FRONT OF YOUR FACE.
YOU KNOW, THE BEST PART IS THE
UNDERGROUND PASSAGE PORTION
BECAUSE YOU KNOW, WE CAN HAVE
ALL THESE SPECIAL ITEM DISPLAYS
THERE, YOU KNOW.
CHEESE SAMPLES.
CHEESE.
AND WE CAN INVITE SOAP OPERA
STARS TO COME UP AND SHAKE
HANDS WITH YOU.
(in deep voice)
I'M JAKE.
I'VE GOT SO
MANY IDEAS, YOU KNOW?
I COULD HELP OUT.
ALL RIGHT, WE CAN
USE THE INPUT.
HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT REJECTION?
I'M GETTING
USED TO IT.
OKAY.
THIS IS THE REPAIR PART
OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
"IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
JOINING ME TODAY IS LOCAL
ROOFER ARNIE DOGAN.
(APPLAUSE)
THANKS.
YEAH, YEAH.
IT'S GOOD
TO BE HERE.
YOU KNOW, MY REAL CAREER IS AS
A COUNTRY AND WESTERN SINGER.
COUNTRY MUSIC IS
IN MY BLOOD.
WHEREAS WITH ROOFING
IT'S JUST THE OPPOSITE.
YOU KNOW, RED, FALLING
OFF HIGH PLACES,
THAT'S AN INTEGRAL PART OF
YOUR ROOFING BUSINESS.
I SUPPOSE.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE
WITH MY BROKEN ARM.
OH, MAN, YOU DON'T WANT
ME TO FIX YOUR ARM, DO YOU?
OH, NO, NO, THE DOCTOR
SET IT IN A CAST.
THEN I WENT UP ON
GEORGE DRINKWATER'S ROOF.
HE'S GOT THE
HIGH-PITCHED ROOF.
YEAH.
I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT YOU'D HAVE
A HIGH-PITCHED VOICE BY NOW.
YEAH, I DIDN'T FALL
OFF ALL THE WAY.
OH, I WAS LUCKY ENOUGH
TO CATCH THE CAST COMING
DOWN ON THE DRAIN BREATHER.
I DID ABOUT FOUR OR FIVE
DOUGHNUTS BEFORE THE CAST BROKE.
SO I WAS WONDERING, RED, MAYBE
YOU COULD REPAIR THAT FOR ME.
DOESN'T THAT HURT
A LITTLE BIT, ARNIE?
SHE STINGS A
LITTLE BIT, RED.
YEAH. YEAH.
ESPECIALLY WHEN
I'M JOGGING.
OH, SURE.
ON THE WAY OVER STINKY
PETERSON'S DOG GRABBED
AHOLD OF THE FINGERS,
JUST WOULDN'T LET GO,
'TIL I GOT A SORT OF WINDMILL
THING GOING, YOU KNOW?
COULDN'T GET HIM
OFF OF THERE.
MAN, OH MAN.
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW,
I THINK YOU SHOULD GO
BACK TO THE DOCTOR WITH THAT.
OH, NO, OH, NO.
SEE, I STILL OWE HIM FOR THE
LEG SPLINTS AND BACK SURGERY.
MAYBE IF YOU COULD JUST JOIN UP
THE CAST I THINK I'LL BE FINE.
WELL, I DON'T REALLY
HAVE ANY PLASTER.
OH, GEEZ.
OH, WAIT A MINUTE.
YEAH, I CAN --
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S TRY THIS.
OH, OH,
OH, OH, OH!
HOW ABOUT
BACK THIS WAY?
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, THAT'S GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, BOY, THIS IS A
LITTLE UNUSUAL, ARNIE.
I APPRECIATE THIS, RED.
BOY, OH, BOY.
I DON'T THINK WE'VE EVER
SEEN THIS PARTICULAR
TECHNIQUE BEFORE.
THAT WILL FIX
'ER UP NICE.
YOU THINK SO?
YOU KNOW, THERE WILL
BE AN UPSIDE TO THIS;
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO PLAY THE
GUITAR BEHIND YOUR BACK.
RED, WHAT'S GOOD
ABOUT THAT?
WON'T BE AS LOUD.
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY,
YOU'RE DONE.
ALL RIGHT, GEEZ.
THANKS RED,
I OWE YOU ONE.
YEAH, OKAY.
TAKE IT EASY.
Red Green:
BILL, AND I ARE GOING
TO GO SKATING THIS WEEK.
GET UP.
UP YOU GET.
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL GET DOWN.
THEN WE CAN BOTH GET UP.
AND LAID OUT A LITTLE TRACK
OF PYLONS THERE.
WE'VE GOT A LITTLE RACE --
RACE AROUND THERE, YEAH.
HOW MANY LAPS WE GOING TO GO?
WE DON'T KNOW YET.
THAT'S UNFORTUNATE.
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING ABOUT
A FROZEN POND TO ME,
JUST SUMS UP WINTER IN
OUR PART OF THE COUNTRY
AND IT'S JUST --
YOU KNOW, I KNOW THEY HAVE
THE ARENAS AND WHAT-HAVE-YOU,
BUT TO ME THERE'S
NO COMPARISON.
IT'S JUST THE KIND OF SKATING
YOU DO WHEN YOU'RE ON A POND
AND, YOU KNOW, TO BE WITH A
FRIEND AND JUST KIND OF
ENJOYING THE DAY
AND GETTING THE FRESH AIR
THERE IN YOUR FACE.
AND, MY GOSH, YOU CAN
HAVE A LOT OF FUN,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE WITH THAT
ONE SPECIAL PERSON THAT YOU
CAN DO THINGS TO,
LIKE THAT.
IT MAKES ALL THE DIFFERENCE.
AND, YOU KNOW,
A LITTLE COMPETITION
DOESN'T HURT EITHER.
NOW, WE'VE TRIED --
THE RACE DIDN'T GO SO WELL,
SO NOW WE'RE GOING
TO COMPETE AT STOPPING.
THE IDEA, BILL WANTS
ME TO SHOOT UP THERE.
LOOK, IT'S
ROCKET RICHARD THERE.
STOP ON A DIME.
THERE YOU GO.
I CAN BACK UP EVEN.
AND BILL'S GOING TO COME --
BILL, BILL, A LITTLE
MORE ACCELERATION.
OH-OH!
ALL RIGHT, WELL, HE DID
EVENTUALLY STOP,
BUT THAT WAS THE TREE.
NOW WHAT ARE
YOU DOING NOW, BILL?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU'VE GOT THE ROPE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
OH, NOW THIS IS
EXCITING, ISN'T IT?
BILLS'S TRYING AN OLD TRICK.
IT'S CALLED CRACK THE WHIP.
AND GET THE OTHER GUY GOING,
AND YOU WHIP HIM AROUND
AND CRACK THE WHIP.
THIS IS ME CRACKING
THE WHIP, RIGHT.
HERE'S HOW YOU DO IT.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET
SOME JUICE GOING.
CRACK THAT BABY.
GET HIM ON THE ICE THERE AND
WHIP HIM AROUND AND LET HIM GO.
OH, BOY.
HANG ON, BILL.
HANG ON.
I'LL HELP YOU.
THERE YOU GO.
OH, THERE,
I GOT YOU DOWN.
YOU'RE FINE.
WANT TO GO SKATING AGAIN, BILL?
YOU WANT TO GO BACK TO --
OH, BILL, ACTUALLY MAYBE YOU'RE
GOING TO NEED YOUR SKATES
I THINK TO...
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
OH, BOY.
WELL, WE'RE ALL SET FOR
OUR BIG MALL OPENING HERE.
IT'S AWESOME.
IT IS SO COOL.
IT'S SO INCREDIBLY AWESOME.
THE SEWER WALLS ALL HAVE
TEEN POSTERS ON THEM,
AND THERE'S
BLACK LIGHTS.
THERE'S EVEN
A VIDEO GAME.
OKAY, IT'S PONG,
BUT STILL...
YEAH, YEAH.
I WAS THINKING YOU GUYS SHOULD
HAVE PICKED A BETTER ANCHOR
STORE FOR THE MALL
BECAUSE USUALLY IT'S A
MAJOR-NAME DEPARTMENT STORE
OF SOME SORT,
NOT JUST THE GASKET SHOP.
HAROLD, IT'S NOT JUST
A GASKET SHOP,
IT'S CUSTOM GASKETS.
O-O-O-H!
WHILE YOU WAIT, FOLKS,
YOU GO IN THERE,
YOU TAKE YOUR FLANGE,
YOUR HOUSING, WHATEVER,
THEN BINGO, BANGO, BONGO
THERE'S YOUR GASKET.
YOU'RE OUT, AND YOU'RE ON YOUR
WAY TO THE ICE CREAM STORE.
WELL, I NEVER THOUGHT
OF IT THAT WAY.
WHAT I WAS THINKING THOUGH,
I THINK YOU SHOULD CHANGE
IT TO A YOGURT SHOP
BECAUSE YOGURT'S
GOOD FOR YOU.
WELL, I DON'T LIKE THINGS
THAT ARE GOOD FOR ME.
WELL, I DO.
I LOVE THINGS THAT
ARE GOOD FOR ME.
I ONLY DO GOOD THINGS
THAT ARE GOOD FOR ME.
I ALWAYS DO THINGS
THEN STOP TALKING.
OKAY.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW,
WHERE WE EXPLORE THOSE THREE
LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
Audience:
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY DON'T EITHER.
THEY TALK AND
THEY DON'T KNOW NOTHING.
JOINING MY UNCLE RED
IS Mr. BUZZ SHERWOOD,
AND HE'S OUR LOCAL BUSH PILOT.
AND BUZZ, YOU'VE
BEEN FLYING SINCE --
UH, SINCE MY VERY FIRST
IRON BUTTERFLY CONCERT.
TODAY'S LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS.
IT SAYS...
"DEAR EXPERTS --"
LA-LA-LA.
LAST YEAR --
OH, THIS IS FROM
REDDING, PENNSYLVANIA.
THAT'S FAR AWAY.
GOTTO KEEP THE STAMP.
"DEAR EXPERTS: LAST YEAR OUR
SON TURNED 15 AND BEGAN
TO REALLY CHANGE,
"LOSING INTEREST IN SCHOOL,
"IGNORING HIS APPEARANCE,
"AVOIDING HIS FAMILY,
"ACTING WEIRDLY AND GENERALLY
TURNING INTO A ROTTEN KID.
"WHAT DID WE DO WRONG?"
WELL, I'LL TELL YOU,
IF I HAD A 15-YEAR-OLD KID,
I'D GET HIM A CAR WITH
A FULL TANK OF GAS,
POINT HIM TOWARD THE TOWN
WHERE NOBODY KNOWS ME,
AND WHATEVER HAPPENS HAPPENS.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE TO
BE 16 TO DRIVE A CAR.
WHATEVER HAPPENS HAPPENS.
NO WAY, RED!
YOU CAN'T PUT KIDS DOWN.
US KIDS, WE'RE THE HOPE
OF THE FUTURE GENERATION.
WE?
YOU'RE STILL A KID,
BUZZ, ARE YOU?
WELL, YEAH, BASICALLY,
BECAUSE I'M
ONLY 25-9
35, 39, 44 --
OH, MAN, I'M 46!
MAN, WHAT HAPPENED?
I THINK YOU SMOKED
THE CALENDAR.
I MEAN, THESE PARENTS THEY OUGHT
TO JUST BACK OFF ON THE KID
A LITTLE AND CHILL,
YOU KNOW, LIKE LET HIM
GO THROUGH THIS PHASE.
HE'S JUST REBELLING A LITTLE.
HE'LL GROW OUT OF IT.
TWHEN?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN HE'S 29, 34, 40 --
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
47.
YOU'RE 56.
I'M 52.
GOT YOU!
(LAUGHTER)
I JUST HAVE THE
ONE QUESTION REALLY.
WHY ARE FIREWORKS LEGAL?
AND WHAT KIND Of MIND WOULD
USE THEM AT A MALL OPENING,
AN INDOOR MALL OPENING?
I WAS IN MURRAY'S STORE
WHEN THEY WENT OFF.
BALL ROCKETS
GOING EVERYWHERE.
A COUPLE OF CANNON-CRACKERS
RIPPED THROUGH THE
GET-WELL CARDS.
I SAW TWO PINWHEELS GOING
ON A LINGERIE MANNEQUIN.
(LAUGHTER)
ACTUALLY THAT BROUGHT
BACK A FEW MEMORIES.
BUT THERE WAS
NO REAL DANGER
BECAUSE THEY GOT THE SPRINKLER
SYSTEM THERE AND THAT WENT OFF.
BY GOSH, THOSE UNITS CAN
REALLY PUMP OUT THE WATER,
JUST EVERYTHING.
UNFORTUNATELY THE
WATER WENT ALL DOWN
AND COMPLETELY FLOODED OUT
THE ENTIRE STORM SEWER,
AND I THINK THERE WERE
SOME SHOPPERS DOWN THERE.
(HAROLD'S SHOES SLOSHING)
OH, OH, OH.
WERE ALL THE
STORES FLOODED?
OH, YEAH.
OH, YEAH!
BOOKSTORE,
BAKERY,
TOY STORE.
OH, HAROLD.
OH, YEAH
WHAT? WHAT? WHAT?
EVEN THE BIG LADIES' UNDERWEAR
STORE GOT FLOODED OUT.
EITHER THAT OR BUSTER'S WIFE
IS GOING TO CATCH HER
DEATH OF COLD.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE
MAKING JOKES.
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH!
DON'T.
YOU SHOULDN'T.
I HOPE YOU LEARNED
SOMETHING TODAY.
I DID, HAROLD.
I LEARNED THAT NO MATTER
HOW MUCH PLANNING YOU DO,
THERE'S ALWAYS ONE IDIOT
WHO'LL MESS THINGS UP.
I ACCEPT THAT
AS AN APOLOGY.
I HOPE YOU LEARNED
SOMETHING TOO, HAROLD.
YES, I DID ACTUALLY.
OH, I LEARNED
SO MANY THINGS...
OH, YES, YES, YES, YES.
FIRST THING I LEARNED
THAT I CAN SWIM,
WHICH IS A VERY GOOD THING TO
KNOW AT TIMES LIKE THAT.
OH, YES.
AND I LEARNED WHILE
SWIMMING IN A SEWER,
I CAN HOLD MY BREATH
FOR TEN MINUTES.
WELL, THAT'S VERY,
VERY GOOD.
OH, IT'S VERY GOOD.
UNFORTUNATELY I WAS
IN THERE FOR AN HOUR!
(POSSUM CALL)
IT'S MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED. YEAH.
IS IT SAFE TO
GO DOWNSTAIRS?
YOU'LL BE FINE.
AWAY YOU GO.
I'LL BE DOWN
IN A MINUTE.
ALL RIGHT.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I'D LIKE TO APOLOGIZE FOR
THE MALL OPENING AND CLOSING.
BUT I THINK THAT'S THE END
OF FIREWORKS FOR ONE DAY,
UNLESS YOU'RE AWAKE
WHEN I COME HOME.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTER]
Harold:
OH, HERE HE IS.
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
TAKE YOUR SEATS PLEASE.
ALL RISE.
Everyone:
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red Green:
SIT DOWN.
Harold:
OKAY, I JUST HAVE
THE ONE ANNOUNCEMENT.
IT'S FROM BAKER'S FUNERAL HOME.
DURING THE FUNERAL PROCESSION
FOR MOOSE THOMPSON'S GRANDFATHER
THE OTHER DAY,
THEY BURNED OUT THE
CLUTCH ON THE HEARSE.
SO FOR THE NEXT TWO WEEKS ONLY,
Mr. BAKER IS FORCED TO USE
HIS SON'S STRATOCHIEF WAGON
AS A HEARSE.
YOU ALL KNOW THAT ONE.
IT'S THE BRIGHT YELLOW ONE WITH
THE FLAMES ACROSS THE HOOD.
IT SAYS "SATAN'S CHOICE"
ON THE TAILGATE.
HE SAYS IF YOU LIKE IT,
WE CAN KEEP USING IT.
SEEMS NO ONE'S
COMPLAINING SO FAR.