YOU KNOW THERE'S
NOTHING WORSE IN LIFE
THAN WHEN SOMETHING FUN
TURNS INTO WORK.
YOU MARRIED GUYS KNOW
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
YOU TAKE ICE
SKATING FOR EXAMPLE.
I MEAN THAT'S FUN.
BUT LIKE SO MANY
PHYSICAL ACTIVITIES,
IT'S TOO DARN PHYSICAL.
WELL, HERE'S A WAY YOU
CAN STRAP ON THE BLADES,
BURN AROUND THE ICE,
WITHOUT EVEN BREAKING A SWEAT.
RECOGNIZE THIS?
IT'S A ROTARY
TELEVISION AERIAL.
YOU KNOW IN THE
DAYS LONG BEFORE CABLE,
THE WHOLE STREET WOULD COME
ALIVE EVERY HALF-HOUR
WITH THESE BABIES
GRINDING AND HUMMING
AS Mr AND Mrs JOHN Q. PUBLIC
WOULD SPIN THE DIAL
IN SEARCH OF SOMETHING HALF
DECENT TO WATCH.
OKAY, NOWADAYS, WE'RE
ALL SUPPOSED TO BE WIRED
OR WIRELESS OR
ON-LINE OR SOMETHING,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN WE
CAN'T USE OUR ROTARY ANTENNAS
TO HAVE A
LITTLE BIT OF FUN.
[cheering and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
SURE DO APPRECIATE THAT.
YOU KNOW, THIS SEASON IS MY
FAVOURITE UP AT THE LODGE,
ALONG WITH THE OTHER
THREE, OF COURSE.
THIS IS THE HARVEST
TIME OF YEAR.
YOU CAN GET THE
FRESH FRUIT AND EVERYTHING.
IT'S - IT'S
REALLY A GREAT TIME.
I GOT SOME PLUMS
FOR YOU Mr GREEN.
YOU LIKE PLUMS?
OH, I SURE DO.
WHERE'D YOU
GET THOSE, MIKE?
THOMPSON'S ORCHARD.
OH,
THEY'LL BE GOOD.
HOW MUCH
THEY COST YOU?
NOTHING.
I JUST SAW THIS SIGN
THAT SAID "PICK YOUR OWN."
OH, I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
WERE SUPPOSED TO PAY.
THEY NEED A
BETTER SYSTEM.
BETTER FENCE, MIKE.
JUST PUT THEM ON THE
TABLE UNTIL THEY COOL
OFF A LITTLE, EH?
WOW! IS THIS THE
COMPUTER HAROLD SENT YOU?
YEAH, YEAH, HIS COMPANY'S
GETTING RID OF ALL THEIR
OLD COMPUTERS,
SO HE GAVE THEM TO ME.
THERE'S A FLATTERING GIFT.
I'M LIKE A GARBAGE MAN
WITHOUT A DUMP.
NO, YOU HAVE A DUMP.
HEY, RED, RED.
DID YOU GET MY E-MAIL?
NO, I HAVEN'T BEEN DOWN
TO THE POST OFFICE YET.
NO, IT'S E-MAIL.
YOU DON'T GO DOWN
TO THE POST OFFICE.
IT'S WAITING
IN YOUR COMPUTER.
HERE, LOOK.
YOU JUST DIAL
UP THE NETWORK.
WAIT FOR
A CONNECTION.
ENTER YOUR PASSWORD.
LISTEN.
SULTRY FEMALE VOICE:
You have mail.
THERE IT IS!
SEE!
THERE'S THE
E-MAIL I SENT YOU.
GO ON, READ IT.
READ IT.
"HI, RED."
ISN'T THAT GREAT!
NO PAPER.
NO ENVELOPE.
AND NO STAMP.
AND NO
PURPOSE, DALTON.
IT DOESN'T
COST ANYTHING?
LIKE E-MAIL
IS FREE MAIL?
NO, NOT QUITE, MIKE.
THE SERVER CHARGES YOU A MONTHLY
FEE ON YOUR CREDIT CARD.
OH, THERE'S A FEE.
SO IT'S FEMALE.
NO WONDER I DON'T
UNDERSTAND IT.
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW WE CALL
IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING.
JOINING ME
TODAY IS MIKE HAMAR.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
FOR US HERE, MIKE?
YEAH, I'VE GOT A
SUITCASE, OF MINE,
AND I CAN'T SEEM
TO GET IT OPEN, THOUGH.
WELL, IT'S
LOCKED, MIKE.
YEAH, AND WELL, YOU KNOW,
I'VE LOST THE KEYS.
WELL, YOU
DON'T NEED KEYS.
THESE ARE
COMBINATION LOCKS.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
I PACKED THIS
ABOUT A YEAR AGO,
AND I'VE JUST FORGOTTEN
ALL THE NUMBERS.
BUT I WAS HOPING
THAT MAYBE YOU COULD
TAKE THE HAMMER AND
SMASH THE LOCKS OFF.
THEN I COULD
GET IN, RIGHT?
THIS IS
A REPAIR SHOP.
IT'S NOT A
DESTROY SHOP.
YEAH, WELL, I KNOW,
BUT RIGHT NOW, THE SUITCASE
IS UNUSABLE, RIGHT?
SO IT'S, LIKE,
BROKEN IN A WAY.
BUT IF YOU SMASH
THE LOCKS OFF,
THEN I COULD
GET IN THERE,
AND THEN IT WOULD
BE FIXED IN A WAY.
OKAY, IF I HELP
YOU OPEN THIS SUITCASE
I'M AN ACCOMPLICE
IN A WAY.
WHAT?
NO. NO. NO.
YOU DON'T GET
IT, Mr GREEN.
THIS IS
MY SUITCASE.
HONEST.
HONEST, I SWEAR.
YOU SWEAR?
I SWEAR.
THE POSSUM LODGE SWEAR?
ALL RIGHT.
OH, BOY, I CAN HARDLY WAIT
TO SEE WHAT'S IN IT.
I MEAN TO REMEMBER
WHAT I LEFT INSIDE IT.
BLACK T-SHIRT.
ANOTHER
JEANS ALREADY
ROLLED UP.
WHITE SOCKS.
HOLY COW.
IT REALLY IS YOURS.
OH, I APOLOGIZE, MIKE.
I ALWAYS THINK
YOU'RE UP TO NO GOOD.
I'M SORRY
ABOUT THAT.
THAT'S OKAY,
Mr GREEN.
I FORGIVE YOU.
OH, HERE'S WHAT
I'M LOOKING FOR.
HERE IT IS,
MY BALACLAVA.
WHAT DO YOU NEED
A BALACLAVA FOR, MIKE?
I NEED IT
FOR SNOWMOBILING.
IT'S NOT
WINTER YET.
I MEAN I NEED IT
TO GET A SNOWMOBILE.
THANKS A
LOT, Mr GREEN.
MIKE. MIKE. MIKE!
[hoarse breathing]
THIS BETTER
BE GOOD, HAROLD.
I BURNED HALF A
TANK OF GAS
AND AN AFTERNOON NAP
JUST GETTING DOWN HERE.
OKAY. OKAY.
UNCLE RED.
YOU KNOW HOW SOME
REALLY IMPORTANT PEOPLE
HAVE SOMEONE WHO
DOES EVERYTHING FOR THEM,
EVERY MENIAL TASK,
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE TOO BUSY
OR TOO LAZY TO
DO FOR THEMSELVES?
WELL, YEAH.
THAT'S WHY I'M
THE LODGE LEADER, HAROLD.
OKAY. AROUND HERE,
WE CALL THEM SECRETARIES.
OH, MY GOSH,
YOU GOT YOURSELF A PROMOTION.
YEAH, STARTING TODAY.
WELL,
WHERE IS SHE?
WHO?
WELL, YOUR
NEW SECRETARY.
WELL, WHO SAYS THE SECRETARY
HAS TO BE A WOMAN?
WELL, ALL RIGHT,
Mr 21ST CENTURY.
WHAT PATHETIC GUY DID THEY HIRE
TO BE YOUR SECRETARY?
I'M NOT GETTING
A SECRETARY.
I AM THE
SECRETARY.
YEAH. I'M THE SECRETARY TO THE
VICE-PRESIDENT OF MERGERS
AND ACQUISITIONS.
LA LA
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU GOT A PROMOTION?
THIS IS
A PROMOTION.
I ACTUALLY RANK
HIGHER IN THE COMPANY,
THAN MY SUPERVISOR
IN MY OLD DEPARTMENT.
I'M GOING TO BE HELPING
THE BOSS ORGANIZE MEETINGS,
SCHEDULING THINGS.
WOMAN'S VOICE:
Harold, could you come
in here for a moment, please?
YES, MA'AM.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
WHO WAS
THAT, HAROLD?
MY BOSS, THE VICE-PRESIDENT OF
MERGERS AND ACQUISITIONS.
OH, MAN, HAROLD,
YOU'VE GOT
A WOMEN BOSS.
SO? SO DO YOU,
AUNT BERNICE.
OH, COME ON, HAROLD.
THAT'S DIFFERENT.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I GET PAID.
WELCOME TO
TALKING ANIMALS
WITH THE LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER, ED FRID.
I UNDERSTAND THAT
ED HAS BROUGHT IN
A VERY, VERY
DANGEROUS SNAKE TODAY.
SO C'MON
UP HERE, ED.
NO, NO, C'MON.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
C'MON UP HERE.
SO WHAT KIND
OF SNAKE IS THIS?
IT'S A COBRA.
A COBRA. WOW!
YOU BROUGHT IN A COBRA.
YEAH. YEAH.
WHAT WAS
I THINKING?
OKAY, SO, CAN WE HAVE A
LOOK AT IT, ED?
OH. NO. NO.
UM, I THINK WE'D BETTER JUST
LEAVE IT IN THE BASKET.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S KIND OF WUSSY.
RED, THIS IS A
BLACK-NECKED COBRA,
BETTER KNOWN AS
A SPITTING COBRA.
OH, THEY SPIT
THE POISON, YEAH.
HOW FAR CAN THAT
COBRA SPIT THE POISON?
FARTHER
THAN THIS.
ARE WE
SAFE HERE, ED?
OH, YEAH, AS LONG AS THE
LID STAYS ON THE BASKET.
UH, ED.
WHAT?
I THINK THE LID
CAME OFF THE BASKET.
REALLY?
UM, WHAT ARE
YOU GONNA DO?
I HAVE NO PLANS.
WHY DON'T YOU PUT THE
LID BACK ON THE BASKET?
WHY DON'T YOU PUT THE LID
BACK ON THE BASKET?
OH. OH.
AH! AH!
OH-H-H.
STAY STILL.
DON'T MOVE.
HE'S STARING
RIGHT AT ME, ED.
DON'T MOVE.
HE'S GETTING
READY TO SPIT.
OH, SO AM I.
OR DID YOU SAY SPIT?
TAKE THIS
GARBAGE CAN LID,
AND PUT IT IN
FRONT OF YOUR FACE.
IT WILL
SHIELD YOU.
BRACE YOURSELF.
I'M OKAY.
Red:
I'M SURE THIS
HAS HAPPENED TO YOU.
YOU'RE DRIVING
DOWN THE STREET
THINKING ABOUT YOUR LIFE AND HOW
IT'S EVERYBODY ELSE'S FAULT,
WHEN ALL OF A SUDDEN...
ALL RIGHT, NO MATTER HOW
MAD YOU GET AT THESE
SMART-ALEC'S,
DON'T RUN AFTER THEM.
YOU'LL JUST
LOOK LIKE A FOOL.
NEVER CHASE TEENAGERS.
YOU'LL EITHER
HAVE A HEART ATTACK
OR FALL ON THE ICE AND RIP THE
CROTCH RIGHT OUT OF YOUR PANTS.
THAT'S MORE
OF A SUMMER THING.
I SAY,
DON'T GET MAD,
GET CREATIVE.
WHAT I'VE DONE HERE
IS TAKEN AN OLD PIE PLATE,
NAILED IT ONTO
THE BOTTOM END OF MY HAMMER.
THAT'S ACTUALLY
GOING TO BE A VALVE,
BUT YOU KNOW I'M GETTING A
LITTLE AHEAD OF MYSELF HERE.
BEFORE I DO THAT,
I'M GOING TO MOUNT THIS OLD
COOLER ON THE ROOF OF
THE POSSUM VAN.
BUT BEFORE
I DO THAT,
I'M GOING TO MAKE UP
A HUGE BATCH OF SNOWBALLS
AND PUT
THEM IN HERE.
OH, MAN.
DARN SUPERBOWL.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS WHERE THE
HAMMER-VALVE COMES IN.
I'VE GOT IT MOUNTED
ON THE CEILING HERE,
AND I'VE PUNCHED A HOLE
UP THROUGH THE COOLER
AND THROUGH THE ROOF OF THE VAN.
ACTUALLY THERE ALREADY WAS
A HOLE IN THE ROOF OF THE VAN.
DON'T EVER GO OVER A SPEED BUMP
WITH A POP CAN IN YOUR HAND.
NOW, I GOT THIS STRING ATTACHED
TO THE BOTTOM OF THE HAMMER,
AND WHEN I'M READY
FOR A SNOWBALL...
YOU'D BE AMAZED
AT HOW EASY THESE
PITCHING MACHINES
ARE TO COME BY
IN THE OFF SEASON.
ALL I'VE GOT TO DO NOW
IS GET IT UP INTO THE VAN,
LINE HER UP
UNDER THE SNOWBALL HOLE,
AND SET THE CONTROL
FOR THE HIGH, HARD ONE.
ALL RIGHT, I'VE GOT HER ALL
LINED UP AND IN POSITION.
NOW ALL I'VE GOT TO DO IS
CLOSE MY BOMBAY DOORS.
THIS IS GREAT, ISN'T IT?
I'VE ALSO GOT AN IDEA
ON HOW TO STOP KIDS FROM
HANGING ON TO
YOUR BACK BUMPER.
I'LL GIVE YOU A HINT.
IT INVOLVES A HEAVY-DUTY
TRUCK BATTERY.
BUT FIRST, LET'S GO KICK SOME
SNOWBALL-THROWING BUTT.
WELL, DALTON, I'M SURE GLAD
YOU CAME BY TO SEE ME
BEFORE YOU ABANDONED
YOUR FAMILY AND HEADED
OFF TO MEXICO.
THE YUCATAN, RED.
IT'S THE YUCATAN,
AND I WOULDN'T HAVE
COME TO SEE YOU
IF I DIDN'T NEED 50
BUCKS FOR GAS.
WELL, I WASN'T GOING
TO GIVE YOU CASH, DALTON.
I WAS JUST GOING TO
LEND YOU MY SIPHON HOSE.
IS IT WRONG?
IS IT CRAZY FOR ME
TO HAVE A DREAM?
IS IT WRONG FOR ME
TO WANT TO HELP PEOPLE?
WELL, NO.
NOT NECESSARILY.
BUT I JUST THINK RUNNING OFF
TO JOIN A LEPER COLONY
IS MAYBE A LITTLE EXTREME.
WELL, IT'S
MY DREAM, RED.
I WANT TO GO SOMEPLACE PRIMITIVE
WHERE I CAN HELP UNFORTUNATES.
YOU CAN DO THAT
RIGHT AT THE LODGE HERE.
IT'S NOT
THE SAME THING.
NO, I KNOW, DALTON.
IS IT POSSIBLE THAT
YOUR RUNNING OFF TO
A LEPER COLONY
INDICATES MAYBE YOU'VE GOT SOME
TROUBLES HERE AT HOME?
WELL, POSSIBLY.
I THINK MAYBE YOU'RE
RUNNING OFF TO A
LEPER COLONY
TO AVOID TALKING
TO YOUR WIFE.
I ALSO THINK YOU SHOULD
GO UPSTAIRS RIGHT NOW
AND SAY SOMETHING
NICE TO HER.
WELL, LIKE WHAT?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW, DALTON.
WHAT DID YOU TWO TALK ABOUT
WHEN YOU WERE DATING?
AMWAY.
DID YOU TELL HER ABOUT
YOUR LITTLE ADVENTURE
YOU GOT PLANNED?
YES, YES, I LEFT
A NOTE SAYING
THAT I WAS GOING TO LIVE
IN A LEPER COLONY IN
THE YUCATAN.
[woman laughing]
YES!
CHAMPAGNE.
SHE'S TAKING
IT WELL.
[woman singing and cheering]
MAN, THIS COMPUTER
CRAZE IS WRECKING OUR TOWN.
NOBODY IS OUTDOORS.
NOBODY IS DOING ANYTHING.
INSTEAD OF PULLED MUSCLES
AND HERNIAS
ALL WE GOT IS
CARPAL-TUNNEL SYNDROME.
I GOT NO USE
FOR THE DARN THING.
BUT YOU CAN'T
EVEN TURN IT OFF.
IT'S LIKE HAROLD.
OH, YOU CAN
TURN IT OFF, RED.
JUST GOT TO SHUT
ALL THE WINDOWS FIRST.
WELL, NOW,
THAT MAKES SENSE.
YOU GOT TO KEEP UP
WITH TECHNOLOGY,
OR IT'S GOING TO
LEAVE YOU BEHIND.
THIS ISN'T
PROGRESS, DALTON.
EVERYBODY IS LOCKED
AWAY IN THEIR HOUSE
SENDING OUT MESSAGES,
LIKE THEY'RE CAVEMEN
BEATING ON THEIR DRUMS,
FOR GOSH SAKES.
SULTRY FEMALE VOICE:
You have mail.
OKAY, HOW MANY E-MAIL
MESSAGES IS THAT FOR ME?
NINETY-THREE.
ALTHOUGH 85 OF THEM ARE
ME ASKING YOU TO PICK
UP YOUR E-MAIL.
YOU KNOW, RED, THERE'S
WAY MORE TO COMPUTERS THAN THIS.
COME ON OVER HERE I'LL SHOW
YOU HOW THE INTERNET WORKS.
OH, I KNOW,
WWW.SIT-ON-YOUR-BUTT-FOR-
12-HOURS-A-DAY.COM.
THIS IS THE GREATEST SOURCE
OF INFORMATION IN THE WORLD.
OKAY, NOW, SAY YOU WANTED TO
KNOW SOMETHING ABOUT, UM,
PLUMS.
OKAY, YOU TYPE IN PLUMS.
LOOK AT ALL THE
INFORMATION YOU GET.
LOOK. LOOK.
THERE'S A GUY WITH
THE WORLD'S LARGEST PLUM.
WOW! LOOK AT THE
SIZE OF THAT THING!
NO, HE'S HOLDING
THE PLUM.
YOU'RE LOOKING
AT HIS WIFE.
AND LOOK, HERE'S SOME
STUFF YOU DIDN'T KNOW,
LIKE PLUMS GOT
VITAMIN C AND D,
THEY FLOAT,
AND PLUMS
CONDUCT ELECTRICITY.
OH, NO.
NOT THESE ONES.
MIKE SAID
THERE WAS NO CHARGE.
OH, RED, RED,
IT'S DONE ON TIME.
I GOT MY NEW ANIMATED
FEATURE READY ON TIME.
WERE YOU WORRIED?
YOU ALWAYS
WORRY ME, GORD.
YOU KNOW, THIS FILM
IS A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
I STILL DREW ALL THE
PICTURES AND DID
ALL THE VOICES,
BUT I THINK THE SUBJECT
MATTER IS VERY EDGY.
YES, WELL, I'M VERY EDGY
RIGHT NOW MYSELF.
OH, SUET?
UM, NO THANK YOU.
NO, NO, NO.
YOU SURE?
WINTER'S COMING.
NOT IF I EAT
THAT IT ISN'T.
NOW, RED, HOW MUCH DO
YOU KNOW ABOUT ROCKS?
ROCKS?
OH, I KNOW
ENOUGH ABOUT ROCKS.
NOT ENOUGH.
LET ME TEACH YOU.
WATCH.
[quirky upbeat music]
PLEASE, MASTER RANGER GORD,
TEACH US THE WAYS OF,
LIKE, HOW NATURE IS.
FINE THEN.
PAY ATTENTION.
YOUR FIRST LESSON WILL BE ABOUT
THESE THICK-SHELLED EGGS,
WHICH OCCUR ABUNDANTLY
IN NATURE.
UH, THAT'S A STONE GORD.
WOW! THAT STONE
WAS AN EGG.
ALL STONES ARE EGGS.
OPEN YOUR EYES, YOU FOOLS.
SO ALL OF THESE
STONES AROUND US, EH,
ARE ACTUALLY EGGS.
DON'T YOU SEE?
STONES HAVE BEEN FOOLING
US FOR MANY YEARS.
WE'VE JUST ASSUMED THAT
STONES ARE MADE OUT OF
NOTHING BUT ROCK.
WHERE DO THE STONES THAT ARE
ACTUALLY EGGS COME FROM?
ATTRACTIVE WOMEN
IN HOT AIR BALLOONS
DISTRIBUTE THE EGGS ALL
AROUND THE WORLD.
OH, THAT'S
RIDICULOUS, GORD.
HI, Mr RANGER GORD.
WE LOVE YOU.
WOMEN HAVE A THING FOR ME.
I HOPE SOME DAY I CAN ATTRACT
WOMEN THE WAY YOU DO,
MASTER RANGER GORD.
GET REAL.
UH, Mr RANGER GORD,
IS THAT STONE YOU'RE
SITTING ON ALSO
AN EGG, EH?
THAT IS CORRECT.
I AM ABOUT TO HATCH THIS EGG.
WELL, WHAT WILL THAT
STONE HATCH INTO?
THIS EGG WILL HATCH INTO
A BLACK HOLE, WHICH WILL DEVOUR
ALL IGNORANCE FROM MILES AROUND.
YOU SEE, BOYS AND GIRLS?
IGNORANCE IS BLISS.
UNTIL A STONE HATCHES INTO A
BLACK HOLE, THAT IS.
[laughing]
DO GO OUT ON A DATE,
YOU KNOW,
LIKE, EVER?
OH, YEAH, ACTUALLY,
I GOT A DATE TONIGHT.
SO WHERE ARE YOU GOING
ON THIS HOT DATE, ANYWAY?
OH, THE MOVIES.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S CHEAP NIGHT AT
THE MOVIES, EH?
TWO GET IN FOR
THE PRICE OF ONE.
THAT'S GOOD THINKING.
WELL, SHE USUALLY
PAYS FOR HERSELF.
I DON'T MIND.
ACTUALLY, SHE'LL PROBABLY
PAY FOR BOTH OF US.
SHE MAKES MORE
MONEY THAN I DO.
I DON'T THINK
THAT MATTERS, DALE.
I MEAN, YOU ASKED HER OUT.
SHE'S YOUR GUEST.
NO, SHE ASKED ME OUT.
SHE ASKED YOU OUT?
SHE PHONED YOU
AND ASKED YOU OUT?
YEAH.
SHE JUST COMES UP
TO YOU AND SAYS,
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU AND I
GO OUT AND PAINT THE TOWN,
LIKE SHE'S THE GUY
AND YOU'RE THE GIRL?
RIGHT.
YOU'VE GOT TO PROVE TO HER
THAT YOU CAN SHOW HER
A GOOD TIME.
LIKE, OF ALL THE
GUYS IN THE WORLD,
SHE'S GOTTA FEEL LIKE SHE'S
LUCKY TO BE WITH YOU.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
ISN'T THAT IMPORTANT TO YOU?
NOPE.
OH, MAN!
GET AWAY FROM THOSE TREASURES,
YOU MARTIAN PIGS!
YOU WANT MORE OF THIS, DO YOU?
YOU WANNA A PIECE OF ME?!
HEY, WHAT HAPPENED?
COME ON!
HEY, SHOULDN'T YOU CLOSE THE
WINDOWS BEFORE YOU BEAT THE
CRAP OUT OF THE COMPUTER?
RED, THE POWER'S GONE OFF.
CAN'T YOU DO SOMETHING?
WELL, I CAN DO LOTS
OF THINGS, DALTON.
THE SUN IS SHINING.
I CAN GO BOATING.
I CAN GO FISHING.
I CAN GO HIKING.
TURN THE POWER ON!
I WAS ON LEVEL FOUR.
I THINK YOU PROBABLY
JUST BLEW THE FUSE HERE.
YEAH, YEAH,
YOU GOT --
GEEZ, DALTON, I HAVEN'T
GOT ANY SPARES.
YOU GOT A COIN?
NO, I HAVEN'T
GOT A COIN!
WELL, GET ME ONE
OF THOSE PLUMS.
I LEARNED ON THE INTERNET THAT
THEY CONDUCT ELECTRICITY.
THAT'S IT!
YOU SEE?
I HOPE IT'S
RIGHT-HAND THREAD.
[explosion]
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD.
NO.
RED, YOU WRECKED
THE COMPUTER.
NO, NO, NO,
YOU DID IT, DALTON.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE
PICKED SUCH A BIG PLUM.
TOO MUCH JUICE.
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD,
Mr GATES.
I'LL BE DOWN
IN A MINUTE.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND, YES, I KNOW
IT'S THE COMPUTER AGE,
BUT LET'S NOT FORGET ABOUT
PERSONAL INTERACTION.
WHEN I GET HOME,
I WANNA SHOW YOU THAT
I'M USER FRIENDLY.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
EVERYBODY GO SIT DOWN NOW.
GO SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, EVERYBODY.
YOU GOTTA SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, AND BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
Dalton:
OR GET AN UPGRADE.
COMPUTER TALK.