THIS HERE IS A TWO-MAN SAW,
AND I'M ONLY ONE MAN.
SEE THE PROBLEM?
AND I'M THE KINDA GUY WHO'D
RATHER FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO DO THIS BY MYSELF
THAN TO ASK SOMEBODY FOR HELP
AND THEN OWE THEM A FAVOUR
WHERE I'VE GOTTA
LEND 'EM A TOOL
OR FIND A BLIND DATE
FOR THEIR SISTER.
SO I'VE COME UP WITH
THE RED GREEN
ONE-MAN TWO-MAN SAW.
FIRST OF ALL,
ON THE ONE HANDLE,
YOU WANNA HOOK
A COUPLE OF BUNGEE CORDS,
AND THEN ATTACH THEM
TO SOMETHING FIXED,
NOT YOUR CAT.
THEN ON THE OTHER HANDLE,
THROW A HUNK OF
CHAIN ON THERE.
NOW, YOU NEED A WAY TO HOOK
THIS CHAIN ONTO ONE OF
YOUR WHEEL NUTS
SO THAT IT WON'T SLIP OFF.
SEE, NO PROBLEM
FOR THE CREATIVE HANDYMAN.
AND THAT'S PRETTY MUCH
ALL THERE IS TO IT.
HEY, IF YOU HAVE ONE OF THOSE
NON-SLIP DEFERENTIALS,
GIVE ME A CALL
BEFORE YOU TRY THIS.
I REALLY ENJOY A GOOD LAUGH.
AND LIKE SO MANY GOOD
THINGS IN LIFE,
IT'S BETTER IF YOU START SLOW
AND THEN SPEED UP LATER.
[applause]
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YEAH, APPRECIATE THAT.
BIG SCHAMOZZLE UP
AT THE LODE THIS WEEK.
HAROLD BROUGHT A BUNCH OF
EXECUTIVE PENCIL NECKS
UP FROM THAT COMPANY
HE WORKS FOR IN THE CITY.
THEY'VE BEEN STAYIN'
AT THE LODGE ALL WEEK.
THEY'RE LIKE ACCOUNTANTS,
BUT WITHOUT ALL
THE PERSONALITY.
EXCUSE ME, UNCLE RED.
I HAVE TO TALK TO YOU.
I GOTTA TALK TO YOU.
DID THE MASSEUSE DROP
THE CAPPUCCINO MAKER
IN TO THE SPA?
NO, NO, I JUST WONDERED.
WHAT IS THAT SMELL COMING FROM
STINKY PETERSON'S CABIN?
STINKY PETERSON.
WELL, ISN'T THAT DANGEROUS
OR TOXIC OR SOMETHING?
WELL, WE MONITOR IT
PRETTY CLOSELY, HAROLD.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE THE
CANARIES HANGING BY
THE DOOR THERE.
PLUS, YOU KNOW,
WHEN HE'S NOT THERE,
THE SMELL IS GONE.
OKAY, OKAY, SO IT'S
NOT THE CABIN ITSELF?
NO. NO.
I THINK THE AROMA'S
LIKE A LIVING ORGANISM
THAT IS USING
STINKY AS A HOST.
PBS SHOULD GET
HIM ON NOVA.
A LOT OF MY GUYS
ARE RATHER CONCERNED.
WELL, OF COURSE
THEY ARE, HAROLD,
BECAUSE THEY ARE
YUPPIE WHINERS.
N-NO!
DON'T EVEN --
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
YOU KNOW WE DON'T EVEN
WANNA BE HERE EITHER.
IT'S JUST THAT THIS IS THE ONLY
RESORT THAT WASN'T BOOKED,
AND, YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT
YOU'D APPRECIATE THE MONEY.
I DON'T MIND
THE MONEY.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO HAVE
TO DO ANYTHING FOR IT.
EXCELLENT.
THAT'S PERFECT.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT MY BOSS
WAS HOPING YOU WOULD SAY.
UNCLE RED, ON BEHALF OF
MULTI-CORP INTERNATIONAL INC.,
I AM AUTHORIZED TO EXTEND
TO YOU A VERY GENEROUS
CASH OFFER
FOR POSSUM LODGE, ALL ITS
PROPERTIES AND BUILDINGS
EXCLUDING
VEHICLES AND BOATS.
WHAT?!
YEAH, THEY WANNA TURN THIS
WHOLE PLACE INTO, LIKE,
A WORLD CLASS RETREAT,
YOU KNOW, FOR THEIR
CORPORATE EXECUTIVES.
IT'S GREAT.
IT'LL LEAVE YOU
ENOUGH MONEY TO RETIRE ON.
YEAH, WELL,
WHAT'LL I DO?
NOTHIN',
JUST LIKE NOW.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
AND TODAY'S GREAT PRIZE
IS A BRAND NEW HOUSE...
ROOF SHINGLE.
AND PLAYING FOR
TODAY'S GREAT PRIZE
IS THE LUCKY CONTESTANT,
Mr. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
Mr. GREEN, YOU HAVE 30 SEC --
COVER YOUR EARS.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS TO
GET Mr. ROTHSCHILD TO
SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON,
THIS IS A REALLY BAD THING.
LEAKY HIP WADERS?
NO, NO, NO.
OKAY.
OKAY, WHEN THERE'S A FLOOD,
WHAT DO YOU CALL THAT?
A CHANCE TO SELL MY BOAT.
SAY THE LODGE BURNS DOWN,
AND I LOSE EVERYTHING,
WHAT WOULD THAT BE FOR ME?
A FRESH START.
NO, NO, NO.
OKAY, WHAT DO
YOU THINK OF
WHEN YOU THINK OF HURRICANES,
EARTHQUAKES, TORNADOES?
RESORT HOLIDAY!
NO, I'M TALKIN' ABOUT
PEOPLE HURT BADLY,
THROWN OUT ON THE STREET.
MIDDLE-AGED GUYS
TRYING TO ROLLER BLADE.
THE TITANIC HIT
THAT ICEBERG, RIGHT?
THEY SAID THAT WAS THE WORST
SOMETHING OF ALL TIME.
DRIVING?
ALMOST OUTTA TIME,
Mr. GREEN.
WINSTON, YOU REMEMBER YOU
DATED THAT AROMATHERAPIST?
OH, DISASTER.
[applause]
IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYIN'.
JOININ' US TODAY IS LOCAL
EXPLOSIVES ENTHUSIAST,
EDGAR K. B. MONTROSE.
WHAT YOU GOT
FOR US, EDGAR?
YEAH, IT IS A
BEAUTIFUL DAY,
BUT THAT'S NOT
WHY I'M HERE.
I NEED YOU TO FIX MY
EXPLOSIVES LOCATOR.
OH, THIS THING FINDS
EXPLOSIVES, EDGAR?
WELL, IT WILL
AFTER YOU FIX IT.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
YEAH.
IT'S A SAFETY TOOL.
IT HELPS ME FIND EXPLOSIVES THAT
I MIGHT HAVE LEFT LYING AROUND,
OR MAYBE JUST FELL OUT OF MY
POCKET WHEN I WAS RUNNING AWAY.
WELL, IT CAN'T BE GOOD TO BE
LOSIN' EXPLOSIVES, EDGAR.
OH, THAT'S FOR SURE,
BUT I ALWAYS LOSE 'EM.
THE BUNCH OF US WERE HAVING
A CAMPFIRE COOKOUT
THE OTHER NIGHT,
AND, YOU KNOW,
IN THE DARK,
STICKS OF DYNAMITE
LOOK A LOT LIKE KINDLING.
THAT MUST'VE BEEN
QUITE A CAMPFIRE.
OH, THE DYNAMITE GOT
IT GOIN' PRETTY FAST.
BUT IT BLEW ALL OUR
WEENIES OUT INTO THE LAKE.
I DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT
ELECTRONICS, EDGAR.
WELL, IT'S PROBABLY
JUST AN ADJUSTMENT.
YOU SEE, WHEN YOU
PUSH THIS BUTTON HERE,
THIS UNIT SENDS OUT A
WEAK ELECTRICAL SIGNAL
UH-HUH.
THAT THE EXPLOSIVE
REACTS TO.
THEN THE MACHINE
CAN SENSE THAT
AND FIND IT FOR YOU.
WELL, THERE'S A THING HERE,
IT'S AT ONE AND A HALF,
AND THE DIAL GOES
ALL THE WAY TO TEN.
HOW HIGH DO YOU
WANT ME TO SET THAT?
ELEVEN.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, THERE YOU GO.
YOU WANNA GIVE 'ER A TRY?
WELL, LET ME JUST AIM
HER DOWN TOWARD
THE BOATHOUSE.
I THINK I MIGHT'VE
DROPPED A FEW CHARGES
WHEN I FELL
OFF THE ROOF.
BUT THIS'LL HELP
ME FIND 'EM.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, HERE GOES
NOTHIN'.
I FOUND 'EM.
THANKS, RED.
[applause]
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN
HAULING THIS GARBAGE CAN
IN AND OUT OF THE DRIVEWAY
EVERY WEEK FOR
THE LAST 30 YEARS.
AND I'VE ALWAYS
HAD TO DO IT MYSELF
BECAUSE CRUEL FATE HAS
DENIED US THE BLESSING
OF HAVING A TEENAGER
AROUND THE HOUSE.
I'M THINKING TO MYSELF,
YOU KNOW, THERE HAS
TO BE A BETTER WAY,
A WAY OF REPLACING WASTED ENERGY
WITH INNOVATION AND ENGINEERING.
AND THEN IT CAME TO ME.
HOW ABOUT A MECHANICAL HOIST
COMING OFF THE POSSUM VAN
THAT WOULD DO THE WORK FOR ME?
IF THOSE SCIENTIST GUYS
CAN MAKE A CANADARM,
WHY CAN'T I MAKE A
GARBAGE CANADARM?
HERE'S WHAT I
FIGURE YOU NEED...
SOME P.V.C. PIPE,
COUPLE OF 45-DEGREE ELBOWS,
HEAVY DUTY FISHING ROD,
COUPLE OF DESK LAMPS,
COUPLE OF COAT HOOKS,
AND A TRUMPET.
OKAY, SO FIRST THING YOU WANNA
DO IS CUT THE P.V.C. PIPE
SO YOU GET AN ARM COMING OFF
THE MIDDLE OF THE ROOF
OF THE VAN,
SWINGING OUT OVER THE SIDE.
AND THEN YOU GLUE THE WHOLE
SCHAMOZZLE TOGETHER
WITH THIS SPECIAL
P.V.C. CEMENT.
EIGHT MILES HIGH --
YOU REALLY WANNA HAVE
PROPER VENTILATION
WHEN YOU'RE WORKING WITH
THE PLASTIC CEMENT.
I COULD'VE LOST A FEW BRAIN
CELLS THERE, I TELL YOU.
WHAT YEAR IS THIS?
OH, WELL.
ANYWAY, WE GOT THE ARM PART.
NOW WE NEED TO ADD THE
ENGINEERING TO IT.
SO WHAT YOU WANNA
DO FIRST OF ALL IS
DUCT TAPE THE COAT HOOKS TO THE
ENDS OF THE DESK LAMPS,
LIKE I'VE DONE HERE.
AND THIS IS IN KEEPING WITH
NASAU'S SPECIFICATIONS.
THESE HOOKS ARE DESIGNED TO
ENGAGE THE HANDLES OF
THE GARBAGE CAN,
EVEN IN A
ZERO-GRAVITY SITUATION.
MIND YOU, IF WE GET
ZERO GRAVITY HERE ON EARTH,
I'M NOT SURE TAKING OUT THE
GARBAGE WOULD BE A TOP PRIORITY.
ANYWAY, THEN WHAT YOU DO IS
YOU DUCT TAPE THE
DESK LAMPS THEMSELVES
TO THE ENDS OF THE PIPE.
AND MAKE SURE YOU HOOK UP
THE LAMP PARTS, EH.
THAT WAY YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO SEE AT NIGHT
BECAUSE THERE'S CERTAIN
KINDS OF GARBAGE
YOU REALLY ONLY WANNA
TAKE OUT AFTER DARK.
NOW WE NEED SOMETHING THAT WILL
SEPARATE THE DESK LAMPS OUT
AND ALSO SERVE AS A GUIDE
FOR OUR FISHING LINE.
NOW, THAT'S WHERE
THE TRUMPET COMES IN.
WE DON'T NEED
THE WHOLE THING,
JUST THE LOUD PART.
OKAY, THERE'S OUR
GUIDE MOUNTED IN PLACE,
AND NOW ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS
RUN THE FISHING LINES UP
FROM THE REEL,
UP THROUGH THE PIPE,
OUT THROUGH THE BELL
OF THE TRUMPET,
AND THEN HOOK ONE ONTO EACH
OF THESE DESK LAMPS.
THAT WAY, WE CAN KIND OF
CONTROL THE OPENING AND
CLOSING OF OUR CLAW.
NOW ALL WE GOTTA DO
IS TAKE THIS UNIT
AND MOUNT IT ONTO
THE ROOF OF THE VAN.
BOY, IF ONLY WE HAD SOME
KIND OF ROTATING MOUNT
THAT WOULD GIVE US SOME
FLEXIBILITY
SO THAT WE COULD SORT OF
SWING THE ARM AROUND --
OH, THERE WE GO.
OKAY, THERE'S OUR 360°
FLOATING MOUNT,
AND I'VE MOUNTED THE
FISHING REEL ONTO THERE
WITH THE LINES RUNNING
DOWN TO THE DESK LAMPS.
SO WE'RE PRETTY WELL
READY TO GO.
OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
MOUNT THE UNIT
ON THERE LOOSELY
SO THAT YOU CAN RAISE
THE ARM UP AND DOWN
JUST BY LEANING
ON THE HANDLE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW LET'S TRY OUT
OUR GARBAGE CANADARM.
WHEN YOU'RE TALKING
WASTED SPACE,
THINK OF ME.
I READ AN ARTICLE
IN A MAGAZINE
ABOUT WHAT MEN CAN EXPECT FROM
THEIR BODIES AT THE AGE OF 45.
APPARENTLY NOT MUCH.
ABOUT NOW, OUR BODIES
ARE LIKE OUR TIRES...
BALD, SOFT, AND LEAKY.
MOST OF US HAVE PUT ON
A FAIR AMOUNT OF WEIGHT.
WE'RE EVEN KIND OF A DIFFERENT
SHAPE THAN WE USED TO BE.
SOMETIMES YOU LOOK
AT YOUR SHADOW
AND YOU GOTTA MOVE SOMETHING
JUST TO MAKE SURE IT'S YOU.
NOW, YOU'RE GONNA BE UNDER
A LOT OF PRESSURE TO GET FIT,
BUT I SAY,
DON'T BE DOING THAT.
THIS IS NOT THE TIME TO GO
OUT FOR A TEN-MILE RUN
FOLLOWED BY TWO HOURS
OF WEIGHT LIFTING.
THAT TRAIN LEFT
MANY YEARS AGO,
AND, BUDDY,
YOU WEREN'T ON IT.
YOU WERE IN THE DEPARTURE LOUNGE
EATING FRIES AND GRAVY.
SO I SAY JUST RELAX.
DON'T PANIC.
YEAH, SURE, YOUR BODY'S
GETTIN' BIGGER
WHILE YOUR BRAIN'S
GETTIN' SMALLER,
BUT THE TWO OF THEM HAVE GOTTEN
ALONG FOR ALMOST HALF A CENTURY
BY NOT EXPECTING TOO
MUCH OF EACH OTHER.
DON'T WRECK IT.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
NOW, MEN, I DON'T EVEN
WANNA WASTE YOUR TIME
WITH THIS ONE,
BUT YOU'RE LODGE MEMBERS,
AND UNFORTUNATELY,
IT'S A DEMOCRACY,
SO YOU GET TO
VOTE ON THIS,
EVEN THOUGH WE ALL KNOW
THIS ONE'S GOING
DOWN THE DUMPER.
IT'S JUST A QUESTION OF
HOW HARD IT'S GONNA HIT.
HAROLD.
WELL, THANK YOU
FOR THAT IMPARTIAL
INTRODUCTION, UNCLE RED.
WELL, MAYBE YOU'VE HEARD,
BUT MULTI-CORP HAS MADE A VERY
GENEROUS OFFER TO PURCHASE
POSSUM LODGE
AND ALL ITS BUILDINGS
AND PROPERTIES.
IT'S A CASH OFFER WITH ONLY
A COUPLE CONDITIONS...
THE DEAL'S SET TO CLOSE IN,
LIKE, 30 DAYS, RIGHT;
AND EVEN AFTER ALL THE BACK
TAXES, ENVIRONMENTAL COSTS
HAVE BEEN PAID,
EACH LODGE MEMBER
CAN WALK AWAY WITH
OVER $25,000!
ALL IN FAVOUR.
WAIT. WAIT. WAIT.
PUT THE HANDS DOWN.
PUT 'EM DOWN.
I'M THE LODGE
LEADER, HAROLD.
I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO
CAN CALL FOR A VOTE.
I'M SORRY.
YES, YOU'RE
ABSOLUTELY --
HE'S RIGHT.
OKAY, YOU GO AHEAD
AND CALL FOR THE VOTE.
I WILL.
IN A MINUTE.
PUT 'EM DOWN.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL 'EM ABOUT
THOSE CONDITIONS FIRST?
OH, OKAY, WELL,
THE DEAL CAN'T CLOSE
UNTIL THAT TIRE FIRE
IS PUT OUT
IN THE NORTH END
OF THE PROPERTY.
THAT THING'S BEEN
BURNIN' SINCE, LIKE --
I DUNNO WHEN.
THAT'S A LANDMARK,
HAROLD.
ARE YOU ASKING US TO TURN
OUR BACKS ON OUR HERITAGE?
WELL, IF YOUR HERITAGE IS
BLACK SMOKE AND TOXIC FUMES,
YES.
ALL RIGHT.
TELL 'EM ABOUT
THE OTHER CONDITION.
TELL 'EM.
WELL, THIS ONE'S
KINDA OBVIOUS,
BUT SINCE
MULTI-CORP IS ACTUALLY
PURCHASING THE LAND
AND DOING ALL
THE RENOVATIONS,
THEY'RE GOING TO TURN
THIS PLACE INTO A RETREAT
FOR THEIR CORPORATE
EXECUTIVES FROM ALL
OVER THE WORLD.
SO IT WON'T BE
OPEN TO THE PUBLIC.
YEAH, BUT THE PUBLIC
NEVER COMES HERE ANYWAY.
YEAH, BUT THAT'S BECAUSE
IT DOESN'T WANT TO,
NOT BECAUSE IT CAN'T.
LET'S GET IT ALL
OUT HERE, HAROLD, EH.
WILL ANY OF US BE ABLE TO
GO TO THIS FANCY NEW PLACE?
HA! NO!
WELL, NO, I SHOULDN'T
SAY THAT.
UNLESS, OF COURSE, YOU'RE
HIRED TO BE AN EXECUTIVE
AT MULTI-CORP,
AND I'M TAKIN' A GUESS HERE
THAT THAT'S A LONG SHOT.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
SO THERE YOU HAVE IT.
THEY WANNA TAKE
OVER THE LODGE,
YUPPIE IT UP LIKE
THERE'S NO TOMORROW,
ERASE EVERYTHING
WE'VE EVER DONE HERE,
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
THEY EXPECT US TO PUT
OUT THE TIRE FIRE
WHEN WE'RE BARELY HALFWAY
THROUGH THE PILE.
BOO.
ABSOLUTELY.
I MEAN, WHO CAN BELIEVE IT?
AND ALL THIS FOR A
LOUSY 25 GRAND A PIECE.
I MEAN, IS ANYBODY
IN FAVOUR?
OH, OH, RED GREEN.
PERFECT TIMING.
I'M JUST ABOUT TO SHOW
MY NEW EDUCATIONAL FILM.
THAT'S THE KIND OF
DAY I'VE BEEN HAVING.
HEY, I HOPE THESE FILMS ARE
HELPING OUT WITH YOUR SHOW.
I HEAR THEY'RE VERY POPULAR
WITH PEOPLE WHO DON'T
WATCH TELEVISION.
YEAH, I SUPPOSE
THAT'S TRUE.
WHY DON'T YOU GET A
PROFESSIONAL ANIMATOR, GORD?
YOU KNOW, EVEN A CLEVER
SIX-YEAR-OLD WOULD HELP
ON THESE THINGS.
OH, NO.
NO, NO, IT'S MUCH BETTER
IF I DO ALL THE DRAWINGS,
ALL THE VOICES.
ONE VOICE,
ONE VISION.
ONE BRAIN CELL.
THIS PARTICULAR ONE IS
ALL ABOUT TREE SPECIES,
TYPES OF TREES.
YOU KNOW THE OLD EXPRESSION,
YOU CAN'T SEE THE FOREST
FOR THE TYPES OF TREES.
THAT'S NOT QUITE RIGHT,
YOU KNOW?
DOESN'T MATTER.
OH.
ACORN?
UH, NOT RIGHT NOW,
BUT MAYBE I'LL STUFF
MY CHEEKS BEFORE I GO.
SUIT YOURSELF.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
SHH!
[quirky upbeat music]
HI, EVERYONE.
TAPPING TREES
TAKES A LOT OF PATIENCE
AND TALENT.
THAT IS
CORRECT, RED.
A TELEPHONE POLE IS
STILL A TREE, YOU KNOW?
JUST BECAUSE IT HAS NO LEAVES OR
BARK AND GROWS NEXT TO A ROAD
DOESN'T MEAN IT
ISN'T A TREE.
WOW, REALLY?
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT TELEPHONE
POLES WERE A SPECIES OF TREE.
WELL, THEY AREN'T, HAROLD,
AND TELEPHONE POLES
DO NOT GROW NEXT TO ROADS.
WELL, NOT UNTIL YOU PLANT
THEM THERE THEY DON'T.
DIG A HOLE, RED.
HAROLD, I WANT YOU
TO PLANT THIS CELL PHONE.
NOW, BOYS,
LET US CELEBRATE THE
BIRTH OF THIS NEW TREE
WITH A DRINK!
AH, YUCKY.
YUCK, THIS ISN'T
MAPLE SAP.
OF COURSE NOT.
MAPLE SAP COMES
FROM A MAPLE TREE.
OH, GORD, WHAT KIND
OF LIQUID
COMES OUT OF A
TELEPHONE POLE?
NITRO GLYCERINE.
NITRO GLYCERINE?
NITRO GLYCERINE!
YEP.
OH, YEAH.
YOU LEARN SOMETHING
NEW EVERY DAY.
UNTIL YOU DRINK
NITRO GLYCERINE, THAT IS.
HA HA HA HA.
[applause]
OH, HEY.
OH, RIGHT, UH, WELCOME
TO MIKE'S TEEN TALK.
A LOT OF YOU TEENS ARE TRYING
TO GET A TOUGH REPUTATION
FOR YOURSELVES
BY PACKING WEAPONS, RIGHT,
EVEN IF YOU CAN ONLY
AFFORD A DILL PICKLE
THAT'S SHARPENED AT ONE END
AND WRAPPED IN TINFOIL.
WELL, I GOT A TIP
FOR YOU GUYS
ABOUT THE MOST SOPHISTICATED
WEAPON YOU CAN PACK,
AND IT WON'T EVEN
COST YOU A CENT.
I'M TALKING ABOUT STUPIDITY.
PEOPLE THINK
YOU'RE AN IDIOT,
YOUR LIFE GETS
A WHOLE LOT SIMPLER.
THE TEACHERS DON'T PAY
ANY ATTENTION TO YOU.
NOBODY BORROWS YOUR NOTES.
EVEN YOUR PARENTS WILL
BACK OFF A LITTLE, RIGHT.
BUT, I MEAN,
IF YOU'RE A BRAINER,
YOU GOT NO LIFE AT ALL.
THEY WANT YOU TO ANSWER
ALL THEIR QUESTIONS,
AND THEY WANT
YOU CURE DISEASES,
AND THEY WANT YOU
TO INVENT STUFF,
LIKE THE WEIGHTLESS POTATO.
YOU'RE WAY BETTER OFF WITH
A ROOM TEMPERATURE I.Q.
ESPECIALLY WHEN SOMETHING GOES
WRONG AND SOMEONE SHOUTS,
ALL RIGHT,
WHO'S THE SMART GUY?
YOU DON'T WANT 'EM
POINTING AT YOU, RIGHT?
I MEAN, EVEN IN PRISON --
EVEN IN PRISON,
THEY KEEP THE SMART
ONES IN WAY LONGER.
THEY LET THE DUMB
ONES OUT EARLIER
BECAUSE THEY'RE
JUST IDIOTS, RIGHT,
AND THEY'LL HAVE NO TROUBLE
FITTING BACK INTO SOCIETY.
SO STAY STUPID.
YOU'LL GET A LOT MORE PRIVACY,
YOU'LL GET
REALLY EASY JOBS,
AND NOBODY'LL MIND IF
YOU WATCH JERRY SPRINGER.
OH, THAT'S IT.
[applause]
OH, MAN.
WELL,
THE FIRE'S OUT.
PUT A LOT OF WATER
ON 'ER, I'LL TELL YOU.
MORE THAN WE
NEEDED, I'D SAY.
WELL, YOU KNOW ME.
I'D RATHER ERR ON
THE SIDE OF SAFETY.
WHERE'D YOU GET
THE FIRE BOMBERS?
OH, THAT WAS A
BRAINWAVE, EH?
I CALLED UP
THE AIR RESCUE.
I TOLD 'EM WE
HAD A TIRE FIRE
COMPLETELY
OUT OF CONTROL.
THEY SURE RESPONDED
WITH A LOT OF FIRE POWER.
YEAH, WELL, I MAY HAVE
MENTIONED SOMETHING
ABOUT P.C.B.s
BUT, HEY,
THE FIRE'S OUT.
THAT'S THE
MAIN THING.
OH, NO!
OH, NO, NO, NO!
THAT'S NOT
THE MAIN THING.
NO, THE MAIN THING IS
THAT ALL THAT WATER
COULDN'T RACE BACK
INTO THE LAKE.
SOMEBODY DROPPED A CORD OF
WOOD IN THE RUN-OFF DITCH.
SON OF A GUN!
YEAH, WELL, IT JUST
RACED DOWN TO THE LODGE
AND FLOODED THE
MAIN DINING ROOM.
YEAH, AND THEN BECAUSE
IT WAS POSSUM LAKE WATER,
IT DISSOLVED ALL
THE MAIN SUPPORT BEAMS.
THAT BUILDING WENT DOWN
LIKE MOOSE THOMPSON
ON ROLLER SKATES.
IT'S A SHAME TOO.
'CAUSE THAT BUILDING
WAS PERFECT FOR SEMINARS.
IT'S ONE OF THE MAIN REASONS
THAT MULTI-CORP WANTED
TO BUY THE LODGE.
YEAH, I'M REALLY
UPSET ABOUT IT.
YEAH, WELL, NOW THE
DEAL'S OFF.
IT'S A SETBACK,
HAROLD.
DON'T SAY THAT.
YOU'RE HAPPY ABOUT IT.
I'M NOT HAPPY,
I JUST ADAPT
WELL TO LIFE.
DON'T GIVE ME THAT.
YOU DIDN'T EVEN
WANNA SELL THE LODGE.
I KNOW WHERE YOU'RE
GOING WITH THIS,
BUT I HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH FLOODING THAT
BUILDING.
I KNOW.
I DID.
YEAH.
YOU DID?
YEAH, 'CAUSE I KNOW THERE'S
GOING TO BE A MULTI-CORP
AROUND EVERY CORNER.
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO SELL THIS
LODGE WHENEVER YOU WANT.
HOLY COW, YOU REALLY
ARE MY NEPHEW.
AND YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
IF I DIDN'T HAVE
THE LODGE, I'D GET BORED.
I'D END UP COMING DOWN TO
THE CITY AND HANGING
OUT WITH YOU.
YEAH, I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY I DID IT.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
IT'S MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO
AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
NOTHING SPECIAL TO REPORT.
PUT OUT A COUPLE OF FIRES,
LOST 25 GRAND,
AND COMING HOME
WITH WET PANTS.
PRETTY AVERAGE DAY.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND ESPECIALLY HAROLD
AND WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
YOU GOTTA SIT DOWN NOW.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS.
JOIN ME IN THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, GUYS, YOU GOTTA PUT
AWAY THE TRAVEL BROCHURES,
THE RIDING LAWN MOWER
CATALOGUES,
'CAUSE THE DEAL'S OFF.
I KNOW I OWE YOU A
REASONABLE EXPLANATION.
OKAY, IT STARTED OUT
AS A GOOD IDEA.
THINGS GOT GOOFIER AND GOOFIER,
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
WE GET NOTHING.
everyone: OH, OKAY.