I like the expression
“waist not want not”.
Or in Harold's case,
want not, you not.
So I found a use for these
little slivers of soap
that are too small
to shower with.
These are a lot
like lodge members.
You always find one
at the end of a bar,
and it usually
gets thrown out.
But don't throw them out.
Instead, cut them
into little pieces
the same width as the legs
of your kitchen chairs.
And then stick them
on to the bottoms
with the handyman's
secret weapon.
See, these things
will stop the chairs
from scratching
your linoleum,
just as good as those felt
pads you can buy at
Dalton's store,
if you're absolutely
made of money.
But that's not
all it can do...
because the next time
your wife asks you to
wash the floor,
you don't even
have to get up.
[ CRASH! ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Thank you very much.
Appreciate it.
All right.
Big, big week up
at the lodge this week --
boy the flies are --
you want flies
with that?
Unbelievable.
They got one of those antique
road show type things in town,
where they invite people to
bring out your old,
useless junk
and they tell you
if it's worth anything.
Dalton's wife
took him over there.
She was hoping
he was worth 40 bucks,
and he was wearing
a $50 hat.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
You are so fly.
Yeah?
Well, you
are so bug.
Well, maybe you won't
feel that way about me
after I'm stinking rich.
Yes, I will,
I just won't mention it.
How are you going
to get rich, Harold?
Are you going
to sue your parents?
Because I think you
have a case.
No, I have a treasure,
something priceless that
I've managed to hold onto
since childhood.
Can't be
what I'm thinkin'.
Oh, man!
What?
Well, do the words
Hello, Dolly,
mean anything to you?
It's not a doll, it's a
priceless porcelain figurine.
Yes, it is, and when
the appraisers see it,
they'll confirm
my suspicions.
Harold, seeing you
with a doll
confirms everyone's
suspicions.
I'll show you what
a treasure looks like.
Look at this baby
right here.
That's a genuine,
turn-of-the-century
antique fishing basket.
This is like a
family heirloom, Harold.
This is my most
prized possession.
More so than
the Possum Van?
How can that be?
You know, sarcasm
is a dangerous tool.
Well, I've learned
from the best,
the dangerous
tool himself.
[ APPLAUSE ]
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Tonight's prize
is a free, uh --
fang --
uh, fing shooi --
uh, sorry.
Uh, what does that say?
Coupon.
Cover your ears, Dalton.
Red, you've got 30 seconds to
get Dalton Humphrey
to say this word...
Yeah, all right,
Winston.
And... go!
Okay, Dalton,
Agatha Christie
is what kind of writer?
Dead.
No, but before
that she was...
British.
Um, this is another
word for whodunit.
Paternity suit?
No, okay, okay,
something happens
and you think it
was an accident,
but it wasn't an accident,
that's called a...
Shotgun wedding.
Uh, almost
outta time, Red.
Yeah.
Okay, Dalton, this starts
with the letter "M",
it's got seven
letters in it,
and whenever you hear it,
you know some
poor guy is dead.
Married.
Dalton, why are you
so negative about marriage?
If you spent a little
more time with Ann Marie,
it wouldn't be
such a mystery.
There we go.
Joining us today
on Harold's Hobby House,
to tell us all
about his hobby
is urban legend
and rural myth,
Mr. Hap Shaughnessy.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I have so many
hobbies, Harold,
I could be your
guest every week.
Well, I think maybe
we should focus.
Well, exactly.
So I've zeroed in
on my love for art,
my ability to evaluate
great paintings.
Oh, okay, and you
can do that as a hobby?
Oh, sure.
It takes a keen eye
and a suspicious mind
to authenticate
a painting.
Now, you take these
two Rembrandts.
Would you have guessed
that one of them
is worthless?
I would've guessed
more than that.
You know, you don't often see
black velvet paintings
done by the masters.
Okay, now,
that's very good.
And if you look
very closely,
you'll see that
this painting
has the same type of velvet
that was popular in France
in the late 1800s.
Yes, but Rembrandt was in
Holland in the 1600s.
Right.
And that's how we know that
this painting is a fake.
Now, then, the other one
is the true Rembrandt.
Another clue is his signature
down here in the corner.
Yeah, that's not how
you spell Rembrandt.
There's supposed
to be a "D".
That's a silent "D",
Harold.
At that time all silent Ds
were written with
invisible ink.
Whatever was
I thinking?
Well, don't feel bad.
You just haven't
done the research.
You don't know
the history.
As you get older,
Harold,
you'll find that history
is the truth.
Oh, really?
Because when
I speak with you,
I oftentimes feel that
the truth is history.
[ APPLAUSE ]
You know, every once
in a while the gods
smile on us.
It might be
a gapped-tooth smile,
but who's complaining?
See, we have this old,
rundown, outdated hospital
in Port Asbestos.
Well, last month
they closed it,
which they figure will save
thousands of lives.
they opened up a new modern
facility with real doctors,
who do things like
wear rubber gloves,
which would make
all the difference.
And the lucky part is
I managed to get my hands
on all this used
hospital gear.
Now, I'm not a doctor,
don't even play one
on television.
But I believe I can transform
this old medical equipment
into something
cheap and useful.
The exact opposite
of what it's been so far.
Now, this unit
is called a gurney,
which is a medical expression
for horizontal wedgie.
The beauty
of this baby
is the adjustable height.
I'm gonna take her down
as far as she'll go
because that gives us
the lowest centre of gravity
and when the horizontal
wedgie kicks in,
I won't have
as far to fall.
Now, the reason for the
low centre of gravity
is because I'm
actually building
a self-propelled
vehicle out of this junk.
If you already
figured that out,
you're startin'
to think like me,
and you might wanna
warn your loved ones.
Now, of course,
using the gurney tires
as drive wheels
would be stupid.
So instead I'm going
with these high precision,
oversized rim
wheelchair racing tires.
Mount the wheelchair backwards
on one end of the gurney.
And make sure she's
on there good and solid.
Not only able
to handle high speeds,
but also high speed
accidents.
Okay, got my drive
train all hooked up.
A couple of
cordless drills
mounted on some I.V. stands
did the trick.
But I need a
little extra speed,
because if people see those
I.V. stands put-putting along
they'll start calling me
a slow drip.
See, the beauty of going
with electric drive
is that it's real easy
to amp up the horsepower.
The drills have got
18 volt motors in them,
but these emergency hospital
batteries are 24 volts each.
Now, you may call
that too much juice,
I call it a good start.
I'm hooking the
batteries up in series
so I'm actually
going to have 72 volts
running through the drills.
They'll go like stink,
but not for long,
which is fine with me.
It's the same prognosis
my doctor gave me.
Now, for those
safety nuts out there,
I've got this anchor attached
to a chunk of surgical tubing.
That'll give me a soft
but effective braking system.
I call it ABS,
A Big Stretch.
My wife just calls it BS.
You can blow up a bunch
of surgical gloves
and use 'em as air bags.
And when they're
not in use,
of course, you'll keep 'em
in the glove compartment.
Okay, we're just about
ready for our test drive.
I thought the
doctor's outfit
would fit in nice with
the medical motif.
At my age, you don't get
to play doctor all that often.
Plus I figure if
things don't work out,
the emergency room doctors
will probably give me
better treatment,
if they think
I'm one of them.
Speaking of hospitals now,
it occurred to me
that brakes are fine,
but steering might
also be a nice touch.
So I wired up this
cardiac defibrillator
to control the amount of juice
going to each of my drills.
And I took off the voltage
regulator knob
and replaced it
with a steering wheel.
so now when I turn right,
most of the electricity
goes to the right-side
defibrillator paddle
and makes that drill
go faster, so I turn right --
no, that would be left.
Okay, no, turn left.
All right, okay,
the steering's backwards,
but I can remember that.
Our roads are
pretty straight anyway.
And that's how you make
an exciting vehicle
out of a bunch of
old hospital junk.
The beauty
of this car is
if you do get
into an accident,
you can actually treat
yourself until the
medics arrive.
So remember, if the women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
Clear!
We have a few father and son
businesses in our area.
You know, like
Jones and Son Heating.
It's always
someone and son.
Of course,
the someone has a name,
the son is just a son.
You never see
Dad and Jones.
And when you're
the father
it's probably natural
to want your son
to follow you
into business.
It's one of the many
downsides of success.
But you should remember
that there are
about 10 million different
careers out there,
and they keep
inventing more...
MP3 driver repairman,
reality TV host,
gay bar bouncer.
Maybe your kid would
rather be one of those.
You may think
he's like you,
but if he doesn't
share your taste
in music, TV, movies,
food or tattoos,
is he gonna share
your taste in jobs?
Or maybe you just
want him to be like you.
Check with his mother.
That may not be
such a hot idea.
Instead, let the kid
decide for himself.
Think of how
many times a year
you go and
visit your dad.
How would like
to see him every day
on the other side
of your desk?
You'd be even lazier
than you are now.
It's one of the
laws of nature
that when the father rises
the son sets.
Remember,
I'm pulling for you.
We're all
in this together.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ FLY BUZZING ]
Well, I just got back
from visiting
those antique experts.
They don't know what
they're talkin' about.
They told me my fishing
basket was a piece of crap.
I told them it dates
back to the early Orient,
but they said
"Made in Taiwan"
doesn't add value.
And the flies
are just brutal.
The windshield
of the Possum Van
looks like Harold's
graduation picture.
a la la la la
la-la la!
Okay, that's it,
Harold,
step away
from the doll.
No, no, I do not think
I will be letting
this doll out of my sight
very soon at all.
Don't tell me it's
actually worth something.
$3,500!
Holy Dina!
Well, you need to put
that somewhere safe.
Somewhere where
nobody but you goes.
How about
your bedroom?
No, I gotta
put it somewhere
where people won't
think to look.
I have to put the
doll inside something
completely worthless,
which shouldn't
be too difficult.
Oh! Oh!
Your fishing basket.
That's perfect.
Yeah. Yeah.
All right, Harold,
but I hope you'll
remember this
when you eventually
sell the doll
in terms of
sharing the upside
with the person that
helped you keep it safe.
Oh, yeah, okay, whatever.
Oh! How brilliant is that!
Oh, yeah, Harold,
you're a genius.
Yes, I am.
Gimme five!
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
RED: Bill and Walter decided
to do a little skateboarding,
and Bill couldn't
even get out the door.
That's a good sign.
Kind of a
dangerous sport for --
well, there you're
through now.
And there's the skateboards.
So Walter comes out and
Bill catches the downspout.
They say most accidents
happen out home.
That explains both of them.
So Walter's lookin'
at the clogged drainpipe.
He's gonna blow it out.
Oh!
She seems clear
as a bell now.
So he apologizes to Bill
and gets cleaned up.
And Walter notices
the entire eavestrough
is just covered with leaves
and twigs and what have you
from many, many seasons.
So they're thinking maybe
they should clean out
the eavestroughs,
and they can probably
combine the hobby
with the job.
Use the skateboards
on a ladder.
So they can roll
the ladder along
and they can clean out the
eavestrough as they go,
but Walter misunderstood
and put it on his end, so --
Now you've got what we
like to call a double ender.
And so get her up
towards the roof there.
And easy now,
Bill, easy, easy.
Easy, easy.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Probably just as well
he doesn't have kids anyway.
So he gets it in place
Yeah, you're good,
you're great.
Yeah, we understand,
we get it.
We get it, boys.
Oh, isn't that
just peachy?
Okay, so Walter goes
up the ladder and the idea is
if he takes one of those
small little garden shovels
he can stick that
in the eavestrough.
And Bill will just
slide the unit along,
and it'll clean out the
eavestrough as they go.
And it's working
real good.
But then, uh,
Walter drops the shovel.
Bill doesn't see it,
and he trips on it,
and he pushes the ladder.
The next thing you know,
Walter's pickin' up
speed here.
This could be dangerous.
No, you're good.
you're good.
You're okay, Walter.
It's okay, there's
a kiddie park there.
That'll slow you down.
You should be fine.
Oh, no, not the swings!
Not the swings.
Okay, take a breath.
Oh, no, you're good --
oh, whoa!
Okay, all right.
So that's what the the
skateboard was for.
Into the clothesline,
back the other way.
Okay, is it all comin'
back to you now, Walter?
Oh, boy!
And, uh, I'll be
home in a minute.
And okay, we said
clean out the eavestroughs,
not clean 'em off.
Okay, so you
remember that, kids.
Skateboarding
is very dangerous.
[ APPLAUSE ]
You know, when you
live in our climate,
guys have to
make a tough decision.
Do you try to impress the
ladies with a sporty
convertible,
or do you get a
vehicle that can survive
the other 11½ months
of the year?
I mean, this baby won't
get stuck in the mud
or avalanches,
but it's not exactly
a chick magnet.
They call it
a pick-up,
but that's
false advertising.
But I'm gonna show you
how you can have
the best of both worlds
using everyday items you find
in your own bedroom closet...
Chain cutters, crowbar,
hockey stick,
crutches and a garden claw.
When the cold weather
starts in late August,
you put everything
back where it was,
but until then,
you get the fun and glamour
of a convertible.
And as far as
the girls go,
I think the main thing
is to get attention.
And believe me,
you'll get attention.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
Well, the Antique Roadshow
hit the road
and we've got
nothing to show for it.
Other than Harold,
the only guy who did okay
was Old Man Sedgwick,
because he had these shoes
that dated back to
the mid-1800s.
They said they
were worth five grand,
but he wouldn't sell because
he's still wearing them.
Hey, Red.
Yeah?
Have you
seen Harold?
Yeah, he's downstairs
hanging strips
of flypaper.
I hear he's getting into the
collectibles business now.
I've got a doll
to sell him.
Dalton,
that's a G.I. Joe.
Yes, but it's valuable.
I'd like $3,500.
But you know, I'm prepared
to let it go for 17 bucks.
I'll tell him
you're here.
Hey, Harold, come on
up here for a minute.
HAROLD: I can't!
I'm stuck
in the fly paper.
Oh, man.
Dalton, no!!
What?
What have you done?
I-It was
an accident.
You swung a
bowling ball at a fly.
What did you think
was going to happen?
A seven-ten split?
Did I just hear
something unfortunate?
My figurine is ruined!
Dalton smashed the basket.
Oh, now,
calm down, Harold.
I was worried about
the thing lying in there,
so I moved it
somewhere safe.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Whoo! Whoo!
Where'd you put it?
Uh, oh, I put it
in that bowling bag.
What? What?
It's in there.
It's fine.
I'm sure
it's fine.
What's wrong?
AUDIENCE: Awwww!
Uh, well, Dalton,
I think you should
give Harold you G.I. Joe.
G.I. Joe?
Okay. Okay.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Meeting time.
Yeah, you guys
go ahead.
I'll be right down.
Oh, boy.
Okay, if my wife
is watching,
I'll be coming straight home
after the meeting.
We all learned an
important lesson today.
That the only value
in something is in using it.
Get it?
And to the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself,
Harold,
and the whole gang up
here at Possum Lodge,
keep your stick
on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Sit down.
Meeting's coming to order.
Everybody sit down.
Sit down.
All rise!
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
RED: Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the man's prayer.
I'm a man, but I can change,
if I have to...
I guess.
Okay, great news, men.
Now that we've proven that
everything in the Lodge
is worthless crap,
we qualify for
cheaper insurance.