[gunshots, explosion]
>> OKAY.
YOU CAN JUST START THE CAMERA
MOVE WHEN YOU HEAR MY VOICE.
UNLESS IT'S ALREADY STARTED.
AH!
IT HAS.
IT STARTED!
OH.
OH, SHOULD WE START THIS AGAIN?
NO?
OKAY, WOW.
OKAY, WE'LL JUST
CUT THIS PART THEN, RIGHT?
OKAY.
OKAY, WE'LL DO THAT.
YOU CAN LOOK FAR AND WIDE.
I DON'T CARE WHERE YOU LOOK, BUT
YOU'RE NOT GONNA FIND ANYONE
BETTER TO HOST THIS SHOW THAN MY
UNCLE, RED GREEN, BECAUSE HIS
NAME HAPPENS TO BE RED GREEN,
WHICH IS THE NAME OF THE SHOW,
AND HE'S PERFECT FOR THE JOB
BECAUSE HIS NAME'S THE SAME.
HERE HE IS, RED GREEN!
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW,
AND THANKS FOR THE OPPORTUNITY
TO MAKE YOUR DAY.
I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE MY
PRODUCER, DIRECTOR, AND ALSO MY
NEPHEW, HAROLD.
HAROLD, COME ON OVER HERE.
HAROLD ALSO DOES MANY OF THE
VARIED ELECTRONIC VIDEO-TYPE
EFFECTS ON THE SHOW.
>> [laughs]
>> LIKE THAT.
SORRY.
HE COULDN'T GET A JOB
AT CABLE TV.
OH, WE HAD A HECK OF A TIME UP
AT THE LODGE LAST NIGHT.
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK DECIDED HE WAS
GONNA WASH HIS HAIR, OR RATHER
HE WANTED US TO WASH IT FOR HIM
WHILE HE WENT DOWN TO THE BINGO
IN A BORROWED HAT, SO HE JUST
LEFT THE TOUPEE SITTIN' BY THE
FRONT DOOR WRAPPED AROUND A
SHAMPOO BOTTLE
HOPING WE'D TOUCH IT.
>> UNCLE RED,
HOW LONG IS THIS STORY?
LIKE, IN HUMAN YEARS.
>> WELL, THE STORY DOESN'T
CONCERN YOU, HAROLD.
>> NO.
NO, BUT THE DURATION DOES,
'CAUSE OUR VIEWERS LIVE IN A
FAST-PACED WORLD, AND THEY
DEMAND FAST-PACED TELEVISION.
>> SUCH AS?
>> SUCH AS GOING
TO THE NEXT SEGMENT.
LIKE THIS.
YOU'LL THANK ME LATER.
>> NO, I WON'T.
>> I WAS TALKING TO THE VIEWERS.
>> both: ♪ BACON DRIPPINGS
♪ BACON DRIPPINGS
♪ BACON
♪ IF YOU WANT TO CALL A SONG
♪ BACON DRIPPINGS
♪ I'M SORRY, IT'S BEEN TAKEN
>> EXCELLENT.
THAT WENT BETTER
THAN I HAD HOPED.
>> THIS WEEK IN HANDYMAN CORNER
WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE
YOUR VERY OWN ADJUSTABLE BED.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY THAT YOU
SPEND ABOUT 1/3 OF YOUR LIFE
ASLEEP, EVEN MORE IF YOU'RE IN
SCHOOL, SO IT'S IMPORTANT THAT
YOU HAVE A COMFORTABLE BED THAT
FITS RIGHT TO YOUR OWN CONTOURS
NO MATTER WHAT SIZE YOUR
CONTOURS ARE.
SO I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW TO
SAVE YOURSELF A LOT OF MONEY AND
MAKE YOUR OWN ADJUSTABLE BED.
WHAT YOU NEED FIRST OF ALL IS A
COUPLE OF PIECES OF 1/2 INCH OR
5/8 INCH PLYWOOD.
THIS IS SOME SCRAP LUMBER
THAT I FOUND.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS CREATE A
HINGE BETWEEN THE TWO HALVES,
AND YOU DO THAT USIN' THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON:
DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, YOU CAN SEE
HERE I'M JUST FINISHING UP THE
TAPING FOR MY HINGE, AND I HAVE
THIS END OF THE BED SUPPORTED BY
MY COLLECTABLES, AND ON THIS END
I HAVE THREE CAR JACKS.
THREE JACKS BEATS TWO PAIR.
SO NOW WHAT I DO IS JUST THROW
MY MATTRESS ON THERE.
AND I HAVE MYSELF
A HOMEMADE ADJUSTABLE BED.
[sighs]
YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT COMFORT?
[laughter]
>> NOW, IF THAT ISN'T COMFORT,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IS.
I CAN'T FEEL ANY PART OF MY BACK
NOW, AND THAT'S PROBABLY DUE TO
THIS BED, SO THERE YOU HAVE IT.
THAT'S THE TRICK.
NOTHIN' REALLY PARTICULAR OR
FANCY ABOUT IT,
BUT IT WORKS GREAT.
AND SO UNTIL NEXT TIME,
REMEMBER: IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK, 'CAUSE I
KNOW YOU WANT TO FIND OUT
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE TOUPEE.
>> WE CAN'T LIMIT OURSELVES
TO WHAT UNCLE RED KNOWS.
WE GOT A WHOLE HALF HOUR
TO FILL.
[laughs]
>> YOU KNOW, HAROLD.
WE WERE TALKIN' THE OTHER NIGHT,
A BUNCH OF US, YOU KNOW, EH, WHO
WE THOUGHT THE SEXIEST WOMAN
ALIVE WAS.
>> OOH!
[laughs]
>> YOU THINK THIS WAY SOMETIMES,
DON'T YOU?
>> SOMETIMES.
MOST OF THE TIME.
>> YEAH. REALLY, EH?
>> WHO DID YOU SAY?
>> WELL, DORIS DAY.
>> OH, SHE IS.
>> YEAH.
>> SHE'S VERY SEXY.
>> YOU EVER SEE HER--
YOU SEE HER IN PILLOW TALK?
>> YES.
>> YEAH.
>> WITH ROCK HUDSON.
>> ROCK HUDSON.
>> AND TONY RANDALL.
>> REALLY?
>> YES.
PILLOW TALK.
>> AND THEN SHE DROVE SOME--A
CONVERTIBLE INTO A SWIMMING POOL
ONE TIME.
>> OH!
>> YEAH.
>> OH, THAT WAS THE ONE
WITH JAMES GARNER.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU GOT 'EM MIXED UP.
YOU SAY--WHO'S SHE SEXY WITH?
>> DORIS DAY.
STILL HER?
>> YEAH.
WHO DO YOU LIKE?
>> CARROLL O'CONNOR.
>> THAT'S A GUY.
>> I MEAN CAROL CHANNING.
CAROL CHANNING.
>> THAT'S A GUY TOO.
>> OH, UM, LYNN SWANN?
>> "IT IS WINTER.
ON THE FRONT LAWN A BIG, ROUND,
WHITE FIGURE.
HIS NOSE IS A CARROT.
HIS EYES, BLACK COAL.
HIS MOUTH IS A POTATO.
HIS EARS ARE STICKS.
WE HAVE THE WORLD'S UGLIEST
POSTMAN."
SO ANYWAY, THE BUNCH OF US ARE
SITTIN' AROUND STARIN' AT OLD
MAN SEDGEWICK'S TOUPEE LIKE IT
WAS A MUSKRAT THAT HAD GONE
THROUGH THE LAWNMOWER.
HE WAS EXPECTIN' US TO WASH IT,
BUT NOBODY WAS VOLUNTEERING
MAINLY BECAUSE WE COULDN'T
REMEMBER OLD MAN SEDGEWICK EVER
WASHIN' THE TOUPEE, SO THE
DISEASE POTENTIAL WAS WAY UP
THERE.
AND IT DIDN'T HELP THAT
BUSTER HADFIELD SAID HE SAW IT
MOVE, BUT WE COULDN'T JUST LEAVE
IT LYIN' ON THE PORCH 'CAUSE THE
WOOD WAS STARTIN' TO STAIN.
>> YEAH.
YEAH, LIKE WHAT?
SO FINALLY SOMEBODY WASHED IT
OR NOBODY EVER WASHED IT, AND
LIFE WENT BACK TO NORMAL THE WAY
IT WAS BEFORE THE INCIDENT
EVER OCCURRED.
WELL, HEY.
WELL, THANKS FOR SHARIN' THAT
GREAT STORY WITH US.
MAYBE I'LL JUST BE WAITIN' FOR
THAT ONE TO HIT THE BIG SCREEN.
[laughs]
CAN WE JUST GET ON
WITH THE NEXT SEGMENT?
ALL RIGHT, AND OUR HUMBLE WAY OF
TRYING TO SAVE THE SHOW?
>> SO FINALLY, STINKY PETERSON
FIGURED OUT HOW TO WASH
THE DARN THING.
THE VIEWERS ARE GONE, UNCLE RED.
THEY'RE WATCHING THE NEXT
SEGMENT, BUT THEY'LL BE BACK.
THEY THINK THE STORY'S OVER.
>> WHOA!
OH, HELLO!
MR. GREEN,
THIS IS SUCH A SURPRISE.
PLEASE, PLEASE COME IN,
AND WELCOME!
>> WELL, THANK YOU, RANGER GORD.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS KIND OF
IMPORTANT WORK THAT YOU DO UP
HERE LOOKIN' AFTER OUR FORESTS,
AND WE JUST LIKE TO DROP BY
AND SHOW OUR APPRECIATION.
>> WELL, THANK YOU.
THAT'S VERY TOUCHING.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
>> [clears throat]
UH, PLEASE EXCUSE THE MESS.
>> NO. NO, THAT'S FINE.
AND I NOTICED YOU CALLED ME
MR. GREEN.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
JUST CALL ME RED.
THAT'LL BE FINE.
>> WELL, THANK YOU, RED.
I FEEL WE'RE BECOMING
VERY CLOSE FRIENDS.
I LIKE THAT.
IT'S WARMING.
>> WELL, YEAH--
NO. NO. NO. NO.
SO, GORD, HOW'S THE FOREST
RANGER BUSINESS BEEN LATELY?
>> WELL, THERE'S A LOT OF
STARTING INTO THE WOODS
WITH THIS JOB.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
>> THAT'S ALWAYS HECTIC.
AND, UH, IT'S A LOT OF
RESPONSIBILITY.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
I SUPPOSE IT IS.
YOU COULD JUST LOOK AWAY
FOR A SPLIT SECOND
AND MISS A FOREST FIRE, HUH?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
OH, ABSOLUTELY. YEAH.
>> [laughs]
>> A SPLIT SECOND.
>> [clears throat]
>> WELL, MAYBE NOT A SPLIT
SECOND, YOU KNOW, MAYBE--MAYBE
THAT WOULD BE A FLASH FIRE.
>> FLASH FIRE.
YEAH.
OH, THAT'S IT.
YEAH. YEAH. YEAH.
[clears throat]
>> AND ONE OF MY OTHER PROBLEMS
IS THAT WHEN I FALL ASLEEP,
I'LL USE MY VIDEO CAMERA HERE AT
NIGHT, SO I'LL TAPE THE WOODS,
AND THEN I CAN PLAY IT BACK
AGAIN THE NEXT DAY.
>> AH, I FOR GOD'S SAKE.
SO YOU'VE BEEN UP HERE
A WHILE THEN?
>> OH, YEAH. YEAH.
I'VE BEEN UP HERE NOW FOR, UH--
[cries]
I'VE BEEN UP HERE FOR 12 YEARS.
>> OH, MY.
>> I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
IT HASN'T BEEN EASY, YOU KNOW?
>> NO. NO.
>> THE LAST TIME I WENT ANYWHERE
WAS 12 YEARS AGO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YEAH.
AND THAT WAS TO A KC
AND THE SUNSHINE BAND CONCERT.
>> OH, MY.
>> I LOVE KC
AND THE SUNSHINE BAND.
>> OH, YEAH. YEAH. YEAH.
>> HOW'S THEIR CAREER
BEEN DOIN'?
>> ABOUT THE SAME AS YOURS,
REALLY.
>> OH, GREAT.
'CAUSE...
♪ THAT'S THE WAY
♪ UH-HUH, UH-HUH
♪ I LIKE IT
♪ THAT'S THE WAY
>> SORRY.
SORRY, RANGER GORD, BUT, YOU
KNOW, IT'S GETTIN' ON IN TIME.
WE GOTTA GET GOIN'.
BUT THANKS A LOT FOR LET--
>> WHY? WHY?
YOU JUST GOT HERE!
>> NO. NO.
WE JUST GOTTA--WELL,
I GOTTA MOVE ON.
>> NO, NO! COME ON, PLEASE!
DON'T--DON'T GO SO FAST!
>> NO. NO, GORD.
SORRY, GORD. GORD. GORD.
>> PLEASE!
>> GORD. GORD.
>> I MADE SANDWICHES!
I MADE FINGER SANDWICHES, EH?
>> MAYBE WE CAN DROP BY
ANOTHER TIME, EH?
WE'LL HAVE THE SANDWICHES THEN.
>> OKAY! GREAT!
>> UH-HUH.
>> YOU'RE COMIN' BACK THEN?
>> YEAH. YEAH. OH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> GREAT.
WHAT ABOUT TOMORROW AT 2:15
'CAUSE THE SANDWICHES WILL KEEP,
I THINK.
>> UH, WELL, I--
UH, WE COULD TRY.
DON'T WANT TO MAKE ANY PROMISES.
>> GREAT. OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW THEN.
>> NO, NO. I SAID WE'LL TRY.
>> DONE!
>> YOU CAN JOIN IN THIS ONE.
>> OH, EXCELLENT.
>> OKAY.
>> ♪ DON'T MARRY A WOMAN
♪ WITH STUFF BETWEEN HER TEETH
>> ♪ HER TEETH
>> ♪ MAKE SURE SHE FLOSSES
♪ ABOVE AND BENEATH
>> ♪ UP AND DOWN
>> ♪ REGULAR BRUSHING
♪ IS THE ONLY GOOD WAY
>> ♪ YUP
>> ♪ YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE
♪ WHAT SHE'S EATING THAT DAY
>> ♪ NOT FOR ME, THANK YOU
>> ♪ 'CAUSE WHENEVER
♪ SHE SMILES
♪ IT'S LIKE A BUFFET
♪ DON'T MARRY A WOMAN
>> ♪ WITH STUFF
♪ BETWEEN HER TEETH
>> [laughs]
EXCELLENT, UNCLE RED!
THAT'S EXCELLENT.
I JUST TOOK THE LETTERS
OUT OF THE MAIL BAG.
I WAS GONNA READ THEM OUT LOUD,
AND YOU WALK IN TO ANSWER THEM.
THAT'S EXCELLENT.
THAT'S--
THIS IS WORKIN' REALLY WELL.
THIS IS FANTASTIC.
THIS IS A VERY WELL-PRODUCED
PROGRAM.
I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT UP FRONT
'CAUSE I TRULY BELIEVE THAT.
[laughs]
LETTER NUMBER ONE.
DEAR RED GREEN, OH.
THAT'S EXCELLENT.
THEY USED YOUR NAME AND
EVERYTHING.
"MY WIFE AND I HAVE BEEN MARRIED
FOR 29 YEARS.
OUR SEX LIFE WAS GREAT FOR A
LONG TIME, BUT FOR THE PAST 28
YEARS, IT'S BEEN HEAVY SLOGGING.
WHAT DO YOU RECOMMEND TO
REVITALIZE OUR LOVE LIFE?"
>> WELL, HAROLD, A SITUATION
LIKE THIS, I KIND OF RECOMMEND
THAT THEY USE WHAT WE CALL
FANTASIES WHERE THE HUSBAND AND
WIFE PRETEND THAT THEY'RE
DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
PREFERABLY PEOPLE WITH A BETTER
LOVE LIFE.
FOR EXAMPLE, NOW, HE COULD
PRETEND THAT HE'S A KNIGHT IN
SHINING ARMOR, AND SHE COULD BE
THE MILKMAID.
>> OH! OH!
OR, LIKE, HE COULD BE THE
PARCEL-TOTING MAILMAN AND SHE
COULD BE THE STARTLED SUNBATHER.
OR--OR YOU KNOW WHAT'S ANOTHER
GOOD ONE?
HE'S THE PIZZA DELIVERY BOY,
AND SHE'S THE DIVORCEE
WHO LOST HER COUPONS.
>> YEAH, OR IF THEY FIND THAT
GETTING REPETITIVE, THEY CAN
KIND OF MIX AND MATCH.
HE COULD BE THE PIZZA MAILMAN
IN SHINING ARMOR, AND SHE COULD
BE THE STARTLED MILKMAID WHO
LOST HER COUPON.
A LOT OF PEOPLE SAY THAT THIS
IS, LIKE, CHEATING,
BUT IT'S NOT.
IT'S A LOT SAFER.
>> YEAH, AND MY SUGGESTION IS
THAT YOU MIGHT WANT TO TRY,
LIKE, SILKY UNDER THINGS OR
PEEKABOO NIGHTGOWNS.
>> YEAH, AND IF THAT DOESN'T
WORK, THEN HE COULD GET HIS WIFE
TO WEAR THOSE.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
OKAY.
I'VE GOT ANOTHER LETTER,
UNCLE RED.
"DEAR RED.
FIRST, DO YOU BELIEVE, AS
EINSTEIN SAID, THAT GOD DOES NOT
PLAY DICE WITH THE UNIVERSE AND
THAT ALL REALITY IS ULTIMATELY
KNOWABLE, OR DOES HEISENBERG'S
UNCERTAINTY PRINCIPLE AND THE
QUARK THEORY PROVE THAT THERE
ARE INTRINSIC PHYSICAL LIMITS TO
RESOLUTION THAT PROVE FREE WILL
EXIST AND PRECLUDES DETERMINISM?
MY SECOND QUESTION IS,
WHEN YOU WENT TROUT FISHING
ON YOUR LAST SHOW,
WHAT KIND OF LURE DID YOU USE?"
SIGNED, ARTHUR.
>> ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
I'D LIKE TO ANSWER THE SECOND
QUESTION FIRST, IF I MAY.
WE USED A MEPPS CRAZY SPOONER ON
A METAL LEADER WITH A 25-POUND
TEST LINE, I GUESS IT WAS.
THE CRAZY SPOONER IS REALLY THE
EXCELLENT LURE FOR TROUT BECAUSE
IT SHOWS UP SO WELL
IN THE FAST-MOVING WATER.
THAT LURE WAS GIVEN TO ME,
INTERESTINGLY ENOUGH, BUT A
FEMALE ARM WRESTLER AT A BAR IN
THE YUKON.
IT WAS NEW YEARS EVE, 1959,
DURING A BOILED EGG EATING
CONTEST.
I WAS LOSIN' THE CONTEST REAL
BAD, AND THEN SHE JUST KIND OF
DROPPED A LURE INTO MY SHORTS
THERE AND GAVE ME A WEDGIE, AND
I GASPED SO HARD I SUCKED IN
ABOUT NINE MORE EGGS AND WON THE
CONTEST, WINNING FIRST PRIZE,
WHICH WAS A STUFFED MUSKRAT, AND
I BELIEVE THAT ANSWERS
THE FIRST QUESTION.
THIS WEEK ON ADVENTURES WITH
BILL, BILL WANTED TO SHOW
YOU--OH, THERE'S BILL NOW.
YEAH. YEAH.
HE WANTED TO SHOW YOU HOW TO
BUILD A SHELTER USIN' A
PARACHUTE.
THAT'S A PARACHUTE.
I DON'T THINK HE PAID FULL
RETAIL FOR THAT ONE.
NOW, THE FIRST JOB IS TO GET THE
PARACHUTE TO OPEN.
SO HE'S GONNA UP THE LADDER
THERE, AND HE HAS A LOT OF FUN,
AND--LOOK OUT. LOOK OUT, BILL.
OH.
MAYBE THAT WAS A BAD SPOT FOR
THE LADDER, YOU KNOW, IN
HINDSIGHT.
NOW WE'VE GOT ANOTHER SPOT.
HE'S GONNA--HE'S HOPIN' THAT THE
CHUTE WILL OPEN JUST IN THIS--IT
DIDN'T WORK REAL WELL, YOU KNOW?
SO NOW HE'S--HE ASKED ME TO--IF
I JUST WOULD SORT OF WHAT WE
CALL A MANUAL DISENFOLDMENT
TECHNIQUE.
IT'S A MILITARY KIND OF A MOVE,
AND WELL, THERE'S A LOT OF
MATERIAL IN THOSE--THEY'RE LIKE
MOOSE THOMPSON'S PANTS.
IT'S A WINDY DAY.
I DON'T THINK--YOU KNOW, IN
RETROSPECT I WOULDN'T HAVE TRIED
TO DO THIS ON SUCH A HIGH
WINDY--BUT THEN BILL, YOU KNOW,
HE SAID, "NO, NO.
WE'RE--THIS IS A PERFECT DAY."
WELL, SEE THERE--WELL, I DIDN'T
WANT TO ARGUE WITH HIM.
HE HAD THE HOOK THERE HANGIN'
FROM HIS BELT, AND I DIDN'T
NOTICE THIS EITHER, BUT THIS
IS--I DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS PART OF
THE PLAN OR WHAT, AND
THEN--WELL, THE WIND TOOK HIM
AND--NOW, AT THIS POINT I'M
THINKING, YOU KNOW, WHAT EXACTLY
IS BILL'S PLAN?
>> [yelling]
>> TO THE AVERAGE PERSON, THAT
WOULD LOOK LIKE HE MIGHT HAVE
BEEN OUT OF CONTROL.
IT'S SO DARN HARD TO TELL WITH
BILL, YOU KNOW?
INSTEAD OF SHELTER, THIS WAS
MORE OF A MOBILE HOME AT THIS
POINT THAT HE WAS MOVIN'.
YEAH, HE WAS GETTIN'
QUITE A WAYS AWAY.
LOOK OUT. LOOK OUT! LOOK OUT!
LOOK OUT! OH!
>> [grunts]
>> UH.
NOW HERE, THIS PART OF THE PLAN
I'M SAYING TO MYSELF, "UH, BILL,
UH--OOH.
IS THIS REALLY NECESSARY?"
BUT I GUESS HE WAS JUST
PICKING THE RIGHT SPOT TO PUT--
TO BUILD THE SHELTER
'CAUSE HE EVENTUALLY
BROUGHT HER TO A HALT AND
FINALLY FOUND A SPOT THAT I
GUESS MUST SUITED HIS LIKING.
[clears throat]
AND DON'T WORRY ABOUT HIM.
HE'S FINE.
"IT IS WINTER.
MY CAR IS SAFELY NESTLED
IN A DITCH.
I STAND BEHIND IT AND WARM MY
FACE IN THE EXHAUST.
IT FEELS GOOD BUT IT MAKES LUNCH
TASTE FUNNY."
[clears throat]
THIS POINT IN THE SHOW,
I STEP OUT OF THE LIMELIGHT
AND KIND OF BRING IN A LEMON.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
CELEBRITY PROFILES.
OKAY?
THIS IS A MAGAZINE THAT
TEENAGERS READ, AND IT'S GOT,
LIKE, CELEBRITY PROFILES IN IT,
BUT THEY HAVEN'T GOT AROUND TO
ME YET.
[laughs]
THAT'S WEIRD, EH?
BUT THE REASON I FIGURE IS
'CAUSE THEY HAVE NO IDEA WHO I
AM, WHICH WILL CERTAINLY DELAY
THINGS, YOU KNOW,
UNDERSTANDABLY, BUT RATHER THAN
WAIT FOR THEM TO COME TO ME,
I'VE DECIDED TO DO MY OWN
CELEBRITY PROFILE TODAY.
[laughs]
OKAY?
ALL RIGHTY.
HERE WE GO.
FULL NAME?
HAROLD DORTMUND
SPOONER MEPPS GREEN.
COOL, EH?
AGE?
18.
OH, NO.
I'M 17.
18?
WHAT MONTH IS THIS?
THURSDAY?
19.
I'M 19.
OKAY, MAJOR TURN-ONS?
FAST WOMEN AND LOOSE CLOTHES
AND NINTENDO.
[laughs]
MAJOR TURN-OFFS?
UM, LET'S SEE.
PEOPLE WITH TANS, UM, GETTIN'
BEATEN UP, INSINCERITY, AND--OH,
I GUESS, THERMAL NUCLEAR WAR
WOULD BE PRETTY TURN-OFFISH.
OKAY.
FAVORITE COLOR?
[laughs]
DARK CHOCOLATE BROWN FOR SURE.
YEAH, THAT'S SO COOL.
FAVORITE FOOD?
UH, DARK BROWN CHOCOLATE.
OH! OH!
OH, THAT WAS COOL.
SEE THAT?
TWO THINGS THAT MATCHED!
THAT WAS SO COOL, I DIDN'T EVEN
PLAN THAT OR NOTHIN'.
IT JUST--THAT WAS COOL.
WHAT A--WHAT A MOMENT WE SHARED.
OKAY.
LAST BOOK READ?
GRAVITY'S RAINBOW
BY, UM--BY--WHAT WAS THAT?
THOMAS PYNCHON.
OH! NO!
NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT WAS?
IT WAS THE INSTRUCTIONS TO MY
DIGITAL WATCH NINTENDO GAME.
THAT AS WELL.
THAT WAS HARD TOO.
PROUDEST ACCOMPLISHMENT?
HMM, OH, WELL.
THAT'S EASY.
PRODUCING THIS SHOW.
NO! NO!
UNDERSTANDING THE INSTRUCTIONS
TO MY DIGITAL WATCH NINTENDO
GAME.
YEAH.
FOR SURE.
>> I KNOW WE HAVE SOME TEENAGERS
WATCHING TONIGHT 'CAUSE
MAYBE THE CABLE'S ON THE FRITZ,
AND THIS IS THE ONLY CHANNEL
YOU CAN GET,
AND I WANT TO TAKE THIS
OPPORTUNITY TO TALK TO YOU YOUNG
PEOPLE ABOUT
THE IDEA OF LEAVIN' HOME.
I KNOW THERE'S A LOT OF APPEAL
IN THE IDEA OF HAVING YOUR OWN
PLACE, YOU KNOW, WHERE YOUR
PARENTS CAN'T HASSLE YOU ABOUT
WHERE YOU GOT ALL THOSE STEREOS
AND WHERE YOU CAN HAVE SOME
PRIVACY TO PLAN BANK ROBBERIES
OR MAYBE HAVE DIVORCEES UP
ON P.D. DAYS.
BUT BEFORE YOU GO MOVING OUT,
I WANT YOU TO THINK
ABOUT HOW MUCH IT MUST BE
COSTING YOUR PARENTS TO HAVE YOU
LIVE AT HOME, AND HOW MISERABLE
IT'S MAKING THEIR LIVES TO HAVE
YOU THERE, AND IT ALL KIND OF
WORKS OUT.
DOESN'T IT?
ANOTHER THING YOU SHOULD
REMEMBER IS THAT AS YOUR PARENTS
GET OLDER THEY START LOSIN' IT,
AND EVENTUALLY THEY END UP
WILLING EVERYTHING TO THE KID
WHO STAYED HOME THE LONGEST.
[clears throat]
MAKE SURE IT'S YOU.
I'M SURE A LOT OF YOU WANT TO
FIND OUT ABOUT THE TOUPEE,
AND I WON'T DISAPPOINT YOU.
>> YES, YOU WILL.
>> I'M GONNA FINISH THE STORY,
HAROLD.
>> I KNOW.
>> NOW, HAROLD, YOU KNOW, YOU
CAN DO WHATEVER YOU WANT WHEN IT
COMES TO GETTIN' YOURSELF A CAR
OR ANYTHING ELSE, REALLY.
IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS, EH?
>> RIGHT.
>> BUT I WOULD ADVISE YOU NOT TO
BUY ANYTHING NEW.
GO USED.
>> OH, NO.
IF IT'S USED, THAT MEANS
IT'S OLD.
>> OH, NO. NO, IT'S NOT OLD.
IT'S--WHAT THEY'VE DONE IS THEY
FOUND THE PROBLEMS AND THEY
FIXED THEM, SO YOU DON'T HAVE TO
PAY FOR THAT.
>> WHAT IF THEY DIDN'T FIX 'EM?
MAYBE THEY ONLY FOUND 'EM AND
THEY LEFT EM THERE HIDDEN
FOR YOU?
>> WELL, YOU'RE GONNA GET THAT
WITH A NEW.
>> WELL, THAT'S TRUE.
THAT'S WHAT THEY SAY WHEN YOU
BUY A LEMON.
>> YOU BUY A LEMON,
AND YOU GET THE SQUEEZE.
>> [laughs]
>> AND THE PITS.
>> OH, THAT'S GOOD!
>> UH-HUH.
>> AND THEN THE RIND.
OH, NO, THAT--
>> NO.
THAT, YOU'D HAVE TO DRIVE TO
GERMANY FOR THAT.
>> WE'RE UP HERE
AT JIMMY MCVEIGH'S PLACE.
SEE HOW HE'S DOING WITH HIS BOAT
RESTORATION.
HE'S NOT HOME YET.
HE WORKS AT THE POST OFFICE.
KIND OF FINANCES THE BOAT THING
BY WORK--
>> [singing]
>> OH, HERE HE IS RIGHT NOW.
HEY, JIM!
HOW YOU DOIN'?
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> HEY, HOW'S IT GOIN' TODAY?
HUH? HUH?
>> IF YOU'RE ANOTHER ONE OF THEM
BOYS THAT ARE HERE TO COMPLAIN
ABOUT NOT GETTIN' YOUR LETTERS,
YOU CAN TALK TO THE SUPERVISORS.
>> NO, JIM. JIM, IT'S ME.
>> OH, HOW YOU DOIN' RED?
>> I'M DOIN' FINE.
>> I THOUGHT YOU WERE ONE OF
THEM DEMENTED NIT-PICKERS
THAT ARE ALWAYS COMPLAININ'
IF THEY DON'T GET EVERY SINGLE
BLOODY ISSUE OF--
>> NO, NO, NO, NO.
I JUST WANTED TO SEE HOW YOU'RE
DOIN' ON THE BOAT 'CAUSE YOU'VE
BEEN WORKING ON THIS BABY
FOR A WHILE, HAVEN'T YOU?
>> I HAVE INDEED.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
>> MIND YOU, IT HAS BEEN
A LABOR OF LOVE.
>> YEAH.
>> 6 1/2 YEARS.
>> BUT NOW I'M PUTTIN' ON
A BIG PUSH.
>> YEAH?
>> I AM HOPIN' TO FINISH HER
BY THIS WEEKEND.
>> REALLY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE LEFT TO DO
ON THAT?
>> THERE'S NOT TOO MUCH LEFT,
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
>> REALLY?
>> NO.
THE WINDSHIELD HERE.
>> YEAH?
>> UH, THE FLAG POLE.
>> YEAH.
I NOTICED THE ENGINE BACK THERE.
>> I'LL BUILD THE ENGINE IN THE
HULL, AND THE CABIN.
>> YEAH. YEAH. OH, YEAH.
YEAH. WHAT IS THIS HERE?
>> THIS IS WHAT YOU--THIS IS
KNOWN AS--
[indistinct speech]
>> OH, YEAH. SOMETHING FOR ME?
>> THIS HERE IS KNOWN
AS TINTED LEXAN.
>> LEXAN?
>> THIS STUFF HERE, THEY SAY,
IS STRONGER THAN STEEL.
>> FOR GOD'S SAKE.
>> IT'S IS ABSOLUTELY IMPOSSIBLE
TO CUT.
>> REALLY?
>> I MEAN, THAT--JEEZ, I HAD A
HELL OF A JOB GETTIN' THIS.
LET ME TELL YOU.
>> YEAH. WHERE'D YOU GET IT?
>> I FINALLY HAD TO KICK IT OUT
OF A PHONE BOX.
>> YOU TOOK THIS
OUT OF A PHONE BOOTH, JIM?
>> I DID INDEED. YES.
I MEAN, I PHONED UP
THE PHONE COMPANY.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
>> SEE, RED.
I PHONED 'EM UP FAIR ENOUGH, AND
I ASKED 'EM, WHERE DO YOU GET
ALL THAT STRONG GLASS YOU PUT IN
THE PHONE BOXES?
AND WOULD THEY TELL ME?
[laughs]
NOT BLOODY LIKELY.
>> OH, GOD.
>> SO WHAT ELSE COULD I DO?
I MEAN, WHAT ELSE COULD I DO?
I HAD TO KICK THE BLOODY THING
OUT.
>> JESUS.
UH, THAT'S LARCENY.
>> NO.
IT'S LEXAN.
I MEAN, I FIGURED I DIDN'T STEAL
THIS STUFF.
>> NO. NO.
>> NO. I EARNED IT.
I MEAN, YOU TRY CUTTIN' THIS
STUFF HERE OUT OF A PHONE BOX
WITH COPS UP AND DOWN THE ROAD
EVERY TEN MINUTES.
THIS IS GONNA BE ONE SIDE OF THE
WINDSHIELD.
THAT SHOULD JUST DO
ABOUT PERFECT.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS NOW I'M
GONNA NEED ANOTHER BIT
FOR THE OTHER SIDE.
>> YOU'RE GONNA NEED
SOME MORE LEXAN?
>> I'M GONNA GO DOWN TO THE
PHONE BOX ABOUT A MILE
DOWN THE ROAD.
I'M GONNA GO DOWN AND GET
ANOTHER BIT FOR THE WINDSHIELD.
>> OH, I KIND OF WANTED TO
TALK TO YOU ABOUT THE BOAT.
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHAT, RED.
COME HERE.
YOU WAIT HERE TILL I COME BACK
AGAIN WITH THE OTHER WINDSHIELD.
>> YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
>> AND HERE, LOOK.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I'LL DO.
YOU HAVE A READ AT SOME OF THEM
TO KEEP YOU OCCUPIED
TILL I GET BACK.
RIGHT?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> FAIR ENOUGH.
>> SO ANYWAY, STINKY PETERSON
MANAGED TO GET OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK'S TOUPEE WASHED.
HE PICKED IT UP WITH A PAIR OF
BARBEQUE TONGS, DROPPED IT INTO
A MINNOW PAIL, AND THEN HE
HOOKED IT ONTO THE ANCHOR OF THE
ALUMINUM BOAT AND TOWED IT
AROUND THE LAKE FOR AN HOUR AND
A HALF OR SO, BUT THEN WHEN HE
PULLED THE MINNOW PAIL BACK IN
THE TOUPEE WAS GONE, AND OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK WAS PRETTY MAD BECAUSE
BY NOW HE WAS GETTIN' TERMINAL
HAT-HEAD, BUT WE HAVE A LEAD ON
THE HAIRPIECE 'CAUSE WE HEARD
THAT A GUY UP THE LAKE CAUGHT A
BASS THAT LOOKED EXACTLY LIKE
HOWARD COSELL,
EXCEPT IT WAS A SMALLMOUTH.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING, I'M
GONNA COME STRAIGHT HOME AFTER
THE SHOW AND I'LL BE PICKIN' UP
A DOZEN DOUGHNUTS, AND IF THE
TRAFFIC'S NOT TOO BAD THERE MAY
BE ONE LEFT FOR YOU.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME, ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD AND THE WHOLE
GANG UP HERE AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]