[quirky upbeat music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> AND NOW IT'S TIME TO MEET THE
MAN WHO MAKES THIS ALL POSSIBLE,
AND THAT INCLUDES SIGNING THE
PAYCHECKS, BUT NOT GOING AS FAR
TO GET T SHIRTS PRINTED UP OR
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
OH, NO.
ANYWAY, HERE HE IS, THE STAR OF
THE SHOW AND MY UNCLE, WHICH IS
TO SAY MY FATHER'S BROTHER, AND
THAT PART'S TRUE.
I SHOULD PROBABLY SAY THAT.
IT'S VERY MUCH SO TRUE.
HERE HE IS, THE STAR OF THE
SHOW, MR. RED GREEN.
>> HELLO, AND THANK YOU ALL FOR
TUNING IN WHEN, YOU KNOW, THERE
ARE SO MANY WORTHWHILE THINGS
YOU COULD BE DOING WITH YOUR
LIFE.
YOU KNOW, NOT EVERYBODY CAN SAY
THAT.
HAROLD, COME ON OVER HERE A
MINUTE.
HAROLD IS THE ANNOUNCER,
PRODUCER, DIRECTOR, AND STAR'S
NEPHEW OF THE SHOW HERE.
>> AND ALSO, I GET TO, LIKE,
CONTROL ALL THE VISUAL EFFECTS.
WATCH THIS.
[laughs]
>> NOW, AREN'T KIDS SOMETHING?
I DON'T HAVE ANY MYSELF.
I ACTUALLY WENT UP TO THE LODGE
YESTERDAY.
BUSTER HATFIELD GOT ALL THE GUYS
TO TAKE OFF THEIR SOCKS AND
SHOES AND HAVE A GAME OF LAWN
DARTS.
YEAH, HE LOVES CONTACT SPORTS.
BUT YOU KNOW WE'VE BEEN ALL KIND
OF SAFETY-CONSCIOUS SINCE WE HAD
THAT METHANE EXPLOSION WHEN
STINKY PETERSON DROPPED A
CIGARETTE DOWN THE TWO-HOLER.
OH, GOD, THAT SCARED A BUNCH OF
US, ESPECIALLY STINKY.
LUCKILY, HE WAS SITTIN' DOWN.
BUT YOU KNOW, BUSTER LOVES
DANGER.
I'D SAY DANGER IS HIS MIDDLE
NAME.
IT'S UKRAINIAN OR SOMETHING.
>> WOW, THAT'S A GREAT STORY,
UNCLE RED, BUT LET'S MOVE ON TO
THE NEXT SEGMENT.
[laughs]
>> WELL, I'M NOT FINISHED THE
STORY, HAROLD.
>> OH, NO>
WELL, THAT'S--THAT'S A EXCELLENT
POINT, BUT MAYBE JUST DON'T GIVE
IT ALL TO THE VIEWERS RIGHT NOW.
HOLD SOME BACK, YOU KNOW?
THAT'S ALL I'M SAYIN'.
>> WELL, YOU'RE THE PRODUCER.
>> YEAH, AND WHILE THEY'RE
AWAITING THE CONCLUSION OF YOUR
STORY, WE'LL SHOW THEM SOMETHING
THAT'S NOT, LIKE, SO BORING.
STAND BACK.
>> YOU KNOW, HAROLD, YOU'RE
GONNA HURT YOURSELF ON THAT
THING ONE DAY.
>> YOU REALLY THINK SO?
>> I'M GONNA MAKE SURE OF IT.
>> [strumming guitar] THERE ONCE WAS A GIRL
IN MY HIGH SCHOOL
THE PRETTIEST GIRL IN CLASS
SHE HAD THE NICEST
AUBURN HAIR
BUT THERE'S NO WAY
THAT THIS LINE'S GONNA RHYME
I WANTED SO BAD
TO TAKE HER OUT
I THOUGHT MY HEART
WOULD BURST
BUT ONCE I SAW
HER FATHER'S BICEPS
I WAS AFRAID
HE'D TAKE ME OUT FIRST
>> THIS WEEK IN THE HANDYMAN
CORNER, WE'RE GONNA TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING UNPLEASANT BUT
NECESSARY, AND I DON'T MEAN
KISSIN' YOUR GRANDMOTHER.
IF YOU'RE LIKE ME, AND YOU OWN A
FULL SET OF POWER TOOLS, YOU
PROBABLY THINK ABOUT DEATH A
LOT.
AND YOU KNOW THEM FUNERAL
PARLORS CAN JUST CHARGE WHATEVER
THEY WANT.
YEAH, I MEAN, THEY CALL THEIR
CUSTOMERS "STIFFS."
THE COFFIN ALONE'S GONNA COST
YOU $2,000 OR $3,000,
OR WHAT YOU CAN DO IS PICK UP
A BROKEN FREEZER CHEAP
AND MAKE YOUR OWN.
IF YOU'RE THE ROMANTIC TYPE, YOU
AND THE MISSUS COULD GO TOGETHER
IN ONE OF THEM SIDE-BY-SIDE
REFRIGERATOR/FREEZER UNITS.
SO ONCE YOU'VE GOT YOUR FREEZER,
THEN YOU JUST PICK OUT THE
FINISH THAT YOU WANT ON IT.
YOU CAN HAVE OAK OR PINE OR
MAHOGANY OR, IN FACT, ANYTHING
THAT'S AVAILABLE IN THE MACTAC
LINE.
AND FOR ABOUT 20 BUCKS' WORTH,
IT'S GONNA LOOK JUST BEAUTIFUL.
IF YOU'VE NEVER MACTACCED
BEFORE, THIS IS AN IDEAL
LEARNER'S PROJECT BECAUSE WHEN
PEOPLE SEE IT, THEY'RE GONNA BE
LOOKIN' AT IT THROUGH A VEIL OF
TEARS, AND THEN LATER, IT'S
GONNA BE SIX FEET UNDER.
SO OPEN HER UP AND, UH...
OPEN HER UP.
THROW IN A HUNK OF FUN FUR FOR
YOUR LINING, AND YOU'RE READY TO
PUT ON THE COFFIN HANDLES.
JUST USE A LITTLE BIT OF THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON ON
THAT, DUCT TAPE.
THESE ARE ACTUALLY TOWEL RACKS,
AND THEY'RE CHEAP, BUT THEY LOOK
GOOD.
AND WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
THERE'S KIND OF A SUBTLE TIE-IN
TO THE OCCASION BECAUSE YOU ARE
THROWING IN THE TOWEL.
NOW, WHAT ABOUT A HEADSTONE?
DO YOU HAVE TO GO THE BIG DOLLAR
FOR THE MARBLE OR THE GRANITE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
WHAT ABOUT SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
REMEMBER THIS FROM A FEW WEEKS
AGO?
THIS IS A TOILET TANK.
IT WAS ORIGINALLY OUR CERAMIC
PORTABLE BEVERAGE COOLER, BUT IT
MAKES A DANDY LITTLE HEADSTONE.
AND WE JUST PUT THESE
PEEL-AND-STICK LETTERS ON.
A LOT CHEAPER THAN ENGRAVING.
AND THESE ARE ACTUALLY DESIGNED
FOR A MAILBOX, BUT WHEN YOU
THINK ABOUT IT, THIS IS YOUR NEW
ADDRESS.
ANYWAY, YOU GET THE IDEA.
YOU CAN DO SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
IT'S CHEAP, AND IT'S JUST THAT
EASY.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME, REMEMBER.
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
HAROLD.
I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU HERE.
WE'RE GONNA TAKE A BREAK FOR
SOME COMMERCIAL MESSAGES RIGHT
NOW, BUT WHEN WE COME BACK, I'LL
FINISH THE STORY ABOUT THE HOT
WATER BOTTLE.
>> OR YOU COULD JUST DO THE
STORY WHILE WE'RE AT
COMMERCIALS.
THAT WOULD WORK TOO.
>> IT IS SPRING.
AT NIGHT, THE AIR IS CLEAR.
YOU CAN HEAR THE DISTANT HOWL
OF WOLVES.
THE SOUND PIERCES THE NIGHT,
SENDS SHIVERS UP YOUR SPINE,
PUTS NERVES ON EDGE.
THE LANGUAGE IS DIFFERENT,
BUT WE WOODSMEN KNOW
THE MESSAGE.
THE SAD AND LONELY WAIL
THAT SAYS,
"I HAVEN'T HAD SEX ALL WINTER."
SO AS I WAS SAYING,
BUSTER HATFIELD REALLY LIKES
DANGEROUS GAMES, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN HE'S--HE'S NOT HAPPY
UNLESS HE'S RISKIN' HIS LIFE,
AND ACTUALLY WITH HIS CLUMSINESS
AND ALL, HE'S HAPPY MOST OF THE
TIME.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT HE WANTED US
TO DO?
HE WANTED ALL THE GUYS TO TRY TO
BLOW UP ONE OF THEM HOT WATER
BOTTLES UNTIL IT EXPLODED.
HE'D SEEN A WRESTLER DO IT ON
ONE OF THEM EDUCATIONAL
PROGRAMS.
SO ANYWAY, WE GAVE HER A TRY.
WE MADE STINKY PETERSON GO LAST
'CAUSE NOBODY WANTED TO PUT
THEIR LIPS ON IT AFTER STINKY
HAD, YOU KNOW?
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK WENT FIRST,
AND, GOD, HE WAS BLOWIN' AND
BLOWIN' AND BLOWIN' AND NOTHIN'
WAS HAPPENIN'.
AND THEN HE TURNED TO THE SIDE,
AND WE COULD SEE THAT HIS LUNG
WAS COMIN' RIGHT OUT HIS EAR
THERE.
>> UNCLE RED, SOME VIEWERS HAVE
A SENSITIVE STOMACH.
>> YEAH, THAT WAS MOOSE
THOMPSON'S PROBLEM.
YOU'RE GETTIN' AHEAD OF ME
THERE, HAROLD.
>> UNCLE RED, WHY DON'T WE JUST
CUE UP THE NEXT SEGMENT?
WE CAN LISTEN TO SOME MORE
STORIES ABOUT YOUR FRIENDS
INFLATING THEIR ORGANS AT A
LATER DATE.
CUE UP IN THREE, TWO, ONE, GO.
>> I'VE LOST CONTROL OF MY OWN
SHOW.
>> BOB.
>> SHH!
FORE!
>> I'M SORRY.
I WAS DISTRACTIN' YOU.
SORRY, BOB.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> I WON'T COUNT THAT STROKE.
>> THEN IT WON'T COUNT
>> OKAY.
WELL, BOB, I HAVE A QUESTION FOR
YOU.
YOU KNOW, I KNOW IT'S YOUR DAY
OFF AND EVERYTHING.
>> DAY OFF?
OH, I WISH.
NO, TODAY'S A WORK DAY LIKE ANY
OTHER DAY, RED.
>> WELL, I, YOU KNOW, I JUST SAW
YOU GOLFING HERE, AND I JUST
DIDN'T REALIZE THE DEPARTMENT OF
NATURAL RESOURCES PAID PEOPLE TO
PLAY GOLF.
>> OH.
OH, THIS.
NO, NO, NO.
I'M DOING GOVERNMENT WORK.
I'M--I'M MEASURING TREES.
OH, YEAH.
THE--THEY'VE GOT ME OUT
MEASURING, YOU KNOW, BIRCHES,
MAPLES, STUFF LIKE THAT.
IT'S JUST TO CHECK THEIR GROWTH
RATE, YOU KNOW, FOR FUTURE
PLANNING.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> SEE THAT WAS 35 CENTIMETERS.
35 CENTIMETERS.
I DID ABOUT A 40 ON THAT LAST
HOLE.
MAKES THE TREES FIVE OVER PAR.
>> WHAT IS PAR ON THE COURSE
HERE?
>> RED MAPLE.
>> OH.
WELL, ANYWAY, BOB, WE--WE HAD
A--WE HAD A LITTLE PROBLEM UP AT
THE LODGE, AND I WANNA TALK--
TALK TO YOU ABOUT IT IF
YOU'VE GOT A MINUTE.
YOU KNOW, I'D JUST LIKE TO--
>> OH, YEAH.
>> WHAT?
OH, YEAH.
[bird twittering]
>> THE HELL WAS THAT?
>> THAT'S A BIRD, ISN'T IT?
>> FORE!
I MISSED IT AGAIN.
>> YEAH, WELL, I MEAN, THERE
AGAIN, I THINK I WAS DISTRACTING
YOU.
I MEAN I--I THINK THAT'S--I
WOULD CHALK THAT ONE UP TO--
>> YEAH, I WOULDN'T--I WOULDN'T
COUNT THAT--THAT SHOT EITHER.
>> NO, NO, ABSOLUTELY NOT.
>> UNDER THE CIRCUMSTANCES.
>> ANYWAY, WHAT I WANT--WHAT
HAPPENED WAS WE HAD A TRU--GOT
INTO A TRUCK AND TRACTOR PULL
KIND OF BY ACCIDENT AT THE
LODGE.
>> RIGHT, MM-HMM.
>> LIKE IT--WHAT HAPPENED WAS
THAT STINKY PETERSON AND MOOSE
THOMPSON GOT THEIR VEHICLES, THE
TRUCK AND A TRA--LOCKED
TOGETHER, 'CAUSE HE BACKED UP,
AND THEN THE HITCH CAUGHT.
AND THEY STARTED GOIN' LIKE SO,
AND THEN BEFORE YOU KNEW IT,
THEY CLEARED A LOT OF TREES
OUT--
>> SHH!
[bird cawing]
SHH!
FORE!
I MISSED IT AGAIN.
[laughs]
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
THREE WHIFFERS IN A ROW.
>> YEAH.
>> THREE OF--I'VE NEVER SEEN
THAT.
>> NO.
>> HAVE YOU SEEN THAT?
OH, THAT'S FUNNY.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT IS REALLY FUNNY.
[laughs]
OH, WAIT TILL THE GUYS IN THE
LODGE HEAR THAT.
I'LL BET THEY'LL R--
THEY'LL LAUGH.
>> THEY WILL.
>> I MEAN 'CAUSE THAT--THAT IS A
RIOT.
THEY WILL LAUGH.
[laughs]
>> YEAH. YEAH.
>> UNLESS, OF COURSE, NOBODY
TELLS THEM.
>> OH, WELL, I, AGAIN, HERE, I
JUST, I THINK I'M--I THINK I'M
THROWING YOU OFF.
I WOULD JUST NOT--I WOULD JUST
NOT COUNT THAT.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, I WON'T COUNT THAT
>> FAIR IS FAIR.
>> YEAH, FAIR IS FAIR.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
SO ANYWAY, I THOUGHT, YOU KNOW,
SINCE WE'VE GOT THIS WHOLE
UNDERBRUSH GONE BEHIND THE
LODGE, AND YOU BEING WITH
NATURAL RESOURCES AND YOU BEING
A LODGE MEMBER, YOU COULD GET US
SOME SEEDLINGS OR--
>> SHH!
FORE!
YES!
[laughs]
>> OH, OH. OH.
YEAH.
>> I GUESS THAT TREE THERE IS
THE NEXT ONE I'M GONNA MEASURE.
>> YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT THE SEEDLINGS?
I NEE--I COULD USE FERNS OR--
>> OH, YEAH.
NO PROBLEM.
>> OKAY, GREAT.
GREAT.
APPRECIATE IT.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
>> [grunting]
ONE!
TWO!
200 ENOUGH?
>> [strumming guitar] SATURDAY NIGHT
WHEN THE SUN GOES DOWN
THAT'S WHEN THE BOYS
ALL GATHER AROUND
THEY COME AND ASK ME
AS NICE AS YOU PLEASE
IF I'LL ENTERTAIN THEM
WITH MY OLD TRICK KNEES
I SNAP 'EM
I POP 'EM
THEY CRUNCH AND THEY CRACK
I SLIP OFF THE CAPS
AND SLIDE 'EM ROUND THE BACK
OH, THE BOYS
THEY JUST LOVE IT
I FEEL 10 FEET TALL
YOU KNOW, IF IT WASN'T FOR
MY ARTHRITIS
WE WOULDN'T HAVE
ANY FUN AT ALL
>> UNCLE RED, YOU BETTER HURRY
UP AND GET THE OLD LEAD OUT
'CAUSE WE GOT LOTS OF MAIL TO
ANSWER TODAY.
THERE SURE IS A WHOLE BUNCH OF
'EM.
WE BETTER JUST JUMP RIGHT IN,
ANSWER 'EM RIGHT AWAY, YOU KNOW,
GET RIGHT IN ON IT.
MAYBE I'LL JUST DO THAT.
I CAN READ 'EM FIRST, AND THEN
YOU CAN ANSWER 'EM.
THAT'LL WORK.
I'LL JUST DO THAT, OKAY?
"DEAR RED, IS IT JUST ME, OR HAS
THE WHOLE WORLD GONE SCREWY?"
>> IT'S BOTH.
>> INTERESTING.
"DEAR RED, AS A FEMINIST, I
WONDER IF YOU FEEL THAT MEN WILL
BE ABLE TO OVERCOME THEIR BASER
INSTINCTS AND THEIR SOCIAL
PREPROGRAMMING AND TREAT WOMEN
AS EQUALS, AS HUMAN BEINGS, AND
AS WHETHER THE SEXES CAN IN FACT
COOPERATE AND RESPECT EACH
OTHER'S DIFFERENCES WHILE
AVOIDING PREDESSING--
PRE--PREJUDGING ON THE OTHER'S
TALENTS AND/OR ABILITIES?"
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
"DEAR RED, WHAT KIND OF LURE DO
YOU USE FOR PICKEREL?"
>> ALL RIGHT, I USE A SPINNER,
A MEPPS NUMBER 7 IF I'M TROLLIN'
IN DAYLIGHT WITH THE SUN, NO
CLOUD.
IF YOU HAVE CLOUD, THEN I GO
WITH A NUMBER 3 OR SOMETIMES A
NUMBER 4 'CAUSE YOU CAN GO DEEP
WITH THOSE, AND THEY STILL PICK
UP ENOUGH LIGHT.
IT GIVES THAT NATURAL SHIMMER
THAT THE PICKEREL REALLY GO FOR.
IF IT'S NIGHT TROLLIN' THAT
WE'RE TALKIN' ABOUT, I GO WITH
THE NUMBER 1 WITH DOUBLE HOOKS
ON IT WHICH I HAD ACTUALLY
CUSTOM MADE FOR MYSELF BY A
JEWELER RIGHT HERE IN TOWN.
LAST WEEKEND IN MAY, MAYBE TWO
YEARS AGO, I WAS PICKEREL
FISHING ON LAKE SCUGOG, AND I
HOOKED INTO A BEAUTY.
IT WAS 14 POUNDS, 21 INCHES OF
FISH, AND I GOT HER IN THERE
WITH A--I THINK IT WAS A 40
POUND TEST LINE WITH A METAL
LEADER ON IT.
>> [laughs]
WE CERTAINLY HIT A NERVE THERE.
OKAY, FINAL LETTER, UNCLE RED.
"DEAR RED, I LIKE FISHING, BUT I
CANNOT ABIDE HUNTING.
MY WIFE, ON THE OTHER HAND, SEES
NO DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THEM AND
SAYS THAT BOTH ARE A FORM OF
MURDER AND THAT WE AS A
CIVILIZATION WILL HAVE TO LEAVE
THEM BEHIND IF WE ARE TO SURVIVE
AS A SPECIES OURSELVES.
I THINK HER NEO BUDDHIST
THEORIES ARE SIMPLY UNTENABLE
AND OVER SIMPLISTIC IN THE
EXTREME.
DO YOU AGREE?"
>> YEAH.
[gunshots]
>> THAT'S IT?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, WE--WE HAVE TIME IF YOU
WANT TO EXPAND ON YOUR ANSWERS,
UNCLE RED.
>> WELL, ALL RIGHT.
THAT DAY THAT I CAUGHT THE
PICKEREL, I'D BEEN FISHING DEEP
ALL DAY, TWO, THREE FEET OFF THE
BOTTOM...
BILL HAD INVITED ME TO COME OUT
BEHIND THE LODGE, AND WE'RE
GONNA FOOL AROUND, DO A
LITTLE BIT OF ARCHERY.
I THINK MAYBE, YOU KNOW, HE
SHOULD'VE WAIT UNTIL I GOT
THERE, BUT ON THE OTHER HAND,
YOU KNOW, ALL THINGS BEING
CONSIDERED, I'M KIND OF GLAD I
DIDN'T WALK BACK THERE.
YEAH, THAT'S A NICE TREAT.
THANK YOU, BILL.
AND HE HIT THE RAD REAL GOOD
THERE.
I BELIEVE THAT WAS ACTUALLY A
NEW HOLE.
I WASN'T TOO HAPPY, BUT HE WAS
FINE.
HE GOT HIS ARROW BACK.
ANYWAY, HE STICKS A TARGET UP,
AND THE IDEA IS THIS IS WHAT
WE'RE GONNA TRY AND HIT, THE TWO
OF US.
NOW, BILL'S A BIT OF AN EXPERT
ON A BOW AND ARROW, AND I'VE
REALLY NER--NEVER DONE ANYTHING
WITH THAT.
BUT HE TOLD ME, "NOW, YOU PUT
THIS THING ON.
IT'S CALLED A QUIVER,"
WHICH IS SOMETHING
THAT YOU DO WHEN YOU'RE
AROUND BILL AND HE HAS A BOW AND
ARROW, BELIEVE ME.
AND HE SHOWED ME HOW TO HOLD IT
AND EVERYTHING, AND I THINK A
LOT OF TIMES IT'S EASIER
TO--MAYBE TO DO SOMETHING THAN
TO SHOW SOMEBODY, YOU KNOW.
AND THEN YOU GET THE ARROW OUT
OF THERE AND, YOU KNOW, KIND OF
A ROBIN HOOD.
NOW, BILL IS HAVIN' A FEW
PROBLEMS.
BILL.
SO I JUST--BILL.
BILL, YOU WANT TO JUST--YOU
KNOW?
MM-HMM. MM-HMM. MM-HMM.
ALL RIGHT, SO WE'RE ALL SET UP
THERE, AND--OH, NO.
HE--THAT WAS GOOD OF HIM TO SHOW
ME SOME OF THE THINGS THAT CAN
GO WRONG WHEN YOU'RE--
AND THEN THEY SEEM TO HAVE A
MIND OF THEIR OWN, SOME OF THESE
ARROWS, I GUESS.
ME JUST BEING A BEGINNER, I
DIDN'T HAVE THESE PROBLEMS.
SO THEN I WASN'T A BAD SHOT.
WE WERE PRETTY DARN--PRETTY DARN
PROUD OF OURSELVES.
THAT'S--THAT'S NOT BAD, YOU
KNOW?
>> [groaning]
>> BILL TOOK A--BILL TOOK A HIT
HERE.
GOLLY, THAT--AND THAT SHIRT--
THAT SHIRT'LL NEVER--OH, LOOK
OUT.
OH.
THAT IS SO DANGEROUS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU CALL THAT,
AND THEN THIS--OH.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS TO A LOT OF
MIDDLE AGED MEN APPARENTLY.
SOME SORT OF--
OH, THAT WON'T WORK, BILL.
NOW JUST AS WE'RE--HE'S GONNA
SHOW ME A PRACTICAL APPLI--
THERE GOES A--AND HE CAN JUST
SHOW ME HOW TO HUNT WITH ONE OF
THESE.
AND HE'S--WE'RE JUST FOLLOWING
THE FLIGHT OF THE BIRD KIND OF.
AND THE--NOW THIS, TO ME, THIS
WAS A MISTAKE.
I DON'T CARE WHAT BILL SAYS.
AND HE WAS MORE INTERESTED IN
THE BIRD.
I WAS WATCHING THAT ARROW 'CAUSE
IT WENT STRAIGHT UP, AND THEN OF
COURSE, WHAT IT DID THEN WAS
COME PRETTY WELL STRAIGHT DOWN.
[clears throat]
OH, BOY.
EH, WE GOT IT RIGHT OUT OF
THERE.
HE WAS FINE TILL HE HAD THE--
AND HE WANTED ME TO LIGHT
THIS ARROW, AND I--WE JUST
COULDN'T QUITE COORDINATE.
I THINK THAT ONE--THAT DIDN'T
STRIKE.
NO, THAT WAS WRONG.
THAT WAS DEFINITELY WRONG, SO I
THOUGHT I'D LIGHT IT FIRST, AND
WE MAY HAVE PUT THE STUFF ON A
LITTLE HEAVY, YOU KNOW?
WE JUST--AND COURSE THIS IS
RETROSPECT AGAIN, YOU KNOW, AND
WELL--WELL, THAT'S NOT--THANK
YOU, BILL.
I DON'T--I THINK HE WENT TO GET
SOME WA--YEAH.
MM-HMM.
YOU MISSED IT, BILL.
SO NOW WE'RE STARTING TO LIGHT
THE LODGE FIELD ON FIRE, AND
BILL PICKS IT UP.
NOW HIS SOLUTION IS HE STICKS IN
THE BUCKET, WHICH I THINK HAD
WATER IN IT, AND THEN HE JUST
THROWS IT INTO--WELL, THAT WAS
GREAT.
THANK YOU, BILL.
THANK YOU.
IT IS SUMMER.
YOU HEAR THE PURE JOY IN THEIR
LAUGHTER OUTSIDE YOUR WINDOW.
YOU WATCH THEM OUT ON THE LAWN
RUNNING THROUGH YOUR SPRINKLER,
A HALF-DOZEN MIDDLE-AGED MEN
NAKED.
IT MUST BE HAPPY HOUR
AT THE LEGION.
>> UNCLE RED, WHEN--WHEN YOU
WERE IN SCHOOL, DID YOU HAVE GYM
CLASS?
>> I THINK SO.
THOSE SEVEN YEARS ARE A LITTLE
BLURRY.
WHY?
>> WELL, I DON'T GET THE POINT
OF IT.
I MEAN OTHER THAN TO GIVE PEOPLE
AN OPPORTUNITY TO FLICK NAKED
FLESH WITH A TOWEL, AN
OPPORTUNITY THAT DOES NOT COME
UP IN MATH OR HISTORY CLASS, WHO
NEEDS GYM?
>> IT'S PART OF YOUR EDUCATION,
HAROLD.
YOU KNOW, IT PREPARES YOU FOR
LIFE.
>> [scoffs]
WHAT IS GYM CLASS REALLY
PREPARING YOU FOR?
YOU SHOW ME ONE CHIEF EXECUTIVE
OFFICER WHO GOT TO THE POSITION
HE'S IN BECAUSE HE WAS GOOD AT
DODGE BALL.
WHERE WOULD WE BE?
WHERE WOULD WE BE IF HENRY FORD
DECIDED TO PLAY FIELD HOCKEY,
AND THEN EVENTUALLY WENT INTO
COACHING, AND FINALLY, INTO
BROADCASTING?
WHERE WOULD WE BE?
OH, YES.
OKAY.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING,
UNCLE RED.
THERE'S A LOT OF GOOD RUSSIAN
GYMNASTS.
BUT HAVE YOU EVER DRIVEN A LADA?
>> WHAT'S YOUR POINT, HAROLD?
>> WELL, I WAS HOPING MAYBE YOU
WOULDN'T MIND PHONING MY DAD AND
GETTING ME EXCUSED FROM GYM FOR
THE REST OF THE YEAR, ESPECIALLY
BEFORE WE HAVE THAT DANCE CLASS
WITH THE GIRLS NEXT WEEK.
THINK ABOUT IT, YOU KNOW?
>> WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE
OF THE SAME.
>> EVEN MORE SO, AND GOOD.
>> IT'S A GREAT DAY FOR FISHIN',
HAP.
AND THAT'S WHY WE ARE.
MIND YOU, WE GOT NO WAY OF
TELLIN' IF THE FISH ARE BITIN'.
>> NO, UNLESS WE WERE IN THE
SUBMARINE.
>> WELL, THAT'S GONNA BE A TOUGH
ONE, HAP.
I DON'T THINK THE LAUNCH RAMP AT
THE MARINA COULD TAKE THE
WEIGHT.
>> NO, THIS IS FRESH WATER.
WHEN I WAS IN THE NAVY, WE
STAYED IN SALTWATER OCEANS.
THE DEEPEST PARTS: CHASMS AND
THE TRENCHES.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE IN THE
NAVY, HAP.
WHAT YEAR WAS THAT?
>> OH, THAT'S CLASSIFIED.
MILITARY SECRETS.
IT WAS AT THE HEIGHT OF THE COLD
WAR.
I JOINED THE UNDERSEA SERVICE.
SUBMARINES, OR AS WE USED TO
CALL 'EM, SUBS.
SIX MONTHS WITHOUT SEEING
SUNLIGHT, UNDER SEA IN A NUCLEAR
SUB PLAYING CAT AND MOUSE WITH
THE RUSSKIS.
>> I DIDN'T THINK THERE WERE ANY
NUCLEAR SUBS IN THE CANADIAN
NAVY, HAP.
>> THAT'S WHY I JOINED THE
AMERICAN NAVY.
THAT'S WHERE THE ACTION WAS.
NUCLEAR SUBS LONG AS THREE
FOOTBALL FIELDS.
>> WOULD THAT BE AMERICAN
FOOTBALL FIELDS OR CANADIAN?
>> OH, THAT'S--THAT'S
CLASSIFIED.
I USED TO WORK IN THE ENGINE
ROOM.
I WAS A STOKER, STOKIN' THAT
NUCLEAR FUEL.
>> OH, NO, HAP, I--I THINK AND
THEY JUST USE THE STOKERS ON
THOSE COAL-POWERED SHIPS.
>> [laughs]
RED, YOU CAN'T--YOU CAN'T BURN
COAL UNDER WATER.
THE WATER WOULD COME DOWN THE
CHIMNEY AND PUT THE FIRE OUT.
NO, THIS WAS NUCLEAR FUEL.
URANIUM 287.
I'D FLING OPEN THE DOOR ON THAT
NUCLEAR FURNACE AND SHOVEL IN A
HEAP OF URANIUM, CLOSE THE DOOR.
>> YOU MEAN TO SAY, HAP, YOU
JUST HAD PILES OF URANIUM LYIN'
AROUND?
YOU JUST WOULD SCOOP THAT UP?
>> WELL, I DIDN'T HAVE TO USE A
LOT.
ONE SHOVELFUL WOULD POWER A SUB
FOR TWO MONTHS.
AND I WORE LEAD PANTS.
I HAD 400-POUND TROUSERS.
THEY HAD TO WELD THE FLY SHUT.
>> WELL, WHAT HAPPENED WHEN YOU
HAD TO GO THE BATHROOM?
>> YOU SEE, THAT'S--THAT'S TOP
SECRET.
>> YEAH, I'LL BET.
>> YEAH, WE HAD TO BE CLEARED.
I'LL TELL YOU, WE HAD A FEW
CASUALTIES.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, HAP, THEY SAY
THAT IN WAR, THE FIRST CASUALTY
IS THE TRUTH.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, BUSTER FINALLY GOT HIS
CHANCE TO BLOW UP THE HOT WATER
BOTTLE, AND GOD, YOU KNOW,
HE--HE DID REAL WELL,
BUT HE GOT IT INFLATED TO THE
POINT WHERE IT HAD FILLED UP THE
DEN AND IT WAS ACTUALLY SPILLING
OUT INTO THE LOBBY HERE.
YEAH, HE HAD HIS ARMS AND HIS
LEGS WRAPPED AROUND IT THERE,
AND YEAH, HE WAS DETERMINED HE
WAS GONNA EXPLODE THE THING, YOU
KNOW?
BUT IT NEVER GOT THAT FAR
BECAUSE IT UNFORTUNATELY CAUGHT
ON ONE OF THE ANTLERS WHICH
PUNCTURED A LITTLE HOLE IN
THERE, AND GAH, THE AIR COME OUT
SO FAST THAT THE WHOLE RIG BLEW
OUT THE SIDE DOOR AND SKIPPED
DOWN THE LAKE WITH BUSTER
HANGIN' ON FOR DEAR LIFE.
YEAH, IT'S NOT EVERY DAY YOU GET
TO SEE A MAN RIDIN' A 15-FOOT
RUBBER BLADDER.
NO HARM DONE, THOUGH, 'CAUSE I
MEAN IT PETERED OUT WAY BEFORE
IT GOT TO THE FALLS, AND BUSTER
JUST SWAM BACK.
BUT NOW THE WHOLE AREA SMELLS
LIKE BUSTER'S BREATH.
ANYWAY, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN'.
I'M COMIN' STRAIGHT HOME
TONIGHT, AND YES, I AM BRINGIN'
THE TV GUIDE.
SO THANKS TO ALL OF YOU FOR
TUNIN' US IN, AND UNTIL NEXT
TIME, ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
HAROLD AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT THE LODGE, KEEP YOUR
STICK ON THE ICE.