I KNOW WE ALL WANT
TO CELEBRATE NEW YEAR'S
BUT WHEN YOU'RE ALONE,
THERE'S A REAL DANGER OF
GOING OVER THE LINE
BETWEEN HARMLESS INDISCRETION
AND SERIOUS JAIL TIME.
AND THAT LINE IS USUALLY
CONNECTED TO THE AMOUNT
AND FREQUENCY
OF YOUR ALCOHOL INTAKE.
YOU SEE, WHEN YOU'RE ALONE,
YOU DON'T HAVE AN ALCOHOL
CONSUMPTION CONSULTANT NEARBY,
LIKE, SAY, A POLICEMAN
OR MEMBER OF THE CLERGY
OR THE ULTIMATE AUTHORITY:
YOUR OWN WIFE.
SO HERE'S SOMETHING YOU CAN
DO TO STOP YOURSELF FROM
DRINKING TOO MUCH.
OPEN UP YOUR CLOCK RADIO,
BREAK INTO THE SNOOZE
CONTROL CIRCUIT.
IT'S NOT HARD TO FIND.
JUST KEEP TOUCHING WIRES AND
PUSHING THE SNOOZE BUTTON.
YOU'LL FIND THE
RIGHT ONES IN NO TIME.
NOW, THE WAY A SNOOZE
ALARM WORKS NORMALLY IS
YOU PRESS THE BUTTON, IT SHUTS
THE RADIO OFF FOR AN HOUR.
BUT FOR OUR PURPOSES
I'M GOING TO SPLICE INTO
THE DISPENSING CIRCUIT
OF THIS POP MACHINE.
OKAY, UH --
YOU MIGHT WANNA
UNPLUG HER FIRST,
BUT I DON'T HAVE
THAT KIND OF TIME.
OKAY, NOW WHAT HAPPENS
IS YOU TAKE ALL THE
POP OUTTA THERE
AND REPLACE IT WITH CANS OF
YOUR FAVOURITE FERMENTED
BEVERAGE.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
NOW IT'S NEW YEAR'S.
YOU FEEL LIKE A BREWSKIE,
YOU PRESS THE BUTTON,
WHICH ALSO ACTIVATES
THE SNOOZE CONTROL.
AND NOW YOU CAN'T HAVE
ANOTHER BEER FOR AN HOUR.
HAPPY NEW YEAR.
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
[cheers and applause continue]
WE APPRECIATE THAT.
WELCOME TO OUR
NEW YEAR'S SPECIAL.
WE'VE NEVER DONE
ONE BEFORE.
I'M SURE THAT'LL BECOME
PAINFULLY OBVIOUS
IN THE
NOT-TOO-DISTANT FUTURE.
DON'T LISTEN TO HIM.
I DON'T.
WE HAVE A GREAT
SHOW FOR YOU.
IT'S OUR WAY OF HELPING YOU
BRING IN THE NEW YEAR.
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND ANYBODY OUT THERE
WHO'S MAYBE OVER 40
AND YOU GOT A COUPLE OF KIDS
AND YOU WANNA CELEBRATE
NEW YEAR'S EARLY
AND BE IN BED SAWING 'EM
BY THE TIME MIDNIGHT
COMES AROUND,
BOY, I ENVY YOU.
[ TOY HORN BLASTS ]
THERE'S THAT WET
BLANKET THING AGAIN.
LISTEN, YOU JUST
DO WHATEVER WORKS
FOR YOU, OKAY?
WE JUST WANNA MAKE SURE
YOU LOOK FORWARD TO
A HAPPY NEW YEAR!
YEAH, THAT'S ALL
I'M SAYING,
BECAUSE THEY MAY HAVE
HAD A CRAPPY OLD YEAR.
THAT'S ALL --
NO, NO, UNCLE RED.
THIS IS NEW YEAR'S.
IT'S A TIME OF EXPECTATIONS
AND OPTIMISM, YOU KNOW!
CAN WE SEE A
LITTLE ENTHUSIASM
AND EXCITEMENT, PLEASE?
YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
I DON'T LIKE EXCITEMENT. YOU KNOW?
EXCITEMENT ENDS UP
IN THE HOSPITAL --
SOMETIMES THE
MATERNITY WARD.
BUT I THINK IF
WE WORK TOGETHER,
I THINK WE'LL GET
THROUGH THIS JUST FINE.
WE'RE NOT GONNA
"GET THROUGH IT,"
WE'RE GOING TO
CELEBRATE IT!
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S NEW YEAR'S!
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GONNA CELEBRATE!
OKAY.
ENTHUSIASM RIGHT NOW.
I WANNA SEE SOME
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, UH,
LET'S WHOOP IT UP.
LET'S WHOOP IT UP, UH,
AND, HEY, LET'S PARTY.
LET'S PARTY.
THERE WE GO,
THAT'S IT?
"WHOOP IT UP"?
WHOOP?
OOH, THEY'RE
GOIN' NUTS, HUH?
WHOOP IT UP.
WELL, YOU GOTTA GO --
COME ON, LET'S GO!
COME ON, LET'S --
IT'S TIME TO
PAR-TAY, MY PEEPS.
[cheers and laughter]
[applause]
WHERE DID WE GO WRONG
WITH YOU, HAROLD?
WELL, IT WAS ALL THOSE YEARS
OF NOT GETTING THE
RESPECT I DESERVE.
YOU GOT WHAT YOU DESERVED;
IT JUST WASN'T RESPECT,
THAT'S ALL.
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
TODAY'S WINNER RECEIVES
A FREE TUXEDO RENTAL
FROM FEATHERSTONE'S
FUNERAL HOME.
TUXEDO NOT AVAILABLE
ON SATURDAYS.
OKAY, DALTON,
COVER YOUR EARS.
HAROLD, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON HUMPHREY
TO SAY THIS WORD...
KISS
OKAY, OKAY,
OKAY.
AND GO!
OKAY, ALL RIGHT,
MR. DALTON,
UM, THIS IS SOMETHING YOU AND
YOUR WIFE SHARE ON NEW YEAR'S.
CAB FARE.
NO, NO, UM --
OKAY, IT'S NEW YEAR'S EVE,
AND YOU'RE DANCING,
AND IT'S MIDNIGHT,
AND ALL YOU WANT IS A...
BACK PILL.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S FORGET NEW YEAR'S.
FORGET NEW YEAR'S.
IT'S GONE.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, THIS MORNING
WHEN YOU LEFT THE HOUSE,
YOU GAVE YOUR WIFE...
OH-HO!
TIME TO COOL OFF.
FURTHER BACK.
LET'S GO FURTHER BACK.
UM, OH, OKAY.
AFTER YOU SAID
YOUR WEDDING VOWS,
THE MINISTER TOLD YOU TO...
RECONSIDER.
DID HE REALLY?
YOU'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
HE WOULD SAY THAT.
IT'S SO BIZARRE
OH! OKAY, YEAH.
WELL, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, MR. DALTON,
THIS IS -- LET'S SEE.
THE LAST TIME YOU HAD
A ROMANTIC EVENING
WITH YOUR WIFE,
WHAT DID YOU DO?
OH, I WENT TO THAT NEW
RESTAURANT IN PORT ASBESTOS.
THERE'S 20 BUCKS
I CAN KISS GOOD-BYE.
[bell ringing]
[applause]
RED ASKED ME TO JOT DOWN A FEW
OF MY NEW YEAR'S RESOLUTIONS
AND SHARE 'EM WITH YOU.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO DO SOME
OF THESE FROM MEMORY.
I WROTE DOWN A COUPLE,
AND THEN I DROPPED THE PEN.
[clears throat]
ON THE PERSONAL SIDE,
I'M GONNA FOCUS MORE OF MY
FREE TIME ON ART AND
LITERATURE.
SO I'M GETTING
A SATELLITE DISH
AND SOME OF
THOSE BOOKS ON TAPE.
I'M ALSO PLANNING TO
DISCONTINUE THE SERVICE
SIDE OF THE MARINA.
DEALING WITH PEOPLE
WHOSE BOATS AREN'T WORKING
IS JUST NOT AN ENJOYABLE
WAY TO MAKE A LIVING.
A LOT OF THEM EXPECT THE BOATS
TO BE FIXED PROMPTLY
AND PROPERLY.
THEY DON'T SEEM TO REALISE
IT'S MY SUMMER TOO.
SO STARTIN' THIS YEAR,
WE'RE GONNA SPECIALISE
IN SALES ONLY.
YOU WANNA BUY A BOAT FROM ME,
IT'S CASH UP FRONT
AND NO TEST DRIVES.
WE ALSO DON'T HONOUR ANY MORE
FACTORY WARRANTEES.
THEY SHOULD BUILD 'EM
BETTER IN THE FIRST PLACE.
AND FINALLY, I'M GONNA TRY AND
CUT DOWN ON MY WORK HOURS.
LAST YEAR I TRIED
THAT 40 HOUR THING,
BUT THAT WORKED OUT TO OVER
THREE HOURS A MONTH.
OH, IT'S NAP TIME.
[sighs]
HAD A BIT OF A CAR
ACCIDENT THIS MORNING.
YOU KNOW, I USED TO BE
ABLE TO DRIVE STANDARD
TRANSMISSION NO PROBLEM.
BUT NOW WITH
THE TRICK KNEE --
THIS IS ONE OF THOSE
SPINNING PLAYGROUND RIDES.
LUCKILY, THERE WERE
NO KIDS AROUND.
THEY'D ALREADY BEEN
ON IT FOR FIVE MINUTES,
SO THEY WERE OVER
IN THE BUSHES BARFING.
I TELL YOU, GOOD THING
DALTON WASN'T WITH ME.
THIS IS HIS CAR.
YEAH, SHE'S JAMMED
ON THERE PRETTY GOOD.
JUST SPINS AROUND
IN A CIRCLE.
BUT I'M THINKIN',
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS IS NEW YEAR'S EVE,
AND THIS ROTATING CAR
COULD BE CONVERTED
INTO A DANDY NOISE MAKER.
I GOT EVERYTHING
I NEED RIGHT HERE.
ANYBODY WITH HALF
A BRAIN COULD DO THIS.
[laughter]
WE GOTTA HAVE
MUSIC AT MIDNIGHT,
SO I HOOKED THIS SPEAKER
UP TO THE EIGHT-TRACK,
AND RIGHT AT THE
STROKE OF 12,
WE'RE GOING TO BE LISTENING
TO "AULD LANG SYNE"
PLAYED BY GUY LINGUINE
AND HIS ROYAL CUSTODIANS.
BUT MAINLY WHAT
WE NEED IS NOISE.
SO I'VE ATTACHED A
TAMBOURINE TO MY DRIVE WHEEL;
MEANWHILE, I GOT MARACAS
PLAYING WIPE OUT ON
THE WINDSHIELD.
AND AS A SPECIAL TREAT
I WEDGED A TROMBONE
IN THE TAILPIPE.
NOT OFTEN YOU SEE A CAR
WITH A HORN IN THE BACK.
I GUESS IT'S A GUY THING.
[trombone blasts note]
OKAY, THAT'S A GOOD START.
BUT WHEN IT COMES
TO BEING ANNOYING,
WE'VE ONLY BEGUN TO
SCRATCH THE SURFACE.
A SNOW FENCE IS THE PERFECT
ADDITION TO A NEW YEAR'S PARTY
BECAUSE IT'S JUST
LIKE THE GUESTS...
IT STANDS AROUND
LOOKING GOOFY,
AND WHEN YOU NEED IT,
IT FALLS OVER.
HOPEFULLY IT WILL BE AS
NOISY AS THE GUESTS TOO,
ESPECIALLY WHEN THESE HOCKEY
STICKS START RAKING ACROSS IT.
I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR A TEST RUN.
I GOT HER IN GEAR, AND I
HOOKED UP THIS REMOTE STARTER,
SO I DON'T EVEN HAVE TO
BE IN THE CAR WHEN IT
STARTS SPINNING.
I'VE PRETTY WELL THOUGHT
OF EVERYTHING.
HMM.
audience: O-O-H!
ALL RIGHT, NO,
I'M FINE.
IT'S AN EMBARRASSING PLACE
TO HAVE TO HAVE A BRUISE,
BUT AFTER 35 YEARS
OF MARRIAGE,
SADLY, NO ONE'S
GONNA NOTICE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S PRETEND
IT'S MIDNIGHT.
LET'S DO THE
COUNTDOWN TOGETHER...
THREE,
TWO,
ONE,
HAPPY NEW YEAR!
[engine revving]
[instruments playing]
[applause]
YOU KNOW, IN HONOUR
OF NEW YEAR'S,
WE HAVE A SPECIAL
PRESENTATION
BY LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER, ED FRID.
ED, TELL EVERYONE
WHAT BROUGHT YOU HERE.
WELL, I WAS ASKED TO
MAKE A PRESENTATION
INVOLVING ANIMALS,
ONE THAT WOULD KICK OFF
THE NEW YEAR TO A GOOD START,
AND, UH, I THINK
I'VE DONE THAT.
YOU DON'T SEEM
VERY ENTHUSED, ED.
WELL, RED, NORMALLY THIS
IS MY VACATION TIME,
A TIME TO BE AWAY
FROM ANIMALS,
A TIME TO REFLECT
AND REVIEW THE RESULTS
OF MY VARIOUS MEDICAL TESTS.
HOW DID THOSE
MEDICAL TESTS GO?
WELL, THE FLEA AND TICK
THING TURNED OUT
TO BE NOTHING.
AND THE HOOF AND MOUTH
CAME BACK NEGATIVE.
[voice breaks]
RABIES IS THE BIG ONE.
WE'RE ALL HOPIN'
FOR THE BEST.
TO ME THAT'S ALL THE MORE
REASON TO HAVE A BIG
CELEBRATION NOW,
SO TELL US ABOUT IT.
OKAY, WELL, I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE A GOOD OMEN
TO RELEASE A FLOCK OF DOVES
TO START OFF THE NEW YEAR.
YOU SEE, THE DOVE HAS
BEEN A SYMBOL OF PEACE
SINCE THE DAYS OF
NOAH'S ARK
WHEN IT RETURNED TO THE SHIP
WITH AN OLIVE BRANCH
IN ITS CLAWS.
YEAH, ACTUALLY,
YOU OWE A LOT TO NOAH
BECAUSE HIS ARK SAVED
ALL THE ANIMALS FROM
BEING EXTINCT.
I HATE NOAH!
OKAY
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S NOT DWELL
ON THE NEGATIVE.
LET'S GET ON WITH OUR
PRESENTATION, EH?
IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN DO
TO HELP RELEASE THE DOVES?
I RECOMMEND YOU
STAND WELL BACK,
AND COVER YOUR
EYES WITH SOMETHING,
PREFERABLY SOMETHING HARDER
THAN A DOVE'S BEAK.
AND ONCE THEY GET UP
IN THE AIR, THEY GET
EASILY EXCITED,
SO I WOULDN'T STAND
UNDER THEM, OKAY?
OKAY, WELL,
WE'RE ALL READY,
SO LET'S RELEASE
THE DOVES.
YEAH, WE DON'T GO
WHEN YOU'RE READY;
WE GO WHEN I'M READY.
OKAY.
SORRY, ED.
I THOUGHT WE HAD AN
UNDERSTANDING, RED.
I KNOW! I KNOW!
I'M FINE. I'M GOOD.
YOU GO WHEN YOU'RE READY.
ALL RIGHT.
LET THESE DOVES
MARK THE BEGINNING
OF A PEACEFUL AND
PROSPEROUS NEW YEAR!
[laughter]
NEW YEAR'S RESOLUTIONS,
YEAH, I GOT A FEW.
I'VE ALWAYS GOT A FEW.
YOU SEE, MY MENTOR
AND PERSONAL GURU,
ANTHONY ANTHONY,
HE'S ADAMANT ABOUT
THE IMPORTANCE OF
SELF-IMPROVEMENT.
AND HE'S MADE A LOT OF MONEY
MAKING GUYS LIKE ME
A BETTER PERSON.
OKAY, THIS YEAR I WANNA TRY
AND NOT BE SO JUDGMENTAL.
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES PEOPLE ARE
DISRESPECTFUL OF ME,
AND I THINK IT'S BECAUSE THEY
SEE THE SEPTIC SUCKING
BUSINESS I HAVE
AND THE DRY SEWAGE
ENCRUSTED ON THE HOSES,
AND NATURALLY,
THEY'RE JEALOUS.
SEE, NOT EVERYONE
CAN BE AN ENTREPRENEUR.
NOT EVERYONE CAN
BE A SUCCESS.
SUCK CESS.
AND I HAVE TO ACCEPT THAT.
I HAVE TO BE SENSITIVE
TO THEIR PAIN
IN THEIR BORING OFFICE JOBS
WITH NO FUTURE
AND NOT EVEN A WHIFF
OF THE KIND OF LIFE I HAVE.
SO NO MATTER WHAT
THEY CALL ME,
I WILL NOT RETALIATE.
I'M GONNA RISE ABOVE IT.
AND THAT'S
IMPORTANT, YOU KNOW,
'CAUSE IN THE SEWAGE BUSINESS,
YOU HAVE TO BE ABLE
TO RISE ABOVE IT.
HAPPY NEW YEAR.
[applause]
WE NOW COME TO THAT
PORTION OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE ADDRESS
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
[giggling]
OKAY, TODAY'S LETTER
READS AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
ALL MY LIFE I'VE SUNG
"'AULD LANG SYNE'
EVERY NEW YEAR'S.
"IT MAKES ME
VERY EMOTIONAL.
"OFTEN I WEEP.
"MY QUESTION IS: WHAT THE HECK
IS THE SONG ABOUT?"
WELL, I HAVE NO IDEA,
BUT IT'S SCOTTISH,
SO IT'S PROBABLY SAD.
IT'S THE BAGPIPES.
WHENEVER I HEAR BAGPIPES
IT BRINGS ME TO TEARS.
YEAH, ME TOO.
I SMILE WHEN
THEY STOP, THOUGH.
YOU KNOW, IT'S OBVIOUS
THAT YOU TWO
KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT SCOTLAND.
FOR EXAMPLE, DID YOU
KNOW THAT IN SCOTLAND
NEW YEAR'S IS MORE
POPULAR THAN CHRISTMAS?
IS THAT BECAUSE
THEY DON'T HAVE
TO BUY PRESENTS?
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S BECAUSE NEW YEAR'S
AND SCOTLAND PREDATES
CHRISTIANITY.
IT'S NOT EVEN
CALLED NEW YEAR'S;
IT'S CALLED HOGMANAY.
IT MEANS 'THE MOON
OF THE HAG.'
WELL, I DON'T THINK
THAT THE MOON FROM A HAG
WOULD BE SOMETHING
I'D EVER WANNA SEE.
NO, NO, NO.
IT REFERS TO
A DATE, MIKE.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE A
SUPERSTITIOUS THING.
IT'S BAD LUCK TO
MAKE A MARRIAGE PROPOSAL
OR TO BREAK GLASS
OR TO SPIN FLAX
OR TO CARRY OUT
THE RUBBISH.
I FEEL THAT
WAY EVERY DAY.
OKAY, YOU KNOW, RIGHT AT
THE STROKE OF MIDNIGHT
THEY FLING OPEN
THE WINDOWS AND DOORS
TO LET OUT THE OLD YEAR
AND DRIVE OUT THE BAD DOGS
OF THE UNDERWORLD.
OH, SO THEY TELL THE
NEIGHBOURS TO GO HOME, HUH?
NO, NO.
AND THEN MUCH LATER
THE BANDS OF ROVING MEN,
CALLED WASSAILS,
GO FROM HOUSE TO HOUSE,
CARRYING A BIG BOWL
OF ALCOHOL
AND ASKING FOR MONEY.
WASSAILS,
I'VE HEARD OF THAT.
OH, SURE YOU HAVE...
YO, MIKE, WA-A-A-SSAIL!
WA-A-A-SSAIL!
OH, COME ON.
STOP THAT!
I'M TRYING TO
EDUCATE YOU PEOPLE HERE
NOW, COME ON.
I'M SORRY.
ARE YOU GUYS
GONNA BE SERIOUS,
OR ARE YOU GONNA
BE GOOFBALLS?
IT'S NEW YEAR'S EVE.
I'M GOIN' WITH GOOFBALLS.
WA-A-A-SSAIL!
OH, HI, EVERYBODY.
RANGER GORD HERE WITH MY
NEW YEAR'S RESOLUTIONS.
DO YOU REALISE WHAT AN
ADVANTAGE IT IS TO BE
A FOREST RANGER
WHEN IT COMES TO MAKING
NEW YEAR'S RESOLUTIONS?
I MEAN, YOU PEOPLE,
WHEN YOU MAKE RESOLUTIONS,
YOU'VE GOT FRIENDS
AND FAMILY
AND CO-WORKERS AROUND
YOU EVERY DAY.
IF YOU HAPPEN
TO BREAK ONE OF YOURS,
EVERYBODY KNOWS, RIGHT?
YOU POOR,
PATHETIC PEOPLE.
NOW, LOOK AT THE
DEAL I'VE GOT.
I CAN MAKE ANY
RESOLUTION I WANT,
AND I CAN BREAK IT,
JUST LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE NOBODY EVER
COMES UP HERE, THAT'S WHY.
I MEAN, I COULD DECIDE,
OKAY, THIS YEAR,
I'M NOT GOING TO BATHE.
WHO WOULD KNOW?
JUST ME.
[weeping]
AND THAT'S JUST
THE WAY I LIKE IT.
[sniffling]
I LIKE BEING ALONE.
I CAN DO
WHATEVER I WANT.
I COULD SPEND THE WHOLE DAY
LICKING THINGS.
[laughter]
FRIENDS DON'T LET
YOU DO THAT, BELIEVE ME.
I CAN STAY UP LATE
WATCHING TV,
WATCHING WHATEVER I WANT.
DIDN'T KNOW I
HAD A TV, DID YOU?
WELL, I DO.
[weeping]
AND IT'LL WORK A LOT BETTER
WHEN I GET ELECTRICITY.
ANYWAY, I'M NOT GONNA
MAKE ANY RESOLUTIONS
BECAUSE I DON'T NEED ANY.
I LIKE THINGS JUST
THE WAY THEY ARE.
NO NOSY NEIGHBOURS,
NO NOSY BOSSES,
NOBODY AT ALL.
JUST ME.
I'M SO LUCKY.
HAPPY NEW YEAR.
YOU KNOW, BRINGING
IN THE NEW YEAR
WITH A CELEBRATORY DRINK
IS AN OLD CUSTOM.
IT GOES WAY BACK
TO ANCIENT TIMES.
I BELIEVE IT WAS
JULIUS CAESAR WHO SAID,
"FRIENDS, ROMANS, COUNTRYMEN,
LEND ME YOUR BEERS."
OF COURSE, ON NEW YEAR'S EVE
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
DRINKING CHAMPAGNE.
BUT THAT CAN BE A PROBLEM
WHAT WITH FRENCH WINE
BEING SO EXPENSIVE
AND YOU BEING SO CHEAP.
SO HERE'S WHAT YOU DO...
YOU MAKE YOUR OWN.
I START WITH
A GOOD-SIZED JUG.
QUANTITY IS AN
IMPORTANT FACTOR.
I FIND WITH ALCOHOL,
PEOPLE EVEN LIKE
THE BAD STUFF
IF THERE'S PLENTY OF IT.
SO WE'RE GONNA MAKE A MAGNUM.
HERE AGAIN,
MAGNUM IS A LATIN WORD,
MEANING HUMONGOUS.
OKAY, YOU KNOW, CHAMPAGNE
HAS A BIT OF A ZING TO IT.
EVEN THE SMELL
TICKLES YOUR NOSE.
WELL, YOU CAN GET THE SAME
EFFECT WITH VINEGAR.
AH, WHAT THE HECK?
IT'S NEW YEAR'S.
OKAY, NOW YOU FILL UP
THE REST OF YOUR MAGNUM
WITH YOUR FAVOURITE BEER --
OR WHATEVER KIND
DALTON BROUGHT.
HE'LL NEVER NOTICE.
HE'LL BE TOO BUSY
CHASIN' THE SHRIMP RING.
OKAY, NOW WE COME TO
THE FUN PART OF CHAMPAGNE.
I DON'T MEAN THAT
TIPSY FEELING YOU GET
WHEN YOU START DOIN' YOUR
JIMMY STEWART IMPRESSION
ALL NIGHT.
NO, NO, I'M TALKING
ABOUT THE BUBBLES.
NOW, IN REAL CHAMPAGNE THE
BUBBLES COME FROM --
I DUNNO, GRAPES WITH
AIR IN 'EM, OR SOMETHING.
BUT WE'RE GOING TO MAKE OUR
BUBBLES BY ADDING BAKING SODA
TO THE VINEGAR WE
ALREADY GOT IN THERE.
NOW, HERE'S THE THING.
WE DON'T WANT THOSE CHEMICALS
MIXING TOO SOON.
SO GET YOURSELF SOME
OF THESE COLD CAPSULES
AND EMPTY THEM
INTO A GLASS.
ALL RIGHT, AND SAVE ALL
THAT FOR LATER,
BECAUSE SOME DAY
YOU MAY HAVE A COLD,
AND YOU CAN DRINK THE WHOLE
THING ALL AT ONCE.
IT WON'T DO ANYTHING
FOR YOUR COLD,
BUT IT'LL GIVE YOU SOMETHING
THE DOCTORS CAN CURE.
OKAY, NOW YOU WANNA
FILL THESE CAPSULES UP
WITH THE BAKING SODA.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I'VE ALREADY DONE A FEW.
SO WE'LL JUST POP
THEM INTO THE MAGNUM.
OKAY, WE JUST GOTTA
GET THE CORK IN THERE
BEFORE THOSE CHEMICALS MIX.
ALL RIGHT, NOW GET
YOURSELF SOME CHICKEN WIRE,
NOT JUST FOR
DECORATION ANYMORE.
YOU WANNA USE THAT
TO HOLD THE CORK IN PLACE.
AND THEN FOR THAT LITTLE
EXTRA TOUCH OF CLASS,
GET YOURSELF
SOME GOLD FOIL
[muffled]
AND WRAP THAT AROUND...
[chuckling]
OKAY, BY MIDNIGHT, THE
CAPSULES WILL BE ALL
DISSOLVED IN THERE,
AND THAT'LL ALLOW THE CARBON
DIOXIDE TO COME FIRING
OFF INTO THE BEER
AS THE BAKING SODA MIXES
IN WITH THE VINEGAR.
SO NOW ALL'S YOU GOTTA DO IS
REMOVE YOUR FANCY FOIL,
TAKE OFF YOUR PROTECTIVE
CHICKEN WIRE OFF THERE.
AND IF YOU PUT
IN ENOUGH VINEGAR,
YOU SHOULDN'T EVEN
NEED A CORKSCREW.
SO HAPPY NEW YEAR --
OR I SHOULD SAY,
HAPPY NEW BEER.
[fizzing sound]
[fizzing stops]
REMEMBER,
DRINK RESPONSIBLY.
[applause]
OH, HI, EVERYBODY.
RANGER GORD HERE.
WELL, IT'S THE
BIG NIGHT, ISN'T IT?
NEW YEAR'S EVE,
WOOHOO.
YOU KNOW, FOREST RANGERS
DON'T HAVE BIG NIGHTS.
WE HAVE LONG NIGHTS,
LONG, COLD, LONELY NIGHTS,
WHEN YOU WAKE UP IN
A COLD SWEAT
WITH YOUR LIPS WRAPPED AROUND
A CAN OF CREAMED CORN.
[shudders]
YOU KNOW, I THINK THE CAPTAIN
AND TENILLE SAY IT BEST
IN THEIR BRAND NEW HIT,
"MUSKRAT LOVE."
BETCHA A FOREST RANGER
WROTE "MUSKRAT LOVE."
ANYWAY, IT'S A
NIGHT OF CELEBRATION,
AND FOR THAT I'VE CREATED THIS
BRAND NEW ANIMATED FILM FOR
YOUR AMAZEMENT.
IT'S ALL ABOUT NEW YEAR'S
EVE IN THE FOREST.
BUT I'VE CALLED IT
"FOREST NEW YEAR'S."
GET IT?
HERE WE GO.
[quirky upbeat music]
TODAY I'M GOING TO TEACH
EVERYONE IN THE UNIVERSE
THE TRADITION OF
A FOREST NEW YEAR'S.
AND I CAN HARDLY
CONTAIN MY EXCITEMENT.
WELL, YOU HAVE A
PRETTY SMALL CONTAINER.
I'M ANXIOUS TO LEARN
ANY BIT OF LORE
CONCERNING THE FOREST
AND ITS MANY TRADITIONS.
GOOD BOY, HAROLD.
THE FOREST NEW YEAR STATES
THAT IN ORDER TO HAVE
A HAPPY NEW YEAR,
YOU HAVE TO HURL A
LUCKY ROCK OVER THE MOON
AND ACROSS THE RIVER
BEFORE THE STROKE
OF MIDNIGHT.
I'VE NEVER HEARD
OF SUCH A THING.
I'M FAMILIAR WITH
HURLING BEFORE MIDNIGHT.
YOU TWO GRAB
THAT LUCKY ROCK
AND BRING IT DOWN
TO THE RIVER.
IT'S THE ONE
ON THE LEFT.
OH, MY MISTAKE.
IT'S THE ONE
ON THE RIGHT.
[grunting]
ALMOST THERE.
TO TOSS THE ROCK, WE'RE GOING
TO USE NATURE'S OWN CATAPULT,
THE PINE TREE.
THAT'S A
MAPLE TREE, GORD.
OH -- OH, WELL, IT ACTUALLY
DOESN'T MAKE ANY DIFF --
OW.
OH, THERE'S A PINE
TREE THERE.
RIGHT THERE.
LET ME GIVE YOU
HAND THERE, HAROLD.
OKAY, STICK THE LUCKY
ROCK ON THERE, RED.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THE
LUCK MAY HAVE WORN OFF
THIS PARTICULAR ROCK.
I'LL GIVE
YOU A HAND!
[screaming]
WE DID IT!
IT'S GOING TO BE
A HAPPY NEW YEAR!
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE HAROLD'S
GOING TO MISS THE FIRST
FEW WEEKS OF IT,
SO I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
HA! HA! HA!
[quirky upbeat music]
[applause]
HAPPY NEW YEAR.
MAY YOUR SEPTICS NEVER
CAUSE YOU A TEAR.
MAY THEY HANDLE
YOUR CHILI BEANS,
BRATWURST AND BEER.
MAY YOUR TANK RUN ON EMPTY
THROUGHOUT THE NEW YEAR.
BUT IF NOT,
MY PUMP AND MY HOSE
ARE RIGHT HERE.
WELL THEN, I GUESS
THE TIME HAS COME
FOR ME TO MAKE MY
NEW YEAR'S RESOLUTION.
I'VE DECIDED TO BE A LOT
MORE SPECIFIC THIS YEAR.
USUALLY I PROMISE
MYSELF SOMETHING LIKE,
I'M GOING TO LOSE WEIGHT
OR START MY OWN BUSINESS
OR HAVE A CONVERSATION
WITH MY PARENTS.
BUT THIS YEAR I'VE DECIDED TO
ZERO RIGHT IN ON THE PROBLEM.
I SOLEMNLY SWEAR BEFORE
ALL OF THESE WITNESSES
THAT FOR THE NEXT YEAR,
AND POSSIBLY LONGER,
I WILL NOT EAT
PEANUT BUTTER SANDWICHES.
PERIOD.
REGARDLESS OF
THE CIRCUMSTANCES,
EVEN IN THE CASE
OF AN EMERGENCY.
THIS IS BECAUSE PEANUT BUTTER
HAS A WAY OF STICKING
TO THE ROOF OF
A PERSON'S MOUTH.
THAT CAN BE DISTRACTING
AND CAN ALSO IMPEDE THEIR
ABILITY TO CALL FOR HELP
WHEN THEY SO
DESPERATELY NEED IT.
NOW, THIS MAY SOUND
LIKE AN ODD NEW YEAR'S
RESOLUTION TO YOU,
BUT YOU'RE NOT AN ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICER, ARE YOU?
NO, YOU COULD PROBABLY SPEND
MOST OF YOUR DAY
SITTING AT YOUR DESK, DRINKING
COFFEE OR DOING WHATEVER
WAS NECESSARY
TO GET THE PEANUT BUTTER OFF
OF THE ROOF OF YOUR MOUTH!
WELL, WHOOP-DE-FREAKING-DO!
I DON'T HAVE THAT LUXURY.
I DON'T WORK IN AN OFFICE.
I WORK IN THE WOODS.
I WORK IN THE
WOODS WITH ELK.
ELK HAVE HORNS,
EYE-LEVEL HORNS.
AND SO THAT IS WHY I PROMISE
TO NEVER EAT ANOTHER
PEANUT BUTTER SANDWICH AGAIN.
EVER.
HAPPY NEW YEAR.
[applause]
Red: NOW, FOR NEW YEAR'S WE
THOUGHT WE'D DO OUR VERSION
OF THE TIME SQUARE DROPPING
THE BALL AT MIDNIGHT.
AND MIKE WAS MAKING
SOME KIND OF PUNCH THERE.
HE'S REALLY SOCKING
THE BOOZE INTO HER.
BUT I HAD WINSTON FILLING
THE OIL DRUM WITH WATER.
THAT WAS GOING TO BE THE
COUNTERWEIGHT.
WHOA, EASY, EASY, EASY.
HOLY COW. MY GOLLY.
NOBODY'S GONNA TRY THAT
WITHOUT HOSPITAL INSURANCE.
SO ANYWAY, I'M GETTIN'
THE BALL UP THERE.
WE JUST HOIST HER UP.
THEN WHAT I DO IS TIE THAT
ONTO THE OIL DRUM
FULL OF WATER.
AND THE WAY IT WORKS, AS I
WAS EXPLAINING TO THE GUYS,
WHAT WE DO IS LET THE WATER
SLOWLY OUTTA THE OIL DRUM,
AND THEN THE MIRROR
BALL WILL COME DOWN.
SO IT'S A VERY
SIMPLE PRINCIPLE.
DO YOU GUYS --
YOU GUYS --
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKIN' --
NOTHING, NOT A THING.
ALL RIGHT, SO I SAY,
I'LL TAKE THAT CORK OUT,
AND THE WATER
GOES OUT AND --
DO YOU GET IT NOW?
NOTHING. NOTHING.
NOT A PULSE THERE.
SO I THOUGHT, WELL,
I'LL JUST DEMONSTRATE.
SO AS THE WATER GOES OUT,
SEE, THAT GOES UP,
AND THE BALL
STARTS COMING DOWN.
OF COURSE, WE'RE GONNA
DO THIS AT MIDNIGHT.
BUT ACTUALLY IT WAS
GOOD WE DID A TRIAL RUN,
BECAUSE WE GOT A PROBLEM.
SHE JAMMED INTO THE PULLEY,
AND NOW I CAN'T GET IT DOWN;
I CAN'T GET IT UP.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
NOW WE GOTTA GET IT
OUTTA THE PULLEY THERE.
SO WALTER HAD THE IDEA
MAYBE HE COULD GET A LADDER,
BUT THERE'S NOTHING, REALLY,
TO PUT A LADDER AGAINST.
GET RID OF THE
LADDER, WALTER.
FORGET THE LADDER.
THE OTHER GUYS, MEANWHILE,
HAD GOT THE HELIUM BALLOONS.
WALTER'S ONLY
ABOUT 130 POUNDS,
AND WITH ABOUT 10 --
10 OR 15, YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN ACTUALLY GET -- WELL,
ANYWAY, THAT'S A GOOD --
YOU KNOW, IN RETROSPECT,
HE PROBABLY SHOULD'VE
HUNG ONTO THE POLE.
'CAUSE THAT WOULD'VE
KEPT HIM --
'CAUSE AS HE GOT UP THERE,
THERE WAS A BIT OF
A CROSS WIND,
AND HE'S, UH, KINDA
GETTING AWAY FROM --
SO, OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
NO, HERE'S WHAT WE DO.
HERE'S WHAT WE DO: IF CAN
GET HIM TO GRAB THE END
OF THE LADDER,
WE CAN PULL HIM
OVER TO THE POLE.
SO WE HOLD THE LADDER.
GRAB THE END, WALTER.
SO ANOTHER GUST
OF WIND COMES.
NOW HE'S PULLING US!
GOING THE OTHER WAY.
WE DIDN'T SEE THE
POWER WIRE THERE.
AND HE'S HANGING ON THERE.
AND THEN IT HITS
THE PUNCH BOWL,
AND OH, BOY.
SO NOW WE GOTTA GET --
I FIGURE IF WE CAN JUST
BREAK ONE BALLOON
WITH A ROCK --
OR MAYBE TWO
OR THREE BALLOONS.
SO I FIRE A ROCK.
I GOT ONE.
OKAY, JUST BREAK
A COUPLE MORE.
DON'T KNOW QUITE
WHAT DALTON HAD IN MIND.
YOU KNOW, BETTER NOT
TO ASK SOMETIMES.
I THINK THE SHIRT
SAYS IT ALL.
OH, PITCHFORK,
THAT'S MAYBE NOT --
MAYBE NOT THE BEST IDEA.
OH, OH.
OH!
OH, OH, OH.
OH, MY GOSH.
WELL, HERE COMES THE BALL!
OKAY, I GUESS
IT'S MIDNIGHT SOMEWHERE,
SO HAPPY NEW YEAR.
[applause]
YOU KNOW, IT'S GREAT TO
HAVE A NEW YEAR'S PARTY,
WHERE YOUR FRIENDS
CAN ENJOY THEMSELVES,
BUT THE LAST THING YOU WANT
IS SOMEBODY TRYING TO
DRIVE A CAR
AFTER THEY'VE
BEEN OVER SERVED.
SO HERE'S WHAT YOU DO...
STACK A BUNCH OF DEAD SOLDIERS
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE ROOM.
THEN LAY AN EMPTY
PIZZA BOX ON TOP.
THAT'S GONNA BE A STEP STOOL
THAT YOUR FRIENDS CAN USE
TO RETRIEVE THEIR CAR KEYS
BEFORE THEY DRIVE HOME.
AND THE REASON THEY
NEED A STEP STOOL,
IS THAT WHEN THEY
ARRIVED AT THE PARTY
YOU TOOK THEIR KEYS AND HUNG
THEM FROM THIS CEILING FAN.
NOW, EACH OF YOUR GUESTS
HAS TO BE SOBER ENOUGH
TO BALANCE ON THE STOOL,
OR THEY DON'T GET THEIR KEYS.
AND TO MAKE IT
A BETTER TEST,
I'VE WIRED THE FAN
INTO A MOTION DETECTOR
SO THAT AS THEY
APPROACH THE UNIT,
IT GETS A LITTLE TRICKIER
TO GRAB THEIR KEYS.
OUCH!
[applause]
I NEED A DRINK.
UNCLE RED, CAN I TALK
TO YOU A MINUTE?
I WAS JUST WORKING
ON MY NEW YEAR'S
RESOLUTIONS,
AND I THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE A GOOD IDEA TO
GET SOME INPUT
FROM SOMEONE I SPEND
A LOT OF TIME WITH
TO MAKE SURE I'M MAKING
WORTHWHILE CHANGES.
WELL, I THINK THAT'S
A GREAT IDEA, HAROLD.
OH, OKAY, GOOD.
GREAT.
IS THERE ANOTHER CHAIR
AROUND THAT I COULD USE?
I GOT A
FOOTSTOOL HERE.
OKAY, THAT'D
BE GREAT.
OKAY, SO --
THANK YOU.
WELL, I HAVE MY
LIST OUT.
PERHAPS YOU'D LIKE
TO TAKE YOURS OUT.
WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
I WAS JUST SAYIN'
WHEN TWO PEOPLE SPEND A LOT
OF TIME WITH EACH OTHER,
YOU KNOW, NEW YEAR'S IS
PROBABLY A REALLY GOOD TIME
THAT THEY COULD SIT
DOWN AND FIGURE OUT
HOW TO MAKE THE
RELATIONSHIP BETTER.
YEAH, NO,
I AGREE WITH YOU.
SO WHY DON'T YOU GO THROUGH
THE CHANGES YOU'RE GONNA MAKE,
'CAUSE I CAN REALLY HELP
YOU OUT THERE.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL START
WITH MINE THEN.
WELL, I RESOLVE
TO LIMIT HOW MUCH I
TALK ABOUT COMPUTERS;
HOW LONG I'M ON
THE INTERNET;
FIND A GIRLFRIEND;
AND TO ONCE AGAIN
NOT TO TAKE UP SMOKING.
OKAY, THAT'S GOOD, BUT YOU
KNOW WHAT ELSE, HAROLD?
YOU SHOULDN'T GIVE YOUR
OPINION ALL THE TIME.
I FIND THAT
ANNOYING.
THAT'S NOT A
VALID CRITICISM.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT RIGHT THERE.
WELL, THAT'S --
THAT'S FOOD
FOR THOUGHT.
OKAY.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
SO ALRIGHTY,
THAT'S MY LIST.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE YOURS
OUT AND READ FROM YOURS?
NO, ACTUALLY, I'M NOT MAKING
ANY RESOLUTIONS THIS YEAR.
NO?
WELL, EVERY YEAR
I MAKE RESOLUTIONS,
AND THEN I BREAK THEM ONE BY
ONE BEFORE THE YEAR IS GONE.
YOU BREAK 'EM ONE BY ONE
BEFORE THE HANGOVER'S GONE.
I'VE KINDA HIT THE GLASS
CEILING, HAROLD.
THIS IS ABOUT AS
GOOD AS I'M GONNA GET,
AND I'M GONNA STOP
FIGHTING IT, REALLY.
THIS IS AS GOOD
AS YOU GET?
YEAH.
IS THAT A PROBLEM?
NO, I'M JUST TRYING
TO GRASP THE CONCEPT
OF YOU BEING SATISFIED WITH
THAT LEVEL OF PERFORMANCE.
GEE, I SURE HOPE I HAVEN'T
UPSET YOU, HAROLD.
OH, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
YOU KNOW, MOST MEN MY
AGE WOULD BE INTIMIDATED
BY THE PROFICIENCY AND
ACCOMPLISHMENTS OF
THEIR ELDERS,
BUT ACTUALLY,
YOU SPARED ME ALL THAT.
YOUR WIFE'S ALL READY
FOR NEW YEAR'S.
SHE'S GOT HER NEW DRESS,
HER NEW HAIRDO
AND HER NEW QUEEN SIZE,
CONTROL TOP PANTYHOSE.
NOW, YOU'RE ABOUT
TO BREAK IT TO HER.
YOU DON'T FEEL LIKE
GOING OUT THIS NEW YEAR'S.
NOW, FOR YOUR OWN SAFETY,
TRY AND LET HER DOWN EASY.
IT'S NO POINT IN POINTING OUT
WHAT A GOOD SPORT YOU WERE
BY GOING TO ALL THOSE
CHRISTMAS PARTIES WITH HER.
NO, ESPECIALLY WHEN
YOU GOT CAUGHT
LYING ON THE COATS IN THE
BEDROOM READING FISHING
MAGAZINES.
IT'S GONNA BE PRETTY
DIFFICULT TO EXPLAIN TO HER
THAT YOU'D RATHER STAY
HOME WITH YOUR FAVOURITE
FUNNY SPORTS
BLOOPERS VIDEOS.
YEAH, YEAH, YOU MIGHT
WANNA DO A 180 ON THAT.
YEAH, LIKE CHANGING
YOUR MIND, SUCKING IT UP
AND GOING TO
THE PARTY AFTER ALL.
YEAH, THINK ABOUT
IT THIS WAY...
IF SHE'S HAVING FUN
AND YOU'RE NOT,
YOU'RE STILL HAVING WAY
MORE FUN THAN YOU WOULD BE
WHEN YOU'RE HAVING
FUN AND SHE'S NOT!
AND JUST REMEMBER,
NEW YEAR'S EVE IS JUST
ONE COLD NIGHT IN JANUARY,
BUT THE GARAGE IS
COLD 24/7, 365.
THINK ABOUT IT.
WE KNOW YOU'LL
DO THE RIGHT THING.
OR AT LEAST
THE SAFE THING.
HAPPY NEW YEAR!
[applause]
OH, YEAH.
UH --
OKAY, MY NEW YEAR'S
RESOLUTIONS.
YEAH, I GOT SOME.
SETTING GOALS AND
WORKING TOWARDS 'EM
IS A BIG PART OF MY
REHABILITATION PROGRAMME.
OKAY... BURGLAR ALARMS.
I'D LIKE TO SEE
THEM OUTLAWED.
IF WE CAN'T LIVE TOGETHER IN
AN ATMOSPHERE OF MUTUAL TRUST,
THEN WHAT KIND OF
A SOCIETY IS THIS?
TO ME, IT IS SO INSULTING WHEN
THAT BURGLAR ALARM GOES OFF,
AND YOU SUDDENLY REALISE,
QUITE INNOCENTLY,
THAT YOU'RE NOT
IN YOUR OWN HOME.
AND THE SAME GOES
FOR PETTY THEFT TOO.
LIKE, I'D LIKE TO SEE PETTY
THEFT TREATED LIKE A
DRIVING OFFENCE.
THE FIRST TIME
YOU STEAL SOMETHING,
YOU GET OFF WITH A WARNING.
AND I GOT A POINT
SYSTEM TOO.
A WALLET IS
WORTH ONE POINT,
AND A PIANO IS, LIKE,
FIVE POINTS.
AND ONCE YOU LOSE
ALL YOUR POINTS,
THEN YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED TO
STEAL ANYTHING FOR A YEAR.
WHICH IS KIND OF LIKE
HOW JAIL WORKS NOW.
ONLY UNDER MY SYSTEM,
YOU'D BE FORCED TO GET A JOB
AND MAKE YOUR OWN WAY,
RATHER THAN BE INCARCERATED,
WHERE EVERYTHING
IS PAID FOR.
WELL, ANYWAY,
THAT'S ABOUT IT,
UM, EXCEPT THAT,
WELL, YOU KNOW,
NEW YEAR'S IS A TIME
FOR FORGIVENESS.
AND IF YOU'RE
PREPARED TO FORGIVE,
THEN I'M CERTAINLY PREPARED
TO ACCEPT THAT APOLOGY.
HAPPY NEW YEAR.
[applause]
YOU KNOW, A LOT OF PEOPLE LIKE
TO COMMEMORATE NEW YEAR'S EVE
BY HAVING SOME SORT OF
AUDIO/VISUAL PRESENTATION
IN THEIR BACKYARD,
MAYBE FIRECRACKERS
OR A LIGHT SHOW.
IT'S THEIR WAY OF CELEBRATING
THE BEGINNING OF A NEW YEAR
AND ALSO SURPRISING
THE NEIGHBOURS
THAT THEY ACTUALLY
KNOW WHAT DAY IT IS.
NOW, I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE THINKING...
"WHERE ARE YOU GONNA
FIND THE MONEY TO DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?"
OR, "MY WIFE WON'T LET ME
HAVE FIRECRACKERS."
OR, "WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, RED?"
WELL, TAKE IT EASY.
WITH MY IDEA YOU DON'T NEED
MONEY OR FIREWORKS.
ALL YOU NEED
IS A TOASTER --
WELL, ACTUALLY,
A FEW TOASTERS.
THAT IT?
AND WE DON'T EVEN
NEED THE WHOLE TOASTER,
JUST THE ELEMENTS
FROM INSIDE.
I MEAN, THEY'RE
PERFECT FOR OUR DISPLAY,
BECAUSE YOU CAN
BEND 'EM INTO SHAPES,
AND THEY GLOW WHEN
THEY'RE HOT.
DON'T YOU WISH MORE THINGS
IN LIFE WERE THAT SIMPLE?
BOY, I'M EXHAUSTED.
THAT WAS A LOT OF SWEARING.
OKAY, NOW WE GOT
THE EASY PART.
WE JUST FORM THE
ELEMENTS INTO THE LETTERS
FOR OUR NEW YEAR'S
EVE SIGN, SEE?
THIS HERE IS
THE LETTER "T."
TODAY'S HANDYMAN CORNER
IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY
THE LETTER "T."
OR IF IT DOESN'T WORK,
IT'LL BE THE LETTER "B,"
'CAUSE IF SHE
DOESN'T WORK,
LET 'ER BE.
OKAY, NOW WE JUST FORM
THE REST OF THE LETTERS
AND THEN JOIN ALL
THE ELEMENTS TOGETHER
MAKING A SIGN THAT'S
NOT ONLY BRIGHT,
BUT ALSO TOASTY WARM.
OKAY, OUR SIGN'S
ALL DONE.
I'VE GOT THE ELEMENTS
HOOKED UP TO THESE WIRES.
AND THEN TO SUPPLY
THE ELECTRICITY,
I'VE GOT THE OTHER END HOOKED
INTO THE POWER SUPPLY
ON ONE OF MY TOASTERS.
NOW WHEN I PUSH DOWN
THIS LITTLE LEVER,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE AN
IMPRESSIVE DISPLAY.
BUT I'VE GOTTA
WAIT FOR NIGHT,
'CAUSE I'VE GOT THE
CONTROL SET ON DARK.
OKAY, WE'RE ALL SET.
SO LET'S SEND OUR
LIT NEW YEAR'S MESSAGE
OUT TO THE WORLD.
JUST A LITTLE SOMETHING FROM
ALL OF US TO EACH OF YOU.
[cheers and applause]
I WANNA TALK TO ALL
YOU MIDDLE-AGED GUYS
WHO ARE OUT CELEBRATING
NEW YEAR'S THIS YEAR.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NEVER TOO SOON
TO START THINKING ABOUT
THE MIDNIGHT KISS.
YOU DON'T WANNA SCREW IT UP
AGAIN, NOW, DO YOU?
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
TO REMEMBER, REALLY...
KISS YOUR WIFE FIRST.
EXCUSES WON'T WORK,
LIKE, "I THOUGHT I WAS
KISSING YOU."
"I TRIED TO, BUT SOMEONE
ELSE'S LIPS GOT IN THE WAY."
OR WORSE STILL, "AH, COME ON,
HONEY, IT'S NEW YEAR'S.
"I'M SUPPOSED TO
BE HAVING FUN."
OKAY, MAINLY, YOU'VE GOTTA BE
ABLE TO FIND YOUR WIFE
AT MIDNIGHT.
THAT MEANS YOU REALLY
WANNA STAY SOBER, OKAY?
IF YOU CAN'T SEE, YOU'RE NOT
GONNA BE ABLE TO FIND HER.
AND BRAILLE
IS NOT AN OPTION.
AND WHEN YOU DO FIND HER,
AND YOU ARE KISSING YOUR
OWN BEAUTY QUEEN,
DON'T BE TRYING
TO MAKE EYE CONTACT
WITH MISS CONGENIALITY.
HAVING A SPLIT FOCUS
AT THAT CRUCIAL MOMENT
CAN LEAD TO
OTHER SPLITS...
SPLIT LIPS,
SPLITTING HEADACHE,
SPLITTING WIFE.
AND DON'T BE USING
NEW YEAR'S AS A WAY
TO HOOK UP WITH SOME OF
YOUR EX-GIRLFRIENDS.
SHOULD OLD
ACQUAINTANCE BE FORGOT?
ABSOLUTELY.
ESPECIALLY IF SHE'S
ATTRACTIVE, SHE'S AT THE PARTY
AND SHE'S CARRYING AROUND A
PICTURE OF A 12-YEAR-OLD BOY
WHO LOOKS
EXACTLY LIKE YOU.
SO JUST COOL IT.
HAVE A HAPPY NEW YEAR.
AND REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM A FIRM BELIEVER IN
THE NEW YEAR'S RESOLUTION.
OH, I KNOW A LOT OF
PEOPLE POOH-POOH IT.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
TO ME THERE'S ALWAYS
ROOM FOR IMPROVEMENT.
SO FIRST OF ALL...
ANN MARIE, MY WIFE,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU COULD BE A
LITTLE MORE TOLERANT
AND MAYBE JUST A LITTLE LESS
CRITICAL OF MY WARDROBE,
AND MAYBE JUST A LITTLE
FRIENDLIER IN THE ROMANCE
DEPARTMENT, HONEY,
YOU KNOW, IF YOU
GET MY DRIFT.
NOW, AS FOR MY
DAUGHTER MANDY,
YOU KNOW, THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH YOUR LIFESTYLE
THAT A NEW BOYFRIEND,
ACCEPTABLE MORALS
AND MAYBE SOME GAINFUL
EMPLOYMENT WOULDN'T SOLVE.
OKAY, AND THIS LAST ONE...
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO
COME INTO MY STORE,
THE WORD "CUSTOMER" IMPLIES
A BUSINESS TRANSACTION
WHERE I SELL YOU
SOMETHING, RIGHT?
SO THIS YEAR, LET'S KEEP
THAT TRADITION ALIVE.
YOU KNOW, THE CUSTOMER'S
ALWAYS RIGHT,
BUT THE BROWSER'S
ALWAYS A PAIN IN THE BUTT.
HAPPY NEW YEAR.
[applause]
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF OUR SPECIAL
WE CALL, IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING.
SO WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
FOR US HERE, MIKE?
THIS IS AN INFLATABLE
CHAIR, MR. GREEN.
RUEFULLY, IT HAS
SEVERAL HOLES IN IT
DUE TO AN UNFORTUNATE
MISUNDERSTANDING.
I NOTICE THIS IS FROM
THE SHADY ACRES REST HOME.
UH, THAT'S CORRECT.
I BORROWED IT.
DID YOU TELL THEM YOU
WERE BORROWING IT?
WELL, I MAY HAVE,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT
OLD FOLKS ARE LIKE.
HOW COME IT'S GOT
ALL THE HOLES IN IT?
WELL, ONE OF THE RESIDENTS
HAD A PELLET GUN.
WELL, I CAN FIX THE HOLES
WITH THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON,
BUT THERE'S NO
REAL HURRY.
IT'S GONNA BE SEVERAL
MONTHS BEFORE YOU GET
INTO THE POOL.
I NEED IT NOW, RED,
'CAUSE I WANNA MAKE IT FLY.
YOU SEE, IF YOU CAN
PATCH UP THE HOLES IN IT
AND PUT SOME KIND OF
A GAS IN IT,
THEN I'LL HAVE
MYSELF A BLIMP.
DO YOU THINK
HYDROGEN WOULD WORK?
UH, YEAH.
THAT'D BE A
NON-SMOKING FLIGHT.
SO WHERE ARE YOU PLANNING
TO GO IN THE CHAIR
ONCE YOU
GET IT FLYING?
OH, YEAH.
AROUND THE WORLD.
YOU SEE, I WANNA MAKE UP
FOR ALL THE NEW YEAR'S EVES
THAT I MISSED OUT ON
WHEN I WAS IN THE SLAMMER.
NOW, THE EARTH HAS 24
DIFFERENT TIME ZONES,
AND I WANNA CELEBRATE
NEW YEAR'S IN EACH AND
EVERY ONE OF 'EM.
OKAY, I UNDERSTAND HOW THE
CHAIR'S GONNA GET UP
IN THE AIR,
BUT WHAT'S GONNA
MAKE IT FLY?
NOTHING.
THAT'S THE BEAUTY
OF A ROTATING EARTH.
YOU SEE, IT'LL JUST
SPIN BY UNDERNEATH ME,
AND I'LL JUST DROP
DOWN IN EVERY TIME ZONE.
I'LL HAVE MYSELF
A QUICK BEER
AND KISS SOMEBODY'S WIFE.
OKAY, MIKE, THERE'S TWO
PROBLEMS WITH YOUR PLAN...
IT WON'T WORK
AND YOU'LL DIE.
SO FORGET ABOUT
THE CHAIR.
GO UP TO THE
AIRPORT BAR,
YOU KNOW,
BY PORT ASBESTOS THERE?
THEY'VE GOT
ALL THE CLOCKS FROM
EVERYWHERE AROUND THE WORLD,
AND EVERY TIME ONE
OF THEM HITS MIDNIGHT,
HAVE YOURSELF A
GLASS OF BUBBLY.
OH, OKAY, THAT MIGHT
BE KINDA FUN,
BUT I'D LIKE SOMEONE
TO GO ALONG WITH ME.
WELL, TAKE ONE OF
THE GUYS FROM SHADY ACRES.
I MEAN, I FIND OLD PEOPLE
REALLY ENJOY CELEBRATING
NEW YEAR'S.
THEY'RE SO SHOCKED
THAT THEY MADE IT.
I DUNNO IF I WANNA SPEND
NEW YEAR'S WITH A BORING
OLD SENIOR CITIZEN.
WELL, TAKE THE GUY
WITH THE PELLET GUN.
HE KNOWS HOW TO PARTY.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
YOU KNOW, THE ONLY
SAD PART IS THAT
I WON'T BE ABLE TO SPEND ANY
TIME WITH ALL MY BUDDIES.
THEY'RE ALL
STILL IN JAIL.
WELL, YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE
GONNA BE AT A 24-HOUR BAR
AND YOUR DRINKING PARTNER
IS AN ARMED SENIOR,
I THINK THE CHANCES OF
YOU AND YOUR JAIL BUDDIES
GETTING BACK TOGETHER
IS REAL GOOD.
GREAT!
YEAH, AWAY YOU GO.
[applause]
WELL, THAT'S IT FOR
OUR NEW YEAR'S SPECIAL.
WE HOPE YOU ENJOYED IT.
T IF YOU DID HAPPEN TO
FALL ASLEEP ON THE COUCH,
WELL, THAT'S GOOD TOO,
BECAUSE NOW YOU'LL BE
ABLE TO STAY AWAKE
UNTIL MIDNIGHT.
AND FOR ALL YOU
YOUNGER PEOPLE OUT THERE,
WE WISH YOU THE
BEST NEW YEAR'S EVER,
AND WE HOPE THE NEXT YEAR'S
JUST AS SAFE AND HAPPY TOO.
YEAH, AND FOR YOU
OLDER GUYS OUT THERE,
LET'S HOPE WE CAN ALL SURVIVE
ANY HAREBRAINED THING
THE YOUNG PEOPLE THROW AT US
OVER THE NEXT 12 MONTHS.
OH, UNCLE RED,
THAT REMINDS ME.
I'D LIKE TO THANK YOU FOR
ALL THE OPPORTUNITIES
YOU'VE GIVEN ME
FOR PERSONAL GROWTH
AND FOR PROFESSIONAL
DEVELOPMENT
OVER THE PAST YEARS.
AND I HOPE WE GET
TO SPEND MANY, MANY
MORE YEARS TOGETHER.
HOW MANY MORE?
MANY, MANY MORE.
OKAY, I THINK IT'S
TIME TO OPEN THE BAR,
SO ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
HAPPY NEW YEAR!
[cheers and applause]