IF YOU'RE
ANYTHING LIKE ME,
AFTER CHRISTMAS
DINNER LAST YEAR,
YOU ENDED UP STRETCHED OUT
ON THE SOFA WITH YOUR
PANTS UNDONE, MOANING,
WHY DIDN'T SOMEBODY
STOP ME?
WELL, HERE'S A LOW FAT
ALTERNATIVE TO EATING
ALL THAT TURKEY AT CHRISTMAS.
IT'S GONNA TAKE THE
STRAIN OFF YOUR WAISTBAND,
AND ALSO GET YOU
OUT IN THE FRESH AIR.
OKAY, THE FIRST
THING YOU WANNA DO
IS GRAB THE FROZEN TURKEY;
GET IT OUT OF THE FREEZER
BEFORE IT DEFROSTS.
THEN WHAT YOU WANNA DO IS TAKE
THE DOOR HANDLE OFF THE FRIDGE.
THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT.
THIS WAY YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO GET INTO THE FRIDGE,
SO YOU CAN'T SNEAK DOWN IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
TO EAT ANOTHER HANDFUL
OF JELLIED SALAD.
NOW ALL YOU GOTTA DO
IS ATTACH THE DOOR
HANDLE TO THE TURKEY
THE WAY I'VE DONE HERE.
AND YOU CAN CURL THAT BIRD
TO A LEANER, HEALTHIER YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
YEAH. YEAH.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
YEAH, WE SURE APPRECIATE THAT.
AND ALL THE BEST
TO YOU AND YOURS
FROM ME AND MINE
AND HIS AND HERS,
AND WHATEVER ELSE
IT SAYS ON THE TOWELS.
THIS HERE IS OUR
CHRISTMAS SPECIAL,
AND AS YOU CAN SEE,
HAROLD CAME UP --
OH.
THAT'S, UH, QUITE AN
OUTFIT YOU GOT THERE.
YOU SHOULD
NOT STAND STILL.
PEOPLE WILL PUT
PRESENTS UNDER YOU.
YEAH, I THOUGHT YOU
MIGHT APPRECIATE IT.
IT'S MY CHRISTMAS OUTFIT.
YEAH, WELL, IT'S BETTER
THAN YOUR BIRTHDAY SUIT.
ANYWAYS, GREAT
TO HAVE YOU UP HERE
FOR THE WHOLE CHRISTMAS
BREAK, HAROLD.
APPRECIATE IT.
NO, NO, NO, I'M JUST HERE
FOR THE CHRISTMAS SHOW.
WHAT?
YEAH, THE COMPANY ASKED
ME TO WORK OVER CHRISTMAS,
AND I SAID YES.
AH, HAROLD, NO.
LOOK, YOU GOTTA
LEARN TO SAY NO.
IT'S NOT THAT HARD.
JUST PRETEND YOU'RE
YOUR OWN GIRLFRIEND,
WHICH I'M SURE
YOU ARE.
YOU KNOW, I WAS KINDA HOPING
YOU WOULD KNOCK IT OFF
WITH THE INSULTS,
YOU KNOW, BEING CHRISTMAS
AND EVERYTHING.
AH, HAROLD,
I'M KIDDING YOU.
WHEN I INSULT
YOU LIKE THAT,
THAT'S BECAUSE
I LIKE YOU.
OH!
YEAH.
OH, OKAY.
THAT'S COOL.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
WELL, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH THEN,
YOU FAT, OLD,
BURNED-OUT DUFUS.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
I'M HERE WITH LOCAL EXPLOSIVES
ENTHUSIAST, EDGAR MONTROSE.
EDGAR, I UNDERSTAND
THAT YOU HAVE A SPECIAL
CHRISTMAS DISPLAY FOR US.
OH, NOT FOR ME,
THANKS, RED.
BUT I WILL HAVE A SLICE
OF THAT PUMPKIN PIE LATER.
THAT'S NOT WHY
I'M HERE, THOUGH.
RIGHT.
I HAVE A CHRISTMAS MUSICAL
DISPLAY I WANNA SHOW YOU.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
RESONANCE IS, RED?
YEAH, THAT'S WHERE
SOMETHING VIBRATES LOUD.
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
IT'S WHERE SOMETHING
VIBRATES LOUD.
AND YOU ALMOST GET
KIND OF A MUSICAL NOTE.
THE SMALLER THE CONTAINER
THAT RESONATES,
THE HIGHER THE MUSICAL
NOTE THAT YOU'LL GET.
OH, SO EACH ONE OF
THESE CONTAINERS
MAKES A DIFFERENT
MUSICAL NOTE?
YOU NEED TO PAY A
LITTLE BETTER ATTENTION.
'CAUSE EACH ONE OF
THESE CONTAINERS MAKES
A DIFFERENT MUSICAL NOTE.
NOW, LISTEN UP.
THIS IS THE IMPORTANT PART.
I PUT A CHARGE OF
DYNAMITE IN EACH CAN,
AND I HOOKED IT
UP TO MY KEYBOARD.
SEE?
I CALL IT MY
PIPE BOMB ORGAN.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO HEAR A
LITTLE CHRISTMAS MUSIC, RED?
YOU KNOW, I THINK I'LL JUST
LISTEN FROM BACK IN --
IN -- IN THIS AREA.
YOU GO AHEAD, THOUGH.
THIS IS MY FAVOURITE
CHRISTMAS CAROL.
FEEL FREE TO
SING ALONG.
A LITTLE SOMETHING
I LIKE TO CALL
SILENT NIGHT.
SI-L-ENT NIGHT
HO-OH-LY NIGHT
A-A-ALL IS --
YOU KNOW, A BIG PART OF
CHRISTMAS HAS TO BE THE EATING.
SOMETHING JUST
COMES OVER PEOPLE.
THEY START CHOWING DOWN LIKE
THEY WERE STOCKING UP
A BOMB SHELTER.
BUT THERE'S ALSO
A DOWNSIDE.
MESSIN' UP YOUR HOUSE
WITH ALL THOSE PEOPLE.
AND MESSIN' UP YOUR KITCHEN,
COOKING ALL THAT FOOD.
BUT YOU KNOW
SOMETHING?
THERE'S A BETTER WAY.
OKAY, THE FIRST STEP IS YOU
CALL UP ONE OF YOUR RELATIVES
AND TELL THEM THAT AFTER 43
CHRISTMASES OF MOOCHING
OFF EVERYONE ELSE,
IT'S FINALLY THEIR TURN
TO HAVE CHRISTMAS DINNER.
OH, SURE, THEY'LL
PROBABLY BALK AT FIRST.
BUT THEN YOU GIVE
THEM THE CLINCHER.
YOU'LL BRING THE FOOD.
NOW, I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE THINKING.
"WAIT A MINUTE, RED.
"THAT STILL MESSES
UP YOUR KITCHEN."
OR "HEY, RED,
I DON'T GET IT."
OR "BOY, I WISH I HAD
A PAIR PANTS LIKE THOSE."
BUT THE KEY TO
THE WHOLE DEAL IS
WE'RE GOING TO COOK CHRISTMAS
DINNER AS WE DRIVE OVER THERE.
OKAY, FIRST THING
YOU WANNA DO,
GET THE AIR CLEANER
OFF THERE
AND PUT THE TURKEY RIGHT
ON TOP OF THE ENGINE BOX.
NOW TAKE THE ENGINE
THERMOSTAT CONTROL UNIT
AND JAM THAT UP THE REAR
END OF THE TURKEY.
NOW, THAT'LL AFFECT YOUR
TEMPERATURE GAGE.
YOU GOTTA CHANGE --
SHOW YOU WHEN THE
TURKEY'S DONE.
AND YOU WANNA DISCONNECT YOUR
WINDSHIELD WASHER FLUID,
AND YOU WANNA FILL THAT UP
WITH THE TURKEY GRAVY.
THEN YOU PUT THE INTAKE
UNIT BACK IN THERE.
YOU DON'T WANT THAT
ALL OVER YOUR WINDSHIELD,
SO YOU WANNA REDIRECT
THE SQUIRTER --
ACTUALLY PUT A PIECE
OF DUCT TAPE ON THERE
AND AIM HER ALL OVER THERE,
ALL OVER THE TURKEY.
AND NOW WHEN YOU ADD THE --
APPLY THE WINDSHIELD
WASHER STUFF,
YOU'RE ACTUALLY
BASTING THE BIRD.
ALL RIGHT, NEXT THING
YOU WANNA DO IS
YOU WANNA FILL THE
RAD WITH FROZEN PEAS.
BOY, I CAN ALMOST
TASTE THOSE NOW.
HERE'S SOMETHING NEW.
TAKE YOUR LIGHTER,
PUT A MUSHROOM CAP ON
THE END OF IT.
YOU CAN THEM RIGHT OUT OF THE
CIGARETTE LIGHTER UNIT THERE.
PUT THAT ONE IN THE JAR,
PUT A NEW ONE ON.
GOING INTO THE THERMOS
THERE TO KEEP THEM WARM.
A NICE TREAT FOR NON-SMOKERS.
HERE'S HOW YOU MAKE
THE MASHED POTATOES.
JUST PUT 'EM
INSIDE THE HUBCAP.
NOW, YOU NEED
THE WHEEL TO BE WARM,
SO YOU PUT THE EMERGENCY
BRAKE ON, THREE CLICKS.
YOU PUT THE PIE IN BEHIND THE
TURKEY ON THE ENGINE BLOCK.
NOW, YOU WANNA
MAKE WHIPPED CREAM?
NO PROBLEM.
STICK THAT BACK ON THE RIM,
YOU'RE IN BUSINESS.
CORN ON THE COB
INTO A JAR,
TAKE ONE OF THE SPARK PLUGS,
ATTACH THAT TO THE LID.
EVERY EIGHT BANGS,
YOU COOK A COB.
YOU PUT THE DOUGH -- LITTLE
DOUGH FOR MAKING ROLLS
INTO THE AIR CLEANER.
PUT THAT BACK ON.
THEY'LL DROP DOWN
THROUGH THE CARB
THROUGH THE INTAKE MANIFOLD
AND COME OUT THE EXHAUST,
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU GOTTA DO FIRST...
A LITTLE BREAD BASKET TO GRAB
'EM AS THEY COME OUT.
NOW YOU JUST
START HER UP,
AND OUT THEY COME.
FIRST, A COUPLE
OF REGULAR ROLLS.
AND THEN A BRAN ONE.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, YOU DRIVE OVER TO
WHEREVER YOU'RE HAVING YOUR
CHRISTMAS DINNER,
AND BY THE TIME
YOU GET THERE,
EVERYTHING SHOULD
BE PRETTY MUCH READY.
SO YOU JUST
POP THE HOOD,
AND LET'S JUST SEE HOW
EVERYTHING LOOKS.
BOY, IT SURE SMELLS GOOD WHEN
YOU'RE DRIVING TOO.
OH, LOOK AT THAT TURKEY.
THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL THING.
OH, IT'S HOT!
HOT! HOT!
OH, MY GOSH.
YEAH, BEAUTIFUL THING.
GET THAT INSIDE
AND THEN COME BACK OUT.
OKAY, THE CORN
NOT SO GOOD.
THE SPARK IS ALL
AT THE ONE END,
LIKE I WAS WHEN
I WAS A KID.
NOW YOU WANNA TAKE THE
MASHED POTATOES OFF THERE.
I THINK IT WASN'T AIRTIGHT.
I THINK THAT WAS THE
PROBLEM THERE.
BUT I KNOW
THEY'LL BE FINE.
NOW, UH, OKAY, I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW TO GET THE PEAS OUT.
ALL RIGHT,
SO THERE'S YOUR PIE.
AND I THINK COOKED
TO PERFECTION.
AND THEN YOU WANNA
WHEEL THAT AROUND,
I BELIEVE IT WAS THE
PASSENGER WHEEL ON THAT.
YOU HOOK UP THE HOSE,
THE TIRE FILLER HOSE,
AND THEN YOU JUST REVERSE
THE PRESSURE AND --
WELL, THERE YOU GO.
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
YOU KNOW, IF WE COOKED THIS
TURKEY ON AN OLD VAN
INSTEAD OF A CAR,
WE COULD'VE
CALLED IT COQ OLD VAN
(play on coq au vin).
audience: A-A-AH!
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
THE PROOF OF THE PUDDING IS
WRITTEN ON THE LABEL.
LET'S SEE HOW THESE
MASHED POTATOES TASTE.
[ CRUNCH ]
BOY, THAT ROCK SALT REALLY
ENHANCES THE FLAVOUR.
OH, GOLLY,
I FORGOT MY KNIFE.
HOW AM I GONNA
CARVE THE TURKEY?
OH, I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
WE GOT A 200 HORSEPOWER
SLICER RIGHT HERE.
SOME PEOPLE WOULD
CALL IT A FAN BLADE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
IF YOU WANT
ANY DARK MEAT,
JUST GRAB IT ON
THE WAY BY.
CALL ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES,
WHEN THERE'S NO
ROOM AT THE INN.
Red: CHRISTMAS IS
THE HOME FIRE
TO GET YOU THROUGH THE DARKES
TIME OF THE YEAR...
JANUARY WHEN THE
VISA BILLS COME IN;
A FIRE TO WARM YOU
THROUGH THE COLD OF YOUR
FATHER-IN-LAW'S QUESTIONS
CONCERNING YOUR EMPLOYMENT
STATUS AND OVERALL SOLVENCY.
SO LIGHT A
FIRE AT CHRISTMAS
TO REMIND YOURSELF THAT IF
YOU DON'T PAY THE GAS
OR ELECTRICITY,
THIS IS BASICALLY WHAT
IT COMES DOWN TO.
LIGHT A FIRE
IN THE STOVE,
AND LIGHT A FIRE
IN THE BEDROOM, IF YOU CAN.
AND MOST OF ALL, LIGHT A
FIRE UNDER YOUR KID.
YOU KNOW, WHEN THE CAVEMEN
LOOKED UP AT THEIR NIGHT SKY,
THEY MIGHT HAVE WANTED THEIR
SUN TO COME BACK AFTER IT LEFT
BUT YOU DON'T
WANT YOURS TO.
DEAR SANTA...
NOW THAT I'M
OUT ON MY OWN
AND HOLDING AN IMPORTANT
EXECUTIVE POSITION IN
THE BIG CITY,
THIS WILL PROBABLY BE
THE LAST LETTER I SEND YOU.
WRITING LETTERS TO SANTA
IS NO LONGER CONSIDERED
APPROPRIATE BEHAVIOUR FOR
AN ENTRY-LEVEL MANAGER
SUCH AS MYSELF.
HOWEVER, I SHOULD LIKE TO
DRAW YOUR ATTENTION
TO MY ENCLOSED ANNUAL
EMPLOYEE EVALUATION REPORT
THAT QUITE CLEARLY
INDICATES THAT I'VE BEEN
A GOOD SECRETARY
TO THE VICE
PRESIDENT OF MERGERS
AND ACQUISITIONS THIS YEAR.
CONSEQUENTLY, AND AS A RESULT
OF THE COMMUNICATIONS WE'VE
HAD IN THE PAST YEARS,
I WOULD APPRECIATE YOUR
CONSIDERING MY REQUESTS FOR..
A BATMAN MOUSE PAD,
AN ELECTRIC PENCIL SHARPENER,
AND A CELL PHONE.
OH, OH, OH!
AND ONE OF THOSE LITTLE THING
THAT HAS SILVER BALLS THAT
SWINGS BACK AND FORTH
THAT REALLY IMPORTANT PEOPLE
HAVE ON THEIR DESKS
AND TELLS PEOPLE THAT THEY
ARE FAR TOO IMPORTANT TO
BE DOING ANYTHING
OTHER THAN PLAYING WITH THIS
REALLY FUN LITTLE
TOY THAT GETS REALLY
BORING AFTER WHILE,
BUT IS WAY BETTER
THAN DOING WORK.
YOUR CO-OPERATION IN THIS
MATTER WOULD BE GREATLY
APPRECIATED.
SIGNED, YOUR
RIEND ALWAYS,
HAROLD GREEN.
P.S. SANTA,
I WOULD LIKE TO
REDIRECT YOUR ATTENTION
TO MY OPENING PARAGRAPH
WHEREIN I STATED
THAT I WOULD "PROBABLY" NO
LONGER BE SENDING YOU LETTERS
THAT'S PROBABLY AS IN
PROBABLY.
THANKS AGAIN,
HAROLD.
IT'S THE POSSUM
LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
AND TODAY
Mr. EDGAR MONTROSE
IS PLAYING FOR
A GIANT EGGPLANT
FROM BERNIE'S
BIG 'N TALL VEGETABLES.
THIS IS JUST
AN EGGPLANT SEED.
HOLY MACKEREL.
Mr. GREEN, YOU HAVE
30 SECONDS
TO GET Mr. MONTROSE
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT, EDGAR,
THIS IS MOST PEOPLE'S
FAVOURITE HOLIDAY.
FIRECRACKER DAY.
NO, NO, PEOPLE STAY HOME FROM
WORK AND GIVE EACH OTHER THINGS.
FLU SEASON?
IT'S AN EXPRESSION.
IN FRENCH THEY SAY JOY-X NOEL,
(joyeux noel)
UH, IN ENGLISH
THEY SAY MERRY...
QUEEN OF SCOTS.
NO, NO, NO.
EDGAR, YOU KNOW
THIS, OKAY.
THIS IS --
WHAT DO YOU CALL IT WHEN YOU
GET A TREAT IN YOUR STOCKING?
LEPROSY.
AH, GEEZ.
ALMOST OUT OF
TIME, Mr. GREEN.
OKAY, EDGAR,
WHAT DO YOU CALL IT
WHEN THE FAT JOLLY GUY
COMES DOWN YOUR CHIMNEY?
OH, DAD LOST
HIS KEY AGAIN.
NO, COME ON, EDGAR.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU
WOULD CONCENTRATE,
WE COULD GET THIS.
WELL, IF "IFs" AND "BUTs"
WAS CANDY AND NUTS,
WE'D ALL HAVE
A MERRY CHRISTMAS.
THERE YOU GO!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
HAVE YOU SEEN A DECENT
WINTER HAT IN HERE, RED?
NOPE.
BOY, YOU'RE KINDA GETTING IN
THE CHRISTMAS SPIRIT THIS
YEAR, AREN'T YOU, HAP?
NO, NOT ESPECIALLY.
WELL, HAP, YOU'RE WEARING
A SANTA COSTUME.
OH, THIS IS NOT A COSTUME.
THIS IS MY WINTER COAT.
I GOT IT FOR
LAST CHRISTMAS.
SURE LOOKS LIKE
A SANTA COAT TO ME.
YEAH, IT'S
A SANTA COAT,
BUT IT'S NOT A
SANTA COSTUME.
YOU SEE, THERE'S
THE DIFFERENCE.
THIS IS SANTA'S
ACTUAL COAT
HE WORE IT
LAST CHRISTMAS.
HE ALWAYS LEAVES IT AT
THE LAST HOUSE HE WAS AT,
AND THAT JUST HAPPENS
TO BE MY PLACE.
OKAY.
SO HE WENT BACK FROM YOUR
HOUSE ALL THE WAY BACK TO THE
NORTH POLE WITHOUT A COAT ON.
BE KINDA CHILLY,
WOULDN'T IT?
WELL, FOR THE LAST
PART OF THE TRIP,
HE WEARS THIS BIG BROWN
SNOWMOBILE SUIT THING.
WHAT'S STICKING OUT OF
YOUR SLEEVE THERE, HAP?
OH, WHAT'S THAT?
WELL, I DUNNO.
OH, IT SEEMS TO BE
A LIST OF SOME KIND.
OH, MAN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS STUFF, HAP.
COME ON.
OH, I KNOW.
DOUBTING PEOPLE
IS A COMMON FLAW.
SOME PEOPLE DON'T EVEN
BELIEVE IN SANTA CLAUS.
THAT'S WHY I FEEL
SO MUCH FOR THE MAN.
SO YOU WEAR
HIS COAT?
RED.
I'D GLADLY GIVE UP
ALL MY WORLD RECORDS,
ALL THE MEDALS,
ALL THE SCIENTIFIC
BREAKTHROUGHS,
ALL THE INVENTIONS
AND THE FAME, EVERYTHING.
I'D GIVE
IT ALL UP --
OTHER THAN THE
WOMEN, OF COURSE,
IF I COULD CONVINCE PEOPLE
THAT THERE IS A SANTA CLAUS.
SO THAT'S WHY I'M WEARING
THIS COAT ALL WINTER;
SO PEOPLE WILL ACCEPT THAT
SANTA'S IN THEIR HEARTS
ALL YEAR ROUND.
OH, HERE IT IS.
HERE IT IS.
NO, NO, NO,
I GOT A BETTER HAT.
I GOT A BETTER
HAT, LOOK.
EASTER BUNNY
LEFT IT FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW, AROUND
CHRISTMAS TIME,
A LOT OF PEOPLE LIKE TO
BUY PETS FOR THEIR KIDS.
SO I THOUGHT I'D GET
LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER, ED FRID,
TO GIVE US SOME
TIPS ON WHAT TO GET.
COME ON UP HERE, ED.
SURE. OKAY.
YEAH, OKAY.
SURE.
SO, UH, ED, WHAT GIFT
WOULD YOU RECOMMEND FOR,
SAY, A NINE- OR
TEN-YEAR-OLD?
A BOOK.
NO, I MEAN WHAT KIND OF
ANIMAL WOULD YOU RECOMMEND?
ACTUALLY, LIKE MICE HERE.
WOULD THAT BE GOOD?
OH, NO, NOT MICE.
NO, THEY'RE RODENTS.
YEAH, THEY CARRY DISEASE,
AND THEY CAN GNAW RIGHT THROUGH
YOUR SKULL AND EVERYTHING.
WELL, MAYBE IF YOU
HAD CHEESE FOR BRAINS.
DON'T EVER JOKE
AROUND THE MICE, RED.
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
SO MICE ARE TOO SERIOUS.
HOW ABOUT THIS GUY HERE,
THIS BUNNY RABBIT.
IS THAT A GOOD IDEA?
WELL, SURE,
BUT YOU KNOW RABBITS,
THERE'S SOMETHING
THAT THEY LIKE TO DO A LOT
THAT MAYBE YOU DON'T WANT YOUR
KIDS WATCHING, YOU KNOW.
THEY EAT WITH
THEIR HANDS.
OH!
YEAH, BUT, I MEAN, LOOK
HOW CUTE AND FLUFFY
THEY ARE, ED.
WELL, YEAH, BUT DO YOU HAVE
ANY IDEA HOW SHARP THOSE
FRONT TEETH ARE?
YEAH, AND LOOK AT
THOSE HIND LEGS, RED.
DO YOU SEE THE SIZE OF
THOSE THIGH MUSCLES?
A FULL-GROWN
RABBIT COULD,
LIKE, KICK IN YOUR
BEDROOM DOOR!
YEAH, HE'D MARCH
RIGHT IN, EH.
AND GNAW RIGHT
THROUGH YOUR SKULL!
OKAY, NO MICE,
NO RABBITS.
SURELY GOLDFISH
ARE OKAY, AREN'T THEY?
FISH ARE BRAIN
FOOD, RED.
WHAT DOES
THAT TELL YOU?
THAT NOBODY
I KNOW EATS FISH.
NO.
THAT THEY'RE SMART,
TOO SMART.
ALWAYS THINKING,
ALWAYS SCHEMING.
HOW DO WE KILL
THE HUMANS?
AND THEN FLUSH
THEM DOWN THE TOILET?
HA HA, THAT'S IT.
WE'LL PLUG THE DRAINS
WITH THEIR BODIES.
WE'LL FLOOD THE WORLD.
LOOK AT THEIR
MOUTHS, EH.
THEY'RE TALKIN',
ALL RIGHT.
THEY'RE TAUNTING,
CHIDING,
"YOU'RE ALL
GONNA DWOWN." (sic)
OKAY, MAYBE NOT AS
INFORMATIVE AS I'D HOPED,
BUT AT LEAST NOW YOU
KNOW WHO NOT TO ASK.
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
IT'S FEEDING TIME.
[ APPLAUSE ]
CALL ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
(in German accent)
WE'RE GOING TO PUMP YOU OUT!
HERE'S SOMETHING SPECIAL
YOU CAN DO FOR THE
HOLIDAY SEASON.
RECORD A CHRISTMAS
MESSAGE RIGHT ONTO
YOUR ANSWERING MACHINE.
YOU MIGHT EVEN PUT SOME
CHRISTMAS MUSIC ON THERE TOO.
HEY, WHAT IS THE POSSUM
LODGE PHONE MESSAGE?
I DUNNO.
NO ONE EVER CALLS IT.
WE'RE ALREADY HERE.
WELL, I'LL PLAY IT.
Harold's voice:
THANKS FOR CALLING
POSSUM LODGE,
BUT NOBODY'S AROUND.
IT'S PROBABLY BECAUSE WE'RE
CELEBRATING THE NEW YEAR,
SO WE'RE DOWNSTAIRS DANCING,
AND NO ONE CAN HEAR THE PHONE
SO LEAVE A MESSAGE.
HAPPY NEW YEAR!
HAVE A GREAT 1988.
UNCLE RED, WHY DON'T YOU
TELL THE FOLKS AT HOME
HOW THEY CAN RECORD
CHRISTMAS MUSIC IN
THE BACKGROUND
AS THEY RECORD
THEIR OWN MESSAGE?
TELL THEM.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
HAROLD.
ACTUALLY, WE'RE GONNA
GO ONE STEP BETTER
THAN THAT.
THE GUYS HERE ARE GONNA
HUM A CHRISTMAS TUNE,
AND I'M GONNA PUT
A MESSAGE ON IT.
OKAY, GUYS.
AND GO.
[ REALLY BAD HUMMING ]
NO, NO, NO.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
YOU CAN'T SING
DIFFERENT SONGS.
PICK ONE CHRISTMAS
SONG AND GO WITH IT.
WELL, HOW ABOUT
"JINGLE BELLS," RED?
WE ALL KNOW THAT ONE.
ALL RIGHT,
"JINGLE BELLS."
ALL RIGHT.
AND GO.
MERRY CHRISTMAS FROM
EVERYBODY AT POSSUM LODGE.
SORRY WE CAN'T COME
TO THE PHONE RIGHT NOW.
LEAVE YOUR NAME AND
NUMBER AFTER THE "HEY."
HEY!
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red: CHRISTMAS IS FEELING
GOOD ABOUT GOING TO CHURCH.
THAT MEANS LOOKING
UP THE ADDRESS,
JUST IN CASE IT MOVED SINCE
EASTER THREE YEARS AGO.
IT'S ABOUT SHOWING UP AT 11:00
FOR THE 9:30 A.M. SERVICE
AND WONDERING WHY THE
PARKING LOT IS EMPTYING
AND YOUR WIFE IS GETTING A
RIDE HOME WITH THE NEIGHBOURS.
IT'S ABOUT SITTING
IN A QUIET PEW ALONE,
AFTER EVERYONE'S GONE,
QUIETLY COUNTING
YOUR BLESSINGS.
AND IT'S ABOUT THE JANITOR
INVITING YOU INTO THE CHURCH
FOR A FREE
CHRISTMAS DINNER
WITH THE REST
OF THE HOMELESS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH
THE GOLDFISH BOWL, MIKE?
OH, GEE,
UH, I DIDN'T SEE
YOU THERE, Mr. GREEN.
UM, WELL, I'M NOT
DOING ANYTHING.
OKAY, SEE YOU.
WHERE YOU GOING?
WELL, I THOUGHT I'D JUST
GO OUTSIDE AND STAND IN
THE SNOW FOR AWHILE.
WITH THAT HAT ON?
WELL, SURE, I MEAN,
IT'S GETTING COLDER
OUT THERE, YOU KNOW.
SEE YOU GOT A
BELL THERE TOO.
OH, YEAH, THIS.
WELL, UM --
I THOUGHT I'D JUST, UM,
RING IT ONCE IN A WHILE,
WHILE I STOOD OUTSIDE
IN THE SNOW.
THAT'S IT?
THAT'S IT.
WELL, THEN YOU DON'T
NEED THE FISHBOWL, DO YOU?
WELL, I THOUGHT IF PEOPLE
WANTED TO, YOU KNOW,
LIKE, DROP, OH --
GOLDFISH INTO IT?
OKAY, ACTUALLY --
ACTUALLY, UM, I WAS GONNA
COLLECT DONATIONS FOR CHARITY.
OH, OKAY, WELL,
THAT'S GREAT.
WHICH CHARITY?
WELL, NO PARTICULAR
CHARITY.
OH.
MORE LIKE FOR ALL
THE NEEDY IN GENERAL.
BOY, YOU KNOW, THERE'S
A LOT OF NEEDY.
TO DISTRIBUTE THAT MONEY
ALL OVER THE WORLD,
THAT'S GONNA TAKE
A LOT OF YOUR TIME.
WELL, THAT' ABSOLUTELY
RIGHT, Mr. GREEN.
THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
I MEAN, I DON'T HAVE THE
RESOURCES FOR THAT, RIGHT?
I THINK WHAT
I'LL DO IS
I'LL COLLECT MONEY FOR THE
NEEDY POSSUM LODGE MEMBERS.
THANKS FOR THE TIP.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
HEY, MIKE,
WHO DO YOU THINK IS THE MOST
NEEDY POSSUM LODGE MEMBER?
WELL, I'D HAVE
TO SAY THAT
THE LODGE MEMBER WHO
HASN'T PAID HIS DUES
FOR THE LONGEST TIME
WOULD NEED THE MONEY
THE MOST, RIGHT?
YEAH, WELL,
THAT'S YOU, MIKE.
OH, YEAH.
WELL, THAT'S RIGHT!
THAT IS ME,
ISN'T IT?
YOU'VE NEVER PAID
YOUR DUES AT ALL,
I DON'T THINK.
NOT IN MY
RECOLLECTION, NO.
I'LL TELL
YOU WHAT, MIKE.
I'M GONNA GIVE YOU
A CHRISTMAS GIFT.
REALLY?!
YEAH, I'M GONNA
WAIVE ALL YOUR DUES.
YOU'VE GOT NO DEBT AT
THE LODGE AT ALL, ALL RIGHT?
HOW'S THAT SOUND?
OH.
SO YOU WON'T NEED THE
FISHBOWL ANYMORE, WILL YOU?
BUT YOU KNOW,
GOING OUT THERE WITH
THE BELL AND THE HAT,
SPREADING CHRISTMAS CHEER,
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
YEAH, I COULD
STILL DO THAT, I GUESS.
WELL, MERRY CHRISTMAS.
[ RINGING BELL ]
NOT IN HERE, MIKE.
NOT IN HERE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, I LIKE TO SPREAD
THE CHRISTMAS CHEER.
I USED TO DO THE
CHRISTMAS CAROLLING,
BUT MY FRIENDS
MADE ME SOUND BAD.
OF COURSE, THEY'D BLAME ME.
THEY'D SAY, "YOU HAVE
NO CONTROL OVER YOUR VOICE.
"YOU JUST DO THE PA RUM
A PUM PUMs IN THE BACKGROUND."
WELL, INSTEAD OF THAT,
I GOT A BETTER WAY TO
SPREAD MUSIC AND JOY
TO YOUR NEIGHBOURS
WITHOUT GOING DOOR TO DOOR INTO
THE BITING COLD THERE.
I'M GOING TO TURN
THE POSSUM VAN
INTO A CHRISTMAS SONG
BROADCASTING VEHICLE.
I COULD PROBABLY COME UP
WITH A BETTER NAME THAN THAT.
NOPE.
ALL RIGHT, ALL'S YOU NEED IS
CHRISTMAS MUSIC PLAYIN' ON
YOUR CAR TAPE DECK,
AND A COUPLE OF SPEAKERS
MOUNTED ON THE ROOF.
DON'T HAVE TO BE
EXPENSIVE SPEAKERS
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE THEY'RE
GONNA BE OUT IN OPEN.
THERE'S USUALLY ONE GUY IN EVERY
TOWN WHO SELLS CHEAP SPEERS,
AS LONG AS YOU
DON'T NEED A RECEIPT.
HEY, MIKE!
OH, MIKE, MIKE,
IT'S JUST ME, RED.
OH, Mr. GREEN.
HEY, GOOD
TO SEE YOU.
SORRY ABOUT YELLIN'
AT YOU THERE, MIKE.
AH, THAT'S OKAY,
Mr. GREEN.
I KNOW YOU DON'T HAVE
THAT MUCH CONTROL
OVER YOUR VOICE.
YEAH, RIGHT.
MIKE, YOU REMEMBER LAST
SUMMER YOU HAD THAT JOB,
YOU WERE SELLIN' SPEAKERS
OUT OF THE BACK OF A TRUCK?
OH, YEAH!
YEAH.
WELL, THAT WAS SORT
OF LIKE A JOB, YEAH.
YEAH, SURE, I MADE SOME
MONEY FROM DOING IT.
YEAH, THAT JOB.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, I WAS WONDERING,
DO YOU HAVE ANY SPEAKERS
LEFT OVER AT ALL?
WELL, I ONLY GOT A
COUPLE OF SPEAKERS LEFT.
THE COPS
TOOK MOST OF THEM,
BUT I TELL YOU, I'D HAVE TO
CHARGE YOU A GOOD PRICE
FOR THOSE LAST
TWO SPEAKERS,
BECAUSE IT TOOK ME THREE DAYS TO
FILE SERIAL NUMBERS OFF THEM.
WELL, I CAN GIVE
YOU 20 BUCKS FOR 'EM.
UH, YEAH, I GUESS I
COULD LET YOU HAVE
'EM FOR 20 BUCKS.
SURE.
YEAH, THEY'RE
IN THE SHED.
UH, MIKE, WHAT ABOUT THE
TELEVISION SET HERE?
OH, SURE, MAKE
ME AN OFFER.
OKAY, NOW ALL I GOTTA DO
IS MOUNT THESE SPEAKERS
ON THE ROOF
SO I'LL BE ABLE TO BROADCAST
MUSIC THROUGHOUT THE
NEIGHBOURHOOD.
ACTUALLY, IT'S SMART
TO PUT 'EM ON THE ROOF.
STUFF YOU BUY FROM MIKE
SHOULD NEVER BE AT EYE LEVEL.
UH, BETTER IDEA.
I'M GONNA GO MONO.
YEAH, THE MONO THING
IS REALLY COMING BACK.
YOU KNOW HOW FADS
KINDA GO IN CYCLES?
YOUNG PEOPLE ARE REALLY
INTO THE MONO MUSIC.
WHAT I'LL DO IS I'LL JUST MOUNT
THIS FACING ONTO THE RIGHT SIDE.
I'LL GO UP THE
STREET ONE WAY,
THEN I'LL TURN AROUND,
COME BACK THE OTHER WAY.
I'LL DO THE OTHER SIDE.
THESE WIRES ARE FROM
UNDER MY DASHBOARD.
THEY'RE MY RADIO
SPEAKER WIRES,
WHICH I'VE DISCONNECTED AND
HAVE RE-ROUTED UP HERE
TO THE SPEAKER.
WASN'T EASY,
BELIEVE ME.
THERE ARE A LOT OF
WIRES UNDER A DASH --
[ HORN HONKING ]
HEY, DALTON.
RED.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
WERE OPEN SUNDAYS.
SHH! IF ANN MARIE
FINDS OUT, I'M A DEAD MAN.
SHE THINKS BEING OPEN SUNDAYS
BREAKS ONE OF THE COMMANDMENTS.
I DON'T KNOW WHICH ONE.
WELL, JUDGING
BY YOUR PRICES,
IT'S PROBABLY
"THOU SHALT NOT STEAL."
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
DID YOU HEAR I GAVE
MIKE HAMAR A TV SET?
IT WAS BROKE AND
HE DIDN'T EVEN KNOW.
WELL, HE KNOWS NOW, DALTON.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I JUST
WANTED TO GET IT OFF MY BACK.
SO I TOLD HIM HE WON IT
BECAUSE HE WAS MY ONE
MILLIONTH CUSTOMER.
[ LAUGHING ]
WOW, YOU'VE HAD
A MILLION CUSTOMERS?
WELL, I WILL EVENTUALLY.
I'M JUST NOT
COUNTING IN ORDER.
CAN I HELP YOU, RED?
WELL, DALTON, I WAS HOPING YOU
HAD AN AUDIO CASSETTE TAPE
THAT I COULD BORROW.
YEP, OKAY.
THERE YOU GO.
TAKE YOUR PICK.
WELL, NOW, SEE,
DALTON, UH,
I WAS HOPING YOU HAD
ONE OF THE NEWER STYLE.
LIKE THIS ONE HERE IN
YOUR ANSWERING MACHINE.
NOPE, YOU CAN'T
HAVE THAT TAPE, RED.
I'M EXPECTING A CALL.
WELL, CAN'T YOU JUST
ANSWER THE PHONE?
RED, I'M EXPECTING A
CALL FROM RANGER GORD.
I NEED THIS
ANSWERING MACHINE.
HE'S GONNA WARN ME IF
HE SEES ANN MARIE
HEADING THIS WAY.
I GOT AN IDEA.
LOOK.
LET ME TAKE
THE TAPE, OKAY.
THEN WHEN YOU
ANSWER THE PHONE,
YOU JUST PRETEND YOU'RE
AN ANSWERING MACHINE.
YOU SAY, "HELLO, I'M NOT IN,
"LEAVE A MESSAGE."
OH, COME ON, RED.
RANGER GORD WOULD HAVE TO BE A
COMPLETE IDIOT TO BELIEVE --
IT MIGHT JUST WORK.
I RECORDED A BUNCH OF CHRISTMAS
SONGS RIGHT OFF THE RADIO
ONTO DALTON'S TAPE HERE.
I EVEN TOOK THE TIME
TO EDIT OUT THE COMMERCIALS.
NOBODY WANTS TO HEAR ADVERTISING
BLARING OFF THE TOP OF MY VAN.
MIND YOU, I PROBABLY COULD'VE
MADE A LITTLE MONEY THERE, EH,
SELLIN' COMMERCIALS
IN BETWEEN THE SONGS.
ACTUALLY, I COULD HAVE VISUAL
ADVERTISING ON THE SIDE
OF THE VAN HERE,
MAYBE HAVE A FEW
SPONSORS, EH?
OH, NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT IN THE SPIRIT
OF CHRISTMAS AT ALL.
NO, I'M JUST GONNA DRIVE
UP AND DOWN THE STREET
GIVING OFF NOTHING BUT
CHEERFUL CHRISTMAS MUSIC.
[ "JINGLE BELLS" PLAYING ]
Dalton's voice:
HELLO, THIS IS HUMPHREY'S
EVERYTHING STORE.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE'RE NOT
AVAILABLE TO TAKE YOUR
CALL RIGHT NOW.
PLEASE LEAVE YOUR
MESSAGE AFTER --
NO MATTER WHAT MOTHER
NATURE HAS TO SAY ABOUT IT.
SO I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
TO MAKE A PRETTY HALF
DECENT SNOWMAKER
OUT OF STUFF YOU
FIND AROUND THE HOME.
SO I'VE TAKEN THIS OUTBOARD
MOTOR OFF A TOBOGGAN --
BOY, THERE WAS
AN IDEA, EH?
ANYWAY, WHAT I'M GONNA DO
IS ATTACH IT TO THE
INSIDE OF A BASIN.
I'M USING ONE OF THESE
OLD CLAW FOOT BATHTUBS.
NOBODY WANTS THESE
THINGS ANYMORE.
THIS IS NOW YOUR SNOWMAKER.
ALL YOU DO IS JUST
ADD ICE IN THERE.
BUT YOU DON'T WANT TO HAVE
TO BE GOING INTO THE HOUSE
EVERY TEN MINUTES
FOR MORE ICE.
SO I'M JUST GONNA HOOK IT UP
TO THE LODGE ICEMAKER,
WITH A PIECE
OF DRYER HOSE.
NOW ALL I GOTTA DO
IS JUST START HER UP,
AND IN NO TIME FLAT,
I'LL BE WALKIN' IN
A TWO-CYCLE
9.9 HORSE WINTER
WONDERLAND.
OH, RED GREEN!
YEAH.
MERRY CHRISTMAS!
YEAH, MERRY CHRISTMAS.
LISTEN, I'M SORRY I DON'T
HAVE A PRESENT FOR YOU.
HOPE YOU DON'T MIND.
NO, IT'S A
RELIEF, GORD.
YOU GAVE ME THAT
DEAD MUSKRAT LAST YEAR,
THREW ME OFF A LITTLE.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
WELL, THAT WAS A
LITTLE OOPSY ON MY PART,
FORGETTING TO PUT
THE AIRHOLE IN THE
TOP OF THE BOX.
GOOD EATIN', THOUGH.
OH, NO, NO.
YOU BETTER
SIT DOWN, RED.
I HAVE A MIRACLE
TO TELL YOU ABOUT.
A MIRACLE?
YEP.
YOU'VE MET
A GIRL?
NO.
NO, I MEAN A
CHRISTMAS MIRACLE;
THE ONE THAT LET'S
ANIMALS SPEAK.
OH, YEAH, I KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN.
THAT CHRISTMAS
LEGEND THING?
WHERE FARM ANIMALS
GET THE GIFT OF SPEECH,
JUST FOR CHRISTMAS EVE.
HM-MMM, HM-HMM.
ALTHOUGH, IT'S NOT SUCH
A MIRACLE THAT FARM
ANIMALS CAN SPEAK.
I MEAN, PARROTS DO
IT ALL YEAR ROUND.
NO, WHAT I'M MORE
INTERESTED IN
IS WHAT THE FARM ANIMALS
HAVE TO SAY TO EACH OTHER.
OH, NO, NO, IT'S NOT A
CONVERSATION, GORD.
THEY JUST GET DOWN
ON THEIR KNEES
AND THEY DO,
I THINK IT'S A SHORT
CHRISTMAS PRAYER.
YES, THAT'S WHAT
I USED TO THINK,
UNTIL I SNUCK INTO
A BARN LAST CHRISTMAS EVE
JUST BEFORE MIDNIGHT
AND TOOK SOME NOTES.
YOU WENT INTO
SOMEBODY'S BARN?
YEAH, DOOR WAS OPEN.
ANYWAY, THIS IS AN
ACTUAL CONVERSATION
THAT TOOK PLACE BETWEEN
THE FARMYARD ANIMALS.
OH, BOY.
THE FIRST TO SPEAK
WAS THE COW.
"COW: 'MOO.'
"THEN THE HORSE:
'HEY, GUYS,
"'IT MUST BE
CHRISTMAS EVE.
"'I CAN TALK.'"
OH, YEAH.
"COW: 'IT STINKS
IN THIS BARN.
"'THERE ARE
TOO MANY FLIES.
"GOAT: 'I WANT
MORE FOOD.'
"COW: 'HEY, GUYS, LOOK.
"'OVER IN THE CORNER
THERE'S A GUY HIDING.
"'HE HAS NOTEBOOK.'
"HORSE:
'EVERYBODY SHUT UP!'"
AND AFTER THAT THE
ANIMALS WERE JUST QUIET.
SO NO PRAYER?
NOT A SAUSAGE.
THE ANIMALS WERE EXTREMELY
WHINY AND SELF-CENTERED.
I THINK WHAT WE ALL
HAVE REALISE, RED,
IS JUST BECAUSE SOMEBODY
HAS THE GIFT OF SPEECH,
DOESN'T MEAN IT'S GOING TO
SAY ANYTHING OF ANY VALUE.
I KNOW IT.
YOU'VE PROVEN THAT, GORD.
THANKS, RED.
[ APPLAUSE ]
HAPPY NEW YEAR
FROM WINSTON ROTHSCHILD,
REMINDING YOU IF OLD
ACQUAINTANCE CAN'T BE FORGOT,
CALL ROTHSCHILD SEWAGE
AND SUCKING SERVICES.
WE'RE Y2K COMPLIANT!
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red: CHRISTMAS IS RECALLING
YOUR OLD CHILDHOOD MEMORIES,
ALL FOR THE SOLE PURPOSE
OF TELLING YOUR KIDS
HOW MUCH WORSE OFF
YOU WERE THAN THEM,
HOW YOU THOUGHT
YOURSELF LUCKY
JUST TO HAVE A MOULDY
POTATO IN YOUR STOCKING
SO YOUR FAMILY COULD
MASH IT FOR DINNER.
AND THE TIME YOU AND THEIR
MOTHER HAD TO SELL
YOUR OWN SHOES
JUST TO BUY EACH
OTHER WARM SOCKS.
BUT MOST OF ALL,
CHRISTMAS IS ABOUT
THE POWER OF IMAGINATION...
LEAVING MILK AND
COOKIES FOR SANTA,
HEARING REINDEER
HOOVES ON THE ROOF,
AND CREATING THESE STORIES
ABOUT YOUR PATHETIC CHILDHOOD
JUST SO YOU COULD
EXPLAIN TO YOUR KIDS
WHY THEY DIDN'T GET EVERYTHIN
THEY WANTED THIS YEAR.
WELL, I KNOW ALL
YOU YOUNGSTERS OUT THERE
HEAR A LOT ABOUT RUDOLPH THE
RED-NOSED REINDEER
AT CHRISTMAS TIME.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS KIND
OF CUTE AND FRIENDLY,
BUT I JUST WANT TO
REMIND YOU CHILDREN THAT
REINDEER CAN KILL!
I MEAN, NORMAL
REINDEER CAN KILL.
HOW MUCH MAYHEM A FLYING
REINDEER COULD CREATE, I --
I DON'T EVEN WANT
TO THINK ABOUT,
ESPECIALLY ONE
WITH A RED NOSE.
YEAH, 'CAUSE IN
THE ANIMAL WORLD,
RED IS A DANGEROUS COLOUR.
YEAH, I WORK WITH
ANIMALS ALL THE TIME,
AND THEY HATE RED.
WELL, THAT'S WHY
MY UNIFORM ISN'T RED.
MY TRUCK ISN'T RED,
AND MY BANDAGES AREN'T RED.
WELL, NOT AT FIRST ANYWAY.
YOU SEE, IN THE
ANIMAL KINGDOM,
RED MEANS IRRITATED.
TAKE IT FROM SOMEONE
WHO'S BEEN THERE.
YOU DO NOT WANT AN IRRITATED
ANIMAL IN YOUR HOME,
ESPECIALLY AT CHRISTMAS.
YOU'D BE SURPRISED HOW EASY
SOMETHING COULD GO WRONG;
FOR EXAMPLE, YOU GO TO LEAVE
A CARROT FOR RUDOLPH
ON A RED NAPKIN.
THAT TURNS INTO
A YULETIDE TRAGEDY!
SO DON'T BE FOOLED
BY THE NICE SONGS.
YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
IT'S A GOOD THING
IF AN ANIMAL
HAS A VERY SHINY NOSE.
YOU KNOW, THAT COULD
EVEN LOOK COOL.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT,
IF IT'S GONE SO FAR THAT
YOU WOULD EVEN SAY IT GLOWS,
I THINK WE'RE
TALKIN' RABIES HERE!
COULD BE SOME NUCLEAR THING
THAT'S GOING ON THERE.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT JUST TAKES
ONE VICIOUS ATTACK
BY ONE RABID, DERANGED,
RADIOACTIVE BEAST,
AND YOUR CHRISTMAS
PARTY'S RUINED.
WELL, UNLESS
IT'S A, YOU KNOW,
OFFICE CHRISTMAS PARTY.
Red: WELL, WE THOUGHT
FOR CHRISTMAS
IT'D BE JUST PERFECT
TO MAKE A SNOWMAN,
AND YOUNG WALTER
COME UP THERE,
AND HE BROUGHT
THE HAT AND --
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
HE HAD A CARROT FOR
THE NOSE AND EVERYTHING.
SO HE'S ALL SET.
SO WE'RE JUST GONNA START
WITH A COUPLE OF SNOWBALLS
AND JUST ROLL 'EM.
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
THEY'VE BEEN DOING IT THIS WA
SINCE THE BEGINNING OF TIME.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL
COME MY WAY.
WHY DON'T WE STAY
TOGETHER ON THIS?
YEAH, THAT'S BETTER.
SINCE TIME IMMEMORIAL,
JUST ROLLING.
IF YOU GET THE RIGHT SNOW,
IF IT'S PACKING --
AND I'M GETTIN' THERE.
THE THING IS YOU GOTTA
FIGURE OUT HOW BIG YOU
WANNA MAKE EACH ONE
BECAUSE I THINK YOU
NEED THREE, DON'T YOU?
OR TWO OR THREE.
ONE FOR THE BODY,
ONE FOR THE MIDDLE,
AND ONE FOR THE OTHER PART.
AND MINE'S COMING
ALONG PRETTY GOOD,
BUT, YOU KNOW, WALTER --
HIS SNOWBALL'S NOT
GETTING ANY BIGGER.
WHY WOULD THAT BE, I WONDER?
OH.
OKAY, NOW, THAT WOULD
BE A SOFTBALL.
AH, OKAY, GOOD.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
OKAY, SO WALTER'S
GOT A GOOD IDEA.
HE'S GONNA START AGAIN.
NO, HE'S GONNA
HAND ME THAT ONE,
HE'S GONNA TAKE
OVER MY SNOWBALL --
I SEE.
ALL RIGHT.
SO AGAIN, WALTER'S
A LITTLE YOUNGER,
AND THIS SOMETHING FOR
THE YOUNG FOLKS TO ENJOY.
I'M GONNA LET HIM DECIDE HOW
BIG I SHOULD MAKE MINE.
MINE'S GETTING THERE.
NO, NO, KEEP GOING.
KEEP GOING.
WALTER'S COMING
ALONG PRETTY GOOD THERE.
THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD ONE.
YEP, YEP.
AND, UH, MINE'S
STARTIN' TO --
WE SHOULD MAYBE THINK --
BOY, WALTER, THAT'S
GETTING PRETTY, UH --
THAT'S GETTING PRETTY
AMBITIOUS THERE, WALTER.
'CAUSE WE GOTTA PICK
THESE UP AT SOME POINT.
THAT MAY --
WALTER, THAT MAY BE ENOUGH.
WALTER --
MINE'S GETTIN' --
YOU KNOW, I THINK WE'RE --
I THINK --
OH, WALTER.
HOLY MACKEREL.
HOLY JUMPIN'.
NOW, YOU SEE, YOU CAN'T EVEN
PUSH IT UP THE HILL.
YOU CAN'T EVEN --
YEAH. YEAH.
NO, NO, DON'T LEAVE --
IT'LL COME --
LOOK OUT.
IT'LL COME.
DON'T LEAVE IT.
YOU CAN'T LEAVE IT.
TOO MUCH?
OH, BOY.
OH, BOY!
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
JUMP TO THE --
OH, BOY!
OH, OH, OH!
JUMP TO THE SIDE!
IT'S COMING AFTER YOU --
OH!
OH, OH, OH!
OH, NO, HE HE'S FINE.
HE'S GOOD.
HE'S ALL RIGHT.
YEP, YEP, YEP.
BOY, OH, SHE'S
HEADING FOR THE RAMP.
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
WALTER, GET OUT OF THE WAY!
OH-OH.
O-O-OH!
THAT'S COMING --
INCOMING.
OH, MY --
AND THERE'S MINE.
OH!
OH, HEY.
THERE'S OUR SNOWMAN.
THIS IS WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
FROM ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES
REMINDING YOU WE'LL
TAKE PLENTY OF DOUGH IN
BEFORE IT STARTS SNOWIN'
AND SANTA'S HO HO HO-IN'
'CAUSE WE'RE SUCKING,
NOT BLOWING.
OH, GEEZ.
AH, FOR PETE SAKE.
OH, YEAH, I WAS
SUPPOSED TO, UH,
GIVE THIS PROGRAM SOME CLASS BY
READING A CHRISTMAS STORY,
BUT I --
LOST THE STUPID BOOK.
ANYWAY, I'LL HAVE TO DO IT
FROM ANY MEMORY I HAVE LEFT.
OKAY, THE STORY IS THE
GIFT OF THE MAGEE. (i.e. magi)
IT'S WRITTEN BY A GUY WHO'S NAME
REMINDS ME OF A CHOCOLATE BAR,
BABY RUTH OR PETER PAUL
MOUNDS OR SOMETHING.
ANYWAY, QUITE
A WHILE AGO,
THERE WAS THIS MAN AND THIS
WOMAN WHO WERE MARRIED.
YOU KNOW, WHICH MEANS THEY
WEREN'T SHACKED UP
WITH HER FATHER,
LIKE MY DAUGHTER AND HER
DO-NOTHING BOYFRIEND.
ANYWAY, THIS MAN
AND THIS WOMAN,
THIS COUPLE WERE
VERY MUCH IN LOVE,
BUT THEY KEPT IT
TO THEMSELVES, YOU KNOW.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO WATCH THEM
MAKING OUT ON THE COUCH
WHEN YOU'RE TRYING
TO CLIP YOUR TOENAILS.
ANYWAY, THIS COUPLE
WAS BROKE,
AND THEY DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO
GET EACH OTHER FOR CHRISTMAS,
SO, YOU KNOW, AT LEAST
THEY HAD THE DECENCY
NOT TO GO TO HER FATHER AND
TRY TO MOOCH FOR A LOAN,
WHICH I'LL
NEVER GET BACK!
ON THE OTHER
HAND, YOU KNOW,
THEY WEREN'T THAT BRIGHT.
SHE CUTS OFF ALL HER HAIR TO BY
HER GUY A WATCH CHAIN,
AND HE SELLS HIS WATCH
TO GET HER A DOODAD
FOR THE HAIR SHE
DOESN'T HAVE ANYMORE.
THE END.
ISN'T THAT JUST ABOUT THE MOST
DUMB AND PATHETIC STORY
YOU'VE EVER HEARD?
OH, SURE, I KNOW IT'S SUPPOSED
TO MAKE YOU FEEL ALL
GOOEY INSIDE,
REMIND YOU OF THE TRUE
SPIRIT OF CHRISTMAS,
WHICH IS, YOU KNOW, SPENDING A
LOT OF TIME AND MONEY,
GETTING GIFTS FOR PEOPLE
THAT THEY DON'T NEED
AND YOU CAN'T AFFORD.
WELL, AT LEAST THAT SUMS UP
THE FESTIVE SPIRIT AROUND
OUR HOUSE.
ANYWAY, MERRY CHRISTMAS,
AND I HOPE THIS STORY'S
TAUGHT YOU SOMETHING,
LIKE, YOU KNOW, GO OUT AND BUY
YOURSELF SOMETHING NICE,
BECAUSE YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN
YOU'RE GONNA GO BROKE
AND LOSE YOUR HAIR AND
HAVE TO SELL YOUR WATCH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red:  CHRISTMAS IS CUTLERY,
SPECIAL KNIVES, ODD SPOONS,
AND MORE FORKS THAN THE
ROAD TO THE LODGE,
PLUS ALL KINDS OF SERVING
DOODADS THAT YOU HAVEN'T SEEN
LET ALONE USED,
IN ALMOST A YEAR.
AND, OF COURSE, AS THE MAN,
YOU'RE EXPECTED TO SURGICALLY
DISSECT THE TURKEY WITH
THESE TOOLS,
WITH A BUNCH OF OTHER
TOOLS HECKLING YOU.
THEY HAND YOU THE FANCY STEEL
KNIFE WITH THE BONE HANDLE
THAT'S DULLER THAN
A BASEBALL BAT,
FORCING YOU TO ASK YOUR GUEST
WHETHER THEY WANT WHITE
PULP OR DARK PULP.
BUT MOST OF ALL,
CHRISTMAS IS
FINISHING YOR MEAL
WITH A HALF DOZEN FORKS
AND SPOONS UNTOUCHED,
WHILE YOU LICK THE MASHED
POTATOES OFF THE PALMS
OF YOUR HANDS.
YOU KNOW,
AT CHRISTMAS TIME,
BY HEART KIND OF GOES
OUT TO THE LESS FORTUNATE.
I'M TALKING ABOUT PEOPLE
WHO DON'T LIKE FRUITCAKE,
AND I'M ONE OF 'EM.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU LOOK AT FRUITCAKE,
THE WEIGHT OF IT
AND THE SIZE OF IT
AND THE DIMENSIONS OF IT,
IF YOU CAN GET
PAST THE GAG REFLEX,
THERE ARE A LOT
OF THINGS YOU CAN DO
THAT ARE PRACTICAL APPLICATIONS
OF THIS UNIT RIGHT HERE.
LET ME SHOW
YOU A COUPLE.
HERE'S SOMETHING
DALTON DOES.
HE SAVES UP ALL
OF HIS FRUITCAKES,
AND HE GIVES 'EM
OUT AT HALLOWE'EN.
IT'S A LOT EASIER THAN JUST
TURNING THE LIGHTS OFF
LIKE HE USED TO DO.
AWAY YOU GO.
RANGER GORD,
ON CHRISTMAS EVE,
HE USES HIS FRUITCAKE
AS A PILLOW.
FRUITCAKE ON A FRUITCAKE.
AND HERE'S GORD
ON CHRISTMAS DAY.
NOW, WINSTON USES HIS
FRUITCAKE AS GOALIE PADS.
I HOPE HE'S ALSO
WEARING A FRUIT CUP.
HERE'S SOMETHING YOU CAN DO.
USE A FRUITCAKE AS A
POOR MAN'S CRUISE CONTROL.
YOU CAN DO ABOUT 80 CLICKS
WITH THAT UNIT ON THERE.
HERE'S DALTON AGAIN,
SWITCHING SANTA'S
NORMAL TREAT
FOR A BIG WAD OF FRUITCAKE.
AND HERE'S DALTON'S STOCKING,
SHOWING SANTA GETTING EVEN.
YOU KNOW, FRUITCAKE HAS THE
SAME PROPERTIES OF WOOD,
INCLUDING TASTE.
YOU CAN KEEP A
STOVE GOING FOR HOURS.
NOW, HERE'S SOMETHING.
USE A PIECE OF FRUITCAKE
AS A LOVELY PARKING BRAKE.
USE FRUITCAKE
AS A BOAT ANCHOR.
IT DOESN'T FLOAT.
NOW, HERE'S THE
BEST ONE YET.
YOU CAN LIFT FRUITCAKE TO GET
YOUR ARMS PUMPED UP
RATHER THAN EATING IT
AND GETTING YOUR
STOMACH PUMPED OUT.
OR HIDE YOUR EXTRA
KEY UNDER A --
NOBODY'S GONNA
LOOK UNDER A FRUITCAKE.
CHRISTMAS IS SUCH A GREAT
SEASON, YOU KNOW.
PEOPLE, I THINK,
ARE ACTUALLY FRIENDLIER
BECAUSE IT DOESN'T
SEEM THE RIGHT TIME
TO TELL OTHER PEOPLE
WHAT YOU THINK OF THEM.
OH, RED, BOY,
I'M GLAD I CAUGHT YOU
'CAUSE I'M HANDING OUT ALL
MY CHRISTMAS CARDS TO THE
LODGE MEMBERS THIS YEAR.
YEAH, SAVING
MONEY ON STAMPS,
ARE YOU, DALTON?
YEAH. YEAH.
AND ENVELOPES.
OH, MAN.
JUST GIVE
ME A MINUTE.
I GOTTA FIND
WHICH ONE IS YOURS.
OH, YEAH,
THERE IT IS, YEAH.
WELL, THANK YOU, DALTON.
KINDA STUCK
TOGETHER HERE.
YEAH, YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT IS?
THAT'S WHITE OUT.
YEAH, I HAD TO MAKE A
FEW CORRECTIONS ON IT.
THERE YOU GO.
"TO RED FROM DALTON."
HOW'D YOU MESS
THAT UP?
NO, I HAD TO CORRECT
THE REST OF IT, RED,
BECAUSE IT USED TO SAY
TO DALTON FROM ANN MARIE.
AND THEN THERE WAS KIND OF
A MUSHY LITTLE LOVE POEM
ON THE OTHER SIDE THERE.
YOU KNOW, I KINDA --
HAD TO WIPE THAT OUT.
YOU KNOW, YOU ARE THE
CHEAPEST MAN I KNOW.
YOU KNOW,
I'M RECYCLING!
AND WHITE OUT
ISN'T CHEAP!
YOU KNOW, IF PEOPLE COULD
ONLY LEARN TO DO THEIR
CARDS WITH PENCIL.
OH, Mr. HUMPHREY.
Mr. HUMPHREY.
I WAS LOOKING FOR YOU.
I WANTED TO THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR SENDING ME THIS CARD.
OH, NO PROBLEM
THERE, HAROLD.
IT'S NOT MY BIRTHDAY,
BUT I REALLY
APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU.
IT'S NOT A
BIRTHDAY CARD,
IT'S A CHRISTMAS
CARD, HAROLD.
LOOK, SEE THERE WHERE I'VE
CROSSED OUT BIRTHDAY
AND WRITTEN IN CHRISTMAS
JUST BENEATH IT?
"HAPPY CHRISTMAS."
YES, THAT'S WHAT
THE ENGLISH SAY.
"TO THE BIRTHDAY BOY."
WELL, CHRISTMAS IS SOMEBODY'S
BIRTHDAY, ISN'T IT?
[ APPLAUSE ]
MERRY CHRISTMAS,
HAROLD.
HEY, THANKS.
IF THE GHOST OF
CHRISTMAS PAST
WON'T LEAVE THE PRESENT,
TIME TO MOVE
INTO THE FUTURE
WITH ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
DISCOUNTS FOR VEGETARIANS.
OKAY, WELL, THAT'S IT FOR
OUR CHRISTMAS SPECIAL.
I HOPE YOU ENJOYED IT --
OR PART OF IT ANYWAY.
AND HAROLD, CAN I
JUST SAY WHAT A,
I GUESS TREAT WOULD
BE THE FAIR WORD,
TO HAVE YOU HERE.
WELL, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH FOR THAT.
UNCLE RED,
AT THIS MOMENT,
I'D LIKE TO PRESENT
TO YOU A LITTLE GIFT.
OH, WELL,
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW, I GOT SOMETHING
FOR YOU TOO, EH.
HANG ON.
THERE YOU GO.
NO, NO,
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
I'LL OPEN MY FIRST.
WE DON'T WANNA
END ON A LOW NOTE.
WHAT DO WE GOT
HERE, HAROLD?
IT SEEMS TO BE A --
LOOKS LIKE A TIMEPIECE
OF SOME KIND.
YEAH, YEAH.
IT'S AN ALARM CLOCK
TO HELP YOU
GET UP.
YEAH, WELL, I DON'T
REALLY HAVE ANYTHING
TO GET UP FOR,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
GOOD TO HAVE.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
I KNOW HOW YOU
HATE SLEEPING
THROUGH DINNER.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, OPEN YOURS,
HAROLD.
THIS IS EXCITING.
THIS WILL SHOW YOU THAT
I FINALLY SEE THAT
YOU ARE A MAN
OR AS CLOSE AS
YOU'RE GONNA GET.
YEAH, PRETTY EXCITING.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
LOOK AT THIS.
YOU'LL LOVE THIS.
YOU WRAP IT YOURSELF?
YEAH.
WOW!
A KEY!
I GOT A KEY.
HE GAVE ME A KEY.
WOW.
I BET YOU THAT'S TO WHAT,
A BRAND NEW CAR?
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S THE KEY
TO THE LODGE.
YEAH, ISN'T
THAT GREAT?
HUH?
YEAH, YEAH.
THANK YOU.
YOU CAN COME UP TO THE
LODGE ANY TIME YOU WANT,
ESPECIALLY WHEN
I'M NOT HERE.
WELL, ACTUALLY, I ONLY LIKE
COMING UP WHEN YOU ARE HERE.
WELL, DON'T
YOU GET IT?
NO, NO, NO.
I'M KIDDING YOU.
OH, YEAH.
[ LAUGHING ]
WELL WE GOTTA GO,
SO HAVE YOURSELF A GREAT
HOLIDAY SEASON.
AND ON BEHALF OF EVERYBODY
WHO HAS MAYBE A HAROLD
IN THEIR LIFE --
OR WORSE YET,
THOSE OF YOU WHO HAVE AN
UNCLE RED IN YOUR LIFE.
MERRY CHRISTMAS!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
closed captioning performed
by INTERCAPTION CANADA
www.intercaption.com
WHEN I INSULT YOU,
THAT MEANS I LIKE YOU.
OH, OKAY.
OH, THAT'S COOL.
THAT'S COOL.
YEAH.
WELL, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH,
FAT, OLD,
DRIED UP BASTARD.
OOPS!
[ LAUGHTER ]