(Beer bottle opening)
AHH.
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW".
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
WITH MY HUMBLEST APOLOGIES,
YOUR HOST, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
(Applause)
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
NOTHING TO APOLOGIZE FOR THERE, HAROLD.
I GOT A GREAT SHOW
FOR YOU TODAY.
THIS IS JUST A HINT OF
WHAT'S COMING UP
IN "HANDYMAN CORNER".
INDUSTRIAL STRENGTH
DIAPERS.
IT'S THE "WINCHY".
IT'S IDIOT PROOF.
HERE, PROVE IT.
PUSH THE UP BUTTON.
SEE.
YOU GOT ONE OF THESE BABIES,
YOU CAN GET THINGS OFF
A HIGH SHELF, NO PROBLEM.
DON'T NEED A STEP STOOL.
GET CHEESIES OFF THE FRIDGE.
GET YOUR HAT OFF THE ANTLERS.
GET YOUR OVER-SERVED
SISTER-IN-LAW
DOWN OFF THE CHANDELIER.
WHATEVER IT TAKES,
YOU'RE THERE.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD,
LET ME DOWN.
(Explosion)
WAY TO GO, HAROLD.
YOU BLEW A FUSE.
YOU PUSHED THE BUTTON TOO HARD.
IT'S NOT A FUSE.
THE POWER'S OUT
ALL THE WAY DOWN TO THE LAKE.
HERE, LOOK.
(Horns honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): TODAY, WINSTON AND I
WORK OUT
A MATHEMATICAL PROBLEM.
HAROLD IS OF NO USE
WHATSOEVER,
ALTHOUGH HE MAKES A GOOD BIRD
ON A -- YOU'LL FIND OUT.
AND I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO DO
SOME SOLDERING,
AS MY SALUTE TO HEAVY METAL.
YOU HAVE A NICE DAY, TOO.
I TOLD THE POWER COMPANY
WHAT I THOUGHT OF
THE BAD SERVICE
THEY'VE GIVEN US.
MAYBE IT HAS SOMETHING TO DO
WITH YOUR BAD CHEQUES.
NO, IT DOESN'T --
POWER IS A C.O.D. BUSINESS.
THEY DON'T GET MY "C"
TILL I GET THEIR "D".
WHEN THEY PUT THE POWER IN,
THEY DIDN'T ANTICIPATE
THE REQUIREMENTS
OF A HANDYMAN SUCH AS MYSELF.
I LIKE THINGS THAT HUM
WHEN YOU TURN THEM ON.
THEY'RE PUTTING
A TRANSFORMER TOWER
ON THE FAR SIDE OF POSSUM LAKE.
OH, GREAT.
THAT TRANSFORMER TOWER
WILL BRING IN
SO MUCH ELECTRICITY,
WE'LL BE BOUNCING CHEQUES
INTO THE NEXT MILLENIUM.
THEY'RE GOING TO
STICK IT IN POSSUM PARK,
BETWEEN THE BOG
AND THE GARBAGE FIRE,
NOW WE GOTTA WATCH
THE BOAT RACES
COWERING UNDER
THIS METAL MONSTROSITY.
GOT AN IDEA, HAROLD.
WHY DON'T WE MAKE
THE TRANSFORMER TOWER
SERVE DOUBLE DUTY?
NOT ONLY BRING
50,000 VOLTS INTO THE AREA,
BUT WE CAN USE IT AS
A VERTICAL GRANDSTAND.
A V-V-VER--
A WHAT?
A VERTICAL GRANDSTAND.
PEOPLE CAN SIT ON IT, HAROLD.
THAT'S YOUR TROUBLE.
YOU GOT
NO ENTREPRENEURIAL SPIRIT!
YOU LOOK HARD ENOUGH,
YOU'LL SEE AN OPPORTUNITY.
BUT WHY DOES IT ALWAYS HAVE
A HOOD OVER ITS HEAD
AND A SCYTHE IN ITS HAND?
(Audience laughing)
(Red): UNBEKNOWNST TO ME,
BILL HAD HEARD ABOUT OUR IDEA
FOR THE GRANDSTAND.
SO HE GOT HIMSELF
SOME MODEL ROCKETS
AS A WAY OF
SERVING REFRESHMENTS TO PEOPLE
SITTING WAY UP IN THE RAFTERS.
KIND OF A HOBBY
AND A SPACE PROGRAMME COMBINED.
HE'S GOT THE WIRES
HOOKED UP TO THE ROCKET.
OH, OH, OH --
SHE'S FALLEN OVER.
SHE'S ON AN ANGLE, BILL.
BILL, SHE'S ON AN ANGLE.
YEAH, YEAH --
WHAT'S THAT?
OW!
THAT'S HOW THAT WORKS.
NOW I'M IN THE VAN
WITH A LIVE ROCKET.
REMINDS ME OF A COUPLE OF DATES
I HAD IN HIGH SCHOOL.
BILL'S PROGRAMME IS
KIND OF LIKE NASA.
WELL, NOT QUITE THE SAME,
BUT IT RHYMES.
WHAT'S HE DOING?
STAND BACK, STAND BACK,
STAND BACK, STAND BACK!
ALL CLEAR.
BILL WILL BE BACK LATER
WITH A COUPLE MORE ROCKETS
AND A LOT MORE TROUBLE.
HERE WE ARE WITH
HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
WE'RE ALL SET TO PLAY
OUR WORD GAME.
WHAT'S OUR PRIZE TODAY?
RED, THE GRAND PRIZE IS
A PAIR OF EARFLAPS
FROM RAYMOND'S HOUSE OF RUBBER.
CERTAINLY A GOOD PRIZE.
HAROLD, GIVE ME THE WORD.
DON'T LOOK AT THIS, HAP.
I'LL TELL THE PEOPLE AT HOME
WHAT IT SAYS.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET YOU TO SAY THIS.
SOMEBODY WHO MAKES UP STORIES.
AUTHOR.
ERNEST HEMINGWAY AND I--
NO, NO, THAT WASN'T IT.
SOMEONE WHO TELLS FALSEHOODS.
POLITICIAN.
WHEN I WAS CHARLES De GAULLE'S
BODYGUARD--
AGAIN, NO, NO.
A PERSON WHO BENDS THE TRUTH.
SECRET AGENT.
I WAS DOWN IN ALGERIA--
NO, NO, HAP.
I THINK I GOT IT.
HAP SHAUGHNESSY,
YOU ARE A...
DEEP SEA DIVER, ASTRONAUT.
NO.                     SUMO
WRESTLER.
INVENTOR.
INVENTOR, YES,
'CAUSE YOU INVENT STORIES,
SO THAT MAKES YOU A...
BROADWAY PLAYWRIGHT.
I HAVEN'T WRITTEN A HIT MUSICAL
IN YEARS.
SAY SOMEBODY SAYS THAT
YOU NEVER WERE AN ASTRONAUT
A SUMO WRESTLER
OR A PLAYWRIGHT.
THAT PERSON IS A...
A LIAR.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU GOT IT.
YEAH.
WELL... DO YOU KNOW,
THE WORST LIAR I EVER MET?
NO.
MICHELLE PFIEFFER.
SHE SWORE THAT
SHE WOULDN'T FALL FOR ME.
SAID IT WAS ONLY GOING TO BE
A SEXUAL RELATIONSHIP.
BUT, OH NO.
(Strums acoustic guitar)
OH, FRUIT, FRUIT,
FRUIT, FRUIT, FRUIT
NATURE'S WAY
OF MAKING THINGS SCOOT
FUN TO EAT
AND FUN TO THROW
BUT IF YOU TOSS 'EM,
HERE'S SOMETHING TO KNOW
I HAD AN EXPERIENCE
DOWN BY THE BEACH
I NAILED A GUY
WITH A ROTTEN PEACH
HE WAS A FULL-FIGURED MAN,
HE COULD REALLY HIT
SO IF YOU'RE PREDISPOSED
TO THROWING PEACHES
I WOULD MAKE SURE THAT YOU
FIRST OF ALL REMOVE THE PIT
IT'S MY IDEA TO BUILD
THIS VERTICAL GRANDSTAND.
WE'LL ATTACH
ALUMINUM LAWN CHAIRS TO
THE STEEL TRANSMISSION TOWER.
I THOUGHT I'D TAKE THIS
"HANDYMAN CORNER"
AND SHOW YOU HOW TO BOND
METAL TO METAL.
IMAGINE THAT THIS IS
THE TRANSMISSION TOWER.
IMAGINE THAT THIS
IS A LAWN CHAIR.
I'M GOING TO START UP
ONE OF THESE SOLDERING TORCHES.
WE'RE GOING TO SOLDER
THIS WHOLE THING TOGETHER.
SOLDER'S A STRANGE WORD.
YOU DON'T PRONOUNCE THE "L".
IF YOU SAY "SOLLLDER"
THE CLERKS ARE GOING TO
STAY AWAY IN DROVES.
YOU GET A WORD LIKE "HELP",
YOU WANT TO PRONOUNCE
THE "L".
HEP, HEP.
SEE, NOBODY COMES.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS
HEAT UP THE METAL.
GET THEM BOTH GOOD AND HOT.
I RECOMMEND YOU USE A TORCH,
BUT YOU COULD USE A STOVE OR,
IF YOU'RE REAL FAST,
YOU COULD USE AN EXPLOSION.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S GOOD.
NOW YOU GET SOME OF
THIS FLUX.
YOU WANT TO PUT THAT ON.
IT KIND OF CLEANS THE THING.
YOU CAN JUST PUT IT ON
WITH YOUR FINGERS...
BUT I WOULDN'T RECOMMEND IT.
ALL RIGHT NOW,
JUST GET YOUR SOLDER,
AND YOU WANT TO HEAT THAT UP.
PUT ENOUGH SOLDER IN THERE
THAT THE METALS BECOME ONE,
ALL JOINED TOGETHER.
AND DON'T BE SHY.
JUST LAY THE SOLDER IN THERE.
THERE, THAT OUGHT TO HOLD HER.
HEP, HEP,
I'M COVERED IN "SOLLLDER."
SEE, NOBODY COMES.
SOLDER'S NOT ALL THAT STRONG.
BUT IF YOU SOCK
ENOUGH ON THERE,
SHE OUGHT TO HOLD.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL HAVE TO GO TO
SOMETHING STRONGER THAN SOLDER.
I'LL JUST GET THIS STUFF
OFF MYSELF,
AND I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
MAN, I FEEL LIKE
A BAKED POTATO.
THIS IS CALLED BRAZING
'CAUSE YOU DO IT WITH BRASS.
IF YOU DID IT WITH COPPER,
YOU'D CALL IT "CRAZING".
IF YOU DID IT WITH
NITROGLYCERINE,
CALL AN AMBULANCE.
ALL YOU'VE GOT TO DO IS ADD
THE OXYGEN TO THE FLAME
AND YOU CAN GET HER
PRETTY DARN HOT.
I DON'T HAVE BRASS.
THAT'S EXPENSIVE.
I'LL TO USE A COAT HANGER.
IT SHOULD BE OK.
YOU JUST GET THIS SO HOT...
YOU DON'T NEED ANY FLUX
WITH THIS.
JUST LAY THE BRASS
RIGHT IN THERE,
OR THE COAT HANGER.
THE BEAUTY OF THIS IS
IT'S SO HOT
YOU CAN USE IT FOR CUTTING
METAL PIPES OR
METAL PLATES
OR METAL GIRDERS EVEN.
OR THAT.
WE'RE GETTING SERIOUS.
THIS IS WHAT THEY CALL
AN ARC WELDER,
WHICH IS SORT OF LIKE
CONTROLLED LIGHTNING,
EXCEPT THIS BABY STRIKES TWICE
IN THE SAME PLACE.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
I'VE SEEN WELDERS
STRIKE IN THE SAME PLACE
FOR 30 YEARS.
TAKE A CLIP LIKE THIS.
CLIP THAT ONTO YOUR WORK.
THAT'S SORT OF LIKE
YOUR GROUND WIRE.
THEN THE OTHER UNIT,
KIND OF AN ODD-LOOKING THING,
TAKE THAT AND STICK THE ROD
IN THE END.
YOU DON'T USE A FLAME.
THIS ROD TOUCHES THE WORK.
THAT CLOSES THE CIRCUIT,
AND THAT DOES YOUR WELDING.
SHE'S BRIGHT
AND CAN HURT YOUR EYES.
SO, FOR SAFETY'S SAKE,
AND YOU KNOW ME,
SAFETY FORCED,
WE'RE GOING TO PUT
THE MASK ON
OH, BOY.
WAIT A MINUTE HERE.
WOW.
BETTER HANG ON TO THE...
(Groaning)
ALL RIGHT, NOW.
YOU CAN'T ALWAYS SEE
WHEN YOU DO THIS.
BUT YOU JUST TOUCH THE ROD
TO THE WORK,
AND THE SPARK WILL
LET YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
THERE WE GO.
SOLID AS A ROCK.
(Audience laughing)
ALL RIGHT, I MAY HAVE WELDED
SOME OF MY TOOLS
AND VARIOUS WORKSHOP
COLLECTABLES TO THE UNIT.
BUT, LOOK AT THE BRIGHT SIDE.
I NOW HAVE
A BURGLAR-PROOF ENVIRONMENT.
I'VE ALSO WELDED
MY WEDDING RING
TO MY BELT BUCKLE,
WHICH IS KIND OF POETIC.
SO, REMEMBER, IF WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
EVERYBODY ENJOYS SEEING A GUY
BEING CHASED BY A MOOSE.
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL.
WHAT HAPPENED? -- YOU STAND
TOO CLOSE TO THE DART TEAM?
I WISH.
I WAS PECKED BY SEAGULLS.
THAT IS IT FOR ME
AND OUTDOOR RESTAURANTS.
DO YOU HAVE
A FEATURE FOR US?
HMM?
A FEATURE.
OH, YES, YES, YES.
TODAY WE'LL TALK ABOUT
HOW TO GET RID OF SOMETHING
A BIT LARGER THAN
WE USUALLY TALK ABOUT.
A MOOSE.
SURE -- WITH A SHOTGUN.
I'LL PRETEND
I DIDN'T HEAR THAT, RED.
NO!
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO --
SAY YOU GOT A MOOSE
HANGING AROUND YOUR HOUSE.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS
GET YOURSELF A CAN OF
MOOSE MUSK.
TO A MALE MOOSE,
THIS IS UM... VERY PLEASANT,
VERY, UM... WELL,
IT'S VERY ATTRACTIVE.
I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
NOW, TAKE THE MOOSE MUSK.
YOU TAKE IT DEEP,
DEEP INTO THE WOODS,
AND YOU TAKE THE TOP OFF.
OH BOY, LOOK AT THAT, HUH?
NOW, THIS WILL ATTRACT
THE MOOSE DEEP INTO THE WOODS.
BOY, THAT'S A HECK OF A LOT
OF MOOSE MUSK THERE.
THERE'S ENOUGH HORMONES THERE
TO START A LIFT BRIDGE.
OF COURSE, YOU DON'T NEED
TO USE NEAR THIS AMOUNT.
A TINY LITTLE BIT WILL DO.
THAT MUCH MOOSE MUSK,
THAT WILL PROBABLY ATTRACT--
LOOKS LIKE 25 TO 30.
I'D SAY AT LEAST 25 TO 30.
THAT MUCH MOOSE MUSK WILL DRIVE
A MOOSE ABSOLUTELY CRAZY.
SENSORY OVERLOAD.
OH BOY.
ANOTHER SUPER DAY.
RUN, HAROLD!
DON'T YOU PASS ME, HAROLD!
MAN, THIS THING BINDS.
(Audience laughing)
THE BEST WAY TO MAKE
MY VERTICAL GRANDSTAND
AFFORDABLE TO EVERYBODY
IS TO HAVE THREE TICKET PRICES.
LIKE REDS, GOLDS AND BLUES?
YEAH, SORT OF --
POP, WINE AND BEER.
NOW, THE POP TICKET
IS 10 BUCKS.
YOU GET UP 10 FEET
ON A PLANK.
THE WINE TICKET,
THAT'S 20 BUCKS.
YOU'RE 30 FEET HIGHER
IN A LAWN CHAIR
WITH A ROPE SEAT-BELT.
I GOT ABOUT 40 ALREADY
DUCK-TAPED UP THERE.
BEER TICKETS BEING THE BEST.
HAROLD, BEER TICKETS
ARE ALWAYS THE BEST.
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL,
REMINDING YOU, DON'T FEED BEARS
WHEN THEY'RE IN HEAT.
AND, OF COURSE, VICE VERSA.
WELCOME TO
THE EXPERT PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THIS WEEK WE HAVE MY UNCLE RED
AND HIS FRIEND,
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD.
(Applause and cheering)
OK.
THE FIRST LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS:
"DEAR EXPERTS...
"MY GUIDANCE COUNSELLOR
SAYS THAT THE AVERAGE PERSON
"WILL HOLD DOWN FIVE
OR SIX JOBS IN THEIR LIFE.
"DOES THAT SOUND RIGHT TO YOU?"
YOU KNOW SOMETHING,
I DON'T LOOK AT IT THAT WAY.
I LOOK AT IT AS FILLING YOUR
LIFE WITH PROFITABLE ACTIVITY.
AS THE GREAT ANTHONY ANTHONY
ONCE SAID,
"IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
SELF-HELP,
"YOU'VE GOT TO HELP YOURSELF."
WELL WORTH 90 BUCKS
FOR THAT TIDBIT, I WOULD THINK.
I THINK HE MEANT THAT
YOU ADD UP THE HOURS IN A DAY
THAT YOU COULD BE WORKING.
SO WHAT IS THAT -- 20?
(Red): 20?
SOMETHING'S OUT OF WHACK THERE,
EITHER YOUR MATH
OR YOUR PRIORITIES.
YOU MULTIPLY THAT
BY THE NUMBER OF YEARS
FROM WHEN YOU LEFT SCHOOL
TILL WHEN YOU RETIRE.
SO HOW OLD WERE YOU
WHEN YOU LEFT SCHOOL?
20.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WENT PASSED
HIGH SCHOOL.
I PASSED IT
ON THE WAY TO THE LODGE.
OK, SO THAT'S --
SO 45 YEARS TIMES
20 HOURS A DAY...
THAT'S...
A LOT OF TIME!
EASILY A LOT.
THAT'S WHAT
I THOUGHT.
AND SEE,
YOU COULD BE MAKING MONEY
WITH THAT TIME.
OH YEAH.
TAKE ME, FOR INSTANCE.
I AM RUNNING A VERY SUCCESSFUL
SEWAGE AND SEPTIC SUCKING
BUSINESS.
AND
I HAVE SOMETHING ON THE SIDE.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO SEE
A DOCTOR ABOUT THAT.
(Audience laughing)
YOU SEE... RED,
THE WAY I SEE IT IS
I'M IN THAT TRUCK
ALL DAY LONG.
I COULD DO MORE THAN SIMPLY
SUCK OUT SEPTIC TANKS.
I SUPPOSE,
YEAH.
SO, I'VE NOW GOT
A PIZZA DELIVERY SERVICE.
(Audience laughing)
AND,
A TAXI SERVICE,
AND A COURIER SERVICE.
"IF IT'S NOT ON YOUR DESK
BY 8:00 TOMORROW MORNING,
"IT'S FREE, GUARANTEED."
A LOT OF COURIER COMPANIES
CAN'T GUARANTEE THAT.
THAT'S MY PIZZA DELIVERY
GUARANTEE.
(Audience laughing)
HERE'S A HANDYMAN HINT.
WHEN YOU'VE GOT
A PIECE OF WOOD
THAT'S JUST A LITTLE BIT
TOO LONG,
YOU CAN SHORTEN IT USING
ONE OF THESE WOOD PLANES.
MAKES IT SMOOTHER, TOO.
REMEMBER, ANY TOOL
CAN BE THE RIGHT TOOL.
AS PREVIOUSLY WARNED,
BILL IS GOING TO BE
FOOLING AROUND WITH ROCKETS.
I'LL BE HIS ASSISTANT.
MANY TIMES A SCIENTIST
HAS AN ASSISTANT.
I'LL DO WHAT
ANY SANE ASSISTANT WOULD DO,
BASICALLY GET OUT OF THERE.
BILL'S GOT HER WIRED UP.
YOU CAN IGNITE THESE ALMOST
LIKE AN EXPLOSIVE CHARGE.
THERE'S AN ELECTRICAL UNIT
IN THERE.
WHEN YOU PLUNGE DOWN,
THE ELECTRICITY
GOES THROUGH THE WIRE.
IT EVEN GOES THROUGH
WHEN YOU PULL UP ON THAT.
"THERE YOU GO, BILL.
"YOU'RE WELCOME."
BILL HOOKS THAT UP.
NONE OF US NOTICED
THAT THERE WAS CLOTHING,
I THINK THE SCIENTIST
LET US DOWN.
AND THIS WAS... THIS WAS...
THIS WAS AN UNFORTUNATE
TURN OF EVENTS.
BUT, ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
THESE ARE
THE HOT NEW FASHIONS
OUT OF POSSUM LODGE.
BILL'S GOT A BIGGER...
I'M DOING THE ASSISTANT THING
TO THE "T" NOW.
CLEAR THE AREA.
BUT, YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS.
THE CURIOSITY, SEE --
CAN'T HELP BUT LOOK.
BILL DID NOT TELL ME
EXACTLY WHAT HE HAD IN MIND.
SO WHEN THE ROCKET
HOOKED AROUND HIS ANKLE,
I DIDN'T KNOW
WHETHER TO MENTION IT.
PLUS, I HADN'T NOTICED IT.
THIS WAS UNFORTUNATE,
BECAUSE AS HE LAY DOWN,
AND WITH HIM JUXTAPOSING
HIS LEGS AROUND,
HE PUT THE ROCKET
IN AN UNCOMFORTABLE PLACE,
AND THEN REALLY KIND OF
WEDGING IT IN THERE.
I DON'T WHETHER
THIS IS HIS PLAN,
OR THIS IS GOING WRONG.
IS THIS WHAT HE WANTS,
OR IS THIS A MISTAKE?
I'M THINKING IT'S A MISTAKE
AT THIS POINT.
NOW I REALIZE, THIS IS
NOTHING TO DO WITH ROCKETS.
THIS IS PART OF BILL'S
AEROBIC EXERCISE PROGRAMME.
HE LOOKS PRETTY AIRED OUT.
THOSE CRAMPS WILL GO AWAY
IN AWHILE,
BUT YOU'LL NEVER GO BACK
TO NORMAL.
STAY TUNED
WHILE HAROLD DROPS IN.
THE WEATHER'S PERFECT
FOR THE BOAT RACE.
TICKETS HAVE BEEN SELLING
LIKE MAD.
HAROLD HAS AGREED TO OPERATE
THE CONCESSION STAND.
RIGHT, HAROLD?
AHH HA HA.
AHH.
HA HA HA HA.
NOW I KNOW WHY WOMEN
WERE SO HAPPY
WHEN THEY INVENTED PANTYHOSE.
YOU'D THINK MY UNCLE WOULD
GIVE ME A TICKET.
YOU'RE GETTING IN FREE.
I JUST ATTACHED
A FEW CONDITIONS TO IT.
WHERE YOU GOING TO BE?
OFF COUNTING YOUR MONEY?
NO -- AS MANAGER OF
THE VERTICAL GRANDSTAND,
I THOUGHT IT WAS ONLY RIGHT
THAT I TAKE THE BOX OFF
MY OLD PICK-UP TRUCK
AND WELD THAT TO
THE TOP OF THE TOWER.
YOUR OWN PRIVATE BOX?!
YOU HAVEN'T LIVED
TILL YOU'VE EXPERIENCED
A BOAT RACE FROM 130 FEET.
MEANWHILE, I'LL BE DANGLING
FROM THIS CABLE
LOOKING LIKE SPIDERMAN
ON A COFFEE BREAK.
I WAS THINKING MORE
DOPE ON A ROPE.
AHHH!
NOW YOU'VE GONE AND DONE IT.
YOU'VE SAID THE ONE THING
THAT ALWAYS GETS MEN
INTO TROUBLE.
YOU HAD TO BE A BIG SHOT.
DOING THAT JOB
AROUND THE HOUSE.
SHE KINDLY OFFERS SOME ADVICE.
AND YOU SAID,
"I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING."
YOU LIED.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
MEN NEVER KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
WHY DRAW ATTENTION TO IT?
SHE'S ONLY GOING TO
CHECK UP ON YOU.
OK, GET YOURSELF
ALONE IN THERE.
NO WITNESSES AROUND.
IF THERE'S ANY INSTRUCTIONS,
READ 'EM.
I KNOW YOU
DON'T READ INSTRUCTIONS,
BUT THERE'S JUST NO ROOM
FOR ERROR THIS TIME.
IF YOU'VE GOT NO INSTRUCTIONS,
YOU CAN HIRE A PROFESSIONAL.
BUT WHAT GOOD WOULD THAT DO?
IT'S ONLY GOING TO
BLOW YOUR COVER.
IF YOU'RE REALLY STUCK,
YOU GOTTA CALL HER DAD
AND ASK HIM TO COME OVER
AND HELP YA.
(Audience laughing)
THE MOST USELESS
HUMAN BEING ON THE PLANET.
(Audience laughing)
HE WON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
BUT HE'LL DO ANYTHING
FOR HIS LITTLE GIRL.
HE'LL PROBABLY WRECK
EVERYTHING IN THE PROCESS.
EXACTLY WHAT
YOU WANT HIM TO DO.
HE CAN TAKE
THE HEAT FOR MESSING UP.
YOU CAN TAKE THE GLORY FOR
ADMITTING THAT YOU NEEDED HELP.
SHE'LL LOVE YOU FOR IT!
REMEMBER, DO EXACTLY
WHAT WE SAID HERE.
TRUST US --
WE KNOW WHAT WE'RE DOING.
(Audience laughing)
(Liquid boiling)
(Applaus
WELL, SPORTS FANS,
WE SHOULD ADVISE
ANY LODGE MEMBERS OUT THERE,
DON'T BE TOO HASTY GETTING INTO
THE VERTICAL GRANDSTAND
BUSINESS.
WARN THEM TO CHECK
WEATHER CONDITIONS
BEFORE THEY CLIMB
ANY TRANSFORMER TOWERS.
SOMEONE LEFT THE RADIO ON
SOMEWHERE?
(Audience laughing)
I COULDN'T SAY NO.
THEY WERE SO ANXIOUS
TO GET UP THAT TOWER.
NOT HALF AS ANXIOUS
AS THEY WERE TO GET DOWN
WHEN THAT LIGHTING STRUCK IT.
LIGHTNING IS FAST.
THAT'S THE LAST TIME
I BUY AN EXPENSIVE TICKET.
I WAS THE LAST ONE
TO GET OFF THE DARN THING.
I WAS CLIMBING
AS FAST AS I COULD.
WHY DIDN'T YOU USE
THE WINCHY?
THE FIRST LIGHTNING BOLT
FUSED THE MOTOR.
SECOND ONE FRIED MY POPCORN
AND THAWED THE FREEZIES.
(Audience laughing)
I HEAR THAT RADIO AGAIN.
YOU WANT TO KNOW
THE TRAFFIC REPORT AT ALL?
(Audience laughing)
I'LL TELL YOU THOUGH,
ALL THAT
TAKEN INTO CONSIDERATION,
IT WAS A BEAUTIFUL SIGHT.
I'VE SEEN A BLUE FLAME BEFORE,
BUT NEVER THAT CLOSE
TO MY FACE,
EXCEPT ONCE AT A STAG.
(Possum
squeal)
MEETING TIME.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD,
YOU GO AHEAD.
MEL'S DOING THE SPORTS, TOO.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I GOT A CLOSE ENCOUNTER
WITH RAW ENERGY.
I WAS HOPING TO SHARE
SOME WITH YOU,
UNLESS I'M GROUNDED.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF, HAROLD,
AND THE WHOLE GANG
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): HAROLD, DID YOU HAVE
ANY ANNOUNCEMENTS?
(Harold): YES, SOMEONE STOLE
A BANANA SEED OUT OF MY CAR
AND I'D LIKE IT BACK
RIGHT AWAY, PLEASE.