WHEN BERNICE MAKES HER
HOME MADE APPLE SAUCE
SHE PICKS THE APPLES
ONE BY ONE,
SHE PEELS THEM,
SHE CHOPS 'EM UP,
SHE BOILS THEM,
SHE PUREES THEM,
AND THEN SHE CANS THEM.
BOY, IF I DIDN'T GO INTO THE
KITCHEN FOR A COLD ONE
DURING THE HALF-TIME SHOW,
I WOULDN'T SEE
HER AT ALL.
SO I'M SAYIN', FORGET ABOUT
PICKING THE APPLES...
THERE'S A BUMPER CROP.
[ CHUCKLES ]
ALL THESE APPLES FALLING,
I FEEL LIKE ISAAC NEWTON.
HE WAS A GENIUS TOO.
BUT I GOT SOMETHING THAT
OLD ISAAC NEWTON DIDN'T
EVEN HAVE...
A VETERINARY COLLAR
JUNIOR SINGLETON PUT
ON HIS GOLDEN RETRIEVER
SO THAT IT WOULDN'T
PAW AT ITS EAR INFECTION.
I GOT A BUNCH
OF FISH BOWLS
AND A GAS-POWERED
SNOWBLOWER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANKS VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
BUSTER HADFIELD IS
SELLING ALL HIS OLD CARS.
HE'S GOT A CAMARO,
A CONVERTIBLE MINUS THE ENGINE,
HE'S GOT A TOYOTA COROLLA
THAT'S ONLY ROLLED
THREE TIMES, I BELIEVE.
AND HE'S GOT 5½ DODGE DARTS.
UH -- UM -- UH --
UH, CAN WE TALK?
I AM.
HE'S GOT AN AEROSTAR,
HE'S GOT A WINDSTAR,
THE MOST OF
A CHRYSLER IMPERIAL,
AND HE'S GOT A
TOW TRUCK.
THE TOW TRUCK
BROKE DOWN,
WHICH IS WHY HE HAS
TO GET RID OF ALL
THE CARS, SEE?
ARE YOU JUST
GOING TO IGNORE ME?
SO FAR SO GOOD.
I have a
personal issue.
HAROLD, TWO WORDS...
CALAMINE LOTION.
[ LAUGHTER ]
NO, IT'S
NOT PHYSICAL.
OH, NO.
IS IT YOUR
GIRLFRIEND?
NO?
YES!!!
I SAW BONNIE DRIVING
AROUND TOWN IN ANOTHER
GUY'S CAR.
A GUY!
A GUY GUY.
WHAT GUY?
SOME GUY WHO WASN'T ME,
THAT'S ALL I KNOW.
GOOD LOOKIN' GUY,
WELL DRESSED, BUFF.
I'VE LOST BONNIE.
HE'S AL GOT AN
AMC JAVELIN THERE,
AND LESS THAN 300,000
MILES ON HER,
AND ALL THE ORIGINAL
FIRE DAMAGE, I MEAN,
IT'S JUST --
UNCLE RED, ARE YOU GONNA
HELP ME GET BONNIE BACK?
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD,
THIS IS REAL EASY.
WHAT DOES THIS GUY
HAVE THAT YOU DON'T?
BONNIE!
NO, NO, NO.
A CAR, HAROLD.
THIS GUY'S GOT
A CAR.
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU
ONE OF BUSTER'S CARS.
OH, OH YEAH!
OKAY, YOU THINK
THAT'LL HELP?
ABSOLUTELY GUARANTEED.
HOW MUCH MONEY
DO YOU HAVE?
TWENTY DOLLARS.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL BRING
YOU THE CHANGE.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S PRIZE
IS THIS COUPON
FOR A DECORATIVE BUFFET
PLATTER FROM MARTHA'S MEATS,
FEATURING PAUL BUNYAN
AND HIS PARENTS,
MA AND PA BUNYAN,
ALL MADE ENTIRELY
OUT OF LIVER.
WE CALL IT
LIVER AND BUNYANS.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
THINGIES, BLAIR.
MR. GREEN,
YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET SNOWMOBILE GUY BLAIR
COBDEN TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH,
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND... GO.
OKAY, BLAIR, AFTER A
DAY OF SNOWMOBILING
YOU WANNA COME
HOME TO YOUR...
TRAILER.
NO, OKAY.
OKAY, WHAT MAKES
YOUR HEART SKIP A BEAT?
THE SOUND
OF ICE CRACKING.
NO, NO, I MEAN, THIS IS
SOMETHING ROMANTIC,
SOMETHING THAT
GETS YOU EXCITED.
A SNOW MACHINE.
NO, BLAIR,
THIS HAS EXTRA CURVES
IN ALL THE RIGHT PLACES.
A THREE-SEATER.
YOU SEE PAMELA ANDERSON
AND YOU SAY, SHE'S ALL...
SILICONE.
OKAY, UM, HELEN REDDY
SANG A SONG,
I AM SOMETHING,
HEAR ME ROAR.
FULL OF GAS?
UH, OKAY, YOU KNOW,
THE GUYS WILL SAY
THEY WISH THAT THIS PERSON
COULD BE MORE LIKE A MAN.
MY COUSIN ERIC.
UH, WE'RE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME, MR. GREEN.
OKAY, OKAY,
BLAIR, YOU KNOW,
THEY SAY THAT NO MAN IS
COMPLETE UNTIL HE
GETS A GOOD...
HELMET.
BUT YOU KNOW, I'D TRADE IN A
GOOD HELMET FOR A GOOD WOMAN.
YEAH!
SCRAPE OFF YOUR PALETTES AND
STRAP ON YOUR APRONS,
BECAUSE IT'S TIME
FOR HAROLD'S HOBBY HOUSE!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, JOINING ME TODAY
IS SEMI-EXPERT
DEMOLITIONIST,
MR. EDGAR K.B.
MONTROSE!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WELCOME, EDGAR.
I UNDERSTAND YOU BROUGHT
A SAMPLE OF YOUR
WORK TODAY.
OH, NO, THE DOCTOR SAID
THAT WOULD CLEAR UP
IF I JUST PUT
THE SALVE ON IT.
BUT I HAVE SOME SCULPT-ART
TODAY, HAROLD.
IT'S A COMBINATION OF
SCULPTING AND PAINTING.
OH! SO I ASSUME YOU
TAKE SOME SCULPTURE,
AND YOU JUST PAINT IT.
NEVER ASSUME THINGS,
HAROLD.
LIKE WHEN YOU SEE
A DOORBELL BUTTON,
NEVER ASSUME THAT IT'S
A DOORBELL BUTTON.
IT COULD BE AN
EXPLOSIVES DETONATOR.
THAT ONE COST ME
A FINGER.
SO!
WHAT IS SCULPT-ART?
OH, IT'S JUST THE BIGGEST
BREAKTHROUGH IN ART SINCE
FINGERPAINTING,
WHICH I HAD TO GIVE UP.
HOW DO YOU START?
WELL, YOU START
WITH A SCULPTURE.
THAT'S A CLOCK.
ARTISTIC LICENSE.
OKAY.
AND YOU CHANGE THAT
SCULPTURE INTO A PAINTING.
[ sniffs ]
THAT'S DYNAMITE.
WELL, WHY,
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
NOW, YOU TAKE A
SCULPTURE LIKE THIS,
AND YOU TRANSFORM THIS
TEAPOT INTO A T.N.T.-POT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WHAT KIND OF
CHARGE IS THAT?
UH, FIVE BUCKS FOR YOU.
AND THEN YOU PUT THE TEAPOT
INTO THE GARBAGE CAN.
IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE ART TO ME.
ART IS IN THE EYE
OF THE BEHOLDER.
THAT'S WHERE I'M AFRAID
IT'S GONNA END UP.
JUST A MINUTE.
OKAY.
AHH!
PUT IT INTO THE CAN.
THIS IS NOT SAFE!
NOW, IF YOU PUT SOMETHING
HEAVY ON THE CANVAS,
MOST PEOPLE WILL THINK
THAT WILL MAKE THE
EXPLOSION SAFER.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, OVER THE YEARS,
MANY OF MY BEST FRIENDS
HAVE BEEN BLESSED
WITH SUDDEN GOOD FORTUNE.
AND GOLLY, DID THEY EVER THINK
TO SHARE ANY OF IT WITH ME?
WELL, NOW THE
TABLE IS TURNED.
LITERALLY.
I RECENTLY BECAME THE OWNER
OF A NUMBER OF HIGHWAY SIGNS
AS THE RESULT
OF A HEAVY WINDSTORM
AND MY OWN CHAIN SAW.
AND WHAT DID I DO
WITH THIS GOOD FORTUNE?
HOW ABOUT A DINING ROOM TABLE
FOR PEOPLE ON THE GO?
OR A TRAY FOR SERVING
DRINKS TO PEOPLE
WHO ARE GETTING
A LITTLE CARRIED AWAY.
OR WHAT IF YOU
LIKE TO SIT OUTSIDE?
OR MAYBE THE PEOPLE
IN YOUR FAMILY
FORCE YOU TO SIT OUTSIDE.
WELL, HOW ABOUT A
HIGHWAY SIGN MUSKOKA CHAIR?
BUT WHAT IF
YOU'RE NOT HANDY?
WHAT DO YOU DO THEN?
KILL YOURSELF I GUESS.
I'M JUST KIDDIN' YA.
NO, YOU CAN JUST USE THE
SIGNS JUST THE WAY THEY ARE.
PUT ONE ON THE BATHROOM.
HECK, PUT ONE
IN THE BATHROOM.
AND YOU CAN PUT ONE
ON THE BEDROOM DOOR
AND A WHOLE BUNCH
MORE INSIDE.
THAT LAST ONE
GLOWS IN THE DARK.
OH, LOOK, HAROLD'S ROOM.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I WANNA TALK TO THE WOMEN OUT
THERE ABOUT SOMETHING
IMPORTANT.
YOU MAY NOT KNOW THIS,
BUT AS US GUYS GET ON IN YEARS,
OUR NEEDS IN
THE BEDROOM CHANGE.
IT'S ALL PART OF THE
TIME-SPACE CONTINUUM.
WE A LITTLE MORE TIME,
BUT WE NEED A LOT MORE SPACE.
SEE, WHEN BERNICE
AND I FIRST MARRIED
WE SLEPT ON A 3/4 BED WITH
OUR ARMS AND LEGS ALL
TANGLED UP,
LIKE FOUR POUNDS OF WORMS
IN A THREE-POUND CAN.
AFTER BEING MARRIED
FOR A COUPLE OF YEARS,
WE BOTH NEEDED A DOUBLE.
AND THEN A QUEEN SIZED,
AND NOW WE'RE
UP TO A KING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S NEXT,
AN ACE OR MAYBE A JOKER.
THE LONGER YOU'RE TOGETHER
THE BIGGER THE BED.
I THINK IF YOU'RE
MARRIED LONG ENOUGH
YOU START SLEEPING
ON THE POOL COVER.
NOW, THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH ROMANCE OR LOVE
OR ANYTHING THEY
TALK ABOUT ON OPRAH.
THIS IS ALL ABOUT TWO BODIES
WHO START HAVING
A MIND OF THEIR OWN,
KICKING AND TWITCHING
AND PUNCHING
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
THAT'S WHY WE
NEED THE HUGE BED.
SO, LADIES, THE NEXT TIME
YOU'RE WONDERING
WHEN YOUR HUSBAND'S
COMING TO BED
ONLY TO REALISE HE'S BEEN
LYING NEXT TO YOU FOR
THREE HOURS,
TRUST ME, HE KNOWS
IT'S SAFER FOR EVERYONE
IF HE SIMPLY ADMIRES
YOU FROM AFAR.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
IF YOU MADE A DEPOSIT
IN THE STOCK MARKET
GOT A BIG RETURN
AND YOU'RE ROLLING IN IT,
CONGRATULATIONS.
IF YOU MADE
A DEPOSIT AT HOME
GOT A BIG RETURN AND
YOU'RE SWIMMING IN IT,
CALL ROTHSCHILD'S.
MAN, YOU TRY
TO HELP A GUY OUT,
OR EVEN A HAROLD OUT,
WHERE DOES IT GET YOU?
WENT TO BUSTER HADFIELD'S
USED CAR SALE,
BOUGHT HAROLD A '74
OLDS TORNADO.
I MEAN,
THAT'S A LOT OF CAR.
YOU'D THINK HAROLD
WOULD BE GRATEFUL.
BUT THEN YOU'D THINK HAROLD
WOULD BE A LOT OF THINGS.
OKAY, UNCLE RED,
OKAY, OKAY,
I SUPPOSE YOU MEANT WELL.
YOU JUST DIDN'T
DO WELL.
HAROLD, WHERE ELSE
ARE YOU GOING TO FIND
A FULL-SIZE LUXURY CAR
FOR 17 BUCKS?
TRUE, BUT SEE THE CAR --
THE POINT OF THE CAR
WAS TO HELP GET BONNIE
BACK INTO MY LIFE.
SHE'S NOT GONNA
GET IN THAT THING.
THERE'S A DOOR MISSING.
IT'S NOT HER DOOR.
HAROLD,
IF SHE'S UPPITY,
I CAN'T HELP YOU.
BONNIE DOESN'T
CARE ABOUT CARS.
I HEARD THAT SHE WENT TO
PORT ASBESTOS WITH HER
NEW BOYFRIEND.
ONCE SHE SEES THE BIG CITY,
I'M NEVER GOING TO SEE
HER AGAIN.
WELL, YOU NEED TO BE
A BIG CITY GUY YOURSELF.
YOU NEED
TO DRESS LIKE --
WELL, I HAVE NO IDEA,
REALLY.
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT!
I NEED TO BECOME
A METROSEXUAL.
WELL, I'VE ALWAYS
SAID --
A WHAT?
METROSEXUAL, IT'S A
MAN WHO HAS THE MOST
DESIRABLE TRAITS
OF BOTH A
MAN AND A WOMAN.
METROSEXUAL.
IF THAT MEANS
TOO CLOSE TO CALL,
IT SURE SOUNDS
LIKE YOU.
I'M GONNA GET ME
A BIG CITY LOOK,
AND I'M GONNA
WIN BONNIE BACK.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GONNA
TAKE THE TORNADO?
NO, I'M IN A HURRY.
[ APPLAU ]
Red: DALTON WAS HAVING
A LITTLE RECYCLING DRIVE,
WHICH MEANS HE GETS US
TO PICK UP ALL THE CRAP
AND HE JUST KINDA PRETENDS.
SO I WASN'T
TOO MOTIVATED,
AND AFTER DALTON HAD PICKED UP
ABOUT FOUR THINGS
HE DECIDED MAYBE HE'D GO
AND GET HIMSELF A COFFEE.
SO YEAH,
SURE, WE'LL JUST --
YEAH, WE'RE HAPPY TO KEEP
WORKING ON YOUR BEHALF.
AND THANK YOU
FOR COMING OUT.
MEANWHILE, HAROLD COMES
OUT OF THE SHED THERE,
HE SAID THERE WAS SOME
KIND OF AN ANIMAL IN THERE,
AND HE WAS ALL UPSET AND ALL
EXCITED ABOUT SOMETHING,
SO BILL SAID HE'D
GO CHECK IT OUT.
CAN'T BE TOO SERIOUS.
AND I COULD JUST SMELL
A LITTLE SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW,
WE BOTH KIND OF --
IT'S FUNNY HOW YOU
HAVE ALMOST AN INSTINCT
LIKE WHEN
YOU SMELL THINGS,
AND YOU ALMOST REGRESS
BACK INTO A --
ALMOST LIKE YOU'RE
ANOTHER FORM.
SO BILL COMES OUT
AND SAYS THAT
ACTUALLY WHAT IT IS,
IS THERE'S A SKUNK.
THERE'S AN ACTUAL
SKUNK IN THE SHED.
AND, WOW,
THAT'S A BIG FELLA.
SO WE JUST KIND OF
FREEZE IN PLACE THERE,
AND OF COURSE,
WHAT YOU WANNA DO
IS NOT BE THE LEAD GUY.
SO I KINDA --
I DON'T MIND OVERSPRAY,
I JUST DON'T WANNA
TAKE THE HIT MYSELF.
AND I SEE THE CAN THERE,
AND I THINK IF WE CAN
GET THE THING INTO A CAN --
SO WE DID A
FULL MILITARY ASSAULT
ON THE SKUNK
WITH THE CANS.
AND, UH, BOY, WE CAME OUT,
I WAS PRETTY SURE I
HAD THE THING.
I HAD HER
TRAPPED IN THERE.
BILL THOUGHT HE HAD HER,
BUT I COULD SMELL IT.
I WAS PRETTY SURE
I HAD IT.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
OH.
NO, NO, NO.
HM, THOUGHT I HAD IT.
OH, YEAH.
OH, IT'S IN THERE.
OH. NO.
SO I GO BACK IN
BECAUSE WE'VE STILL GOT
THE OTHER CAN IN THERE.
OH, I GOT HER FOR SURE.
I CAN FEEL IT RUMBLING
AROUND INSIDE THE CAN.
I GOT HER THIS TIME.
WE'RE GOLD.
WE GOT IT.
OH, YOU CAN EVEN TELL,
IT'S GOT THAT BIT OF
A STINK TO IT, YOU KNOW.
WATCH THIS, TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS, BILL, SEE.
SEE, LOOK.
OH. NO.
OKAY, SO HAROLD
HAS THIS IDEA
THAT CATS DON'T LIKE TO BE
SPRAYED WITH WATER,
AND HE'S THINKING THE SKUNK
IS PART OF THE CAT FAMILY,
THE PART THAT NEVER
BATHES, I GUESS,
AND HE SAYS TO BILL,
GO WITH THE HOSE,
AND THEN WHEN YOU SEE THE
SKUNK YOU CAN JUST SQUIRT HIM,
AND JUST SIGNAL ME,
AND HE WOULD TURN ON THE TAP.
SO BILL'S LOOKIN' AROUND
FOR THE SKUNK,
AND HE SEES
THE BOARD MOVIN',
SO OKAY,
SHE'S COMIN' UP.
SO HE'S, HAROLD,
TURN ON THE TAP.
AND HAROLD OPENS
HER UP FULL BLAST.
AND BILL JUST
KIND OF DOES A BLIND SIDE,
ROUND THE CORNER --
A LITTLE HIGH FOR A SKUNK,
I'M THINKING, BILL.
A LITTLE HIGH.
THAT'S MORE SUITABLE
FOR A PERSON.
YEAH, NO --
ALL RIGHT.
SO MEANWHILE, HAROLD'S
WONDERING WHERE THE SKUNK IS,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN THE
SKUNK COMES UP BEHIND HIM,
AND HE JUMPS -- OH!
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY
WHEN YOU SEE A SKUNK
JUST TO STAY
PERFECTLY STILL.
IT DOESN'T ALWAYS WORK.
WOW, THAT'S A ROUGH DAY.
SO NOW BILL'S
SNEAKING AROUND,
HE COMES UP ON THE SKUNK,
HE'S ALL SET,
AND HE GOES TO SQUIRT
THE DARNED THING,
BUT NO WATER COMES OUT,
SO NOW HE SIGNALS HAROLD,
HAROLD, TURN ON --
UH-OH.
HAROLD, QUICK,
TURN ON THE TAP!
WELL, HAROLD'S LOOKIN'
LIKE NEW YEAR'S DAY.
OH!
SO HE COMES UP
SNEAKIN' BY ME
AND I GRAB HIM AND
GET HIM INTO THE BAG.
MEANWHILE DALTON COMES
BACK WITH HIS COFFEE CUP.
AND WHERE WOULD YOU --
THE CAN, THE PAPER?
OH, JUST CHUCK THAT
ON THE GROUND, FINE.
SO DALTON'S ASKING
FOR MY BAG.
NO, YOU DON'T
WANT THIS, DALTON.
OH, OKAY.
[ chuckles ]
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
AND THE BOYS COME BACK.
AND THEY'RE NOT
SMELLING TOO SPECIAL.
AND THEN DALTON
COMES WHEELIN' --
HOW DO YOU LIKE
YOUR COFFEE, DALTON?
YOU LIKE IT BLACK
WITH CREAM ON THE SIDE?
YOU KNOW, TO ME THERE'S
NOTHING MORE COMFORTING
THAN SITTING OUTSIDE
WITH A NEWSPAPER,
ESPECIALLY AT
A NUDIST CAMP.
BUT AS SO OFTEN
HAPPENS IN LIFE,
A LITTLE WIND
AT THE WRONG TIME
CAN REALLY KILL THE MOOD.
LUCKILY,
I HAVE A SOLUTION.
REMEMBER AEROSOL HAIRSPRAY?
THEY OUTLAWED THIS STUFF A FEW
YEARS AGO FOR SOME REASON.
NOW IT'S AS HARD
TO FIND AS THE OZONE.
I HAD A FEW CANS
TUCKED AWAY IN A DRAWER.
BUT THANKS
TO MY LUCKY HAT
AND THE BLESSING
OF MALE PATTERN BALDNESS,
I DON'T NEED IT ANYMORE.
THIS STUFF DRIES STIFFER
THAN BUSTER HADFIELD'S DRINKS.
IT'S LIKE VIAGRA FOR HAIR.
HAIRSPRAY IS GREAT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ALL
THE BIG FUSS IS AOBUT.
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
ONCE AGAIN SCIENCE
CONQUERS NATURE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, TALK ABOUT
EASY COME, EASY GO.
I BOUGHT ALL OF
BUSTER'S UNSOLD CARS,
AND THERE'S A WHACK OF 'EM.
AND THEN BERNICE TELLS ME
WE GOT NO PLACE TO
KEEP 'EM ALL,
UNLESS WE EXTEND
THE DRIVEWAY 200 FEET
RIGHT THROUGH
HER VEGETABLE GARDEN,
AND I SAID, OKAY.
BUT I MISUNDERSTOOD.
BUT IT'S KILLING ME
TO TAKE THESE CARS BACK.
I MEAN, I PAID LESS FOR THEM
THAN HAROLD'S NEW OUTFIT.
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG WHEN
YOU CAN BUY A '72 PACER
FOR THE SAME PRICE
AS A BELT.
[ WOLF WHISTLES
AND CHEERS ]
IT'S PRETTY HARD
TO WALK IN LEATHER.
YEAH.
NOW I KNOW WHY
COWS MOVE SO SLOW.
SO HAS BONNIE SEEN
YOUR NEW LOOK YET?
OH, NO, NO, NO.
BUT HER MOTHER SAYS
SHE COMES BACK FROM
PORT ASBESTOS TODAY,
SO I THOUGHT I MIGHT JUST
CRUISE INTO TOWN
A LITTLE LATER.
OH, YEAH?
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
WAIT UNTIL AFTER DARK,
AND DON'T GO ANYWHERE
NEAR THE LEGION.
[ CAR APPROACHES ]
OH, THAT'S
BONNIE'S CAR!
THAT'S BONNIE'S CAR.
OH, YOU KNOW, WHAT IF
SHE DOESN'T LIKE THIS?
WHAT IF IT'S OVER?
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
I DON'T LOOK METROSEXUAL,
I LOOK LIKE A COUCH.
[ CAR DOOR SLAMS ]
HAROLD, HAROLD, HAROLD.
IF YOU START SWEATING,
THE LEATHER WILL SHRINK,
AND YOU'LL
BE CRUSHED, OKAY.
YEAH, OKAY.
[ KNOCK AT DOOR ]
COME IN!
OKAY, NOW START
SINGING Y.M.C.A.
Red: OH, MAN.
BONNIE?!
HAROLD?!
YOU LOOK
LIKE J-LO.
YOU LIKE...
HER TOO.
WELL, THIS IS
MY NEW LOOK.
YEAH, WELL, I HEARD YOU'RE
DRIVING AROUND TOWN
IN SOME GUY'S CAR.
HA, HE'S MY COUSIN!
HE'S A
FASHION DESIGNER.
I ASKED HIM TO HELP ME
GET A NEW LOOK
FOR MY SWEETHEART.
OH, YEAH, YOUR
SWEETHEART, HE GETS A  --
I'M YOUR SWEETHEART?
THAT'S ME.
OH! HA! HA!
HERE I WAS,
I WAS ALL NERVOUS
THAT YOU WERE
LEAVING ME,
SO I TRIED TO MAKE
MYSELF MORE ATTRACTIVE.
OH, HAROLD, I COULD
NEVER FIND YOU MORE
ATTRACTIVE!
[ APPLAUSE ]
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO CHANGE.
TO CHANGE EITHER.
LET'S GO CHANGE.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
YOU TWO BETTER NOT
UNDRESS TOGETHER.
YOU'LL FORGET
WHO'S WHO.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME,
HAROLD.
YEAH, RIGHT.
AWAY YOU GO, HAROLD,
IT'S THE MEETING.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
AWAY YOU GO.
GO ON,
HAROLD, HAROLD, HAROLD!
BE CAREFUL
ON THE, UM --
[ CRASH ]
STAIRS.
Harold: YEAH, RIGHT!
OKAY.
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M NOT GOING TO TAKE THE CARS
BACK UNTIL TOMORROW MORNING,
SO IF YOU WANNA TAKE A LITTLE
TRIP DOWN MEMORY LANE,
WE'VE GOT 76 BACK SEATS
TO CHOOSE FROM.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN, SIT DOWN.
MEETING COMING TO ORDER.
SIT DOWN,
C'MON, SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY, YOU GUYS IN FRONT,
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, I'VE GOT
400 GALLONS OF GAS FOR SALE
AT 10¢ A GALLON.
ANYBODY INTERESTED?
BOY, NOTHING TURNS THESE
GUYS ON LIKE CHEAP GAS.
THEY'RE PETRO-SEXUALS.