THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF TALK
LATELY ABOUT ACCOUNTABILITY.
PEOPLE TAKING RESPONSIBILITY
FORTHEIR OWN ACTIONS.
THE MEN I KNOW DON'T
HAVE THAT PROBLEM.
WE TAKE CARE OF
THINGS OURSELVES.
WE DON'T
NEED SALES CLERKS,
WE DON'T ASK FOR DIRECTIONS,
WE DON'T BOTHER WITH DOCTORS.
I WOULD RATHER SOLVE
MY OWN PROBLEMS
THAN SUFFER THE EMBARRASSMENT
OF HAVING TO EXPLAIN
TO A TOTAL STRANGER WHY
THE BARBECUE LID
IS ON THE ROOF
OF THE CHURCH.
IT'S NOT SMART OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT MAKES US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red: ON TODAY'S SHOW, BILL
TURNS NATURE INTO ART
DOING SOME
CHAINSAW SCULPTING;
HAROLD FINALLY FINDS A JOB
SUITED TO HIS UNIQUE ABILITIES;
WINSTON HAS LOST SOME
OF HIS ENTHUSIASM
FOR THE SEWAGE
SUCKING BUSINESS;
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW
TO MAKE A CAR INTO A TANK.
AND NOW HERE IS THE OLDEST
HUMAN BEING STILL HOSTING
HIS OWN TELEVISION SHOW,
AT LEAST, YOU KNOW, AT THIS
POINT IN TIME AND
IN THIS AREA,
MY UNCLE RED GREEN!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AND HERE IS OLDEST
HUMAN BEING
WHO'S NEVER HAD A DATE IN ANY
AREA, MY NEPHEW HAROLD.
HAVING A BIT OF
TROUBLE RIGHT NOW
WITH STINKY PETERSON'S TRABANT.
WELL, HE BETTER GET THAT LOOKED
AT BECAUSE THAT COULD FESTER.
HAROLD, A TRABANT IS
A CAR, NOT A BODY PART.
OH YEAH. OH YEAH.
OKAY. RIGHT.
NO, I KNEW THAT.
I FORGOT.
YOU SHOULD EXPLAIN THAT A
TRABANT IS AN EAST GERMAN CAR.
IT WAS MADE IN
WHAT WAS EAST GERMANY,
BUT IS NOW
EASTERN GERMANY.
AND NOT THE GREATEST
AUTOMOBILE EVER MADE.
ONE OF THE REASONS THE
BERLIN WALL CAME DOWN
WAS SO THEY COULD
GET THE TOW TRUCKS THROUGH.
I GUESS THE REAL GOOD
COMMUNIST SCIENTISTS
WERE WORKING ON
ROCKETS AND TANKS
AND WOMEN ATHLETES.
ANYWAY, STINKY HAD RUN
THE BATTERY WAY DOWN
ON THE TRABANT
FROM LISTENING TO THE RADIO,
'CAUSE THOSE TUBES REALLY SUCK
THE JUICE OUT OF HER THERE,
AND HIS GIRLFRIEND WANTED
TO GO INTO TOWN,
SO HE JUST GAVE HER A LITTLE
PUSH START AND SENT HER
MERRILY ON HER WAY.
BUT SHE DIDN'T
MAKE IT, DID SHE?
SHE WAS OKAY TILL SHE
GOT TO THE HILL.
I THINK IF SHE HAD
BACKED UP IT...
BUT, ANYWAY,
SHE STALLED HER,
AND NOW WE GOT TO GO DOWN
THERE AND RESTART IT.
WELL, I THINK SHE'S QUITE
CAPABLE OF HANDLING THE
SITUATION HERSELF.
SHE DOES NOT NEED YOU
TO GO DOWN THERE AND
RESCUE HER.
SHE SHOULD JUST CALL
FLINTY McCLINTOCK.
HE'S GOT THAT
EMERGENCY ROAD SERVICE.
NO, HAROLD, IT'S STINKY'S
GIRLFRIEND THAT CAUSED
THE PROBLEM,
AND STINKY'S
GOT SOLVE IT, NOT FLINTY.
IT'S A GUY THING.
THAT IS JUST
STUPID CHAUVINISM.
WELL, STUPID CHAUVINISM
IS A GUY THING TOO.
SHE'S TWICE AS CAPABLE OF
HANDLING IT THAN STINKY IS.
YOU KNOW, PLUS FLINTY
IS SLOWER CLOSER.
FACE REALITY, UNCLE RED,
SHE SHOULD JUST CALL FLINTY.
FLINTY CHARGES FIVE BUCKS.
OOOOOOH.
OH A BULLET COMES OUT
THE END OF A GUN
LIKE A ROCKETSHIP HURTLING
THROUGH SPACE
IT TRAVELS MUCH FASTER
THAN ANIMALS RUN
BUT IT DOESN'T GO TO MARS
OR REALLY FAR PLACE LIKE
THAT, YOU KNOW
WELL I PREFER ROCKETS
TO BULLETS
BULLETS
BECAUSE THEY MAKE A
SOUND THAT PEOPLE CAN HEAR
AND A ROCKET WON'T
RICOCHET OFF A BOULDER
DO A U-TURN AND TAKE
OFF YOUR EAR
OKAY, IT'S SATURDAY
AFTERNOON
AND YOU HAVE SPENT THE
LAST FIVE MINUTES ALIGNING
THE LUMPS IN THE COUCH
WITH THE DENTS IN YOUR
RECLINING BODY,
AS YOU SETTLE DOWN FOR
AN AFTERNOON WITH
THE THREE ALs,
ALCOHOL, CHOLESTEROL,
FOOTBALL.
THEN THE LITTLE
MISSUS COMES IN.
AS RUMPOLE WOULD SAY,
SHE WHO MUST BE
OKAYED, EH?
AND SHE'S GOT REARRANGING
THE FURNITURE ON HER MIND
WHICH INVOLVES YOU
IN A BIG WAY.
ALL RIGHT, YOU MIGHT
POSSIBLY HAVE A NEGATIVE
REACTION TO THIS,
BUT I THINK IT MIGHT BE
TIME TO LOOK AT IT IN
A MORE MATURE WAY.
YEAH, LIKE, YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE PROBABLY
GOING TO SAY,
NO, NO, THE ROOM
LOOKS FINE, EH,
WHEN REALLY YOU JUST WANT
TO GET BACK TO WATCHING
THE GAME.
SO SHE LEAVES THE ROOM.
OKAY.
THIS IS A TRAP.
IT'S A REAL "CATCH-23."
YEAH. YEAH.
BECAUSE SHE KNOWS
THE ROOM LOOKS BAD.
SHE WAS GOING TO TRY
TO FIX IT THE CHEAP WAY
BY JUST REARRANGING
THE JUNK YOU HAVE
TO COVER THE DENTS
AND STAINS AND HOLES.
BUT NOW THAT YOU
HAVE REFUSED,
SHE IS LEGALLY ENTITLED
TO GO OUT AND BUY
NEW STUFF, EH?
SO SUDDENLY THIS IS GOING
TO BE THE MOST EXPENSIVE
FOOTBALL GAME
YOU NEVER EVEN WENT TO.
YEAH.
LUCKILY, YOU CAN SOLVE THE
PROBLEM WITH AN OUNCE OF
PREVENTION, ALL RIGHT?
TAKE A FEW HOURS,
SPEND A FEW BUCKS,
PUT EVERYTHING YOU
OWN ON CASTERS.
OH, YEAH, NOW YOU CAN
WHIP THE STUFF AROUND
THERE REAL EASILY,
REAL QUICKLY, IN ABOUT
THE SAME DURATION AS,
LIKE, A HALF-TIME
SHOW, EH?
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN JUST MOVE THAT
CRAP AROUND FOR 20 YEARS
BEFORE YOU HAVE TO
BUY ANYTHING NEW.
ONE CAUTION, THOUGH,
MAKE SURE THE FLOOR
IS IS LEVEL;
OTHERWISE, YOU GO LAY
DOWN ON THAT COUCH
TO WATCH TV,
YOU'RE GOING TO GO
ROLLING RIGHT DOWN
THE BASEMENT STAIRS
FOLLOWED BY THE
DINETTE SET AND THE
ENTERTAINMENT CENTRE!
AND YOUR WIFE MAY
NOT EVEN MISS YOU.
BUT SHE WILL
MISS THE COUCH.
YOU KNOW, WITH STINKY
PETERSON'S GIRLFRIEND
GETTING THE CAR STUCK,
IT KIND OF STRUCK A NERVE
BECAUSE THERE IS NOTHING
MORE EMBARRASSING FOR A GUY
THAN TO HAVE HIS
VEHICLE IMMOBILIZED.
WELL, THERE IS ONE THING
MORE EMBARRASSING,
BUT THEY TELL ME THAT'S
JUST A NORMAL PART OF
GETTING OLDER.
SO I THOUGHT I WOULD TAKE
THIS WEEK'S HANDYMAN CORNER
AND SHOW YOU HOW YOU CAN MAKE
YOUR CAR LESS VULNERABLE
TO SINK HOLES,
MUD SLIDES, AVALANCHES
AND QUICKSAND.
TO BE ABLE TO GOT WHERE
ANGELS FEAR TO GO TREAD,
YOU NEED ONE HELL OF
A TREAD, A TANK TREAD.
HERE IS AN IDEA SO SIMPLE
YOU'LL WONDER WHY YOU
NEVER THOUGHT OF IT.
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW
TO TURN YOUR CAR INTO A TANK.
THE FIRST THING YOU'RE
GOING TO NEED IS A ROLL
OF SNOW FENCE,
SOME TIN SNIPS AND A
NORMAL METAL TIN BOX
AND AN AXE.
STEP ONE, YOU WANT TO CUT
THE EMERGENCY BRAKE CABLES
ON THE LEFT SIDE
OF THE VEHICLE.
THERE WE GO.
NOW THE EMERGENCY BRAKE IS
ONLY GOING TO WORK THE WHEELS
ON THE RIGHT SIDE OF THE CAR,
SO WHAT WE GOT TO DO NOW IS
DISCONNECT THE BRAKE LINES
FROM THE RIGHT
SIDE OF CAR,
AND THEN WHEN YOU STEP
ON THE BRAKE PEDAL,
IT WILL ONLY WORK THE WHEELS
ON THE LEFT SIDE OF THE CAR.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS PART,
AND IT'S A VERY BAD SIGN.
NOW, TO DO THAT YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED A 7/16 WRENCH.
NO, THAT'S A HALF INCH.
YEAH, THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT, YOU DISCONNECT
THEM RIGHT DOWN TO THE
WHEEL CYLINDER.
[ GRUNTING ]
BOY, THESE BABIES ARE
REALLY ON THERE.
RUST CLUMPS THE SIZE
OF HORSE BUNS.
[ BOING! ]
OKAY, I DON'T KNOW WHY
I'M BEING SO FINICKY.
I MEAN, THE GOAL IS JUST
TO DISCONNECT THE BRAKE LINES.
NOBODY SAYS WE HAVE TO
UNSCREW THEM OFF THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, YOU GOT TO HAVE
ROOM FOR THE TANK TREAD
TO MOVE FREELY
AROUND THE CAR,
SO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO IS
YOU GOT CUT OFF THE FRONT
HALF OF THE FRONT FENDER
AND THE BACK HALF
OF THE BACK FENDER,
AND YOU CAN DO THAT WITH,
WELL, JUST AN ORDINARY HACKSAW.
[ PANTING ]
I'LL TELL YOU, THEY HAVEN'T
INVENTED THE CAR THAT
I CAN'T CUSTOMIZE.
THERE WE GO.
NOW, YOU'RE READY FOR
YOUR TANK TREAD.
AND FOR THAT YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED A TANK TREAD,
WHICH YOU CAN BUY THROUGH AN
ARMY SURPLUS MAGAZINE,
OR YOU CAN MAKE ONE OUT
OF AN ESCALATOR.
IF YOU'RE NOT
MADE OF MONEY,
I SUGGEST YOU JUST
GO WITH A SNOW FENCE.
NOW, THE SNOW FENCE IS
TWICE AS WIDE AS YOU NEED,
SO YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
TO CUT HER IN HALF,
WHICH YOU CAN DO WITH A
NORMAL HOUSEHOLD HACKSAW.
OR AN AXE.
OKAY, YOU SEE THE
PROBLEM HERE --
I'M SURPRISED YOU DIDN'T
THINK OF THIS EARLIER,
YOU NEED SOMETHING
TO USE AS GUIDES
TO KEEP THE TREAD
UP ABOVE THE ROOF.
MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING
IN THE TRUNK.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
OH, I DON'T HAVE TO GO
TO ALL THAT TROUBLE, DO I?
NO, IT'S AN OLD SET
OF GOLF CLUBS.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I GOT AN IDEA.
I ALWAYS SAID MY IDEAS
ARE WAY ABOVE PAR.
WELL, SHE'S READY
TO ROLL, HUH?
WHEN I WANT TO TURN LEFT,
I JUST STEP ON THE
BRAKE PEDAL,
WHEN I WANT TO TURN RIGHT,
I STEP ON THE EMERGENCY.
I DON'T EVEN NEED A MAP
OF WHERE I'M GOING,
ALL'S I NEED ARE
THE COORDINATES.
SO REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
LET'S SEE HOW SHE HANDLES.
Red: STAY TUNED TO SEE WHAT
HAPPENS TO BILL WHEN THE
CHIPS HIT THE FAN,
AND THEN GLEN IS GOING
TO LET ME HELP OUT
AT THE MARINA,
NICE OF HIM.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU ALL YOU
MIDDLE AGED GUYS ABOUT
FADING URGES.
YOU KNOW THAT SENSE THAT
YOU'RE MAYBE NOT
THE PASSIONATE LOVER
YOU ONCE WERE --
AT LEAST THE WAY
YOU TELL IT.
OKAY, SO MAYBE YOU'VE CHANGED
FROM BEING A YOUNG STAG
EAGER TO RUT
INTO AN OLD DRAG
STUCK IN A RUT.
WELL, THIS IS A GOOD THING
BECAUSE THERE'S LESS CHANCE
THAT YOU'LL BE A FATHER
AT A TIME WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE
THE PATIENCE, ENERGY
OR BRAIN POWER
TO HELP WITH HOMEWORK.
AND THERE'S ANOTHER UPSIDE
TO LOSS OF YOUR SEX DRIVE,
AND THAT IS THAT THIS MEANS
ONCE OR TWICE A WEEK,
FOR MAYBE TWO OR
THREE MINUTES AT A TIME,
YOU'LL ACTUALLY BE ABLE TO
CONCENTRATE ON SOMETHING ELSE,
LIKE, SAY, YOUR JOB.
YOU REALIZE THAT MOST OF
LIFE'S GREAT DISCOVERIES
WERE DONE BY GUYS
WHO WERE OLD?
LIKE COLONEL SANDERS,
HE WAS ALMOST RETIRED
BEFORE HE GOT THE INSPIRATION
TO DEDICATE HIS LIFE
TO FRIED CHICKEN.
AND WHAT ABOUT THAT 70-YEAR-OLD
TELEVISION PRODUCER
AARON SPELLING?
I'LL TELL YOU, NOBODY WHO
WAS SEXUALLY ACTIVE
WOULD HAVE COME UP WITH A
CONCEPT LIKE "THE LOVE BOAT."
SO I SAY JUST ACCEPT YOUR
DECLINING DESIRES.
YOUR WIFE IS PROBABLY
JUST AS HAPPY TO READ IN BED,
AND THIS WAY YOU GET TO SEE
THE END OF THE HOCKEY GAME
EVEN IF THERE'S OVERTIME.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU
'CAUSE WE ARE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, WE RAN INTO A SNAG
TRYING TO JUMP START
STINKY'S TRABANT.
WENT DOWN THERE
IN STINKY'S TRUCK,
AND THE BATTERY IN THAT
THING IS IN NO GREAT
SHAKES EITHER,
BECAUSE HE HAD
A CRACK IN IT,
AND HE KEPT TOPPING
IT UP WITH VINEGAR.
SO THEN HE FIGURES IF HE
GETS THE TRUCK REAL CLOSE
THAT WILL WORK
'CAUSE THE ELECTRICITY WON'T
HAVE TO TRAVEL AS FAR.
THAT WON'T MAKE
ANY DIFFERENCE.
WELL, I KNOW THAT,
HAROLD,
BUT THEN I'M NOT STUPID,
AND NOBODY CALLS ME
STINKY, DO THEY?
IF YOU SAY SO.
SO STINKY --
STINKY DROVE HIS TRUCK AROUND
THE OTHER SIDE OF THE TRABANT
AND HE GOT THE REAR WHEELS
STUCK IN A SINK HOLE
LIKE ONE OF THEM MUDBATHS
THAT RICH PEOPLE GO TO
TO SEE WHAT IT FEELS
LIKE TO BE DIRTY.
SO NOW HE'S GOT HIS CAR
AND HIS TRUCK STUCK AT
THE SIDE OF THE ROAD?
HAVE YOU GOT FLINTY'S
EMERGENCY PHONE NUMBER
BECAUSE I'LL LEND
YOU THE $5.
IT'S NOT THE MONEY, HAROLD,
NOT TOTALLY.
WE'RE MEN,
WE HAVE PRIDE.
STINKY'S GIRLFRIEND CAUSED
THE PROBLEM,
IT'S UP TO STINKY
TO SOLVE IT.
IS SHE STILL STUCK AT
THE SIDE OF THE ROAD?
WELL, ACTUALLY, NO,
SHE GOT A RIDE INTO TOWN
WITH A PASSING VEHICLE,
FLINTY'S ROAD
EMERGENCY THING.
OH, THIS IS GOOD.
SO NOW HE'S LOST HIS CAR,
HIS TRUCK AND HIS GIRLFRIEND.
YEAH, BUT HE'S STILL
GOT HIS PRIDE.
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
CALL ME IF YOU GOT A GUSHER
AND CAN'T FLUSHER,
1-800-555-SUCK.
Red: NOW, HERE WE ARE AT
BRAXTON'S MARINA
WITH OWNER/OPERATOR
GLEN BRAXTON.
HOW ARE YOU
TODAY, GLEN?
ON THE ROAD TO
RECOVERY, RED.
FEELING BETTER THAN I DID
BEFORE THE HEART ATTACKS.
GREAT.
CUT WAY BACK ON
THE DRINKING,
QUIT SMOKING, YOU KNOW.
YEAH, AND I GUESS THE
CHOCOLATE ECLAIRS
WITH THE DOUBLE
WHIPPED CREAM ON TOP
ARE PRETTY MUCH A THING
OF THE PAST, ARE THEY NOT?
WELL, ONE STEP
AT A TIME, RED.
WELL, TODAY WE'RE GOING
TO LEARN HOW TO PULL A
BOAT OUT OF THE WATER.
WHAT WE GOT TO DO IS WE
GOT TO HOOK THIS BOAT WINCH
ON TO THAT LITTLE RING
THERE ON THE BOTTOM.
YEAH.
HERE YOU GO, RED.
ME?
ON, YEAH, SINCE THE
HEART ATTACK, RED,
I CAN'T GET TOO CLOSE
TO THE WATER.
ALL RIGHT.
BOY, IT SURE IS ODD
TO LOOK AT THE BOAT
RAMP THERE
AND NOT SEE YOUR OLD
R.V. SITTING IN IT,
I'LL TELL YOU.
WELL, LIFE IS FULL
OF CHOICES, RED.
I HAD THE BUSINESS,
I HAD THE FAMILY,
HAD THE R.V.
I COULDN'T KEEP THEM ALL.
OTHER PEOPLE DO.
OH WELL, I GUESS.
BUT OTHER PEOPLE DON'T
HAVE SEVEN DAUGHTERS
THAT NEVER WEAR
HAND-ME-DOWNS EVER.
GOT 'ER.
GREAT.
YOU CAN CRANK
HER UP, RED.
OH MAN.
I TELL YOU ONE THING,
THOUGH, GLEN,
I THINK THESE HARD TIMES
HAVE BEEN GOOD FOR YOU.
OH 'ABSOTUTELY,' RED.
YEAH.
MY PRIORITIES ARE
BACK IN LINE.
NEVER MIND THE FACT,
YOU KNOW,
MY ENTREPRENEURIAL
OPPORTUNITIES
ON THE LAKE.
I'M THE ONLY MARINA.
YEAH.
KEEPS THE MARGIN
IN LINE.
SURE.
YOU KNOW, I'M WONDERING IF
THIS BOAT WINCH WOULD BE
STRONG ENOUGH
TO PULL, SAY, A COUPLE
OF TRUCKS OUT OF THE MUD?
OH I GOT THREE-TONNE
BLOCK AND TACKLE UP
BEHIND THE HOUSE.
YOU CAN -- I CAN RENT
IT TO YOU
OR YOU CAN
BORROW IT FOR MONEY,
WHATEVER YOU LIKE.
YEAH, WELL, WE'LL WORK
SOMETHING OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S GOT HER.
SHOULD WE HAVE DONE
SOMETHING
TO MAKE SURE THE BOAT IS ON
THERE STRAIGHT, DO YOU THINK?
OH, NO RED, NO, NO,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT THAT.
IF IT'S NOT, YOU JUST
DROP HER BACK IN,
AND YOU TRY IT
ALL OVER AGAIN.
IT'S ONLY 25 BUCKS A
SHOT FOR THE RAMP, SO...
FINE, THANKS A LOT FOR
YOUR HELP THERE, GLEN.
MY PLEASURE TO BE
OF SERVICE, RED.
OH, RED, BY THE WAY,
HOW ARE WE GOING
TO PAY FOR THIS?
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU LEND ME
THE BLOCK AND TACKLE,
AND WE'LL JUST
CALL IT EVEN?
UNCLE RED, WHY DO YOU
THINK KIDS GO BAD?
WELL, MAYBE THEY'VE BEEN
LEFT OUT IN THE SUN
TOO LONG.
NO, I MEAN, LIKE,
YOU KNOW,
DO YOU SUBSCRIBE
TO THE NATURE OR
NURTURE THEORY?
OH, YOU MEAN DO I BLAME
THE KIDS' PARENTS
OR JUST ALL
PARENTS EVERYWHERE?
YEAH, EXACTLY.
WELL, SORT OF
WHAT I MEAN, YEAH,
BECAUSE LIKE NATURE SAYS
WE ARE WHAT WE INHERIT
FROM OUR PARENTS;
WHEREAS, NURTURE SAYS
WE'RE SHAPED BY
SOCIAL FACTORS.
SO IF A KID'S BAD
THEY SAY IT'S NATURE,
OR IF A KID'S BAD
THEY SAY IT'S NURTURE.
WELL, I KIND OF GO WITH
THE THEORY OF "NOT YER."
NOT YER?
YEAH, IF THERE'S
A PROBLEM WITH A KID,
YOU SAY IT'S
NOT YER KID.
UNCLE RED, I WAS HOPING YOU
WOULD TAKE IT A LITTLE MORE
SERIOUSLY THAN THAT.
WELL, IT'S
NOT YER PROBLEM.
IT IS IF I WANT TO DISCUSS
MATTERS OF IMPORTANCE.
IT'S NOT YER SHOW.
OKAY, GOOD POINT.
Red: TIME FOR
ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
BILL HAS BEEN UP A TREE
WITH A CHAIN SAW,
WHICH IS APPARENTLY
ONE OF HIS HOBBIES.
HOW ARE YOU
DOING THERE, BILL?
ABOUT THE SAME I GUESS.
AND WHAT HE'S GOING
TO SHOW US TODAY
IS HOW TO DO SOMETHING THAT'S
KIND OF MIXING ART
WITH THE HANDYMAN THING
OR AN OUTDOORSMAN
OR A LUMBERJACK
WHAT HAVE YOU.
AND THIS IS ACTUALLY
SCULPTING USING A CHAIN SAW.
HE'S GOING TO -- I'M NOT SURE
LEAVING A LIT OIL LAMP
OUT IN THE WOODS
IS THE GREATEST IDEA.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW HERE'S A SAFETY TIP.
YOU GOT TO PUT YOUR FOOT
ON TOP OF THE CHAIN SAW
WHEN YOU START IT.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S AN
IMPORTANT SAFETY TIP,
ESPECIALLY WITH THE GUY
STANDING BEHIND YOU.
THE OTHER THING
IS WATCH OUT, DON'T --
WELL, THERE'S SO MANY
SAFETY TIPS THERE TODAY
IT'S REALLY HARD TO
IDENTIFY ALL OF THEM
WITHOUT BORING OURSELVES
BEYOND HUMAN BELIEF.
ANYWAY, BILL COMES BACK,
GOT THE CHAIN SAW RUNNING.
NOW HE'S USING THE ARTIST
LEONARDO DA VINCI
APPROACH THERE.
HE'S KIND OF THUMBING
IT UP, AS WE SAY,
THUMBING IT UP.
YEAH, BILL.
AND HE'S GOING TO TRY TO --
SEEMS LIKE AN AWFUL THING
TO DO TO A TREE, BUT ANYWAY.
BILL IS GOING TO TRY TO --
MAYBE I'M STANDING A
LITTLE TOO CLOSE MYSELF.
ANOTHER SAFETY TIP THERE.
AND I GUESS THAT WOULD
BE AN OIL LAMP.
BOY.
THAT WILL BURN FOR
A WHILE THERE,
IT'S A PRETTY
GOOD SIZE STUMP.
NOW BILL ASKED ME TO TAKE
THE OIL LAMP AND PUT HER DOWN.
HE'S GOT KIND OF A LITTLE
TOY PARROT THING THERE
THAT WILL SIT
UP ON THERE.
I GUESS HE'S GOING TO NOW
TRY TO CARVE US SOMETHING
THAT LOOKS LIKE --
IS THAT A PARROT?
YEAH, THAT'S A PARROT.
THAT TREE DOESN'T LOOK MUCH
LIKE A PARROT TO ME,
BUT HE'S THUMBING
HER UP AGAIN.
WHEN IT COMES TO
THUMBING THINGS UP,
BILL IS ABOUT AVERAGE.
EXTRA TWIGS IN THERE MADE
IT A LITTLE SPECIAL.
I'M AN ART CRITIC MYSELF.
YEAH, PERFECT.
NOW HE'S GOT SOMETHING
REAL SPECIAL.
HE WANTS ME TO DO ONE OF
MY MANLY POSES
THAT I WAS GOING TO DO IN THE
MR. OUTDOOR UNIVERSE CONTEST
IF I EVER LOOKED GOOD.
AND HE'S TRYING TO PICK A
TREE THAT HE THINKS --
FOR SOME REASON OR OTHER HE
DIDN'T THINK THAT TREE WAS
GOING TO DO IT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT
WAS ABOUT THE TREE,
IT LOOKED PERFECTLY
FINE TO ME,
BUT I GUESS HE FELT THIS TREE
HERE MIGHT BE A LITTLE
BIT BETTER.
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETHING ABOUT IT --
OH I SEE.
ALL RIGHT.
SO ANYWAY, HE'S CUTTING
AWAY THERE.
AND AS HE STARTED -- I THINK
HE STARTED WITH THE
TORSO ON THAT.
BOY, YOU CAN GENERATE QUITE
A FEW WOOD SHAVINGS AND SMOKE.
SOMETIMES IF YOU
OIL THE CHAIN SAWS,
THEY DON'T HEAT UP
QUITE SO BAD.
THERE HE GOES.
HE GOT HER ALL DONE.
I BELIEVE THAT'S JUST
THE SHAVINGS.
NOW HE'S --
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
HE WANTS TO SHOW ME
WHAT HE'S DONE.
LET'S HAVE A LOOK AT THIS.
THAT'S A PRETTY
AGGRESSIVE AMBITION.
HOLY MACKEREL!
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS, BILL!
NO, NO, I CAN'T FOOL YOU,
THIS ISN'T THE SCULPTURE.
THIS IS WAYNE FRASER,
WINNER OF THE VERY FIRST
RED GREEN
LOOK-A-LIKE CONTEST.
Red: STAY TUNED.
WINSTON HAS GOT ONE OF HIS
DARNED SELF-HELP TAPES FOR YOU
AND THE BOYS AND I ARE GOING
TO TRY AND HOIST A FEW.
"WINTER SURPRISE," BY ME.
"I TOBOGGAN IN THE WINTER
COLD THE WHOLE AFTERNOON,
"THEN I STAGGER INDOORS TO
THE WARMTH OF THE FIRE.
"AS I PEEL OFF MY
PARKA AND BOOTS,
"A WHITE FROZEN LUMP FALLS OUT
OF MY TOQUE AND SKITTERS
ACROSS THE FLOOR.
"IS IT A SNOWBALL?
A LUMP OF ICE?
"A PINE CONE?
"ONLY, NO,
IT'S MY LEFT EAR.
"I FEEL I SHOULD
GO PAINT SOMETHING.
"PERHAPS THE SHED."
THE EARTH IS AN
AMAZING THING, ISN'T IT?
OUT THERE IN THE FOREST IS A
PATCH OF MUD CAN'T BE MORE
THAN FIVE FEET ACROSS,
AND WE'VE GOT 17 VEHICLES,
NINE POWER TOOLS AND A
MULE STUCK IN IT.
AND COUNTING.
NO, NO, HAROLD,
WE'RE GETTING
SERIOUS NOW.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE THIS
POWER WINCH OUT THERE,
HOOK HER UP TO THE BIG OAK
TREE ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE STREET
AND JUST WINCH EVERYTHING
OUT OF THERE.
UNCLE RED, THAT IS SUCH
A FALSE ECONOMY.
I MEAN, FOR 5 BUCKS FLINTY
WOULD HAVE COME AND STARTED
STINKY'S CAR,
AND THE WHOLE THING WOULD
HAVE BEEN DONE WITH,
BUT INSTEAD LOOK AT ALL
THE MONEY YOU'VE SQUANDERED.
WE HAVE SQUANDERED
ZERO, HAROLD.
EVERYBODY PROVIDED
THEIR OWN VEHICLES,
AND WE ALL OWN THE TOOLS
AND THE MULE WAS STOLEN,
WHERE'S THE FALSE ECONOMY?
OKAY, WELL, ALL RIGHT,
WHAT ABOUT ALL THE GAS
YOU BURNED?
AND WHAT ABOUT YOUR TIME?
WHAT IS YOUR TIME WORTH?
WHAT DOES A PROFESSIONAL
INCOMPETENT CHARGE?
ZERO, HAROLD.
WE DON'T CHARGE PEOPLE
FOR HAVING FUN.
THAT'S A MUCH OLDER
PROFESSION THAN ANY
OF OURS.
BUT STILL, BUT STILL,
STINKY COULD HAVE HAD THE
TRABANT GOING FOR 5 BUCKS.
STINKY CAN REPLACE
THE TRABANT FOR 5 BUCKS.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO,
YOU CANNOT BUY A NEW
TRABANT FOR $5.
YOU CAN BUY STINKY'S AS IS,
WHERE IS, HOW IS.
NO CHANCE IS.
WELL, THEN FINE,
EXCUSE ME,
I GOT AN APPOINTMENT
WITH A BIG OAK TREE.
UNCLE RED, THAT'S WHAT
THE BATHROOM'S FOR.
I'LL TELL YOU, WINSTON,
WITH THE POWER IN THIS RIG,
WE'LL HAVE EVERYBODY OUT
OF THE DITCH AND HOME
FOR SUPPER.
LET'S GO.
RED... I CAN'T.
WHAT, DID YOU LOSE
THE KEYS?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
I KNOW HOW TO HOT-WIRE
THESE THINGS.
RED, WE CAN'T USE
THE TRUCK.
I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
WHEN I BROKE INTO
THIS SLUDGE SUCKING
BUSINESS, RED,
I MADE MYSELF ONE PROMISE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT
PROMISE WAS?
ALWAYS WASH YOUR HANDS
BEFORE LUNCH?
NO.
I JUST MADE A PROMISE TO
MYSELF TO ONLY USE THIS
TRUCK TO MAKE MONEY.
YOU MAY FIND THIS
HARD TO BELIEVE,
BUT I HAVE NEVER ONCE USED
THIS TRUCK FOR PLEASURE,
JUST BUSINESS.
SO YOU WON'T HELP
A FRIEND IN NEED?
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT
ANTHONY ANTHONY SAYS
ABOUT THAT, EH?
OH MAN, NOT THAT SUCCEED
THROUGH SUCCESS BOZO ON
T.V. AT NIGHT.
HEY, WAIT
A MINUTE, RED,
ANTHONY ANTHONY JUST HAPPENS
TO BE FINANCIAL ADVISOR
TO FLORENCE HENDERSON,
GAVIN McLEOD AND A
HOST OF OTHER IMPORTANT
HOLLYWOOD CELEBRITIES
WHO JUST LOVE TO POP IN
ON HIS INFOMERCIALS
AND SAY HELLO.
YOU KNOW
WHAT HE SAYS, EH?
HE SAYS THAT A FRIEND
IN NEED IS A CUSTOMER.
YOU GOT TO HEAR IT,
IT'S REALLY GOOD.
I'M NOT GOING
TO LISTEN TO THAT.
SO WHAT DOES ANTHONY ANTHONY
HAVE TO SAY ABOUT PUBLIC
RELATIONS
AND COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT?
I DON'T KNOW, IT WAS ON
THE OTHER SIDE OF
THAT TAPE.
I WAS GOING TO LISTEN
TO IT TONIGHT.
HOLY.
WELL, I GOT TO TELL YOU,
A BLOCK AND TACKLE IS
ONE POWERFUL TOOL.
DID YOU GET ALL THE
VEHICLES OUT OF THE MUD?
DON'T GET AHEAD
OF ME, HAROLD.
WE HOOKED EVERYTHING UP TO
THE BIG OAK TREE ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE ROAD THERE,
AND WE STARTED
WINCHING IT.
WE WINCHED AND WE WINCHED
AND WE WINCHED,
AND NOT ONE VEHICLE MOVED.
WELL, THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE,
SOMETHING HAD TO HAVE MOVED.
YOU'RE RIGHT, HAROLD.
THE OAK TREE COME RIGHT
ACROSS THE ROAD,
ROOT BALL AND ALL.
SO THEN WE FIGURED, GEE,
IF WE HAD ENOUGH EXTRA CHAIN,
WE COULD PROBABLY
HOOK THE WHOLE RIG UP TO
BUSTER HADFIELD'S HOUSE.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
BUSTER HADFIELD'S HOUSE IS
QUITE A DISTANCE FROM
THAT FOREST.
NOT ANYMORE.
NO, BY THE TIME WE
GOT DONE WITH HER,
HIS HOUSE WAS RIGHT IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE VEHICLES.
LOOKED GOOD TOO, THE CAR AND
TRUCKS ARE KIND OF LIKE
LAWN ORNAMENTS THERE.
OF COURSE, HE HAD THE
BIG OAK, WHICH IS NICE.
UNCLE RED, IT'S OKAY TO
DAMAGE YOUR OWN JUNK,
BUT YOU GOT TO REPLACE
EVERYTHING ELSE.
TO LIFT EVERYTHING BACK
TO WHERE IT'S SUPPOSED TO GO.
OHHHHHH.
WELL, ISN'T IT LUCKY THAT
YOU DIDN'T PHONE EARLIER?
HE WOULD HAVE MADE A MERE $5
REMOVING JUST THE ONE VEHICLE.
YEAH, HE FIGURES HE'S
GOING TO MAKE ENOUGH MONEY
TO PAY FOR THE WEDDING.
WEDDING?
HE'S GOING TO MARRY STINKY'S
GIRLFRIEND, RIGHT?
WELL, WE DON'T CALL HER
STINKY'S GIRLFRIEND ANYMORE.
WE CALL HER FLINTY'S
FIANCéE NOW.
SO LET ME JUST SEE THEN.
SO WHAT STINKY HAS TO
SHOW FOR HIS FOOLISH PRIDE
IS MERELY A MUD COVERED
BROKEN DOWN TRABANT.
NO, NOT EVEN THAT.
HE'S GIVING HER THAT
FOR A WEDDING PRESENT,
SO HE'S GETTING SOME
REVENGE IN THERE.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, IT'S MEETING
TIME, UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD,
HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN AFTER I
GET CLEANED UP.
OKAY.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND YOU KNOW HOW YOU ALWAYS
WANTED THAT MUD ROOM?
WELL, I THINK TONIGHT'S
YOUR LUCKY NIGHT.
HOPEFULLY,
IT WILL BE MINE TOO.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
AND ON BEHALF OF HAROLD
AND MYSELF, UNTIL NEXT
TIME AROUND,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.