YOU KNOW, SOMETHING
WEIRD HAPPENS TO A MAN
WHENEVER HE GOES
TO A SPORTING EVENT.
LIKE TAKE THIS LITTLE
PRACTICAL ITEM HERE.
WHEN THE GAME'S OVER WHAT
EXACTLY DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GONNA DO
WITH A GIANT FINGER?
I SUPPOSE YOU COULD
GIVE IT YOUR WIFE,
BUT I HAVE A FEELING
YOU'D GET ONE RIGHT BACK.
HERE'S A BETTER IDEA...
NEXT TIME YOU'RE
CLEANING YOUR VEHICLE,
THINK ABOUT THOSE
HARD-TO-REACH PLACES
THAT YOUR REGULAR
SPONGE JUST CAN'T GET AT.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE GRILL,
OR AROUND THE TIRE RIM
OR EVEN UP
THE TAIL PIPE,
BUT BE CAREFUL THERE, EH.
AND WHEN IT COMES
TO THE REAL DETAIL WORK,
LIKE AROUND
THESE DOOR FRAMES,
HEY, IT'S TIME TO
GET SERIOUS
AND CALL IN A PACKERS FAN.
[ SPONGE SQUEAKING ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
YEAH, APPRECIATE IT.
BOY, BEEN A WACKY WEEK
UP AT THE LODGE HERE.
GOT A COMIC BOOK
CONVENTION IN THE AREA.
WHAT A BUNCH OF WEIRDOS!
IT'S LIKE A HORROR MOVIE...
NIGHT OF A THOUSAND HAROLDS.
I WOULDN'T EVEN
BE HANGING AROUND,
BUT I GOT THIS COMIC BOOK,
AQUAMAN NUMBER 1.
HAD IT SINCE I WAS A KID.
I FIGURE I COULD SELL IT
TO ONE OF THE DELEGATES.
PROBABLY GET LIKE
100 BUCKS FOR IT.
ONE OF THE UPSIDES
OF THE COMPUTER AGE
IS NERDS HAVE MONEY NOW.
UNCLE RED!
LOOK WHAT JUST ARRIVED!
WELL, NOW,
THAT'S EXCITING.
A CARDBOARD BOX, EH?
IT'S A COSTUME FOR OUR GUEST
SPEAKER WHO ARRIVES TOMORROW,
AND THE DELEGATES ARE GONNA
FREAK OUT WHEN THEY SEE
WHO IT IS.
REALLY?
IS IT A WOMAN?
I HAVEN'T SEEN ANY HERE.
NO.
RECOGNIZE THIS?
YEAH, THAT'S THE JIFFY POP
POPCORN, ISN'T IT?
NO! IT'S THE HELMET OF
THE GREATEST TV AND
COMIC ACTION HERO
IN THE HISTORY
OF THE WORLD!
THE SILVER WASP.
WHAT THE HECK'S
THIS HERE?
IT'S A CANE.
HOW OLD IS THIS
SUPERHERO, HAROLD?
IT'S NOT A CANE.
THAT'S THE SILVER SCEPTER,
THE SILVER WASP'S ULTIMATE
WEAPON IN BATTLING EVIL.
AND UNEVEN SIDEWALKS.
STOP THAT!
WHAT ELSE YOU GOT
IN THERE, HAROLD?
I GOT HIS COSTUME --
THE REST OF HIS COSTUME.
AND I GOT HIS
SIDEKICK'S COSTUME,
STINGER.
STINGER CAN'T
BE HERE, THOUGH.
HE'S GOT A PRIOR COMMITMENT
AND COURT ORDER THAT
SAYS HE CAN'T.
WELL, HAROLD,
HOW CAN YOU HAVE A
WASP WITHOUT A STINGER?
WELL, I HAVE VOLUNTEERED
TO STAND SIDE BY SIDE
WITH THE SILVER WASP.
I SHALL BE STINGER!
OH, YES, YES.
YES.
OH, THAT'S --
OH, YEAH.
YEAH. YEAH.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE POSSUM
LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER WILL RECEIVE A
COUPON FOR DINNER FOR TWO
AT SAM 'N' ELLA'S
(salmonella's) RESTAURANT,
CONVENIENTLY LOCATED
RIGHT NEXT TO THE HOSPITAL.
OKAY, MIKE,
COVER YOUR EARS.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS TO
GET MIKE TO SAY THIS WORD...
ALL RIGHT,
DALTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, MIKE, THIS IS
A PIECE OF PAPER
THAT CAUSES YOU TO
LOSE YOUR JOB.
WHAT'S IT CALLED?
A WARRANT.
OKAY,
THINK ABOUT THIS...
FREUDIAN...
ARE WE STILL
PLAYING IN ENGLISH?
OKAY, OKAY.
IF THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO SAY,
BUT IT ACCIDENTALLY COMES
OUT IN CONVERSATION,
THAT'S CALLED A...
CONFESSION.
OKAY, OKAY,
I KNOW.
MIKE, THIS IS WHAT
YOUR MOTHER'S GOT ON
UNDER HER DRESS.
TASSLES.
TIME'S ALMOST UP, RED.
YEAH.
OKAY, OKAY, MIKE,
THIS IS SOMETHING PEOPLE
ARE AFRAID WILL HAPPEN
TO THEM IN THE SHOWER.
AT HOME OR IN PRISON?
[ LAUGHTER ]
AT HOME.
OH, SLIP.
YEAH!
Red:
CAREFUL WHERE YOU
AIM THAT THING, DALTON.
Dalton:
I SEE YOU, RED.
Red:
YEAH, WELL, IT'S NOT YOUR
EYES I'M CONCERNED ABOUT.
Dalton:
WELL, EXCUSE ME FOR LIVING.
Winston:
WOULD YOU GUYS
JUST QUIT BICKERING.
Red:
I'M NOT BICKERING.
THERE'S THE GUY THAT'S
BICKERING RIGHT THERE.
Dalton: OH, PLEASE.
Winston:
YOU SEE THE BOOK
I'M READING HERE?
"THE ANGER TREE"
BY ANTHONY ANTHONY.
HE TELLS US THAT
THE ANGER TREE GROWS
FROM DEEP BENEATH THE SOIL.
IT MEANS THAT
YOU NEED TO UNEARTH
THE PSYCHOLOGICAL ROOTS
OF YOUR CONFLICT.
Red:
YOU KNOW, WINSTON,
AN APOLOGY WORKS JUST AS WELL.
Dalton: APOLOGY?
-Dalton: APOLOGY?!
-Red: THAT'S RIGHT.
Dalton:
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I WOULD ACCEPT AN APOLOGY?
Winston:
OKAY, DALTON,
RED SAYS THAT YOU'RE
INVADING HIS SPACE.
BUT WHAT HE'S REALLY SAYING
IS THAT YOU NEED TO DEVELOP
WELL-DEFINED
EGO BOUNDARIES.
OKAY, RED,
AND WHAT DALTON IS SAYING IS
THAT YOU NEED TO CONTROL
YOUR INNER PARENT.
Red: YOU KNOW, I'M NOT
SO SURE ANTHONY ANTHONY
UNDERSTANDS MEN.
Winston:
HE'S A MAN.
Red:
I'M NOT SO SURE
ABOUT THAT EITHER.
I'M JUST MAD AT DALTON
BECAUSE HE WRECKED MY
PRESSURE WASHER.
Dalton:
I DIDN'T BREAK
YOUR PRESSURE WASHER.
Red: YOU DIDN'T?
Dalton: NO, I DIDN'T EVEN
USE YOUR PRESSURE WASHER.
I HAVE MY OWN
PRESSURE WASHER.
THINGS YOU KNOW, RED.
Red:
YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
Dalton:
I HAVE MANY THINGS.
I'VE GOT A LAVA LAMP,
SOME STAMPS,
A GARDEN GNOME --
Red:
OKAY, DALTON,
YOU'RE AFFLUENT, ALL RIGHT?
WELL, THEN WHO THE HECK
BORROWED MY PRESSURE WASHER?
Winston: WHAT?
OKAY, LOOK, MY TRUCK
WAS REALLY DIRTY, OKAY?
HOW WAS I SUPPOSED TO KNOW
YOU CAN'T HOOK THAT STUPID
THING UP TO A FIRE HYDRANT?
Dalton: OH, BROTHER.
I JUST FEEL SO
STUPID, YOU KNOW.
WE'VE BEEN MAD AT
EACH OTHER ALL AFTERNOON.
Red: AND WE SHOULD
HAVE BEEN MAD AT WINSTON.
Winston:
THAT'S GOOD. THAT'S GOOD.
WHAT YOU JUST
ENGAGED IN THERE,
THAT'S CALLED TRANSFERENCE.
Red: TRANSFERENCE?
Winston:
LET ME TAKE ANOTHER PAGE OUT
OF ANTHONY ANTHONY'S BOOK.
Red:
YOU CAN TAKE 'EM ALL OUT,
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED.
-Dalton: MAY I HAVE A LOOK?
-Winston: SURE.
IT CAN REALLY HELP
YOU OUT, YOU KNOW.
Dalton:
IS IT EASY TO READ?
Winston: NOT BAD.
A LITTLE DRY IN SPOTS.
Dalton: IS IT?
WELL, I CAN FIX THAT.
Winston: HEY!
Red: (chuckling)
TRANSFER COMPLETE.
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
[ CRASH! ]
OKAY, YOU'RE PROBABLY
WONDERING HOW SOMETHING
LIKE THIS COULD HAPPEN.
WAS I DRIVING TOO FAST?
DID THE BRAKES FAIL?
MAYBE I FORGOT I HAD
A FREEZER ON THE ROOF.
IS THAT MY FAULT?
I DON'T THINK SO.
I MEAN, IT TOOK FOUR GUYS
AT DALTON'S STORE TO
PUT IT UP THERE.
THERE'S NO WAY I COULD
TAKE IT OFF BY MYSELF.
AND IF THE CARS THESE DAYS
HAD A DECENT SIZE TRUNK,
I WOULDN'T NEED TO PUT THE
FREEZER ON THE ROOF IN
THE FIRST PLACE.
OH, NO, I'M TELLING YOU,
THIS WAS AN ACCIDENT.
BUT INSTEAD OF WHINING
OR POINTING FINGERS,
TODAY ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW,
WITH A LITTLE WORK
AND IMAGINATION,
YOU CAN ACTUALLY MAKE
SOMETHING OUT OF AN ACCIDENT.
THAT'S WHAT MY
PARENTS DID WITH ME.
OKAY, NOW I TOOK THE
GARAGE DOOR TRACKS
AND I MOUNTED THEM
FREEZER WIDTH ON THE ROOF
AND THEN DOWN OVER
THE TRUNK OF THE CAR.
NOW I'M JUST SECURING THE
GARAGE DOOR OPENER ITSELF
TO THE HOOD.
AND DON'T BE AFRAID TO USE
THE LONG SCREWS ON THIS BABY.
AND THEN YOU REALLY WANNA GET
HER ATTACHED SECURELY THERE.
IT MIGHT BE A GOOD IDEA
TO EVEN OPEN THE HOOD
AND CHECK THAT YOU'VE
GOT A REAL GOOD GRIP THERE.
YEAH, THAT'S FINE.
OKAY, NOW ALL I GOTTA DO
IS PUT MY FREEZER INTO PLACE.
I DON'T NEED THIS AS A
GARAGE DOOR OPENER ANYMORE,
SINCE I NO LONGER
HAVE A GARAGE DOOR.
NOW IT'S MY AUTOMATIC
ROOF RACK HOIST.
IF YOU'LL NOTICE,
I TOOK THE ROLLER HARDWARE
OFF MY GARAGE DOORS
AND ATTACHED IT TO THE FOUR
CORNERS OF MY ROOF RACK BOX,
FORMERLY KNOWN AS
MY FREEZER.
LIKEWISE,
THE GARAGE DOOR HANDLE
BECOMES CLEAT FOR
MY HOISTING MECHANISM.
SO ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
FIT MY ROLLERS ON TRACK,
AND THEN GIVE
THE HANDLE THE HOOK.
OKAY, LET'S GIVE
HER A TEST RUN.
AND DON'T WIMP OUT,
YOU KNOW.
FREEZERS CAN HANDLE
A LOT OF WEIGHT,
PLUS THEY KEEP
EVERYTHING FRESH.
BEST BEFORE MAY 12.
OF COURSE NOW,
THE BEAUTY HERE IS
TO GET MY ROOF RACK
UP ONTO THE ROOF,
WELL, I DON'T HAVE
TO LIFT A FINGER.
I JUST GRAB MY
GARAGE DOOR OPENER
AND LET NATURE
TAKE ITS COURSE.
SEE, THIS WAS NO ACCIDENT;
THIS WAS A PROJECT.
SO REMEMBER IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OKAY, UM, NEXT WEEK WE'RE
GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE
GREAT JIGSAW PUZZLES
FOR YOUR KIDS.
WANNA TALK TO YOU
OLDER GUYS FOR A MINUTE
ABOUT YOUR WARDROBE.
YOU KNOW, THERE COMES
A POINT IN A MAN'S LIFE
WHEN THERE ARE CERTAIN
PIECES OF CLOTHING
HE SHOULD NO LONGER
BE WEARING.
LIKE THAT OLD PAIR
OF JEANS YOU'VE GOT
WITH THE SIZE 32
WAIST ON 'EM.
OKAY, MAYBE YOU CAN
STILL PULL 'EM ON,
AND ON A GOOD DAY YOU MIGHT
EVEN BE ABLE TO ZIP 'EM UP,
DEPENDING ON YOUR
LONG CAPACITY.
BUT LATER ON,
WHEN YOU ZIP THEM DOWN,
KIND OF LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY
TEARING OPEN A BAG OF
INSULATION.
NOW, EVEN IF YOU
KEPT YOURSELF IN SHAPE,
THERE ARE SOME ITEMS
IN YOUR CLOSET
THAT SHOULD NEVER
SEE THE LIGHT OF DAY AGAIN,
UNLESS IT'S COMING THROUGH THE
CRACK IN THE DUMPSTER LID,
LIKE, SAY, THAT SOUVENIR
ROCK CONCERT T-SHIRT
FROM 1967.
JUST BECAUSE THE BAND IS STILL
EMBARRASSING THEMSELVES
STILL BEING ON TOUR,
DOESN'T MEAN YOU HAVE TO
EMBARRASS YOURSELF
WEARING THE DARNED T-SHIRT.
AND DON'T EVER THINK
THAT YOU CAN BE CURRENT.
A MAN OF OUR AGE HAS GOTTA
WEAR HIS BALL CAP
FACING FORWARD.
THE SHOES HAVE GOTTA
COVER HIS TOES.
AND THE CROTCH OF
HIS PANTS NEEDS TO BE
IN THE GENERAL VICINITY
OF THE CROTCH OF HIS BODY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
BUT I GOT GOOD
NEWS FOR YOU.
IF THIS SEEMS LIKE
TOO MUCH TO REMEMBER,
IF YOU HAVE A WIFE,
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE TO.
YOU JUST PUT ON WHATEVER
SHE TELLS YOU TO, OKAY.
YOU'RE JUST THE GUY
WHO WEARS THE CLOTHES.
WE HAVE TO LOOK AT YOU!
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IF YOUR TANK'S IN TROUBLE
AND ALL FULL OF MUCK;
IF THE GROUND'S GETTING SOFT
AND YOU FEEL LIKE A SCHMUCK;
GIVE ROTHSCHILD'S A CALL,
AND I'LL COME IN MY TRUCK.
I'M THERE IN THE BOOK.
JUST LOOK UNDER "SUCK".
MAN, THERE'S A LOT OF MONEY
CHANGING HANDS OUT THERE.
THEY OFFERED
MOOSE THOMPSON 75 BUCKS
TO POSE AS THE
INCREDIBLE HULK.
THAT'S A LOTTA GREEN,
BELIEVE ME.
HEY, MIKE.
OH, HI,
MR. GREEN.
WHAT DO YOU
GOT THERE?
OH, WHAT THIS?
OH, IT'S NOTHING.
IT'S JUST AN OLD COMIC BOOK
WAS GONNA HAVE APPRAISED.
AQUAMAN NUMBER 1?
OH, YEAH,
IT IS!
HOW ABOUT THAT.
OKAY, SEE YOU.
THAT BETTER NOT BE MY
AQUAMAN NUMBER 1,
OR YOU'RE IN
DEEP NUMBER 2.
[ STAMMERING ]
I WAS PLANNING ON
SELLING IT FOR YOU.
AS A SURPRISE.
HOW MUCH DO YOU
WANT FOR IT?
I WANT $100
FOR IT, MIKE.
WELL, I'LL GIVE
YOU 100 BUCKS FOR IT.
WELL, GREAT.
HAND IT OVER.
WELL, NOT MY 100 BUCKS.
I'LL SELL IT
AND I'LL GIVE 100 BUCKS
OUT OF WHATEVER
I GET FOR IT.
NO, NO, NO.
YOU GO GET ME AN OFFER.
WE'LL TAKE IF FROM
THERE, ALL RIGHT?
ANYWAY, YOU CAN'T
SELL SOMETHING WHEN
YOU DON'T EVEN OWN IT YET.
WELL, MY STOCK BROKER
DOES IT ALL THE TIME.
UNCLE RED, I GOT A PROBLEM.
[ WHISTLES AND APPLAUSE ]
JUST THE ONE?
I'M STINGER.
BUT THE PROBLEM IS THE
SILVER WASP ISN'T COMING.
WHAT? HE BUGGED
OFF ON YOU?
HE LOOKED POSSUM LAKE
UP ON THE MAP,
AND IT WASN'T THERE,
SO HE'S NOT COMING.
OH, MAN, HAROLD,
HOW ARE YOU GOING TO GET A
SUPERHERO ON SHORT NOTICE?
WELL, I'VE STILL
GOT HIS COSTUME HERE.
HE'S NOT REALLY THAT MUCH
OF A SUPERHERO ANYWAYS.
HE'S KIND OF OLD
AND USELESS.
SO I WAS THINKING
MAYBE YOU COULD DO IT.
OH, I CAN'T BE
THE SILVER WASP.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I'LL DO ALL THE ENTERTAINMENT.
I'LL SIGN THE AUTOGRAPHS.
KEEP EVERYBODY HAPPY.
YOU THINK WE COULD
ACTUALLY PULL IT OFF?
SURE. YEAH.
I'LL DO ALL THE WORK,
AND YOU TAKE ALL THE CREDIT.
IT'LL BE JUST LIKE
OUR TV SHOW.
Red (voice over):
I WAS OUT BEHIND THE LODGE.
I LIKE CUTTING THINGS.
I'VE GOT THE CIRCULAR SAW.
JUST CUT STUFF AT RANDOM
IS WHAT I LIKE TO DO.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY, WHEN I
GOT OVER TO THE OUTLET,
WHICH ONLY HAD THE ONE, THERE
WAS SOMETHING PLUGGED IN.
I THOUGHT, WHAT THE HECK
IS PLUGGED IN THERE?
AND IT'S AN EXTENSION CORD,
SO I FIGURED, WELL, I DON'T
WANNA JUST UNPLUG IT.
MIGHT BE SOMETHING IMPORTANT
AT THE OTHER END.
SO -- BUT THERE'S
NOTHING THERE.
SO I SAY, I WONDER WHERE
THE HECK THIS GOES?
AND I COME AROUND AND
THINKING WHAT THE HECK --
OH, THERE WE GO.
THERE'S A LAWN MOWER.
OF COURSE.
IT'S A LAWN MOWER.
EXCEPT THAT'S
A GAS LAWN MOWER.
SO THE EXTENSION
CORD KEEPS --
NOW WE'RE GETTING --
THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD SIZE
EXTENSION CORD ON THERE.
COMING UP OVER THE FENCE
THERE AND ALL THE WRECK,
AND THEN GOES RIGHT
ACROSS THE ROAD THERE
AND UP INTO THE BUSH,
AND I'M THINKING,
HOLY COW.
I DIDN'T SEE
WALTER COMING ALONG,
AND I HAD TO RAISE THE WIRE
UP TO GO THROUGH THE BUSH.
YOU KIDS BE CAREFUL
OF THAT AT HOME.
I COME TO THE END,
AND IT'S TIED AROUND A TREE.
SO ACTUALLY THEY'RE USING
IT AS A CLOTHESLINE.
SO MAYBE IT'S AN ELECTRIC
CLOTHES DRYER OF SOME KIND.
BUT IT'S STILL NOT THE END.
IT JUST KEEPS GOING.
SO I KIND OF FOLLOW
ALONG A LITTLE FARTHER.
WHAT THE HECK IS THIS --
AND NOW I GET TO --
I NOTICE IT'S MOVING,
WHICH MEANS I MUST BE GETTING
CLOSE TO WHOEVER'S USING IT.
SO I THINK, OKAY, I'M GONNA
CATCH THEM RED HANDED.
AND I COME OUT THERE,
AND I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON.
OKAY, AND EVEN THE KIDS
DON'T HAVE THE END OF IT,
SO I KEEP GOING THERE,
AND WOULDN'T YOU KNOW IT,
I COME UP TO DALTON'S STORE
AND IT GOES RIGHT UP
THE OUTSIDE WALL
OF HIS STORE.
SO I FIGURE, WELL, I'LL
HAVE TO GO UP ON THE ROOF
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
THIS IS ALL ABOUT.
LUCKILY MY COMMANDO
TRAINING CAME IN HANDY.
AND UP OVER THE ROOF,
AND THERE IT IS.
HE'S RUNNING A HUGE NEON SIGN
PLUGGED INTO THE LODGE.
SO I FIGURE THE HECK WITH
THAT, SO I UNPLUG HER.
NOW DALTON COMES
RUNNING OUTTA THE STORE.
WHAT THE HECK'S GOING ON.
AND THEN HE SEES IT'S ME.
IT'S A WHOLE DIFFERENT TUNE.
SO I GIVE HIM A
FLICK OF THE WRIST.
AND IT'S LIGHTS OUT
FOR DALTON.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THAT'S MY WIFE'S
CAR BACK THERE.
ONCE IN A WHILE WHEN SHE
SENDS ME ON AN ERRAND,
TO, SAY, YOU KNOW, THE MALL,
SHE DOESN'T WANT ME
TO TAKE THE POSSUM VAN.
SHE'S AFRAID SOME OF HER
FRIENDS WILL SEE ME IN IT.
SO I TAKE HER CAR.
BUT THEN WHEN I COME OUT
OF THE MALL TO GO HOME,
IT LOOKS SO MUCH LIKE THE
HUNDREDS OF OTHER CARS
IN THE PARKING LOT,
I CAN NEVER FIND
THE DARNED THING.
OH, SURE, I KNOW THE TRICK
WHERE YOU PRESS THE REMOTE
BUTTON AND HONK THE HORN.
[ HORN HONKING ]
BUT AFTER 40 YEARS OF
DRIVING THE WAY I DRIVE,
I'M AT THE POINT WHERE
I CAN'T EVEN HEAR CAR
HORNS ANYMORE.
SO I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
I'LL GIVE YOU A CLUE.
SOME OF YOU COULD USE ONE.
THIS CAR HAS
A POWER ANTENNA,
AND I GOT BERNICE
TO MAKE ME A SMALL FLAG.
OKAY, I RE-WIRED
THE HORN RELAY,
SO NOW INSTEAD OF THE HORN
HONKING WHEN I HIT
THE REMOTE,
IT'S GONNA TURN ON THE RADIO
AND THE WINDSHIELD WIPERS.
THAT'S BECAUSE THE
WINDSHIELD WIPER'S GOT THE
POWER ANTENNA MOUNTED ON IT,
AND I GOT BERNICE'S
FLAG ON THAT.
LOOKS LIKE SHE JUST
USED AN OLD TEA TOWEL,
WHICH IS FINE.
I WAS KINDA HOPING SHE'D
EMBROIDER THE FAMILY
CREST ON THERE.
I GUESS A BUNCH OF
ASSORTED FOOD STAINS
AND A COUPLE OF BURN
MARKS IS CLOSE ENOUGH.
I'LL TELL YOU ONE THING,
WHEN I OUT OF THE MALL NOW,
I GOT NO PROBLEM.
[ POUNDING AT DOOR ]
I'LL TELL YOU
SOMETHING,
THOSE NERDS CAN
REALLY MOVE.
ALL THE YEARS OF RUNNING
AWAY FROM BULLIES
REALLY BUILDS UP THE
LEG MUSCLES, I GUESS.
WE GOTTA DO SOMETHING,
UNCLE RED.
THEY'RE MAD.
THEY KNOW YOU'RE A FAKE.
WHY DID YOU MAKE
THAT SPEECH?
WELL, HAROLD, THEY WERE
JUST STARING AT ME
LIKE THEY WERE
EXPECTING SOMETHING.
AND I DIDN'T GIVE
MUCH OF A SPEECH.
I JUST SAID, THE SILVER WASP
WELCOMES YOU GUYS TO THE
COMIC BOOK CONVENTION.
THAT WAS IT.
BUT THE SILVER WASP
NEVER SPOKE!
OH.
WASPS CAN'T TALK,
UNCLE RED, DUH!
[ POUNDING CONTINUES.
OH, NO,
THEY'RE COMING.
HAROLD, HERE, GIVE THEM
MY AQUAMAN COMIC.
[ ARGUING ]
HAROLD! THEY'RE YOU'RE
KIND OF PEOPLE!
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT.
I GOT AQUAMAN
NUMBER 1 FOR YOU.
HERE, TAKE IT.
JUST GO.
GOOD WORK,
STINKER.
STINGER!
MR. GREEN,
THE DEAL IS DONE.
GIVE ME THE AQUAMAN COMIC.
I FOUND A BUYER.
AND I THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO BE VERY, VERY HAPPY.
I DON'T.
WHY NOT?
I GOT --
NO, MIKE,
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I DON'T CARE IF YOU EVEN
GOT 200 BUCKS FOR IT.
IT MAKES
NO DIFFERENCE.
I GOT AN OFFER
OF $10,000.
audience: OHHHH.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
THAT'S MEETING
TIME, UNCLE RED.
YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I NEED TO THINK
ABOUT KILLING MYSELF.
OKAY, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
AND I REALLY HOPE YOU'RE NOT,
I MAY NOT BE FASTER
THAN A SPEEDING BULLET,
BUT I JUST SCREWED MYSELF
OUT OF TEN GRAND IN
A SINGLE BOUND.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND STINKER
AND THE WHOLE GANG
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
EVERYBODY TAKE YOUR SEATS.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
HAVE A SEAT.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, THIS IS
HAROLD'S NEW LOOK.
HE'S HOPING TO FIND
A LITTLE HONEY.
MAYBE SET UP A HIVE.
AND IF ALL GOES WELL,
THERE'LL BE ANOTHER SON OF
A BEE AT THE LODGE SOME DAY.