YOU KNOW, THESE DAYS
EVERYBODY WANTS TO SAVE MONEY.
WELL HERE'S A REAL SIMPLE WAY.
GET YOURSELF ONE OF
THESE WRECKING BALLS
OFF OF A DEMOLITION CRANE.
IF YOU'RE WONDERING
HOW YOU'RE GONNA DO THAT,
HERE'S A HINT.
THEY DON'T WORK WEEKENDS.
ALL RIGHT, HANG THAT
FROM YOUR FRONT FENDER,
AND BASICALLY
YOU'RE DONE.
OH, I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE THINKING.
SURE IT LOOKS SHARP,
BUT HOW'S THAT
GONNA SAVE ME MONEY?
WON'T DO MUCH FOR
YOUR GAS MILEAGE,
BUT IT'LL SAVE YOU
25% ON TIRES, GUARANTEED.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
OH, YEAH,
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, MAN.
I KNOW -- I KNOW
WHY YOU'RE SO EXCITED...
BECAUSE THIS IS THE VERY FIRST
SHOW OF OUR NEW SEASON HERE.
HAROLD'S RUNNING
A BIT LATE.
I THINK HE WENT TO
A BIRTHDAY PARTY
AND PROBABLY GOT HIS TEETH
CAUGHT IN A PIÑATA.
I'M HERE.
WHOA.
SORRY I'M LATE.
LOOK AT YOU.
WHAT KIND OF BIRTHDAY
PARTY WAS THAT, EH?
DID THEY HAVE A ROLEX
IN YOUR LOOT BAG, HUH?
BIRTHDAY PARTY?
I WASN'T AT A BIRTHDAY PARTY.
I WAS AT A
JOB INTERVIEW,
IN THE CITY!
YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T
NEED A JOB IN THE CITY;
YOU'VE GOT A JOB RIGHT
HERE IN THE COUNTRY.
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT THE
COLLEGE WANTED ME TO GO
SO THEY COULD KEEP THEIR HIGH
JOB PLACEMENT RECORD INTACT.
THOSE COLLEGE PEOPLE,
THEY HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YEAH, I KNOW.
YOU JUST STAY
HERE, HAROLD.
YOU JUST GRADUATED.
YOU DON'T WANNA WORK
IN THE CITY.
YOU'D HAVE TO
LIVE IN THE CITY.
OH, NO.
OH, NO, THE CITY!
WITH ITS HUNDREDS
OF MOVIE THEATRES,
CABARETS,
MODEL TRAIN CLUBS.
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
YOU JUST STAY
HERE, HAROLD.
YOU JUST GRADUATED
FROM COLLEGE.
YOU'VE GOT YOUR WHOLE
LIFE AHEAD OF YOU,
RIGHT HERE
AT POSSUM LAKE.
YEAH, WHO KNOWS?
MAYBE I'LL GROW UP
AND BE ABLE TO BELCH
LIKE YOU GUYS.
THAT'D BE GOOD, EH?
NO, DON'T, NO.
NO, I GOT IT.
I'VE BEEN PRACTICING.
NO. NO. NO.
NO, HAROLD, NO.
[ COUGHING ]
IT WAS CLOSE.
THAT WAS CLOSE, THOUGH.
HAROLD.
ONE DAY.
YOU HAVE FRIENDS
HERE YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, YOU DON'T HAVE
A GIRLFRIEND YET,
BUT MAYBE SOMEBODY
NEW WILL MOVE IN,
WHO DOESN'T KNOW YOU,
AND THEN YOU'LL
HAVE A SHOT, HUH?
WE HAVE A GREAT
LIFE HERE, HAROLD.
A GREAT LIFE.
WE HAVE A GREAT
LIFE HERE.
I'M IN NO HURRY
TO GO ANYWHERE.
AH, YOU DIDN'T
GET THE JOB, EH?
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
NOW EVERYBODY KNOWS THE BEST
TIME TO WEED YOUR LAWN
IS BETWEEN 11:00 A.M.
AND 3:00 P.M.,
IN THE HEAT OF
THE NOONDAY SUN,
WHEN THE WEEDS ARE FEELING
HEALTHY AND FULL OF LIFE.
11:00 TO 3:00 IS
ALSO PRIME NAP TIME,
SO THAT MAKES WEEDING
RIGHT OUT OF THE QUESTION.
BUT HERE'S HOW
YOU CAN DO BOTH...
YOU TAKE SMALL JAM JARS,
AND YOU FILL 'EM WITH ABOUT
HALF AN INCH OF GASOLINE.
THEN YOU PLACE 'EM ON THE LAWN
IN CLOSE PROXIMITY TO THE WEEDS.
AND THE HEAT OF THE NOONDAY SUN
WILL FOCUS THROUGH THE GLASS.
AND JUST WHEN THAT
WEED'S FEELING PERKY,
[ EXPLOSION ]
IT'S BYE-BYE, WEED.
[ SHATTERING GLASS ]
I SUGGEST MAYBE YOU WANNA
TAKE YOUR NAP INDOORS.
[ GLASS SHATTERING ]
[ SERVICE BELL ]
OH.
I'LL GET THAT
FOR YOU, SIR.
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS A LOT.
APPRECIATE IT.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
FILL 'ER UP, SIR?
UH, NO,
YOU BETTER NOT.
THE GAS TANK LEAKS
WHEN SHE'S OVER HALFWAY.
FIVE BUCKS'D
BE PERFECT.
SURE.
COULD YOU TURN
OFF THE VAN, SIR?
OKAY, BUT I HOPE YOU'VE
GOT JUMPER CABLES.
UH, DO YOU KNOW YOU
HAVE NO GAS CAP ON
YOUR TANK, HERE,
JUST A BALL
OF DUCT TAPE?
YEAH, JUST STUFF THAT
BACK IN THE HOLE WHEN
YOU'RE DONE THERE.
THAT WORKS PERFECT.
ACTUALLY, I LOST THE REGULAR
GAS CAP IN A POKER GAME.
RIGHT.
OKAY.
IS THIS GRAFFITTI
ON YOUR VAN HERE?
DID SOMEBODY VANDALIZE
YOUR VEHICLE?
OH, YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT THE POSSUM.
A POSSUM DID THIS?
NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS A POSSUM VAN --
THIS IS A POSSUM VAN.
OH, YOU TRANSPORT
POSSUMS.
NO, NO, I PAINTED THE
VAN TO LOOK LIKE A POSSUM.
THIS IS THE OFFICIAL
POSSUM LODGE VEHICLE.
YOU'RE NEW
HERE, AREN'T YOU?
I JUST STARTED.
I'M A STUDENT.
I PUMP GAS AND WORK
PART TIME IN THE GARAGE.
MY NAME'S DALE.
I'M PLEASED
TO MEET YOU, DALE.
I'M RED GREEN.
THIS HERE'S
WILFRED LAURIER.
THANKS, Mr. GREEN.
ALL RIGHT.
NO PROBLEM.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW,
IT STARTED.
YOU KNOW, Mr. GREEN,
IF YOU EVER NEED ANYBODY
TO DO WORK ON YOUR VAN,
I'D BE HAPPY TO TAKE
A LOOK AT IT FOR YOU.
WELL, THANKS, DALE,
BUT I PRETTY MUCH DO ALL THE
MECHANICAL WORK ON THIS
BABY ALL BY MYSELF.
IT'S TIME TO PLAY THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ APPLAUSE ]
TODAY, Mr. DALTON HUMPHREY
FROM HUMPHREY'S
EVERYTHING STORE
IS GOING TO PLAY FOR
THE GRAND PRIZE FROM
SAM'S SHOE STORE.
A BUY-ONE-SHOE-GET-
THE-OTHER-ONE-FREE COUPON.
OKAY, Mr. HUMPHREY,
COVER YOUR EARS NOW.
Mr. HUMPHREY HAS 30 SECONDS
TO GUESS THIS WORD.
YEAH,
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
OKAY,
AND GO.
ALL RIGHT, DALTON,
DINNER BY CANDLELIGHT.
POWER FAILURE.
YOU GET YOUR WIFE
A BOUQUET OF FLOWERS.
OH, APOLOGY!
YOU'RE FEELING
KIND OF LOVEY-DOVEY,
YOU KNOW, IN THE MOOD,
HOW DO YOU ACT?
WHINEY?
ALMOST OUT OF
TIME, Mr. GREEN.
OKAY, FORGET
YOU AND ANN.
IF YOUR DAUGHTER ELOPED
WITH THAT BOYFRIEND OF HER'S,
WHAT KIND OF A
MOMENT WOULD THAT BE?
IT WOULD RENEW MY
FAITH IN THE ALMIGHTY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE THEY'D BE IN LOVE,
WOULDN'T THEY, DALTON?
OH, YEAH. YEAH.
HER WITH THE PURPLE HAIR,
HIM WITH THE HARDWARE
COMING OUT OF HIS FACE;
OH, YEAH. THAT
WOULD BE A REAL
ROMANTIC NOVEL.
THERE WE GO.
[ RINGING BELL ]
EVERY MAN HAS A FEW
THINGS IN HIS LIFE
THAT HE KNOWS HE SHOULD DO,
BUT HE NEVER
QUITE GETS AROUND TO.
NOW MAYBE FOR YOU,
IT'S PAYING YOUR TAXES
OR VISITING A RELATIVE
OR GETTING THOSE EMPTY
BEER BOTTLES OUT OF THE SINK.
FOR ME, IT'S
CLEANING OUT MY CAR.
I TRY TO DO IT
ONCE EVERY YEAR.
IT'S BEEN A
PRETTY GOOD YEAR.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW THIS IS A SITUATION
THAT OFTEN FACES
THE HANDYMAN.
DO YOU JUST PRESS ON
WITH A HOPELESS CAUSE,
OR DO YOU TRY TO COME
UP WITH SOME CREATIVE WAY
TO DO THE JOB BETTER,
OR DO YOU JUST GO FOR A NAP?
WELL, I'M GONNA COME UP
WITH A BETTER WAY TO DO THIS
'CAUSE I CAN'T BE SLEEPING
ON MY TELEVISION SHOW.
THAT'S YOUR JOB.
ALL RIGHT, I'M THINKING
WHAT WE GOTTA DO IS GET
THE ROOF OFF OF THERE,
AND I WANT TO DO IT WITH
AS LITTLE EFFORT AS POSSIBLE.
I HAVE A REPUTATION
TO CONSIDER.
OKAY, NOW I NEED TO ADD
A COUPLE OF STEEL CHANNELS
ON THE SIDE.
HERE AGAIN,
INNOVATION IS THE KEY.
DON'T KNOW QUITE
WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR,
BUT I'M SURE I'LL
RECOGNIZE IT WHEN I SEE IT.
LIFE IS A SMORGASBORD.
NOW I KNOW I'M NOT GONNA
FIND EXACTLY WHAT I WANT,
SO I'M GONNA HAVE TO ADAPT.
I NEED A COUPLE OF CHANNELS,
YOU KNOW, SORT OF
LIKE EAVESTROUGHS.
GOTTA BE SOMETHING HERE
THAT'S SORTA LIKE AN EAVESTROUGH
OR SOMETHING I COULD MAKE INTO
SOMETHING LIKE AN EAVESTROUGH.
OKAY, IT TOOK A LITTLE
EXTRA TIME AND A LITTLE
EXTRA IMAGINATION,
BUT WE NOW HAVE THE PERFECT
WAY TO CLEAN OUT YOUR CAR.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO ANY BENDING.
YOU DON'T NEED A VACCUUM,
AND IT WON'T KILL
A WHOLE AFTERNOON.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OH, WERE YOU WONDERING HOW
THE CAR CLEANING THING WORKS?
I'LL GIVE YOU THREE GUESSES.
I WANT TO TALK
TO YOU OLDER GUYS.
MAYBE YOU'RE HAVING A TOUGH
TIME AT WORK OR WORSE STILL,
MAYBE YOU'RE HAVING
A TOUGH TIME AT HOME.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
MARRIAGE PROBLEMS.
MAYBE YOU'VE BEEN MARRIED
A LONG, LONG TIME,
EVEN IN DOG YEARS.
THINGS ARE GETTING A
LITTLE STALE,AND IT'S HARD
TO KEEP THAT MARRIAGE GOING.
MAYBE YOU'RE TIRED OF
THE SAME OLD ROUTINE.
MAYBE YOU'RE TIRED OF MAKING UP
NEW EXCUSES FOR YOUR BEHAVIOUR.
MAYBE YOU'RE EVEN THINKING
ABOUT MOVING OUT AND STARTING
OVER ON YOUR OWN.
WELL, BEFORE YOU DO THAT,
I'D LIKE YOU TO
TRY SOMETHING FOR ME.
GO INTO A PRIVATE
ROOM IN YOUR HOME.
MAYBE THE BATHROOM,
MAYBE THE BEDROOM,
DOESN'T MATTER.
AS LONG AS THERE'S A FULL-LENGTH
MIRROR AND YOU CAN BE ALONE.
NOW LOCK THE DOOR,
TAKE OFF ALL OF YOUR CLOTHES.
ALL OF THEM.
NOW STAND IN FRONT
OF THAT MIRROR AND
TAKE A GOOD HARD LOOK.
DON'T LOOK AWAY.
DO NOT LOOK AWAY.
LOOK UP.
LOOK DOWN.
LOOK UNDER IF NECESSARY.
TURN TO THE SIDE.
TURN TO THE OTHER SIDE.
TURN RIGHT AROUND AND
LOOK BACK OVER YOUR SHOULDER
IN THAT MIRROR.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
THERE'S PROBABLY LOTS TO SEE.
NOW ASK YOURSELF THIS QUESTION,
ARE YOU IN DATING SHAPE?
THINK ABOUT IT.
IS THERE ANYTHING IN
THAT MIRROR THAT YOU'D
LIKE A STRANGER TO SEE?
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
NOW GET BACK OUT THERE
AND MAKE THAT MARRIAGE WORK.
AND PUT YOUR CLOTHES ON
FIRST AND DON'T TAKE THEM
OFF UNTIL IT'S REAL, REAL DARK.
AND REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, I TELL YOU.
IT SURE IS GOOD TO BE BACK
ON TELEVISION AGAIN
BECAUSE WHEN THE SHOW'S NOT ON,
I TRY A LOT OF THIS
STUFF AT HOME,
AND IT PUTS A LOT OF STRAIN
ON THE MARRIAGE, I TELL YOU.
OH, EXCUSE ME, RED.
OH, YOU REMEMBER
DALTON HUMPHREY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
NO, NO, NO.
NO, WELL I WENT TO A
LOT OF TROUBLE TO GET THESE.
CEMETERY GATES WERE
LOCKED WHEN I GOT THERE.
OH, MAN.
I JUST WANTED TO COME BY
AND CONGRATULATE YOU.
YOU'RE GETTING YOUR SHOW
BACK ON THE AIR
AND YOU KNOW WHAT I HEARD,
HAROLD GOT A JOB IN THE CITY.
NO, NO, HE DIDN'T.
SO I WAS --
I GUESS YOU'RE GONNA WANT BE
THINKING ABOUT REPLACING HIM.
YOU KNOW GETTING A KIND
OF A NEW CO-HOST THING.
NOT REALLY, NO.
WHAT WOULD THAT
JOB PAY, ROUGHLY?
ROUGHLY, ZERO.
THAT'S PRETTY ROUGH.
YEP.
WELL, IT'S BASED ON
PERFORMANCE, THOUGH.
I GOTCHA.
FORGET IT.
MIKE HAMAR.
YOU KNOW MIKE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Mr. GREEN, I GOT
SOMETHING FOR YOU.
I JUST WANTED TO THANK YOU FOR
EVERYTHING YOU DONE FOR ME,
SINCE I GOT OUT
OF THE SLAMMER,
AND IF YOU EVER NEED
ANY EXTRA HELP AROUND,
YOU KNOW, ON THE SHOW THIS YEAR
NOW THAT HAROLD'S FINALLY GONE,
I'M HERE FOR YOU.
THANK YOU, MIKE.
THANK YOU.
I JUST BROUGHT YOU
A LITTLE GIFT.
WHAT'S THAT?
IT LOOKS LIKE A CAR KEY.
IS THAT A CAR KEY?
YEAH, IT'S AN EXTRA
KEY FOR YOUR VAN.
OR, ACTUALLY, ANY VAN.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
WELL, RED, THANKS ANYWAYS FOR
HELPING ME WITH TRANSPORTING
THE, UH, THE -- THE, UH,
RABID MAN-EATING
BOBCAT?
NO, RED,
NOT MAN-EATING.
HE WOULD NEVER
EAT YOU.
WELL, I'LL TELL
YOU ONE THING.
WE'RE LUCKY WE GOT OUT
OF THE VAN WHEN WE DID.
I TOLD YOU WE SHOULD'VE
USED A CAGE.
WELL, IT'S NOT
WIDE ENOUGH.
RED, YOUR VAN IS NOT
WIDE ENOUGH FOR
A BOBCAT CAGE.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR
TRANQUILIZER GUN?
I THOUGHT THAT DART WOULD'VE
KNOCKED HIM OUT BY NOW.
WELL, UH, IT HASN'T
KICKED IN YET.
YOU WAIT.
HE'LL CALM
DOWN, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, A BIT.
AND THEN WE CAN GET
BACK IN THE VAN AND
FINISH OUR TRIP.
[ ANIMAL ROARING ]
OH! OH!
DRIVE FAST.
WHAT?
IF WE GET IN THE VAN
AND DRIVE FAST,
AND THEN HE'LL BE STUCK
TO THE BACK OF THE VAN.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
YOU'RE GOING TO
STAND RIGHT HERE.
LIKE THAT, ALL RIGHT.
RIGHT?
I'M GOING TO OPEN
THESE DOORS, OKAY.
I'M GOING TO RUN AWAY.
AND THEN WHEN THE
BOBCAT COMES OUT TO
RIP YOUR FACE OFF,
YOU NAIL HIM WITH
ANOTHER DART OUT OF
YOUR TRANQUILIZER GUN.
READY?
ALL RIGHT. YEAH.
WE COULD DO THAT,
BUT THE GUN IS
EMPTY, RED.
HUH?
WELL, I USED THE LAST
DART ON THAT BOBCAT.
OH, MAN.
YEAH, YEAH, THIS IS NOTHING
MORE THAN AN AIRGUN.
[ GUNSHOT ]
O-O-OH. O-O-OH.
OH, OH, GREAT.
OKAY, I GUESS THERE
WAS ANOTHER DART.
I GUESS THERE WAS
ANOTHER DART IN THERE.
MY MISTAKE.
HALF DOSAGE.
YEAH, I SHOULD'VE HIT HIM
WITH TWO DARTS, AND I --
I FEEL A LITTLE
TIRED HERE, RED.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M GONNA TAKE A NAP,
JUST FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
UMM, LET ME SEE,
I'M ABOUT 200 POUNDS
SO THIS, UH,
I'LL BE WAKING UP IN
AROUND THREE OR FOUR HOURS.
OH, MAN.
OR, UH, YOU COULD
CALL FOR HELP.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
HELLO, POLICE?
WE HAVE A
SITUATION HERE.
UH, YEAH, I'D LIKE TO
REPORT A STOLEN VEHICLE.
OH, RED, RED,
THIS IS GREAT.
YOU'RE JUST IN TIME FOR
TODAY'S EDUCATIONAL FILM.
I'LL COME BACK LATER.
NO. NO. NO. NO.
THIS IS PERFECT.
IT'S A NEW
PROJECT OF MINE.
I MAKE THESE
FILMS MYSELF.
OH, BOY, THIS ISN'T YOU
AND SMALL ANIMALS OR
ANYTHING, IS IT?
NO. NO. NO. NO.
NO, THOSE AREN'T
FOR COMPANY.
NO, THIS IS A CARTOON.
YOU KNOW THEY HAVE CARTOONS
FOR ADULTS, YOU KNOW.
FELIX THE CAT, THE JETSONS,
THAT SORT OF THING.
SO YOU MADE A CARTOON
HERE HAVE YOU?
YEAH.
I DID ALL THE VOICES, DREW
ALL THE PICTURES MYSELF.
WOW.
BUT IT'S NOT JUST
A CARTOON.
THIS -- THIS
FILM WILL TEACH PEOPLE
ALL ABOUT DIFFERENT
THINGS IN THE FOREST.
OH, YEAH.
THIS PARTICULAR ONE
WILL TEACH EVERYONE
ABOUT TREE HOLES.
TREE HOLES?
YEAH.
SOUNDS RIVETING.
HERE WE GO.
[CHEERY MUSIC]
WELL, FOLKS, TIME TO LEARN
ABOUT THE DANGERS OF TREE HOLES.
WHAT'S A TREE
HOLE, RANGER GORD?
WELL, HAROLD, THAT'S
THE COMMON NAME FOR
A HOLE THAT IS IN A TREE.
BUT, MOST PEOPLE DON'T
REALIZE THAT A TREE HOLE
IS ACTUALLY A TREE'S MOUTH.
WOW.
I, UH, THINK YOU'RE
WRONG ABOUT THAT, GORD.
YOU DON'T USUALLY MAKE
A LOT OF SENSE, YOU KNOW.
I THINK YOU'RE
WAY OUT THERE.
AH-H-H!
NOW, THIS PARTICULAR KIND OF
TREE IS CALLED A FAMILY TREE.
IT'S CALLED THAT BECAUSE IT CAN
EAT A WHOLE FAMILY OF ANIMALS
WITHOUT FEELING FULL.
WHAT KIND OF
FAMILY THOUGH, RIGHT?
YOU HAVE TO SAY WHAT KIND OF
ANIMAL FAMILY THE TREE EATS.
DON'T INTERRUPT ME.
YOU ALWAYS BRING UP POINTS
THAT DON'T MATTER, HAROLD.
HAVE SOME RESPECT
FOR MY PRESENTATION.
OH, SORRY, GORD.
SORRY.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
IF IT WEREN'T FOR, YOU I'D BE
WALLOWING IN IGNORANCE FOREVER.
ALL OF US WOULD BE.
WELL, THAT'S SO TRUE.
SO LISTEN UP.
REMEMBER, FOLKS, THAT
IT'S NEVER SAFE TO PUT
ANYTHING IN A TREE'S MOUTH.
WELL, LUCKILY THIS TREE
IS FAST ASLEEP,
OR IT WOULD HAVE
TASTED LITTLE HAROLD
AS SOON AS I
SHOVED HIM IN THERE,
AND IT WOULD HAVE BIT HIM
RIGHT IN HALF.
AH, GORD, WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING IS NOT VERY LOGICAL.
MAYBE I CAN
HELP YOU OUT HERE.
WELL, WHAT DID YOU SEE IN THE
TREE'S MOUTH, LITTLE HAROLD?
BEES.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS TYPE OF FAMILY TREE
LOVES TO EAT BEES.
NOW, LET'S WAKE UP
THE TREE AND TEASE IT.
THAT WAY WE'LL GET AN
IDEA OF HOW THE FAMILY
TREE HUNTS FOR FOOD.
GOOD MORNING!
WAKE UP!
WHY HAVE YOU DISTURBED ME?
BAD MOVE, TREE.
THEY MIGHT HAVE
BEEN IGNORANT,
BUT THEY WERE
FRIENDS OF MINE.
WHOA,
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
AND REMEMBER,
FRIENDS DON'T LET
FRIENDS GET EATEN BY TREES,
WITHOUT THEN SNAPPING THAT
TREE OFF AND THROWING
IT INTO THE SUN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
HEY, HOW ARE YA?
OH, RIGHT, UH, IT'S TIME
FOR MIKE'S TEEN TALK.
UH, I'VE GOT AN IDEA FOR
YOU TEENAGE BOYS OUT THERE.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
PULL YOUR PANTS UP HIGHER.
LIKE, MAYBE, UP TO AROUND,
SAY, YOUR WAISTLINE, YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, UH, DON'T THINK
I DON'T APPRECIATE THE
VALUE OF REALLY BAGGY CLOTHES.
BELIEVE ME, I KNOW THE
VALUE OF REALLY BAGGY CLOTHES,
ESPECIALLY WHEN I'M SHOPPING.
BUT YOU KNOW, RIGHT NOW
YOUR WALLETS ARE HANGING DOWN
AROUND THE BACKS OF YOUR KNEES.
TALK ABOUT EASY
PICKINGS, YOU KNOW.
NOT THAT YOU GUYS CARRY
TOO MUCH CASH IN THESE THINGS.
AND HOW DO YOU RUN WITH
THE CROTCH OF YOUR PANTS
AROUND YOUR KNEES LIKE THAT?
I MEAN, I'D BE A DEAD MAN IF
I COULDN'T RUN, YOU KNOW?
AND THEN THERE'S
YOUR APPEARANCE.
I KNOW, ALL YOUR FUNNY HAIR AND
THE RINGS ON YOUR FACE AND STUFF
IS YOUR WAY
OF STANDING OUT.
I KNOW THAT.
BUT SOMETIMES STANDING
OUT ISN'T SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
LIKE, SAY, IN A POLICE LINEUP.
NOW MY ADVICE TO YOU WOULD BE
TO EITHER MOVE TO NEW GUINEA,
OR TRY TO LOOK LIKE
EVERYBODY ELSE RIGHT AND --
AND BE JUST LIKE
THEM TOO, ONLY BE SNEAKIER.
HEY, YOU MIGHT
EVEN GET ELECTED.
THAT'S IT.
WHERE THE HECK IS HAROLD?
I NEED TO TALK TO HIM.
UH, WHAT IS
IT UNCLE RED?
AWAY YOU GO.
C'MON.
FOR PETE'S SAKE.
HAROLD, HAROLD,
HAROLD, COME HERE.
BOY, THEY LOOK SHARP.
THE COLLEGE CALLED.
THE COMPANY CHANGED
THEIR MIND.
THEY'RE OFFERING
YOU THE JOB.
YOU'RE KIDDING!
OH, OH, THAT'S SO GREAT.
THAT'S GREAT.
THAT'S GOOD.
OH, BUT I'D HAVE TO GO,
AND I COULDN'T LEAVE YOU
TO DO THE SHOW ALONE.
OH, NO, NO.
I KNOW THAT.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU,
THAT'S ALL.
YEAH, YEAH.
I'M GONNA STAY
HERE LIKE YOU,
ALL YOUR LIFE, RIGHT
HERE AT POSSUM LAKE.
I DON'T NEED THE HASSLES
OF THE BIG CITY.
YOU SURE DON'T.
NO, SIREE.
HAROLD, YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M THINKING?
I'VE NEVER HAD
A CLUE REALLY.
JUST THINK ABOUT
THIS, OKAY.
WHAT SAY YOU TAKE THE JOB
WITH THE COMPANY JUST FOR
A LAUGH TO TRY IT OUT.
TAKE THE JOB?
JUST FOR A LAUGH
TO TRY IT OUT.
YEAH, AND I'LL COME DOWN
AND VISIT YOU AT YOUR JOB,
AND WE'LL MAKE THAT
A SEGMENT IN THE SHOW.
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
YOU SHOOTING
IN THE CITY?
FROM WHAT I HEAR,
EVERYBODY'S SHOOTING
IN THE CITY.
AND THEN, ONCE IN
A WHILE, YOU COME UP
HERE TO THE LODGE
AND BE ON THE
SHOW HERE.
OKAY -- OKAY LET'S TRY IT.
LET'S GIVE IT A SHOT.
ALL RIGHT GOOD
FOR YOU.
I'LL TELL YOU
SOMETHING, HAROLD,
YOU'RE NOT SUCH
A BAD GUY.
I'LL TELL YOU
SOMETHING, UNCLE RED,
YOU'RE NOT SUCH A
BAD GUY EITHER.
YOU KNOW
SOMETHING ELSE?
YOU'RE PRETTY SMART.
YOU'RE NOT SUCH
A BAD GUY EITHER.
[ APPLAUSE AND LAUGHTER ]
OH, MEETING TIME.
I GOTTA GO.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
HAROLD.
WELL, THAT'S IT
FOR OUR SHOW,
BUT BE SURE TO TUNE IN
NEXT TIME
WHEN I'M GOING TO
MAKE A VISIT TO THE
CITY AND VISIT HAROLD
BEFORE HE LOSES
THAT JOB OF HIS.
AND IF MY WIFE IS
WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AND IT LOOKS LIKE
HAROLD HAS FINALLY
MATURED AND GROWN UP,
BUT I DON'T SEE
IT HAPPENING TO
ME ANY TIME SOON.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING, AND
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND, WELL, THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
closed captions performed
by INTERCAPTION CANADA.
www.intercaption.com
ALL RISE. ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.