(Garbage cans clanking)
(Crashing and banging)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE YOU
TO THE WISEST, KINDEST,
GENTLEST WOODSMAN
THERE EVER WAS,
BUT HE WAS EATEN BY A BEAR,
SO INSTEAD, HERE'S
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause)
(Cheering)
(Whistling)
(Applause)
(Whooping)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I'M HAPPY TO ANNOUNCE
WE HAD A BREAKTHROUGH
IN OUR ONGOING CASH CRUNCH.
WE HAVE DECIDED TO GROW
SOME OF OUR OWN FOOD.
GARDENING?
THAT'S EXCELLENT!
THAT'S WAY-- OH, THAT'S GREAT.
GARDENING SHOWS GET
WAY BETTER RATINGS
THAN HUNTING AND FISHING SHOWS,
OR WHATEVER THIS IS.
HAROLD, WE'RE NOT GONNA GARDEN.
MEN DON'T GARDEN.
MY WIFE GARDENS,
MY MOTHER GARDENS.
MEN DON'T GARDEN --
THEY FARM, ALL RIGHT?
IT'S THE SAME IDEA,
BUT YOU LOSE MORE MONEY.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED
TO SAVE MONEY.
WELL, WE WILL, HAROLD.
WE LISTED THE FOOD
WE SPEND THE MOST ON.
WE PICKED ONE WE'RE GONNA GROW.
SO, LIKE, FRUITS
OR VEGETABLES OR... ?
NO.
BEER NUTS.
(Audience laughing)
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): RANGER GORD'S GONNA DO
A LITTLE STEP-DANCING FOR YOU.
EDGAR MONTROSE IS WORKING
TIRELESSLY, AS USUAL.
I'M GONNA DO A LITTLE
POWER-GARDENING
OUT BEHIND THE LODGE.
GOOD OLD GARTH HARBLE'S
GONNA GO OUT OF CONTROL.
I CANNOT BELIEVE BEER NUTS IS
THE NUMBER-ONE EXPENSE.
IT ISN'T, BUT WE DON'T KNOW
HOW TO GROW PIZZA.
HOW ABOUT SOMETHING
LIKE RADISHES OR GREEN BEANS,
SOMETHING THAT'S EASILY GROWN?
WE WANT TO GROW STUFF
THAT WE EAT, ALL RIGHT?
LAST YEAR, OUR WHOLE
VEGETABLE BUDGET WAS $7.00.
WE ENDED UP
WITH A $6.00 SURPLUS.
YOU CAN'T JUST PLANT ONE THING.
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR THE SOIL.
YOU GOTTA ROTATE YOUR CROPS.
IF THAT'S LIKE
SPINNING YOUR WHEELS,
I'M DOING THAT RIGHT NOW.
SAY, FOR INSTANCE...
OK, SAY I TAKE A LEEK.
I'D RATHER YOU DIDN'T.
NO...
(Audience laughing)
NO, I'M TALKING
ABOUT BEANS AND LEEKS
AND CUCUMBERS.
YOU GOTTA ROTATE
YOUR BEANS AND LEEKS
AND CUCUMBERS.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE
A CUCUMBER AND ROTATE IT?
(Audience laughing)
(Applause)
(Cheering and whistling)
AND THEY WONDER WHY THE YOUNG
PEOPLE ARE LEAVING THE FARM.
(Red): BILL'S GONNA BE CLEARING
LAND FOR OUR GARDEN.
HE'S GOT ONE OF THESE
CHIPPER-SHREDDER UNITS
THAT TAKES EVERYTHING
AND SHREDS AND CHIPS IT.
THAT'S HOW THEY GOT--
WELL, THE NAME IS
KIND OF SENSIBLE...
KIND OF A SENSIBLE THING.
I HADN'T NOTICED THAT HE WAS...
GOTTA GET THOSE BRAKES
CHECKED...
(Sputtering)
THIS IS EDGAR MONTROSE.
YOU KNOW, TODAY'S EXPLOSIVES
ARE MORE POWERFUL THAN EVER.
FOR EXAMPLE,
THERE'S A NEW KIND OF DYNAMITE
THAT CAN BLOW AN ENTIRE TREE
OVER...
498, 499...
500.
... OVER 500 YARDS.
OOHHH!
(Coughing)
RED...
YOUR DAUGHTER
HAS JUST BROUGHT HOME
HER LATEST ROMANTIC CONQUEST.
ANOTHER FLOAT IN A PARADE
FULL OF LOSERS.
SHE'S JUST SAID THOSE SIX WORDS
YOU'VE BEEN DREADING
SINCE SHE STARTED DATING
THIS DOORKNOB.
"WHAT DO YOU THINK OF HIM?"
NOW, BE CAREFUL.
SHE IS YOUR WIFE'S DAUGHTER.
ONE FALSE WORD, SHE COULD
BLOW UP JUST LIKE HER MOTHER.
EVEN WORSE -- SHE'S YOUNGER.
SHE'S GOT MORE ENERGY.
YOU KNOW THE GUY'S A DEADBEAT.
EVEN YOUR DOG DOESN'T LIKE HIM.
YOU CAN'T TELL HER THAT.
ALL RIGHT, SO, YOU HAVE TO LIE,
BIG TIME.
YOU SAY HE'S A FINE YOUNG MAN.
SAY HE'S OUTSTANDING.
RESPECTABLE.
REALLY NICE.
SAY YOU WANT TO SPEND
TIME WITH HIM.
SAY YOU WANT
TO TAKE HIM FISHING.
OR... OR... OR...
SAY YOU WANT TO TAKE HIM
TO LODGE MEETINGS!
SHE'LL DROP HIM IN A FLASH.
SHE CAN'T STAND THE THOUGHT
OF TELLING PEOPLE
THAT SHE'S DATING
A FRIEND OF HER FATHER'S.
(Audience laughing)
(Applause and cheering)
(Strums acoustic guitar)
OH, THERE'S SOMETHING
ABOUT A CAMP-FIRE
THAT MAKES US ALL
FEEL WARM
NOT JUST ON THE OUTSIDE
BUT IN MANY
OF OUR INTERNAL ORGANS
IT HELPS
TRUE FRIENDSHIPS FORM
OH, THERE'S SOMETHING
ABOUT A CAMP-FIRE
THE SMOKE, THE SMELL
ARE SUBLIME
AND IT'S REALLY, REALLY
MANLY TO BURN UP A FOREST
ONE LOG AT A TIME
(Coughing)
THOUGHT I'D USE
"HANDYMAN CORNER"
TO DO A LITTLE FARMING FOR
ALL OF YOU WHO SEE THE SENSE
IN GROWING YOUR OWN BEER NUTS.
THE MOST IMPORTANT PART
IS PICKING THE GROUND.
DON'T PLANT
WHERE PEOPLE PARK CARS,
ESPECIALLY IF THEY'VE GOT
LEAKY GASKETS.
DON'T PLANT 'EM
NEAR A FIRE HYDRANT.
THAT REALLY AFFECTS
THE TASTE OF THE NUTS.
THEY TASTE LIKE PISTACHIOS.
THE DEAL WITH NUTS IS THAT
THE NUTS ARE THE SEEDS
OF THE NUT PLANTS,
SO TO SEED THE NUT PLANTS,
YOU GOTTA PLANT THE NUT SEEDS,
AND, OF COURSE, VICE VERSA.
FIRST THING YOU WANT TO DO IS
DIG A HOLE THREE INCHES DEEP.
JUST ROUND THAT OUT--
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S FINE.
YOU MAY NEED A SHOVEL
TO GIVE YOURSELF THE LEVERAGE.
NO SHAME IN THAT.
BOY, THIS IS TOUGH STUFF, HERE.
(Gasping and grunting)
(Sniffing)
ALL RIGHT, AT THIS POINT,
A LOT OF PEOPLE WOULD PICK
ANOTHER PIECE OF GROUND.
BUT A LOT OF PEOPLE
AREN'T ME...
NOT THAT THAT BOTHERS THEM.
I FIGURE I'M A MAN
AND THIS IS DIRT.
DIRT DOES NOT TELL ME
WHERE TO GO.
EVERYBODY ELSE DOES THAT.
IF I'VE GOT THE PLAN
TO PUT MY SEEDS HERE,
IT'S UP TO THE SPOT HERE
TO ADAPT TO MY PLAN.
(Grunting)
(Drill squeaking)
OH!
WHEN THE PIONEERS SETTLED
THIS GREAT COUNTRY,
THEY HAD TO OVERCOME OBSTACLES,
OBSTACLES LIKE FAMINE,
DROUGHT, HARD GROUND,
EXPENSIVE BEER NUTS.
DID THAT BOTHER THEM? NO, SIR.
THEY TRIED TO REASON
WITH THE PROBLEM,
TRIED TO SOLVE IT
IN A PEACEFUL WAY,
BUT EVENTUALLY,
WHEN PUSH CAME TO SHOVE,
THEY'D TAKE THEIR BEER NUT
AND THEY'D SHOVE IT
INTO THEIR CUSTOMIZED
B.B/BEER NUT PLANTER.
JUST LOAD 'ER IN THERE...
FIRE 'ER UP...
AND LET NATURE TAKE ITS COURSE.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
HEY, MAYBE THE PEOPLE NEXT DOOR
WOULD LIKE TO HAVE
A BEER NUT TREE OF THEIR OWN.
THAT WOULD BE NEIGHBOURLY.
HEY!
SORRY!
MUST BE VEGETARIANS.
WE GOT SOME PICTURES
TO SHOW YOU IN "MALE CALL".
OUR FIRST ATTEMPT
AT GROWING OUR FOOD
WAS NOT A COMPLETE SUCCESS.
HAD ALL THE EQUIPMENT.
HAD THE ENGINES WAILING AWAY.
HAD A ROAD SALTER THERE
TO SPREAD OUT THE BEER NUTS.
WINSTON HAD HOOKED UP
HIS SEPTIC TANK TO A ZAMBONI.
THAT WAS GONNA GIVE US
THE FERTILIZER.
HAD A STREET CLEANER
FOR IRRIGATING THE FIELD
BUT THE PRESSURE WAS SO STRONG,
IT WASHED THE WHOLE FIELD AWAY,
RIGHT DOWN TO THE BARE ASPHALT.
YOU CAN GET TOPSOIL AT GRACIE'S
GARDEN CENTRE AND VIDEO STORE.
SURE YOU CAN,
BUT IT'S $30 A BUSHEL.
BEER NUTS ARE ONLY
$25 A BUSHEL.
THIS IS NOT "ECONOMICALLY
VIABLE", ALL RIGHT?
YOU'RE GONNA
NEED TOPSOIL.
MAYBE IF EVERYBODY WIPED THEIR
BOOTS, YOU'D GET ENOUGH.
NO, HAROLD, AFTER DARK,
WE'RE GONNA GO TO THE GOLF CLUB
WITH A SNOW-PLOUGH
AND A DUMP-TRUCK.
WE'RE GONNA PEEL BACK
ABOUT FIVE ACRES
ON ONE OF THEM PAR FIVES,
TAKE OUT A FEW TONS OF DIRT
AND JUST LAY 'ER
BACK DOWN AGAIN.
(Audience laughing)
I'VE HEARD OF REPLACING
YOUR DIVOT--
UNCLE RED, YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
NO HARM, THERE, HAROLD.
IT WILL STILL BE A PAR FIVE,
JUST A FOOT LOWER.
NOBODY WILL EVEN NOTICE ONCE WE
HAMMER THE CUP INTO THE GREEN.
YOU COULD ALWAYS MAKE
YOUR OWN TOPSOIL.
YEAH, IT'S REAL EASY.
JUST GET A COMPOSTER.
YOU TAKE FRUIT
AND VEGETABLE SCRAPS
AND SOME WORMS
AND BIPPETY-BOPPETY-BOOP,
YOU GOT GRADE "A" LOAM.
AND IT'S FREE.
FREE, HAROLD?
FREE.
FREE?
FREE -- "ECONOMICALLY VIABLE".
(Laughing)
(Audience laughing)
TOO OFTEN, A PERSON
FORGETS ABOUT SAFETY,
AND FAR TOO OFTEN,
THAT PERSON IS BUZZ SHERWOOD.
YO, RED GUY!
HAROLD, I OWE YOU A NUGGIE.
COME HERE, HAROLD.
OH, COME ON, HAROLD.
MAN, A LITTLE DAB'LL DO YA.
SO, BUZZ, WHAT IS
THE SAFETY THEME TODAY?
I'M GOING FOR A LONG-DISTANCE
ENDURANCE FLIGHT,
SO SAFETY IS CRITICAL.
KIND OF A LONG-DISTANCE
RECORD.
I HOLD THE PROVINCIAL RECORD
FOR THE BIGGEST
MID-AIR EXPLOSION,
AND MOST FLAMES
IN TAKE-OFF
AND
LANDING.
YOU'RE THE ONLY PILOT
TO EVER LAND ON ONE PONTOON.
WHEN DID I DO THAT?
LAST YEAR, YOU BROUGHT 'ER DOWN
IN THE SEWER.
YEAH, BUT THIS STUNT,
I'M DOING ON PURPOSE.
OH! YOU CERTAINLY GOT
ENOUGH STUFF OUT HERE.
I GOT EVERYTHING, MAN.
I GOT THE LIFEJACKETS --
SAFETY FIRST.
ABSOLUTELY.
I GOT EXTRA FUEL,
AND CHECK THIS OUT.
HAVE YOU SEEN THESE?
THEY'RE CALLED "MAPS".
YOU LOOK AT IT AND
IT'S LIKE A LITTLE PICTURE
OF WHERE YOU CAN GO.
NAMES ON IT
AND EVERYTHING -- COOL!
ALL RIGHT, SO WHERE
ARE YOU GOING ON THIS FLIGHT?
WEATHER PERMITTING --
YOU KNOW, SAFETY FIRST --
I'LL BE UP AT THE CRACK OF NOON
AND I'M GOING DUE EAST--
NO, EAST IS OVER THIS WAY.
SORRY, OK, RIGHT.
I'M GOING DUE EAST
TO PORT ASBESTOS--
NO, PORT ASBESTOS, NOW,
THAT WOULD BE DOWN THIS WAY.
REALLY?
OH, YEAH.
FAR OUT! I'M FLYING IN THE
DIRECTION OF PORT ASBESTOS.
OK, AND THEN WHAT?
I'M GONNA FLY TO PORT ASBESTOS
AND LAND, NON-STOP.
THAT'S ONLY ABOUT 20 MILES.
THAT'S NOT GONNA BE
A LONG-DISTANCE RECORD.
OH, NO, I'M NOT GOING
FOR A WORLD RECORD.
THIS IS, UH...
I'M SORT OF GOING
FOR A PERSONAL BEST HERE.
(Laughing)
OH! OH! OH...
(Coughing)
THIS IS EDGAR MONTROSE,
REMINDING YOU
THAT USING
JUST A LITTLE EXTRA FUSE WIRE
IS WORTH THE EXPENSE.
GIVE ME ANOTHER 30 YARDS!
IT'S "MALE CALL"!
(Applause and cheering)
OUR LETTER TODAY COMES FROM FRED
FROM FENELON FALLS
AND HE SENT US
SOME PHOTOS, HAROLD.
WHY DON'T YOU READ THE LETTER?
OKEY-DOKEY, IT GOES
AS FOLLOWS... UM...
"THESE ARE PICTURES
FROM OUR FISHING TRIP.
"THE FIRST ONE SHOWS
THE SIX OF US
"IN OUR FISHING OUTFITS,
MAKING SILLY FACES.
"NEXT IS OUR FAVOURITE
FISHING SPOT, SIX STONE RIDGE.
"THE THIRD PHOTO
SHOWS OUR LUNCH,
"A HALF-DOZEN
OPEN-FACED SANDWICHES,
"AND FINALLY, TWO BIG TROUT
AND FOUR BASS."
THESE ARE NOT THE CLEAREST
PICTURES I'VE SEEN, HAROLD.
I THINK THAT'S
THE FAMILY OF SIX.
NO, I THINK THOSE ARE
THE SIX FISH, THERE.
(Audience laughing)
WHAT'S ALL THAT GREEN STUFF?
THAT'S... THAT'S MOSS.
THAT'S THE SIX STONES.
THAT COULD BE THE LETTUCE
ON THE SANDWICHES.
AREN'T THOSE EYES?
THOSE ARE FISH-EYES, I THINK.
NO, THOSE ARE PIMENTOS.
OH, YEAH.
THOSE ARE THE-- THOSE ARE THE--
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THOSE ARE THE FISH.
THERE'S THE FISH
OVER HERE.
LOOK, TWO TROUT,
FOUR BASS.
OH... WHY ARE THE TROUT
WEARING RUNNING SHOES?
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
THANKS FOR WRITING, FRED.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU HAD
A GREAT TIME ON YOUR HOLIDAY.
EITHER THAT'S A DILL PICKLE
OR MOM NEEDS A NOSE JOB.
RANGER GORD,
THERE'S A LOT MORE TO YOUR JOB
THAN JUST WATCHING
FOR FOREST FIRES.
GOSH, YES, RED, INFINITELY.
IF I ONLY HAD TO WAIT
FOR FIRES,
I'D HAVE GONE NUTS BY NOW.
I ALSO KEEP TRACK
OF THE WEATHER.
IT'S TIME TO TAKE
TODAY'S WEATHER REPORT.
IF YOU LIKE, YOU CAN WATCH.
THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
I DON'T MIND.
(Clearing throat)
SUNNY...
WELL...
NO.
NO WAY -- PARTLY CLOUDY.
I'D SAY SO, YEAH.
AND...
... WARM.
OK, THERE IT IS.
YOU CALL THAT IN
TO THE WEATHER OFFICE?
NO, I JUST KEEP THEM.
I'VE GOT 16 YEARS
OF WEATHER REPORTS IN MY TOWER,
ALL READY TO GO.
READY TO GO FOR WHAT?
WHATEVER.
OH.
WHATEVER!!
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH!
ANOTHER IMPORTANT PART
OF THE FOREST RANGER'S JOB
IS WILDLIFE MANAGEMENT.
IT'S MY JOB TO WATCH
THE SPECIES
AND TO MAKE SURE
THAT ANY ONE SPECIES
DOESN'T BECOME TOO NUMEROUS.
IF THEY DO,
I HAVE TO THIN THEM OUT.
BY KILLING THEM, GORD?
YEAH.
YEAH, IT'S NECESSARY
TO MAINTAIN NATURE'S BALANCE.
I'M VERY CAREFUL, THOUGH.
I ONLY TRY TO TAKE OUT
THE ELDERLY OR THE WEAK
OR THE VERY LONELY.
UM, FOR INSTANCE, HERE.
LET'S HAVE A LOOK
AT THESE ANTS.
YOU NOTICE
THERE'S WAY TOO MANY OF THEM.
YOU SEE THAT?
SO THEY HAVE TO BE THINNED OUT.
HERE WE GO.
(Yelling)
DIE! DIE! DIE! DIE!
OH, HE-E-E-ERE'S JOHNNY!
OH, YOU THINK SO, HUH?
AHHH!
SEE THAT BIG ONE THERE?
(Yelling)
DIE! DIE! DIE!
LIKE I SAID, IT KEEPS ME SANE.
WELL, I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE DOING IT ENOUGH, THEN.
OK.
(Yelling)
(Humming)
THE POSSUM LODGE COMPOSTER
HAS BEEN OFFICIALLY OPENED.
WE'RE ACCEPTING ANYTHING
FROM ANYONE WHO WANTS
TO DUMP SOMETHING.
WE'VE HAD SCRAPS OF BROCCOLI
AND TURNIP,
BUT SO FAR, IT'S MOSTLY TIRES.
UNCLE RED, YOU CAN'T MAKE
TOPSOIL OUT OF TIRES.
YOU NEED PLANT MATERIAL.
IT'S A CHEMICAL REACTION.
IF YOU HAVE CHEMICALS,
YOU'LL HAVE REACTIONS.
IT'S SITTING THERE NOW.
STINKY'S GONNA BRING SOME
PAINT CANS AND SOME KIELBASA.
THAT SHOULD GET 'ER GOING.
LIFE'S SO SIMPLE WHEN YOU DON'T
KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
(Red): MEANWHILE, BACK AT
THE CHIPPER AND SHREDDER,
WE'RE STILL TRYING
TO HAVE AN ADVENTURE.
WE USED TO RENT THESE THINGS,
THESE UNITS.
THEY'RE PRETTY--
... PRETTY EXPENSIVE.
WELL, THAT WILL BE FINE.
IT WILL BE COVERED.
JUST GET-- OW! OW!
BY GOLLY.
ANYWAY-- NO, BILL,
GET THE HAND OUT.
GET THE HAND OUT --
THERE WE GO.
YEAH, GET THE HAND--
THESE UNITS ARE GAS-POWERED,
WITH A FOUR-CYCLE.
YOU DON'T NEED A LOT OF POWER.
THEY REALLY THROW
THE CHIPS, THOUGH.
I WOULD SUGGEST THAT YOU...
THAT YOU EMPTY THE UNIT,
UM, BEFORE STARTING.
YOU PUT THE BRANCHES IN,
AND LOOK AT THAT THING.
ISN'T THAT BEAUTIFUL?
JUST SHRED EVERYTHING UP.
THEY'RE A GOOD UNIT.
THOSE ARE ROCKS OR STONES.
YOU'RE GONNA-- BILL!
THOSE ARE GONNA FIRE
OUT OF THERE!
OH, MY GOSH!
LOOK OUT! LOOK OUT!
I PUT THE VAN
BEHIND THE BARN.
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
NO, TAKE IT OFF
THE PITCHFORK, BILL.
TAKE IT OFF THE PITCHFORK.
NO, I DON'T MEAN THAT WAY.
NO, BILL, THAT'S--
METAL FORK-- METAL--
HANG ON, HANG ON, HANG ON!
OH, BOY! OH, BOY!
OH, BOY!
OHHHH, MAN!
ALL RIGHT, BILL,
DON'T EVER DO--
BILL, YOU'RE--
COME ON OUT OF THERE.
STOP PLAYING IN--
DON'T PLAY IN THERE.
GET OUT OF THERE.
OUT YOU COME, OUT YOU COME.
ONE GOOD YANK AND--
OH! SHOE'S COME OFF!
OH, BOY! OH, BOY!
OHHHH!
YOU ALL RIGHT, BILL?
(Groaning)
WELL, HE'S SHREDDED,
BUT HE LOOKS PRETTY CHIPPER.
(Laughing)
OH, MAN.
STAY TUNED FOR AN IMPORTANT
LESSON ON PAINT FUMES.
WHOO!
HO! HEY! OW! HELLO!
WHAT IS THAT SMELL?
WHOA
(Laughing)
IT'S GREAT, ISN'T IT?
THE OLD COMPOSTER'S
REALLY STARTING TO HUM.
OH! ARGH!
THE TRUCK BATTERIES
KIND OF GAVE IT A JUMP-START.
I HEARD AN EXPLOSION.
HOW DO YOU MAKE COMPOST
EXPLODE?
I NEVER HEARD
OF THAT BEFORE.
WE ARE THE MEN
OF POSSUM LODGE, HAROLD.
WE'RE CUTTING-EDGE.
(Audience laughing)
CUTTING CORNERS
IS MORE LIKE IT!
I SAW BUSTER
THROWING
A MATTRESS ON THERE.
COMPOSTERS DON'T LIKE
MATTRESSES.
WELL, HE SEEMED TO ENJOY IT.
"HE"?
IT'S ONE OF THE GUYS NOW?
YEAH, YEAH.
WE GAVE IT A NAME.
WE CALL IT IAN THE COMPOSTER.
WE PUT THE MATTRESS ON, AND
IAN SNIFFED AT IT AND THEN...
REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE MAP OF THE PONDEROSA
AT THE BEGINNING OF "BONANZA"?
YEAH, LITTLE BROWN SPOT.
IT GOES UP IN FLAMES
AND THE WHOLE MAP'S IN SMOKE.
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE MATTRESS.
INSTEAD OF FLAMES,
IT WAS GREEN GOO.
THAT'S WHEN THE REALLY BAD
SMELL STARTED.
EVEN STINKY PETERSON
IS COMPLAINING.
WOULDN'T BE SO BAD
IF WE WERE UPWIND.
WE ARE.
OH, BOY.
YEAH.
(Audience laughing)
WE'RE ALL SET TO PLAY
OUR POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME
WITH ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER
GARTH HARBLE.
JUST GET THE WORD FROM HAROLD
AND SHOW IT TO THE PEOPLE
AT HOME.
AHHH...
SAY THIS IN 30 SECONDS OR LESS,
YOU'LL WIN OUR GRAND PRIZE --
A YEAR'S SUPPLY OF LAXATIVES
AND A USED TUBA.
OH, OK.
YOU READY TO GO?
OK.
UH... GUIDANCE.
GUIDANCE, GUIDANCE, GUIDANCE...
GUIDANCE COUNSELLOR.
USELESS, USELESS.
NO, THAT SQUIRREL
MAULED YOUR ARM.
IT WAS OUT OF...
... ITS GOURD.
NO, NO -- PROBABLY,
BUT WHAT IT LACKED WAS...
VITAMIN "C", I WOULD SAY.
PEOPLE WEAR A GIRDLE
BECAUSE IT GIVES THEM...
... A RASH.
WHAT?
UH, I'VE BEEN TOLD.
ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
WHAT DO YOU DO TO ANIMALS?
CLEAN 'EM, GROOM 'EM,
CURSE 'EM!
WHAT IT SAYS ON YOUR TRUCK.
UH, ISUZU!
NO, YOUR JOB NAME!
UH, AREA REPRESENTATIVE!
WHAT DO MEAN PEOPLE DO
TO ANIMALS?
TURN 'EM INTO CHICKEN FINGERS!
REALLY?
YEAH, APPARENTLY.
OK, WHAT YOUR BOSS DOES TO YOU.
OHHHH! CONTROL!
THAT'S THE ONE!
BOY, THAT WAS GREAT.
ALL RIGHT, THE IMPORTANT THING
WHEN USING SOLVENTS IS, UH...
CAN'T REMEMBER RIGHT NOW.
(Laughing)
OH, THAT'S PRETTY, ISN'T IT?
OH, HELLO!
UH, YEAH, I THINK IT'S, UM...
UH, THERE'S SOMETHING.
BOY, THAT WAS A GREAT ALBUM.
OHHH... OHHHHH...
NO, NO, I REMEMBER --
VENTILATION.
IT'S 3:00 IN THE MORNING.
SHE'S ROLLING OUT OF BED
TO ANSWER THE CALL O' NATURE.
SHE'S LIVED WITH YOU
FOR 15 YEARS
SO THERE'S NO NEED
TO TURN THE LIGHT ON.
AND THEN YOU HEAR
THAT CRASH AND SPLASH
AND THAT SHRIEK.
(Audience laughing)
SHE TOLD YOU
TO LEAVE THE SEAT DOWN.
(Audience laughing)
YOU PROMISED HER
YOU'D LEAVE THE SEAT DOWN.
GUESS WHAT.
SEAT WASN'T DOWN.
NOW SHE'S GOT A COLD PORCELAIN
RING AROUND A WARM PART OF HER,
HER KNEES ARE UP TO HER CHIN,
AND SHE'S STUCK.
(Audience laughing)
SHE'S THE ONE
SPORTING A BULL'S-EYE
BUT YOU'RE THE ONE IN TROUBLE.
MAJOR DEEP, SO WHAT DO YOU DO?
CAN'T HELP YOU THERE,
LITTLE BUDDY.
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
(Audience laughing)
(Applause)
WELL, I'LL TELL YA.
LIFE IS STILL THE SAME MYSTERY
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN.
WELL, NO,
UNCLE RED,
I'M SORRY I WAS DOUBTING
YOU GUYS.
I DO NOT SMELL
IAN THE COMPOSTER,
SO YOU WERE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT
IN WHAT YOU WERE DOING.
DON'T BE SO SURE, HAROLD.
I WAS WRONG -- I'M SORRY.
I DON'T SMELL IAN
SO YOU WERE RIGHT IN PUTTING IN
THOSE MOTOR WINDINGS
AND ANTIFREEZE AND SOCKS.
I WAS WRONG.
THE REASON YOU DON'T SMELL IAN
IS BECAUSE HE'S GONE, HAROLD.
WHAT?
GONE? HOW'S HE GONE?
HE LEFT UNDER HIS OWN POWER
IN THE NIGHT.
HE GOT UP,
AND YOU CAN SEE THE PATH.
THE GRASS IS DEAD AND THERE'S
ACID BURNS IN THE TREE BARK.
UNCLE RED,
WHAT HAVE YOU CREATED?
THAT MONSTROSITY'S HEADING
RIGHT FOR TOWN!
HAROLD, HE'LL HAVE TO CROSS
MERCURY CREEK.
(Laughing)
IF THAT DOESN'T FINISH HIM,
THE PUNKS
AT THE VIDEO ARCADE WILL.
OH, YEAH!
LOOK AT THIS --
YOU DID ALL THAT WORK, BUT YET,
(Singing) YOU STILL DO NOT
GET YOUR FREE BEER NUTS.
WRONG AGAIN,
MR. OVERBITE.
SOMEBODY
BROUGHT OVER
A 50-GALLON DRUM
OF OLD PEANUT BUTTER.
WE FISHED THAT OUT OF THE PILE.
WE'LL ROLL IT INTO BALLS,
DRY IT, SALT IT,
AND GOBBLE THEM DOWN.
WELL, ISN'T THAT NICE?
YOU'LL BECOME
YOUR OWN LITTLE COMPOSTER.
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME.
GRAB SOME PEANUT BUTTER
AND START ROLLING.
CLEAN YOUR FINGERNAILS FIRST.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
THIS IS A GOOD NIGHT
TO INVITE YOUR PARENTS OVER.
I'VE SEEN SO MANY CHEMICAL
REACTIONS TODAY,
IT WOULD BE NICE TO BE
WITH SOMETHING INERT.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Cheering and whistling)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): OK, STAND UP.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Harold): THE TRAVELLING DENTIST
IS COMING THROUGH TOWN AGAIN.
IF YOU CAN'T MAKE IT,
LEAVE YOUR TEETH IN A BOX
AT THE BACK OF THE ROOM.