Seems like everywhere you go lately, you see
more and more of these bobblehead dolls.
Oh sure, it was fine with hockey players,
baseball players and important guys like
that. But now that everybody's trying to
make a quick buck, this thing has really
gotten out of control.
On the other hand, they do make a nice gift.
Of course, like any good, handy man, I like
to take existing ideas and make them bigger,
better and potentially more disturbing.
A lot of people don't carry these mannequins
around in their car to discourage stalkers.
Also lets them use the carpool lane.
But I'm thinking we can make this unit a lot
more lifelike by using an old car spring to
turn this baby into a full size bobblehead.
Let's hope nobody just tuned in.
I'm a pretty good driver, and I.
It. Big, big week up at the lines this week.
This is our annual softball tournament.
We got a pretty good team this year.
Mr. Hatfield is shortstop.
Mose Thompson his wide stop.
And old man Sedgwick is third base.
He's not playing third base, he is.
Well, we got a problem.
Just a minute, Harold, grab grab the bat
there, will you just about everything right
there on the game? Yeah, yeah.
Ok, now think fast. Come on.
Come on. Go for it. Wow!
A digger. Oh, yeah.
Baseball is not my sport.
No, no. I would imagine that you're not.
My sport list is pretty extensive, Harold.
I'm not sports oriented.
I'm not sports oriented. No, no, no, no, no.
Those who can do those who can't.
Yeah. You know, our problem is they'll
hardly any guy in the team can afford the
twenty dollars entry fee.
Oh, I know that that's because the government
cut off all their unemployment checks.
They do that if you don't have any work for
a while.
The only way to keep getting paid for doing
nothing ever is to actually work for the
government.
Well, it's a shame that the team won't have
any representation in the tournament this
year. Is there anything I can do?
Not usually. We'll see, you know, me, do the
guys could find work even for a week?
See that would that would trigger their poky
to start up again?
Oh, I heard down in the amusement park,
they're hiring people to hose off the world
and hurl.
Now, we don't need real jobs, we just we just
need fake jobs you don't like.
One guy could get a second guy to do
something, you know, and then pretend to pay
him. And then the third guy could work for
the second guy and then the fourth guy for
the third guy. And then eventually the money
would come all the way around, you know?
Ok, but what does that money come from?
Well, that's a great idea, you can lend it to
us.
Yeah. You just asked me for anything you
could do.
And you get the money back.
I will.
Yeah, yeah, OK.
Well, all right. If you say so, then OK.
All right. You know what, though?
I just don't see it.
Well, Harold Harold,
You know, of course you don't see it.
You're an umpire, huh?
It's time for the
Possum Lodge word game.
Today's prize is this coupon for a shampoo
and hairstyle from the exclusive hair salon
Fabio of Port Asbestos.
If you're bald, he'll do your dog.
Ok. Cover your ears, Dalton Red, you've got
30 seconds to get Dalton to say this word
infatuation in at you.
All right. And go.
All right, Dalton, you see a guy who's got a
glazed look on his face.
He's been a victim of this.
Too many donuts. No, OK, no, no, no, this is
like an obsession.
Something about a person that means you
can't stop thinking about them.
They owe me money.
Ok, no, no. This is something that really
holds your interest, a bank.
Now don't get off that, OK, this is
personal, OK?
Like something really special about a girl?
I mean, she may not be the most beautiful
woman in the world, but you know she can
afford to pay for dinner.
I read you're almost out of time.
Ok, Don, remember back in high school,
Bernice broke up with me.
I was real sad. I put on about 40 pounds.
That's because she had this power over me.
Power, come on. And that's because of all the
salt and fat you ate.
There we. That's the
repair shop, part of the show we call, if it
ain't broke.
You're not trying. Joining me today is local
demolitions expert and explosives enthusiast
Edgar Montrose. What do you got for us
today, Edgar?
Oh, never on an empty stomach red.
That's not why I'm here.
I'm having trouble getting these jars open.
Yeah, give it a try.
Why do you want the lids off anyway?
Well, I got a hot date tonight and I think
one of these jars definitely has mouthwash in
it.
What's on the other one?
Nitroglycerin. Well, quick jumping around
read, You're making me nervous.
I still need the mouthwash.
Ten minutes. Yeah. You wrap your hands around
the jar.
Ok, hold a real solid OK.
Yeah. Might help if that finger wasn't
missing or
It's not missing, right?
I know exactly where it is.
It's up at the quarry, still pointing at the
no smoking sign.
Ok, there you go, check that
Huey P. Huey, that's the
Nitro. All right, all right.
No, no. Put her down towards the edge.
Not too close to the edge.
We're down over there. Hey, that's good.
Ok, all right. Good.
And I'll just pop this one open for, you
know, it should be good.
There you go. Everybody can breathe easier
now.
Oh, good. Good.
Bottoms up. Yeah. Good idea.
What?
Well, I guess they're both natural.
Well, Edgar, you better cancel that date.
Oh, no.
Women like hot men, red, where's that red hot
men?
Wait till she sees this.
You know, when you look back over the history
of man since the beginning of time, you see
an evolution from a pathetic creature who
spent most of his time on all fours,
sometimes called the husband to a Homo
erectus, which is Latin, but still scares me.
And finally, to the ultimate stage of a
middle aged man's development full recline.
This is the perfect position for a man to
watch television or read the newspaper or
receive his behavior modification therapy.
It's well known we've all heard of the
recline of the American empire.
While a full recline is the perfect position
for the middle aged man, doesn't it make
sense to allow him to be in that position as
often as possible, not just for things he
does once a year? I go to church hard at
work.
I'm talking about reclining on a daily
basis, like when you're driving your car.
I can reach the pedals from the prone
position, so I didn't need to do anything
about those, but I figure I may need to
steer at some point.
So I took the drive assembly off this ten
speed bike, added some chain to her and made
myself a remote steering wheel.
Thanks to the simple technology of chain and
sprockets, I can now drive flat out.
Big wheel, keep on turning rubber just keeps
on burning.
And if my arms get tired from driving
straight legs, say, going across the Scotch
one, I just put her in cruise control.
Now, of course, seeing where you're going is
almost as important as being comfortable, so
I need to look up through the roof.
It would be helpful if this car had a
sunroof, but I'm not going to complain about
that when I look around at all the riches
that I do have.
Ok, thanks, thanks very much.
Yeah, I got a tip for you.
You know, there's some type of foam
insulation in the roof of a car and it's very
flammable. A lot of you may not know that.
Ok, amount and a full length mirror at just
the right angle so that I'll be able to see
the road while I'm laying down this mirror
is actually mounted on our back door, so I
just took the whole thing. Of course, now
with no bathroom there, that means we can't
have company. So it's a win win.
Some of you probably already realize that
that mirror is going to make things look
upside down to me.
It's the same thing that happens with
binocular lenses.
So what I did was I took the lenses out of
this made myself a pair of glasses that'll
make the reflection right side up.
I'm a lot smarter than I look.
Ok, don't don't put the glasses on until
you're actually driving the car.
Get a real bad headache. That's our if the
women don't find you handsome, they should at
least find your handy, OK, time to prove
that a lazy boy is not just a chair, it's a
way of life.
I read in the paper that more and more men
are taking off all of their body hair with
razors, lasers and, yes, even duct tape.
Let me just say this about that, our.
And apparently, some guys are even having
the bikini waxing so they can wear a thong.
Please don't do that. No guy looks good in a
thong.
Where one and especially don't shave to do
it, then God gave you body hair to hide the
ugly parts. It's really his way of saying
yikes.
So don't go against that whole thing.
Keep the body here and go one step further.
Wear clothes, lots of clothes.
The more close you have on, the more
attractive you are.
That's actually true with ninety nine
percent of people.
That's why the birth rate is so low at
nudist camps.
Don't take my word for it.
Go ahead. Ask your wife, she'll tell you.
Do you want you to wear as many clothes as
possible as often as possible?
And the only thing she wants you to shave is
your face.
And it's not just because she's the one who
has to clean out the bathtub.
Remember, I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
If you eat something, set it free.
If it comes back to you.
Call me.
Our fake work make work project is going
great.
Mike just has to pay me for pretending to
stack is firewood, and we're done.
See, I got the two hundred bucks from
Harold, and then I hired Junior Single to
give me stock market investment advice,
which was don't.
And then he hired Stinky to do a little feng
shui around his outhouse.
And then Stinky hired Buster to pretend to
be a male escort.
And then Buster paid Mike not to rob him.
Read.
Yeah, I need that two hundred dollars back
now.
Well, no, no, no, not not yet, Harold,
because actually when I get that money, we
need that to pay our entrance fee into the
softball tournament.
Ok, but when do I get my money?
Wallace, you know, it's going.
It's going to be a while because the guys
are all going down to the government office
this afternoon. They're going to report
their recent employment, and that's going to
trigger the benefits to start up again.
So it's it's actually Harold.
It's a little complicated.
Don't try to understand it.
Oh, here we go now, Mike, you got my two
hundred bucks for me.
Well, yeah, I'd like to pay you, Mr.
Green, but I just had to look at the wood
pile and I'm not happy.
Well, don't look at it. Just give me the
money and honest day's pay for an honest
day's work.
Shame on you, Mr.
Green. It was fake work.
Mike, I was just pretending to stack the
firewood.
Well, fine. I'll just pretend to pay it.
I got you. I got my money anyway.
Why don't you just give it to me and I'll be
happy to help you stack your wood, Mike?
Ok? See, that's what friends do.
It's pretty complicated, Uncle Read, Don't
try to understand.
Building walls, we're having a game of
foosball out behind the lines, not the kind
of game I like to do something more action
at least can feel like almost like video
game. I try to take part in that.
But what are very defensive and that's how
they roll.
Maybe I join. They don't like, they don't
like you to join these two.
So I'm just and I'm just standing there
watching, you know, what am I supposed to do
watching? That's no fun.
So they come over to see if I'm OK.
I thought I was really just to retrieve the
ball.
But I didn't hurt that bad, so I figured
give it one more note.
All right, but I'm a quick learner.
I'm giving my. Little gap never hurt
anybody.
Now, Walter, he's he's athletic, he's young,
and he's got the quick moves and everything.
He's got all got the feet going, got
everything going.
Bill is what can I say that's not
insensitive?
Yeah, that's not really says it for me, and
Bill got he got his clothes caught in one of
the authors not noticing, so has he spins
that handle that certain bills trying to get
get himself on the hook from that?
And then he starts to have other problems
and that is, his pant leg gets caught in
there and then, oh. Why that is that has got
it.
And Walter, just in his own, in his own
world there really in, oh boy, that is.
That can't be good. So I'm pointing out, no,
we've got a problem here, and Bill is really
jammed up good. So I figure if I turn this
one counterclockwise and that just just a
little bit, just turn it. No, no, no, no,
no, that's wrong.
That's wrong. Hey, no.
Walter figures third one over with a good,
hard clockwise spin, and he's OK.
Yeah, no. I think we're going to.
We're got never got. And I think, yeah,
yeah,
Yeah, we got him good.
All right. Now what happened was Bill gets
up and it turns out the whole thing was a
ruse. He was just faking it because he had a
moon in mind.
It comes right about now, scores the winning
goal, gets into the big celebratory dance,
but intellectual often in life.
You don't always have the last laugh back
then.
Oh boy.
Ernest, what about one of these fancy
stainless steel fridges?
Oh, I know they look great from a distance,
but who wants to be looking at their
reflection as they're reaching for a whole
bowl of gravy?
I have two things at my disposal.
A screwdriver and my imagination.
They're about the same size.
Ever been to those fun houses?
Remember how they had those magic mirrors
that make you look skinny?
Well, those mirrors are kind of like
magicians.
They're not actually magic.
They're just a little bent.
Ladies and gentlemen, we
Interrupt the Red-Green show so that I may
bring you the following important
environmental message.
Greetings, campers, ranger Gord here with
another one of my patented Holderness safety
tips, say now here's a bucolic scene a
couple of amateur orthodontists out for a
leisurely afternoon of birdwatching.
Oh, Boy Scout Ranger hard, we're watching
those woodpeckers up there.
Ho, ho, ho ho.
Fine specimens, too.
But unfortunately, what you bird brain bird
watchers don't know is that when a woodpecker
senses an intruder, he's liable to feel
threatened.
That's why it's always safer to disguise
yourself as a tree or a shrubbery.
Here we go.
They're all safe now.
Mr. and Mrs. Woodpecker.
Oops, I forgot.
There's nothing woodpeckers love more than
dead wood.
You make fun.
You didn't have to say anything, Harold, we
were doing OK.
You weren't telling the truth.
When is that OK?
Man, I wish you were married.
Don't give me that lying is never right,
those are the rules.
So anyway, we go down to the government
offices to get the guys unemployment
insurance reinstated and reported that each
one of them had just had two hundred dollars
in gainful employment.
See, which is not true.
Well, so what? Ok, but here's what they said.
They can't collect any of the policy until
they pay each one of them 50 bucks in income
tax and another four bucks in UIC,
Which is true.
This great country of ours can not continue
to survive if each and every person is not
willing to pay their fair share.
I can't believe you still have all those
teeth.
Let's see, our ace in the hole was we had
never identified ourselves.
We're just going to walk out scot free, but
oh no, George Washington here has to jump out
of the cherry tree. Give them all our names
and address.
So I called it.
Well, it was the wrong call.
It was the right call.
It was a stupid, stinking.
You watch yourself, Mr.
If they took on the
Stupid, stinking wrong calls in the history
of stupid, stinking wrong calls and put them
in a stinking pile, and it was stinking.
You could still smell your stinking call.
That's it. Yeah, right?
I was just getting a hair that, you know,
with some meeting time where everybody's out
of here. Let's get this.
Get you. Yeah, you're good.
You're good. So my wife is watching, I'll be
coming straight home after the meeting, I had
no runs, no hits, a couple of errors and I'm
still hoping to get home on a fielder's
choice might even go into extra innings, but
I doubt it.
And the rest? Yeah, thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself and Harold and the whole
gang up here at Possum Ranch, keep your stick
on the ice.
We. All right.
Why this he set out?
Buyer heads for the Malmesbury.
I'm a man, but I can change if I have to.
I guess. All right, as we are officially out
of the softball tournament, and I think this
is a time for us to show a little maturity,
restrain ourselves.
Grow up a little bit.
Suck it up. Don't worry about it.
No big deal. Nobody's fault.
All is forgiven. That kind of thing.
Just let it just let it go.
It's such a stupid call.