YOU KNOW, IF YOU NEED
NEW HUBCAPS,
JUST DIG A HOLE.
OF COURSE, WHAT'S IMPORTANT
IS WHERE YOU DIG IT.
OH, THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
I'VE GOT A COUPLE THAT MATCH.
[ SOUND OF CAR DRIVING BY ]
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE IT.
UH, YOU KNOW, SOMEBODY LEFT A
BIG LOAD OF STEEL DRAINPIPES
UP BY THE MAIN ROAD THERE.
WELL, REALLY, DEPARTMENT OF
HIGHWAYS OR WHATEVER.
AND THEY'RE JUST
LYIN' THERE,
JUST A FLIMSY LITTLE CHAIN
LOCKED AROUND THEM THERE.
IT'S A SHAME TO SEE THEM JUST
SITTIN' THERE, YOU KNOW.
THEY'RE HEAVY, BUT IF YOU CAN
GET 'EM UP ONTO YOUR SHOULDER,
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN
ACTUALLY CARRY 'EM.
I ONLY TOOK A
COUPLE DOZEN,
BUT, UH, MIKE AND DALTON
PRETTY MUCH CLEANED THE
PLACE RIGHT OUT,
OH, UH,
HEY, DALTON.
HOW'S THE NECK?
OH, IT'S PRETTY SORE,
YOU KNOW.
A LITTLE STIFF.
I DIDN'T REALISE YOU
WERE LEFT-HANDED.
YEAH.
BOY, THAT IS SORE.
YOU KNOW, I HAD TO SLEEP
ON THE FLOOR LAST NIGHT.
ANNE MARIE WASN'T EVEN HOME.
BOY, I TELL YA, THAT
LITTLE MIKE'S GONNA BE
HURTIN' TODAY, HUH?
OH, BOY.
I BET HE'S CURLED UP LIKE
A STRIP OF BACON.
[ LAUGHING ]
OH, OH!
HI, GUYS.
WHAT'S UP?
DOUBLE LYNCHING?
GEEZ, MIKE.
HOW COME YOU'RE NOT
ALL BENT OUTTA SHAPE?
'CAUSE I TAKE GOOD
CARE OF MYSELF.
DID YOU KNOW POSSUM LAKE
HAS A NEW CHIROPRACTOR,
AND I WAS HER
FIRST CUSTOMER.
HER?
OH, YEAH.
OH, MY,
YEAH!
YOU GUYS SHOULD
GO DOWN AND SEE HER.
SHE DID THINGS TO MY
BODY THAT ARE BARELY LEGAL.
WOW!
IT'S THE WORD BARELY
THAT SCARES ME.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I SAID I'D FIND
HER SOME NEW CUSTOMERS.
YOU GUYS IN OR OUT?
NO, I'M OUT.
MY BACK IS,
SO I'M IN.
GOOD MAN.
LET'S GO.
HEY, IT'S NOT TOO
LATE TO CHANGE YOUR
MIND, Mr. GREEN.
NO, NO,
YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I'M FINE.
YEAH,
YOU LOOK FINE.
ALL RIGHT.
GOT MY MOVIES
THERE, ED?
OH, YEAH, I GOT
'EM RIGHT HERE.
BOY, IF THAT WORKS,
I WASTED A FORTUNE
ON A VCR.
[ LAUGHING ]
YOU THINK ANNE MARIE'S GONNA
NOTICE I DIDN'T GET ANY
MOVIES SHE WANTED?
WELL, WHAT MOVIES
DID SHE ASK FOR?
WELL SHE ASKED FOR
"STEEL MAGNOLIAS"
AND "BEACHES".
AND WHAT MOVIES
DID YOU GET?
"SCARFACE" AND
"THE TERMINATOR".
WELL, I THINK WHEN
AL PACINO FIRES UP
THE CHAIN SAW,
SHE MIGHT
TWIG ONTO IT.
YOU GUYS ARE GONNA
HAVE TO HELP ME HERE.
YOU COULD TELL HER THAT THE
VIDEO STORE WAS ALL OUT.
IT'S POSSIBLE.
THERE'S A LOT OF OTHER
WOMEN IN THE AREA, EH.
YEAH, WELL, WHAT IF SHE
PHONES THE VIDEO STORE
AND FINDS THAT ALL 30 COPIES OF
BOTH MOVIES ARE STILL THERE?
OH, NO, NO. SHE CAN'T
PHONE THE VIDEO STORE.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE ON YOUR
WAY INTO THE HOUSE,
YOU'RE GONNA CUT
THE PHONE LINE.
HA HA.
AND THE CABLE.
YOU CUT THE CABLE,
AND YOU WALK IN WITH TONIGHT'S
ONLY ENTERTAINMENT RIGHT
IN YOUR HANDS.
THAT'S BIG POINTS
THERE, BUDDY.
THAT'S FOOL PROOF!
IT'S FOOL
SOMETHIN'.
ALL RIGHT.
SEE YOU, GUYS.
THANKS FOR
THE TIP.
[ CHUCKLING ]
HE'S A DEAD MAN.
YEP.
DEAD MAN WITH
NO PHONE OR CABLE.
[ ELECTRONIC CRASHING SOUNDS ]
OH, UNCLE RED!
HAROLD!
OH, I DIDN'T
SEE YOU THERE.
SIT DOWN.
WOW, THIS IS
A SURPRISE.
YEAH, WELL,
YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
LIFE IS FULL
OF SURPRISES.
ACTUALLY, YOU'LL FIND
THAT OUT VERY,
VERY SOON.
I GOTTA GO.
DID YOU TOUCH ANYTHING
ON MY WORK STATION?
UM --
LIKE, LIKE,
MY CHAIR!
YOU TOUCH MY CHAIR?
WELL, HAROLD,
I MAY HAVE.
SORRY.
SORRY?
SORRY!
YOU COMPLETELY LOST THE
SETTINGS OF MY ERGONOMICALLY
CORRECT WORK STATION.
SORRY!
HAROLD, RELAX.
IT'S A SWIVEL CHAIR,
FOR CRYIN' OUT LOUD.
WELL, I --
TAKE IT EASY.
I KNOW.
YES, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M UNDER A LOT
OF PRESSURE LATELY.
THIS ACCOUNT
I'M WORKING ON --
HAROLD, THAT CAN WAIT
A LITTLE WHILE,
ALL RIGHT.
NOT RIGHT NOW.
GIVE ME ABOUT A
10-MINUTE HEAD START.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
WELL, HOLD IT A SEC.
I WANNA SHOW YOU WHAT
I GOT TO WORK WITH.
I'VE GOT 20 YEARS OF
THEIR FILES IN HERE,
AND I'M ALMOST DONE.
BOY, IF I LOST THIS,
I DO NOT KNOW WHAT
I WOULD DO.
JUST HOLD ON.
I WANNA SHOW YOU
'CAUSE IT'S NEAT.
HUH.
WHERE IS IT?
WHERE'D IT GO?
I'LL CHECK THE PARKING LOT.
[ ELECTRONIC CRASHING SOUNDS ]
UNCLE RED.
YOU EVER HEARD
THIS BEFORE?
NO, I -- DUNNO.
OH, NEVER HEARD
IT BEFORE?
NO, NO.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
IT'S MY SCREEN SAVER THAT
COMES ON EVERY TIME I
LEAVE MY COMPUTER ON.
[ LAUGHING ]
I GOT YOU.
YOU KNEW ALL ALONG,
DIDN'T YOU?
OH, YEAH.
I GOT YOU, BABE!
WE JOKE LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW, I REALLY TRY TO
STAY AWAY FROM CURRENT
TRENDS AND FADS,
AND I HAVE DONE EVER SINCE I
WORE THAT NEHRU JACKET TO MY
GRADE EIGHT DANCE.
BUT YOU GOTTA GIVE
IN ONCE IN AWHILE,
OR PEOPLE WILL THINK
YOU'RE BEHIND THE TIMES.
LIKE RIGHT NOW,
MY WIFE, BERNICE,
SHE WANTS ONE OF THOSE AUTOMATIC
BREADMAKING MACHINES.
I'M SAYIN', HEY, LET'S SEE IF
THIS HANDYMAN CAN MAKE OUR OWN.
MAYBE MAKE IT OUTTA
SOMETHING WE ALREADY HAVE,
SOMETHING WE ONLY
USE ONCE A WEEK,
LIKE MAYBE AN
AUTOMATIC WASHING MACHINE.
IT'S WATERTIGHT,
IT HAS TIME CYCLES.
IT'S EVEN GOT AN AGITATOR,
SO LIKE MOST OF US,
IT NEEDS THE DOUGH.
I'LL RECYCLE ANYTHING.
OKAY, WHAT YOU GOTTA DO TOO IS
YOU GOTTA CHANGE SOME OF THE
WORDING ON THE CONTROL PANEL.
LIKE WHERE IT
SAYS HEAVY DUTY,
THAT'LL BE WHOLE WHEAT.
DELICATE, UH,
SWITCH THAT TO PASTRY.
AND REGULAR, LEAVE THAT
AS REGULAR I GUESS.
THEN OVER HERE WHERE
YOU GOT SIZE OF LOAD,
YOU WANNA CHANGE
THAT "D" TO AN "F",
AND IT'S SIZE OF LOAF.
AND YOU CAN ADD DIFFERENT
INGREDIENTS IN HERE,
SO YOU CAN GET ALL YOUR
SPECIALTY BREADS.
LIKE YOU COULD
PUT MALT IN THERE.
GIVE YOU MALT BREAD.
COUPLE OF SHOTS OF RYE,
YOU GOT RYE BREAD.
HEY, IT'S A WASHING MACHINE.
THROW SOME SHORTS
IN THERE,
YOU GOT SHORTBREAD.
ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S ABOUT IT,
EXCEPT FOR THE HEAT.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED SOME SORT OF
A SOURCE OF HEAT ON THAT.
I WOULD SUGGEST THAT YOU TAKE
A HEATING ELEMENT OUT OF
AN EXTRA TOASTER.
IF YOU GOT NO EXTRA TOASTERS
LYIN' AROUND YOUR HOUSE,
GET MARRIED.
NOW, THE ELEMENT SHOULD POP
RIGHT OUT OF THIS.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MAKE BREAD.
[ TIMER RINGING ]
OKAY, SHE'S ALL DONE.
MAN, SMELLS GREAT,
DOESN'T IT?
IS THAT A BEAUTIFUL
THING OR WHAT?
AND TO CLEAN OUT THE MACHINE,
JUST A RUN A LOAD OF
WORK SOCKS THROUGH THERE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
WHO WANTS A SANDWICH?
HALT!
WHO GOES THERE?
WHAT'S THE PASSWORD, MISTER?
IT'S ME, GORD.
OH, RED GREEN.
PLEASE COME IN.
HAVE A SEAT.
I'LL BE WITH YOU
IN A MINUTE.
I COULD COME BACK.
WON'T TAKE LONG.
WHAT YOU LOOKIN' AT, GORD?
RESULTS OF SOME
PSYCHOLOGICAL TEST?
NO, RED, THIS IS A SIGN
I'VE BEEN WORKING ON.
I WOULDN'T MIND IF YOU
PROOFREAD IT FOR ME.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELL, IF YOU'RE
GOING FOR STOP,
YOU'RE RIGHT
ON THE MONEY.
PERFECT.
YOU PUTTING TRAFFIC SIGNS
IN THE WOODS, GORD?
THAT'S RIGHT, RED.
I'VE BEEN WATCHING
THE ANIMALS OUT THERE,
AND IT'S CHAOS.
THEY CAN NEVER DECIDE
WHO HAS THE RIGHT OF WAY.
IT USUALLY GOES BY SIZE,
BUT THAT'S JUST NOT FAIR.
I THINK MAYBE THAT'S WHAT
MOTHER NATURE INTENDED.
SURE, THAT'S WHAT MOTHER
NATURE INTENDED, ALL RIGHT.
BUT SHE'S OUT
OF HER MIND.
GORD, DO YOU THINK MAYBE IT'S
TIME FOR YOU TO BE WITH PEOPLE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE?
NO, RED, MY JOB IS
TOO IMPORTANT HERE.
IT'S UP TO ME TO MAKE SURE THAT
ALL THE ANIMALS OF THE FOREST
OBEY THE TRAFFIC RULES OF
THIS GREAT COUNTRY OF OURS.
I THOUGHT YOUR JOB WAS
TO WATCH FOR FOREST FIRES.
HOLY COW,
THAT'S RIGHT!
YOU KNOW,
I SHOULD PROBABLY GO.
I'M DOUBLE PARKED.
YOU KNOW WHAT PIGEONS ARE LIKE.
HOLY HANNA!
HEAD-ON COLLISION, RED.
TWO BUCKS COMING
TOWARD EACH OTHER
AND BANG,
HEAD ON.
THE BIGGER ONE WAS
IN THE WRONG LANE.
IT WAS CLEARLY MARKED, MISTER!
RED, I HAVE A BIG
FAVOUR TO ASK OF YOU.
GORD, YOU KNOW,
I'M HAPPILY MARRIED.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, RED, I'D LIKE YOU,
IF YOU WOULD,R
TO PUT THIS TRAFFIC
TICKET ON HIS ANTLER
ON YOUR WAY DOWN.
NO PROBLEM.
THANKS, RED.
WELL, I GOT ALL THOSE
STEEL PIPES INSTALLED
TO DRAIN THE PARKING LOT.
NOT THAT WE GET
THAT MUCH RAIN,
BUT WE GET A LOT OF RUNOFF FROM
THE LODGE VEHICLES.
AND FROM THE MEMBERS
THEMSELVES, ACTUALLY.
BOY, I REALLY
WRECKED MY BACK.
I DECIDED TO DO
THE WHOLE THING MYSELF.
MIKE'S THE ONLY ONE WHO
CAN STAND UP STRAIGHT,
AND HE WAS BUSY TAKING
DALTON TO THE CHIROPRACTOR.
HEY, RED, I THINK I'M
FEELIN' BETTER!
OH, MAN.
YEP, I'M FEELIN'
BETTER!
YOU SEEM
PRETTY CHIPPER.
I AM CHIPPER.
IT'S VERY ANNOYING.
IT IS,
ISN'T IT?
YEAH, YOU KNOW, RED, YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO TRY THIS
CHIROPRACTIC THING
BECAUSE ANGELA IS THE BEST.
ANGELA?
NOT Dr. ANGELA?
NOT TO ME, NO, SIR, NOW THAT
SHE KNOWS ME OH, SO WELL.
RED, IT IS FANTASTIC.
WAS ALCOHOL INVOLVED IN
THIS MIRACLE AT ALL?
NO, SIR.
JUST THE HEALING HANDS OF THE
MOST BEAUTIFUL, STATUESQUE
REDHEAD YOU'VE EVER LAID
EYES OR ANYTHING ELSE ON.
YOU KNOW, YOU GO IN THERE,
SHE'S GOT THE LIGHTS TURNED
DOWN NICE AND LOW.
SOFT MUSIC PLAYING.
AND THEN, RED,
SHE CRACKS YOUR BONES!
NO KIDDIN'?
OH, YEAH.
SHE POURS OIL ALL OVER YOU
AND THEN STARTS MASSAGING
YOUR MUSCLES.
WOW.
WHAT ARE YOU WEARING
WHEN ALL THIS IS GOING ON?
A REALLY BIG SMILE.
OH, MAN.
HEY, THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH THIS.
THIS IS MEDICAL TREATMENT.
I MEAN, LOOK AT ME.
STOP IT.
WHAT!
STOP DOING THAT.
C'MON, WE GOTTA GET YOU DOWN
THERE AND GET YOU FIXED UP.
I'LL TAKE YOU DOWN THERE AND
MAKE SURE EVERYTHING GOES OKAY.
ALL RIGHT?
WELL, I GUESS I COULD
GIVE IT A TRY.
THERE YOU GO.
YEAH.
WE'LL GO ROUND BY WAY
OF THE CHURCH.
WHY WOULD WE
DO THAT?
THAT'S WHERE YOU
CAN RING THE BELL.
I'D WRING YOUR NECK,
IF I COULD GET
AHOLD OF IT.
SLOW DOWN.
Red:
WAITIN' FOR DALTON TO SHOW UP,
AND WINSTON'S JUST FOOLIN'
AROUND WITH HIS HAMMER THERE.
NO, WINSTON, NO.
ANYWAY, DALTON COME
IN WITH THE LUMBER.
OH, THAT'S A NICE
TRUCK HE'S GOT THERE.
BUT IN THE TRUCK TOO,
HE ALSO --
OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THE HAMMER.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
HE ALSO HAD A BARBECUE.
THAT'S KINDA ODD.
WHAT WE'RE GONNA TRY AND MAKE
IS ONE OF THOSE, UH,
PLAY THINGS FOR THE KIDS THAT
COME UP TO THE LODGE.
SOMETHIN' FOR THEM
TO SWING ON AND EVERYTHING.
SO I TOOK THE FIRST LOAD.
I FIGURED THE GUYS'D BE --
THE GUYS'D BE RIGHT BEHIND ME
WITH THE REST OF THE --
WHERE THE --
AH.
GET OVER HERE!
C'MON, YOU GUYS.
WE GOT WORK TO DO HERE.
SO, ANYWAY, WE BOUGHT
ALL THE LUMBER.
IT WAS ALL LAID OUT,
AND THEY GOT THESE
GREAT KITS NOW.
THEY TELL YOU EXACTLY
WHAT TO BUY,
SO MANY PIECES OF THIS,
SO MANY PIECES OF THAT.
GRAB THAT ONE THERE.
GET OUTTA THERE.
THAT'S YOUNG WALTER.
HE'S NEW AT THE LODGE.
PITCHIN' IN.
HE JUST DOES EVERYTHING
HE CAN TO HELP PEOPLE.
THERE YOU GO.
SO GOT --
WATCH IT.
THERE'S A SINKHOLE THERE.
WALTER, SINKHOLE.
SINKHOLE!
EASY THERE, EASY.
GET HIM UP.
NOW, YOU GOTTA BE CAREFUL
WHERE YOU STEP AT THE LODGE
'CAUSE WE'VE BEEN
HERE A WHILE.
AND, UH, WE GOT
THE INSTRUCTIONS.
I DON'T KNOW WHO
WRITES THESE --
HOW DO YA --
MAYBE, UH, GOSH, UH,
HM-M-M.
UM-M-M.
NO, I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
YEP.
ALL RIGHT,
SO WE ALL GET BUSY.
AND WALTER, YOU'RE --
WALTER YOU'RE STANDIN'
IN THE --
WALTER, YOU'RE STANDIN'
IN THE SINK --
WALTER!
DO YOU NOT
NOTICE THAT, WALTER?
NOW, HERE'S SOMETHIN'
FOR YOU YOUNG KIDS.
YOU BE CAREFUL,
YOU YOUNG KIDS.
IT CAN HAPPEN.
SO ANYWAY --
SO WE GOT HER ALL BUILT,
AND IT JUST DIDN'T LOOK LIKE
ANYTHING THE KIDS WOULD
HAVE ANY KIND OF FUN ON.
I GUESS IT'S --
SORT OF RIGHT AND, UH --
NOPE, I GOT IT.
THIS IS WHERE IT
DONNED ON ME.
I KNOW WHAT
WE'RE DOIN' WRONG.
YOUNG WALTER'S STILL
MEASURIN' THAT BOARD.
COME ON OUT.
WE'RE NOT PUTTING
IT IN THE BASEMENT.
NOW, COME ON.
NOW, IF WE CAN ALL
JUST PITCH IN.
THIS IS WHERE IT'S
GOOD TO HAVE FRIENDS.
EVERYBODY GRAB A CORNER.
PICK 'ER UP.
PICK 'ER UP, GUYS.
WE'RE GONNA TAKE
'ER OVER THERE.
WE'RE GONNA --
SET 'ER DOWN.
BIT ROUGH.
OH, MAN, I GOT THE HEAVY END.
C'MON, SET 'ER DOWN.
SET 'ER DOWN.
DROP 'ER DOWN
RIGHT OVER THERE.
CAREFUL, DON'T STAY
IN THERE LONG, WALTER.
YOU KNOW WHY, DON'T YOU?
YOU KNOW WHERE WE'RE
SETTIN' IT.
YOU KNOW WHERE
WE'RE SETTIN' IT.
RIGHT ON THE OLD --
WELL, YOU KNOW.
YOU KNOW.
WE'RE SETING HER DOWN ON THE
OLD SINKHOLE AND LET --
YOU KNOW, THIS IS WHAT
YOU GOTTA DO.
LET THE ENVIRONMENT
WORK WITH YOU.
DON'T FIGHT IT.
GIVE 'ER A CLUNK AT THE BOTTOM
THERE AND WATCH WHAT HAPPENS.
AND THERE WE GO.
THERE'S OUR SWING SET.
GOOD WORK.
GREAT STUFF.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
WHEN HE WAS ELECTED,
HE WAS THE MOST POPULAR MAYOR
POSSUM LAKE HAD EVER HAD.
HE PROMISED TO PUT
THE TOWN ON THE MAP
AND DECREASE
THE UNEMPLOYMENT RATE.
INSTEAD, HE PUT THE
TOWN IN THE RED
AND INCREASED THE
ILLEGITIMACY RATE.
HE WAS HONEST JOHN JONASSEN.
HE WALKED INTO POSSUM LAKE ONE
DAY, LOOKIN' TO BUY A CAR.
HE ASKED US WHERE THE LOCAL
ROLLS ROYCE DEALERSHIP WAS.
HE JUST COULDN'T
BELIEVE THAT A TOWN
WITH THIS KIND OF VIBRANT ENERGY
AND COSMOPOLITAN FLAIR
WOULDN'T CATCH THE EYE
OF THE ROLLS ROYCE PEOPLE.
IN HINDSIGHT, THAT SHOULD
HAVE BEEN A TIP-OFF.
OH, HE WAS A CHARMER.
I'LL GRANT YOU THAT.
HE ASKED ME HELP HIM
WITH POSSUM LAKE'S BID
FOR THE 1986 WINTER OLYMPICS.
WELL, I DIDN'T KNOW HOW
MUCH HELP I COULD BE.
IT'D BEEN YEARS SINCE
MY LAST GOLD MEDAL
IN PICKLING.
WHEN I ASKED HOW OUR
BID COULD STAND A CHANCE,
HE FLAT OUT TOLD ME.
HE WAS GOING TO BRIBE
THE OLYMPIC OFFICIALS.
HE WAS AHEAD OF
HIS TIME REALLY.
JOHN ALSO SOLD TIMESHARING
HOLIDAY PROPERTIES DOWN SOUTH.
HE WOULD SHOW US THESE
PICTURES OF THESE BEAUTIFUL
BEACH FRONT CONDOS,
AND THEN HE WOULD EXPLAIN THAT
WE COULD SWAP ONE OF OUR PLACES
HERE IN POSSUM LAKE
WITH SOMEBODY WHO LIVED
IN ONE OF THESE JOINTS.
BOY, THAT GUY
COULD SELL, YOU KNOW.
HE -- HE COULD HAVE
SOLD GHANDI A BIG MAC.
ANYWAY, WE BOUGHT INTO IT,
AND TWO WEEKS LATER,
HE SHOWS UP WITH
THIS FAMILY FROM FLORIDA
AND SAYS THAT THEY'RE HERE
TO TIMESHARE WITH US FOR
A MONTH NOW!
SO HE GOES OUT TO HIS CAR,
OPENS THE TRUNK
AND OUT GET FIVE GUYS
WITH BED ROLLS.
THEY WALK INTO OUR LIVING ROOM,
AND THEY CAMP OUT ON THE FLOOR.
THESE PEOPLE WERE WEIRD,
EVEN FOR FLORIDA.
I RECOGNIZED THOSE GUYS.
I'D DONE TIME
WITH THREE OF 'EM.
THEY WERE JUST GUYS ON THE LAM
LOOKIN' FOR A PLACE TO HIDE OUT.
I MEAN, WOULD GUYS FROM
FLORIDA HAVE NO TAN?
AND SCURVY?
C'MON.
HIS BIG SCAM WAS
HONEST JOHN'S PYRAMID SCHEME,
AND THESE WEREN'T
PYRAMID SALES.
THESE WERE REAL PYRAMIDS.
JOHN WANTED TO
BUILD PYRAMIDS,
AND FOR 500 BUCKS, YOU COULD
BE BURIED LIKE KING TUT.
WE THOUGHT HE WAS
ON THE UP AND UP
BECAUSE HE HAD FUNDING FROM
THREE LEVELS OF GOVERNMENT.
WELL, LISTEN TO ME.
THEN HE SOLD A BUNCH OF US
THESE MUNICIPAL BONDS.
THEY WERE MADE OF PAPER,
WHICH WAS GOOD
BECAUSE EVERYBODY IN POSSUM LAKE
HAS A FIREPLACE AND AN OUTHOUSE.
HONEST JOHN JONASSEN KNEW
HE WAS IN TROUBLE.
NOBODY COULD IGNORE THAT
MANY EGGS SMASHIN' AGAINST
THEIR HOUSE.
THEN ONE NIGHT
HE JUST DISAPPEARED.
NOBODY KNOWS HOW.
SOME SAY HE DROWNED TRYING
TO SWIM ACROSS POSSUM LAKE
WITH 700 POUNDS OF PARKING METRE
COINS IN HIS PANTS POCKETS.
WE'D HAVE TO DREDGE
THE LAKE TO KNOW FOR SURE,
BUT WE'RE NOT GONNA GO LOOKIN'
FOR HIM UNTIL WE MISS HIM.
OH, MAN!
I FEEL GREAT.
I TOLD YOU.
THAT ANGELA IS
A MIRACLE WORKER.
I THINK I MIGHT
GO EVERY WEEK.
ME TOO.
WELL, PREVENTION
IS A BIG PART OF
HEALTH CARE, DALTON.
ABSOLUTELY.
BOY, AND SHE
IS GOOD, ISN'T SHE?
OH, SHE IS VERY GOOD.
VERY GOOD.
NOT OFTEN YOU SEE A PROFESSIONAL
DOCTOR WITH EYES LIKE, HUH.
AND THAT RED HAIR.
AND THE SKIN,
LIKE ALABASTER.
SHE'S GOT THE
WHOLE PACKAGE.
OH, MY.
OH, MY GOSH.
Mr. GREEN.
OH, MIKE,
WATCH THIS.
SHOW HIM, DALTON.
HUH?
MAN, THAT'S
HARD TO WATCH.
LOOK, YOU GOT SO MUCH ENERGY,
YOU BETTER GET THOSE PIPES BACK
TO WHERE YOU FOUND THEM
'CAUSE THE ARE ONTO US.
WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
WHO TOLD THEM?
YOU GUYS DID.
NO WAY I SAID ANYTHING.
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
WELL, WHO DID YOU
TELL THEN?
NO, I DIDN'T --
I DIDN'T TELL ANYBODY.
NOBODY?
YOU MUST'VE TALKED ABOUT THEM
PIPES WHEN YOU WERE
GETTIN' TREATED!
ANGELA!
WELL, YEAH,
IT TURNS OUT THAT ANGELA
ISN'T A CHIROPRACTOR
AFTER ALL.
SHE'S A COP FROM
PORT ASBESTOS.
SHE'S WORKIN' UNDERCOVER.
ANGELA'S A COP!
WAIT A MINUTE.
PORT ASBESTOS DOESN'T
HAVE ANY WOMEN POLICE.
YEAH, WELL, SEE,
HERE'S THE OTHER PART.
O-O-O-H.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT'S NOT ANGELA,
IT'S ANGELO.
O-O-O-H!
E-E-E-W!
AH, GUYS,
LOOSEN UP.
I'VE NEVER
FELT BETTER.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
ANGELO, HE'S GONNA MOONLIGHT AS
A MASSEUR OUT OF HIS OWN PLACE.
YOU GUYS INTERESTED?
NOPE.
WELL, I SURE AM.
[ POSSUM SQUEAL ]
OH, MEETIN' TIME.
C'MON, GUYS.
YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
AND I REALLY HOPE YOU'RE NOT,
IF YOU ARE, I'LL BE COMIN'
STRAIGHT HOME AFTER THE MEET --
I THINK I'M GONNA
HAVE A BATH TONIGHT
IN BOILING BLEACH.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
SORRY YOU WATCHED.
UNTIL NEXT TIME, ON BEHALF
OF MYSELF AND
ANGELO,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
closed captioning performed
by INTERCAPTION CANADA
www.intercaption.com
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
HURRY UP.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS,
JOIN ME IN THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE
IF I HAVE TO
I GUESS,
BUT NOT THAT MUCH!