IT’S THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW.
HERE'S THE HOST WITH THE MOST,
IN TERMS OF FACIAL HAIR
AND CREDITORS, THAT IS,
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
HEY, HAROLD.
APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
WELL, BY GOLLY.
YOU'VE PROBABLY GUESSED,
TODAY IS OUR ANNUAL TOURNAMENT
FOR THOSE OF US IN THE P.G.A.,
POSSUM GOLF ASSOCIATION.
SO, IN A FEW MINUTES
THE LODGE MEMBERS WILL BE OUT THERE
THWACKING THEIR NIBLICKS
AND SWINGING THEIR MASHIES
OUT ON THE LINKS.
YOU GUYS BELONG OUT ON
THE LINKS, THE MISSING LINKS.
HA! HA! HA!
THE MISSING LINKS!
I HEARD YOU GUYS WERE BANNED
FROM THE GOLF COURSE
FOR LIFE WITHOUT PAROLE.
WELL, YEAH, WE PLAYED THE GAME
THE WAY THE BRITISH PLAY GOLF,
WHERE THEY DIVIDE IT UP
INTO TEAMS.
POLO.
THEY PLAYED POLO
ON A PUBLIC GOLF COURSE.
WE WEREN'T PLAYING POLO.
ON POLO, THEY'RE ON HORSES THERE.
WE WERE ON
ALL-TERRAIN VEHICLES.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MESSAGE BEING,
DON'T THINK ABOUT
CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
I’LL TELL YOU SOMETHING,
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
WELL, EVEN THOUGH WE'VE BEEN BANNED
FROM THE POSSUM LAKE
GOLF AND SKI CLUB,
WE'RE GOING AHEAD
WITH OUR TOURNAMENT
AT ANOTHER LOCATION.
AT FIRST, WE WERE THINKING OF USING
THE PORT ASBESTOS INSTITUTE
FOR THE CRIMINALLY INSANE.
THEY GOT THAT BIG GRASSY AREA.
BUT, THE INMATES
THOUGHT IT WOULD
INTERFERE WITH THEIR REHAB.
SO, INSTEAD,
WE'RE GOING TO USE A COURSE
BY THE DRIVE-IN THEATRE.
WHAT COURSE IS THAT?
THERE'S THAT EMPTY FIELD
WITH OLD SCHOOL BUSES IN IT.
THEN THERE'S CITY HALL,
THE GO-KART TRACK,
THEN THERE'S THE HOSPITAL.
AFTER THAT--
HA! HA-HA!
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
YOUR TOURNAMENT
AT PETE'S PARK AND PUTT
MINI GOLF!
OH, YES!
WELL, MAYBE IT'S NOT
THE MASTERS.
BUT IT'S FLAT, IT'S GREEN,
IT'S GOT 18 HOLES.
BIG WHOOP -- SO DOES
MOOSE THOMPSON'S UNDERWEAR.
BIG DEAL.
(Red): SOMETHING SPECIAL--
OH BOY.
I WAS ABOUT TO SAY
SOMETHING SPECIAL THIS WEEK.
BILL INVITED ME TO COME
OVER AND DO SOME,
GONNA DO SOME GLASS BLOWING.
HE WANTED ME TO PICK UP
A BOOK FROM THE LIBRARY.
DIDN’T REALIZE WE HAD
A LIBRARY IN TOWN.
THERE WE GO.
GLASS BLOWING MADE EASY.
IT’S A BOOK THAT’S
ALL ABOUT GLASS BLOWING
BOY, IT WAS A HOT DAY.
I'M TRYING TO GIVE HIM A HINT
AS TO HOW WARM I...
BILL, I'M KINDA WARM HERE.
IF YOU HAD ANY KIND OF
A SOFT DRINK--
THERE WE GO.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW COLD THAT WILL BE.
WELL, THAT COOLED ME DOWN
A LITTLE.
MIND YOU, I WAS HOPING TO
TAKE IT INTERNALLY.
NOT SOMETHING I SAY
ALL THAT OFTEN.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE, BILL?
FOR GOSH SAKES,
HE WANTS TO USE THE BOTTLES.
THIS IS AN ANCIENT ART.
YOU TAKE ANY KIND OF GLASS.
I GUESS HE WANTED
THE COLOUR OF THE BOTTLES.
BECAUSE YOU GET THAT IN THERE,
AND THEN IT WOULD COLOR--
(Glass breaking)
(Cow mooing)
OH BOY.
I THINK HE MAY HAVE HIT
ELSIE THE SAFETY COW
WITH A PIECE OF SHREDDED GLASS.
ANYWAY, THERE'S ANOTHER SOURCE
OF GLASS.
THESE ARE NEVER PROBLEMS,
THEY'RE OPPORTUNITIES.
RIGHT BILL?
HE CAN GET THAT WINDOW GLASS
IN THERE WITH THE BOTTLES
AND THE VARIOUS OTHER GLASSES
HE HAS IN THERE.
AND THEN JUST KIND OF, YUP.
YOU WANT TO BREAK THEM UP
INTO THE SMALL, TINY PIECES.
AND JUST, UH...
I'M STARTING TO WONDER ABOUT
BILL'S ABILITY TO GRIP THINGS.
ANYWAY...
SO... OH.
NOW HE'S ADDED SAFETY GLASS,
WHICH IS A GOOD IDEA WITH BILL.
ANYWAYS,
HOPEFULLY,
HE'S GOT ENOUGH GLASS.
NOW HE CAN BREAK THAT
INTO LITTLE PIECES.
JUST USE THE VAN
ANY WAY YOU WANT, BILL.
THAT’S FINE,
THAT'S ABSOLUTELY FINE.
AND YOU CAN USE
ANY KIND OF GLASS YOU WANT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHERE'S YOUR GLASSES, BILL?
(Laughing)
(Audience laughing)
(Strums acoustic guitar)
OH, ALL THE MEN
UP HERE KNEW HER
THEY CALLED HER
THE ROSE OF THE LODGE
SHE HAD A FACE
OF AN ANGEL
AND THE REAR END
OF A '53 DODGE
OH, THE ROSE OF THE LODGE
THEY CALLED HER
AND I'LL TELL YOU
THE REASON FOR THAT
HER FATHER WAS BUD
HER MOM WAS A CLIMBER
AND SHE HAD THORNS
ALL OVER HER BACK
(Strums acoustic guitar)
OK, TODAY'S CONTESTANTS
ARE PLAYING FOR
A FREE OIL, LUBE AND FLUID CHECK
FROM STANLEY'S FRIED CHICKEN.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. DALTON HUMPHREY
OF THE HUMPHREY’S
EVERYTHING STORE
TO SAY THIS WORD.
"IMAGINATIVE."
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT,
DALTON.
CREATIVE.
SNEAKY.
SOMEONE WITH
ORIGINAL IDEAS IS...
TROUBLE-MAKER.
BAD INFLUENCE.
IT'S A FOREIGNER.
(Audience laughing)
NO -- PEOPLE WHO WRITE BOOKS
AND MAKE MOVIES AND HAVE ART,
THEY'RE
VERY...
RICH.
NO, NO, NO...
PEOPLE WHO SEE THINGS
OTHER PEOPLE DON'T SEE.
OH... DELUSIONAL.
NO, NO, NO...
WEIRD.
SICK IN THE HEAD.
NO, NO, NO...
INVENTIVE.
OH... SMART ALECK.
NO.
INGENIOUS.
NOT NORMAL.
ALRIGHT, ALRIGHT DALTON.
PEOPLE BUY THAT CRAP IN YOUR STORE.
THEY THINK THAT YOU’RE
LYING, CHEATING,
YOU'RE RIPPING THEM OFF.
BUT IN YOUR MIND, YOU'RE BEING...
IMAGINATIVE.
THERE WE GO!
THERE YOU GO.
THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I THOUGHT I'D TAKE
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S COFFEE TABLE
AND RESTORE IT TO
ITS ORIGINAL CONDITION.
MAYBE NOT ORIGINAL CONDITION,
BUT THE CONDITION IT WAS IN
BEFORE MOOSE THOMPSON
SAT ON IT.
(Blowing)
THE PROBLEM HERE IS THE LEGS
ARE WAY TOO SPINDLY ON THIS,
AS THEY ARE ON
OLD MAN SEDGWICK.
SO, I'M GOING TO FIX THAT UP.
I GUESS A LOT OF PEOPLE
WOULD THROW THAT OUT.
BUT, HEY, I'M NOT
A LOT OF PEOPLE.
I'M BARELY ME.
I'M GOING TO TURN A NEW SET
OF LEGS FOR THAT TABLE
WITH THIS ELECTRIC LATHE.
THE ELECTRIC LATHE,
GREAT FOR MAKING ROUND STUFF,
LIKE CANDLESTICK HOLDERS,
SWIMMING POOLS, HATS.
TAKE THE WOOD STOCK--
WELL, NOT WOODSTOCK REALLY.
AND YOU JUST FIRE THAT
IN THERE, JUST LIKE THAT.
AND YOU TAKE ONE
OF THESE TOOLS,
LIKE THIS, AND SHAVE OFF
ANYTHING THAT ISN'T ROUND.
LIKE WHAT YOU DO IN THE SHOWER
IN THE MORNING.
PLUG HER IN.
FIRE HER UP.
(Sparking)
(Glass breaking)
OKAY, DID I MENTION TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU CENTRE THE WOOD
IN THE LATHE?
MARK THE CENTRE OF EACH END
OF THE PIECE OF WOOD
USING THE MOST ACCURATE DEVICE
IN THE HANDYMAN'S REPERTOIRE,
YOUR EYE.
(Sparking)
(Lathe starting)
(Crashing)
(Glass breaking)
SO I'M THINKING, HEY,
IF WE'RE GONNA MAKE
ROUND THINGS OUT OF WOOD,
WHY NOT START WITH
A ROUND PIECE OF WOOD?
SURPRISED YOU DIDN'T
FIGURE THAT OUT EARLIER.
LET'S HAVE A SERIOUS MOMENT
NOW, THOUGH, ABOUT SAFETY.
PROTECTION FOR YOURSELVES.
THAT'S A VERY POWERFUL
INDUSTRIAL TOOL.
I'D RECOMMEND YOU GET
A HIGH-QUALITY SAFETY HELMET,
SOME SORT OF EYE SHIELD,
SAFETY-GOGGLE TYPE OF UNIT.
AND EXTRA THICK
INDUSTRIAL-STRENGTH GLOVES.
ALL OF THESE THINGS ARE IMPORTANT.
THIS IS YOUR HEALTH AT STAKE HERE.
THERE WAS ONE OTHER THING.
CAN'T REMEMBER.
I GUESS IT WASN'T IMPORTANT.
LET'S GET LATHING.
THE TOOLS ARE OVER THERE.
(Ripping)
THAT WAS THE THING
I FORGOT TO MENTION.
DON'T WEAR LOOSE CLOTHING.
OK, LET'S MAKE TABLE LEGS.
(Glass breaking)
WRONG TOOL.
AND, LOOK AT THAT!
YOU'VE MADE LEGS FOR YOUR TABLE
USING YOUR LATHE.
HA HA HA HA.
JUST THAT SIMPLE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
(Wood snapping)
OH BOY.
STAY TUNED AND RELAX.
WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE'VE GOT A LOT MORE OF IT.
ALRIGHT.
WELCOME TO "AUTOBIOGRAPHY",
WHERE MEMBERS OF POSSUM LODGE
TALK ABOUT CARS THAT HAVE
SOME SIGNIFICANCE TO THEM.
THIS WEEK WE HAVE
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
OF ROTHSCHILD SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
NO TANK TOO BIG,
NO TANK TOO SMALL.
TEACUP OR CESSPOOL,
WE SUCK 'EM ALL.
(Audience laughing)
(Applause)
ARE WE THERE YET?
YEAH, WE’RE ALRIGHT.
WINSTON, MAYBE YOU COULD
TELL US ABOUT
YOUR FIRST CAR.
OH GEEZ, GREAT MEMORY.
SHE WAS AN OLD FORD.
I'LL NEVER FORGET.
COUNTRY SQUIRE RANCH WAGON.
YEAH, I REMEMBER IT.
THAT'S THE ONE THAT HAD
THE REAL, HONEST TO GOODNESS,
IMITATION-WOOD SIDES.
(Audience laughing)
WHAT A GREAT CAR
THOSE FORDS WERE.
THE BODY, FORGET ABOUT IT.
RUSTS RIGHT OFF.
BUT THE V8 ENGINE,
GO FOREVER.
YOU KNOW, THE NEW FORDS, UH,
JUST DON'T RUST LIKE THE OLD ONES.
(Audience laughing)
SORT OF MISS THAT,
TO BE HONEST.
YEAH.
THAT WAGON,
THAT WAS A BIG UNIT.
OH, IT WAS HUGE!
I RAN MY FIRST BUSINESS
OUT OF THAT WAGON.
DID NOT KNOW THAT, SIR.
I THOUGHT YOU JUST HAD
THE SEPTIC BUSINESS.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING THEN?
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
WHAT?
OH YEAH.
I MOUNTED THE PUMP
IN THE PASSENGER SIDE
RIGHT NEXT TO ME.
WHERE YOU ARE.
THEN I'D FLIP
THE BACKSEAT DOWN
THEN I’D PUT A SWIMMING POOL
LINER IN THERE.
SHE'D HOLD 400 GALLONS.
SO YOU’RE CARRYING SEWAGE
AROUND IN THE BACK OF YOUR CAR?
FOR A SHORT TIME,
UNTIL I GOT ENOUGH MONEY
FOR THE DOWNPAYMENT
ON THE TRUCK --
BUT I WAS MOTIVATED
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW, THAT WAS
THE HOTTEST SUMMER ON RECORD.
(Audience laughing)
BUT, HERE'S WHAT I DID.
I WOULD POP OUT
THE FRONT WINDSHIELD,
AND I'D STICK MY HEAD
OUT THE SIDE.
AND I'D GO LIKE A BANSHEE,
AND THE WIND
WOULD KNOCK ALL OF THAT
INTO THE BACK.
OH, SURE, YEAH.
ALTHOUGH, I GOT TO TELL YOU,
I STILL BREAK OUT INTO
A COLD SWEAT
EVERY TIME I SEE A STOP SIGN.
(Audience laughing)
(Playing bagpipes)
OH!
(Audience laughing)
(Applause)
(Cheering)
(Cheering and whistling)
YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH.
WELL... WELL, WE HAD OUR ANNUAL
GOLF TOURNAMENT AT
PETE'S PARK AND PUTT MINI GOLF.
WE CARRIED ON THE PROUD
POSSUM LODGE TRADITION
OF GETTING BANNED
FROM EVERYWHERE WE GO.
(Snaps putter)
YEAH!
(Rattling)
(Whimpering)
I DIDN'T KNOW GOLF WAS
A FULL-CONTACT SPORT.
IT IS, THE WAY WE PLAY IT, HAROLD.
ALTHOUGH IN FAIRNESS,
THE MINIATURE GOLF THING
CONFUSED SOME OF THE GUYS.
WE SHOULD HAVE TOLD THEM
NOT TO USE DRIVERS.
YEAH, AND THEIR
ELECTRIC GOLF CARTS.
YEAH.
THOSE GUYS ARE THE WORST SPORTS
I'VE EVER SEEN.
GOLF'S A FRUSTRATING GAME, HAROLD.
THE GUYS’ TEMPER GETS AHOLD OF THEM
ESPECIALLY THAT HOLE
WHERE YOU PUTT
BETWEEN THE LEGS OF SNOW WHITE
AND THE SEVEN DWARFS.
ON HIS 9th TRY,
STINKY LOST HIS TEMPER
AND BURIED HIS PITCHING WEDGE
IN SNEEZY'S FOREHEAD.
CLEARED HIS SINUSES.
YEAH.
ANYWAY, WE FIGURED OUT THAT
THE PROBLEM WITH MINIATURE GOLF
IS NOT THE GOLF.
IT'S THE MINIATURE.
WE'RE GONNA START AGAIN WITH
A NEW COURSE, NEW EQUIPMENT,
AND A BRAND-NEW GAME
WE CALL MAXI GOLF.
MAXI GOLF?
MINI GOLF IS OUT,
MAXI GOLF IS IN, HAROLD.
BIG HOLES, BIG CLUBS,
BIG BALLS.
(Audience laughing)
(Siren)
(Siren stops)
POSSUM 911 -- WHAT'S YOUR
NAME AND MEMBERSHIP NUMBER?
UH, MY NAME'S DAVE.
MY NUMBER IS 4--
OH, 5-6-7-9-2.
OKAY, JUST HOLD ON DAVE,
WE'RE GONNA INSERT THAT
INTO THE POSSUM LODGE COMPUTER
TO VERIFY YOUR MEMBERSHIP.
YEAH.
(Clacking pliers)
OH, DAVE, YOU'RE BEHIND
IN YOUR DUES, AREN'T YOU?
UH...
IT'S IN THE MAIL.
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME, DAVE --
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
RED, I'VE GOT A REAL EMERGENCY
HAPPENING HERE.
WE'RE LOOKING TO BUY
A NEW VEHICLE
AND SHE WANTS TO BUY --
OH, GOSH -- A MINIVAN.
OHHH, MAN!
THAT'S A TOUGH ONE, DAVE.
A MINIVAN, RED --
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
I REALLY DON'T SEE THE PROBLEM.
I THINK THEY'RE SPORTY
AND SHARP AND FUEL-EFFICIENT.
THEY’RE PRACTICAL, I WISH I HAD ONE!
YEAH, SEE, RED?
I DON'T WANT TO END UP
LIKE HAROLD.
NO, NO, NO.
I'M WITH YOU, THERE, DAVE.
I’LL TELL YOU SOMETHING THOUGH,
A MINIVAN MAY SEEM
ON THE FEMININE SIDE
BUT YOU CAN DRESS 'EM UP, DAVE.
YOU CAN GET THE MASCULINE
ACCESSORIES ON THAT.
THAT'S TRUE.
JUST BE CAREFUL, YOU KNOW?
DON'T GET BAD STUFF,
LIKE THOSE CUSTOM WHEEL COVERS.
THEY'RE GAUDY, THEY REALLY ARE.
OR THOSE TACKY MUD-FLAPS WITH
SILHOUETTES OF NAKED LADIES.
THERE'S NO RESPECT
FOR THE FEMININE PERSONAGES
BY DOING THAT.
OR PEOPLE PUT THOSE NEON LIGHTS
UNDERNEATH THE VEHICLE!
WHAT'S GOIN' ON THERE?
THAT'S A WASTE OF ENERGY.
A WASTE OF EN-ER-GY!
IF YOU'RE LOOKING
AT THE GROUND,
YOU'RE NOT WATCHING THE ROAD!
THEY GOT THESE AIR-HORNS --
SOUND LIKE THEY STOLE THEM
OFF A DIESEL TRAIN
OR SOMETHING.
AND THOSE MUFFLERS GO...
(Imitating loud muffler)
I THINK LIKE A BAND OF DRUMMERS
ARE COMING AT ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT'S ABOUT.
THEY GOT THESE MUD-FLAPS
AND FENDER SKIRTS
AND RUNNING BOARDS.
RUNNING BOARDS?
I TRIED RUNNING.
YOU CAN'T GET ANY SPEED AT ALL.
KEEP RUNNING OFF THE THING.
AND THEN YOU GOT THOSE TAILPIPE
EXTENSIONS -- COME ON!
DID YOU GET ALL THAT, DAVE?
WHAT WAS THE LAST ONE?
TAILPIPE EXTENSIONS.
YES, UH, THANKS.
I HOPE WE CAN AFFORD ALL THIS.
(Laughing and applause)
(Red): ALL RIGHT,
IT'S GLASS-BLOWING TIME,
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL", HERE.
PUT THE GLASS INTO THE--
PUT THE GLASS--
THAT'S NOT GLASS.
THESE ARE PLASTIC ITEMS, BILL.
WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
I GUESS HE DECIDED
TO ABANDON THE GLASS THING.
HE'S GONNA BLOW PLASTIC.
THAT'S KIND OF UNUSUAL.
ALL KINDS OF PLASTIC--
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
MELT ALL THE PLASTIC TOGETHER
AND MAKE A BIG GOOPY--
OHHH!
MAKE A BIG GOOPY THING, THERE.
GOLLY, TAKE A GOOD--
WOW! I'M TELLING YOU!
HOLY MACKEREL, THAT WILL
SET YOU BACK A COUPLE OF YEARS.
BOY, OH, BOY, , , BOY, OH, BOY!
IT'S CHEAPER THAN
A CASE OF BEER, I’LL TELL YA.
UP SHE COMES --
WHAT THE HECK WE GOT THERE?
WOW! HE LOOKS GOOD WITH A PIPE.
WHOA! AND THERE WE GO,
AND THEN, SEE,
THAT IS JUST A PIECE
OF COPPER PIPING.
GETS A BALL OF THE GOOP
ON THE END.
HE SWIRLS THAT SO IT SEALS UP.
THEN HE CAN BLOW IT.
I GUESS THIS IS THE MODERN
VERSION OF GLASS BLOWING.
YOU'RE BLOWING THE PLASTIC.
GOT ALL THE CARCINOGENS,
BLOWING THEM UP.
BILL, I THINK THAT MIGHT BE...
BILL, THINK THAT MIGHT--
BILL, I'M THINKIN'-- BILL!
BILL, I'M THINKIN'...
I'M THINKIN'
SEE YOU LATER, BILL.
THAT'S WHAT I'M THINKIN'.
BY GOLLY, WOULDN'T THAT BE
EIGHT FEET ACROSS?
IT'S GONNA GO-- NO, NO, NO, NO!
(Bill): OHHHHHH!
AHHHHHH!
(Thud) OHHHH!
(Red): TOLD YOU.
THERE'S BILL,
A VENEER OF HIS FORMER SELF.
EITHER THAT, OR HE'S PLASTERED.
YOU OK, BILL?
(Smack)
AHHHH!
(Red): HERE'S A PAIR
OF POSSUM LODGE BINOCULARS
SENT TO US BY A VIEWER.
(Audience laughing)
WELL, WE'RE ABOUT
READY TO TEE OFF
FOR THE FIRST POSSUM LODGE
MAXI GOLF TOURNAMENT.
YOU WANT TO BE
IN MY FOURSOME,
HAROLD?
MAYBE, IS THAT THE TROPHY?
WHO WOULD WANT
TO WIN THAT?
IT'S NOT A TROPHY, HAROLD.
THAT'S OUR GOLF TEE.
(Audience laughing)
IF THAT'S THE TEE,
HOW BIG IS THIS MAXI GOLF BALL?
PRETTY DARNED MAXI.
YOU KNOW THAT BIG BRASS BALL
THEY GOT PAINTED LIKE JUPITER,
HANGS OVER THE ENTRANCE
OF THE JUPITER DRIVE-IN?
IT'S NOT THERE ANY MORE.
THAT THING'S, LIKE,
SIX FEET ACROSS.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED, LIKE,
HOLES 7 FEET ACROSS,
10 FEET DEEP.
WHERE WILL YOU FIND
18 OF THOSE?
THE POT-HOLES ON THE ROAD
INTO TOWN.
OH, YEAH, HE'S RIGHT.
THAT’S RIGHT,
YOU COULD
DO THAT.
WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA USE
TO HIT 'EM WITH?
IT'S NOT A REGULAR GOLF BALL.
IT'S LIKE A... A PLANET!
MY BIG BLUE EIGHT-IRON, HAROLD.
THE POSSUM VAN.
OHHH!
BIG, BLUE, IT'S A V-8
AND IT'S MADE OF IRON.
AND A HUGE SWEET SPOT --
THE WHOLE FRONT GRILLE.
TALK ABOUT DRIVING THE BALL,
EH, HAROLD?
(Audience laughing)
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW!
WHERE WE EXAMINE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO DIFFICULT TO SAY....
(Audience):
"I DON'T KNOW!"
NEITHER DO THEY!
OK, ON THIS WEEK'S EXPERT PORTION,
WE HAVE GUESTS.
MY UNCLE RED, NATCH,
AND HIS BEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE ROOM,
PILOT BUZZ SHERWOOD!
(Applause and cheering)
OK.
(Cheering and whistling)
THIS VIEWER WRITES,
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"I'M FED UP WITH CRIME.
"I'M THINKING OF MOVING FROM
THE CITY TO POSSUM LAKE.”
"IS THERE MUCH CRIME
WHERE YOU ARE?"
AHHH -- GOOD QUESTION.
THERE'S NO CRIME UP HERE,
UNLESS BORROWING SOMETHING
AND NEVER GIVING IT BACK
IS CALLED THEFT.
(Buzz): WELL... I KNOW
SOME OF THE WARDROBE CHOICES
UP HERE BORDER ON THE CRIMINAL.
(Laughing)
YEAH, YOUR OUTFIT COULD GET
A TICKET FOR LITTERING.
YEAH, WELL, YOURS WOULD GET ONE
FOR... LOITERING!
(Laughing)
OK, ABOUT THIS LADY'S QUESTION,
THOUGH...
LET'S JUST SAY, MA'AM,
THAT NOBODY HERE WOULD BE ON
"AMERICA'S MOST WANTED".
MAYBE "AMERICA'S MOST WASTED".
"AMERICA'S"...
UH, "AMERICA'S
MOST" WHAT?
WANTED.
"AMERICA'S
MOST WANTED".
YOU DON'T WATCH TELEVISION,
MR. SHERWOOD?
NOT SINCE "THE MOD SQUAD", MAN.
(Audience laughing)
WELL, "AMERICA'S MOST WANTED",
IT'S A TELEVISION SHOW.
IT SHOWS UNSOLVED CRIMES FROM
5, 10, EVEN 20 YEARS AGO.
ACTORS PLAY THE CRIMINALS,
WHICH ISN'T A STRETCH.
20 MILLION BUCKS
FOR "CABLE GUY"? PLEASE!
THEY SHOW SUSPECTS' PICTURES.
THEY ALWAYS LOOK LIKE MOOSE THOMPSON'S
DRIVER'S LICENSE PHOTO.
YOU EVER NOTICE THAT?
LOOKS JUST LIKE MOOSE THOMPSON'S
DRIVER'S LICENSE PHOTO.
ROBERT STACK'S THE HOST.
HE DID "THE UNTOUCHABLES"
AND NOTHING SINCE.
HE SAYS, "DO YOU RECOGNIZE
THIS FACE?
"DOES THIS PERSON
LOOK FAMILIAR?
"IF SO, PHONE IN NOW."
EVERYBODY AT HOME GOES,
"MY GOD, I KNOW HIM!"
"THAT MY STEPFATHER."
"THAT GUY SITS RIGHT
BESIDE ME AT WORK."
AND THEY PHONE IN AND SAY,
"HELLO, ROBERT STACK?
"THE GUY'S HERE --
COME AND GET HIM!"
(Audience laughing)
(Applause)
THAT'S "AMERICA'S
MOST WANTED".
YOU NEVER SEEN THAT?
WHAT? WHAT?
WHAT? WHAT? WHAT?
(Audience laughing)
SHOULD WE PHONE
ROBERT STACK?
(Laughing)
(Whimpering)
AHHHH!
EXCUSE ME, HAROLD.
WELL, GOTTA TELL YA,
OUR GAME OF MAXI GOLF
WAS A BIG, BIG HIT.
I GOT HIT
BY THE BALL!
YEAH, BIG, BIG HIT.
WELL HAROLD, YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE
BEEN ON THE FAIRWAY.
I WAS STANDING IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE ROAD!
I WAS WALKING
AHEAD OF YOU GUYS.
WE WERE PLAYING THROUGH,
HAROLD.
BESIDES, THIS MAKES YOU LOOK
LIKE A REAL GOLFER.
YOU GOT A DOG-LEG LEFT.
WELL, YOU SHOULD HAVE YELLED "FORE!"
IT WAS A CHRYSLER --
I SHOULD HAVE YELLED "DODGE!"
(Laughing)
YEAH, BY GOLLY.
WHAT A GREAT GAME, BOY!
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
(Laughing)
MAN, OH, MAN, THE BUNCH OF US,
DRIVING OUR CARS,
BASHING INTO THAT BALL.
JUNIOR SINGLETON NEEDS
A FRONT-END ALIGNMENT.
HE WHIFFED ON ONE SHOT, ROLLED
HIS TRUCK INTO THE RAVINE.
(Laughing)
TALK ABOUT
YOUR BAD LIES.
WAIT TIL YOU HEAR THE ONES
HE TELLS HIS WIFE!
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
SQUEAL
OF THE POSSUM.
AWAY YOU GO, HAROLD.
OH, BOY.
(Audience laughing)
WELL...
(Laughing and applause)
(Laughing)
(Applause)
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I’LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I KNOW YOU'VE NEVER BEEN
A REAL BIG FAN OF GOLF,
BUT I WAS HOPING MAYBE LATER
WE COULD PLAY "A ROUND"...
UNLESS YOU'RE TEED OFF!
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND MR. NIBLICK BACK THERE,
AND THE WHOLE GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN, GUYS. HAROLD?
(Harold): WE GOT
A FLASH BULLETIN TODAY.
MOOSE THOMPSON'S MAKING
SOME OF HIS WORLD-FAMOUS CHILI.
SO, IF YOU KNOW ANYONE
WHO LIVES SOUTH OF US,
YOU MIGHT WANT TO START
SENDING OUT SMOKE SIGNALS,
OR PHONE CALLS,
WHATEVER YOU CAN THINK OF.
SAVE A LIFE!