One of the things
I like doing best
is taking something
pretty normal
and then using
it in a way
that nobody's ever
thought of before.
Like, for example,
using a floor polisher
for a back massager
or a trolling motor
as a Cuisinart
or a British car as a reliable
means of transportation.
I think the big
difference is
I don't see things
the way other people do.
See, like, normal people look
at this, and what do they see?
They see a sprinkler on
the end of a garden hose.
I'm not normal...
thank goodness.
I don't see a sprinkler
on garden hose.
I see an instant
campfire.
[ cheers and applause ]
Thanks very much.
Appreciate it.
Big, big news up at
the Lodge this week.
The government has put a new
building across the lake
on top of Duff's Bluffs,
named after Figgy Duff,
a guy who used to get in
to arguments with his
dad all the time
and then threaten
to get a job.
Which is why they call it
Duff's Bluffs.
The problem is this building
is directly between us
and the TV satellite,
so now we don't
get any stations.
Well, the guys are trying to
raise the satellite dish up
by putting the tower
on top of the lodge,
stick her up about
30 feet or so.
But it's not easy.
It almost makes you wish
we'd watched some of
those how-to shows.
Uncle Red,
what are you doing?
[ cheers and applause ]
I'm doing a
television show.
You know
what I mean.
That lumber was specifically
earmarked for a new dock,
a new dock that we
were supposed to build
by order of
the government.
I didn't see it
as an order.
I took it more as
a bureaucratic suggestion.
It was an order,
and I take orders
very seriously.
Yes, but you're
not married.
The government said our old
rotten dock was ruining
the environment.
Well, their new building
blocking our TV signals
is ruining
my environment.
We're fighting fire
with higher.
We can live without
television.
I'm going to pretend
I didn't hear that.
Hundreds of years ago,
people sat around at night
and had long
conversations.
Right, and the life
expectancy was 37.
That's not
a coincidence.
Listen we'll have plenty
of wood left over
after we build the
darned tower to
build the dock.
We're only going up
about 30 feet or so.
Are you sure you guys
know what you're doing?
What do you think,
Harold?
[ loud cracking sound ]
[ applause ]
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ cheers and applause ]
Today's prize is this coupon
for a round trip ticket
to Port Asbestos!
"... on a big orange
school bus.
"Be prepared for
frequent stops."
All right, Hap, you gotta
cover your ears.
Red, you have 30 seconds
to get Hap Shaughnessy
to say this word...
Yeah, all right,
Winston.
And... go!
Okay, Hap, Hap!
What do you call it when
people stretch things?
Yoga.
Okay, no not their muscles.
When they stretch
the truth a little.
Oh, unicorn salesman.
No. Okay.
Um, when people make things
bigger than they really are,
what do you call that?
Breast implants.
Okay, Hap, supposing I told you
I was abducted by aliens
and taken to Saturn and
had dinner with Elvis,
what would I be doing?
Reading my
autobiography.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, Hap, like,
when you tell a story,
you always do this,
and I never do it.
Make it interesting.
Almost out
of time, Red.
Okay, see, Hap,
you do this.
It's not exactly lying,
but it's not tellin'
the truth either.
What's that called?
Politics.
Yes, and you'd be a great
politician because you...
... are a Kennedy.
Hap, you have to be the
biggest bafflegabber
the world has ever seen.
Oh, no,
not the biggest.
I think you exaggerate
a little there, Red.
There we go!
[ snoring ]
RED: Dalton,
you're snoring again.
DALTON: I am not
asleep, Red.
RED:
Well, you're snoring.
I told you
I can't help it.
[ snores ] It's a
medical condition.
Can't you wear
nose plugs?
Can't you
wear ear plugs?
Can't we all
just get along?
Stop being
so immature.
RED: I'm not
the immature one.
Are so.
Am not.
Stop it!
That's enough "are so's"
for one day.
DALTON:
What'd he say?
RED: I dunno,
but I agree with him.
Let's talk about
something else.
I had this weird
dream last night,
where I was running
down the street naked
with a mob of people
chasing me.
Have either of you
ever experienced that?
My wife doesn't let
me watch that channel.
It's not TV,
it's a dream.
Don't you ever
have dreams?
I used to.
When I was single
I dreamt I was Superman.
But then I married
Kryptonite.
Dreams can tell
a lot about you.
There are people
that make their living
interpreting dreams.
RED: Yeah, they're
called bartenders, Mike.
Mr. Green, I don't think
you should poo-poo dreams.
I'm not poo-pooing
anything.
I wasn't poo-pooing,
was I?
I hope not.
Mr. Green, you have a
tendency to be very negative
towards people whose
opinions you disagree with.
RED: Oh, put a sock
in it, Mike.
Dreams are a
recognized indicator
of the
subconscious mind.
RED: Oh yeah?
Yeah.
Dreams can tell you a
lot about people's
brain activity.
RED: Really?
Well, I don't even
have dreams.
See?
That proves it.
These days you hear a lot of
hot air about saving gas.
There's only a couple
of ways to really save gas.
One, buy a
smaller vehicle...
yeah right.
The other is to make your
vehicle more aerodynamic.
Now, I don't know
much about that stuff,
but I'd rather
learn something
than drive around
in a dinky toy.
So I looked up 'aerodynamic'
in the encyclopedia.
That took a while
until I realized
it started with an 'A'.
Now, they got a bunch of
diagrams and charts,
but the basic message,
it's all about wind
resistance.
Driving the Possum Van
is like pushing a cow
through a mud bath.
But what if, instead of
having to go around the van,
the air could just
shoot right through it?
Like the difference
between these two racquets.
See, this one has a lot
of air resistance,
so I can only
go like that.
But the tennis racquet lets
the air go right through,
so I can go like this.
Okay, it's the same,
but this is easier.
Okay, let's move on.
All we need is something that
takes the air that's
hitting the van
and lets it pass
right through the van.
In one end
and out the other.
I'm not sure where that
expression started,
but I'm guessing it was
during flu season.
See, so if we can get
enough of these hoses,
we can scoop the air that's
gonna smack into the
front of the van,
and re-route it
out the back
through the van.
Just gotta find
some openings
so I can put the hoses
straight through.
Okay, I figure I've
reduced the wind resistance
by about 30%
and improved the appearance
of the vehicle by...
somewhat less than that.
So now the air flows
smoothly through the hoses,
instead of being stacked up
like Dolly Parton in
a halter top.
It comes out here and smacks
into the guy tailgating you.
[ chuckles ]
Okay, it means I have to leave
the back doors open
all the time,
but I don't mind.
It's cheaper than
deodorizers.
Kinda looks like a rocket
launcher, doesn't it?
Hmmm.
Oh baby, this project
is a win-win.
We're saving gasoline by
reducing the wind resistance,
and we're saving gasoline by
adding this propane
auxiliary drive system.
Finally a hybrid
car I like.
So remember, if the women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I've gotta go
save the environment.
Have you seen
all the nostalgia
that's popping up on TV
and the radio these days?
Nostalgia is fine,
but this is nostalgia
from the '80s.
I haven't had a chance
to miss the '80s yet,
and even if I had,
I wouldn't.
The clothes were neon,
the cars were gutless
and the music was either
made in a computer
or by something
called "Wham".
But, see, that's the
way nostalgia works.
As things go sour
in the present,
we all start imagining they
were better in the past.
It's why we remember
the Bee Gees so fondly
and the Captain and Tenille
at all.
It's all about what
you're comparing stuff to.
So I go out of my way to
introduce my wife
to guys my own age who've
let themselves go mentally,
physically and socially.
I know that some day soon
that nostalgia factor
is gonna kick in,
and she's gonna start
seeing me
as better than
I've ever been.
And let me tell ya,
there'll be a
hootenanny that night!
Remember,
I'm pulling for ya.
We're all
in this together.
Call Rothschild's,
because what goes down...
shouldn't come up.
Well, we had a rethink
on the TV tower
and decided to build it
from the Lodge floor up.
That way it would be
as solid as the Lodge.
Take it easy there, Mike.
MIKE: (mumbling)
Pardon me?
Take the nails
out of your mouth.
MIKE:
I had nails in my mouth.
Uncle Red,
I don't think you're going
to have enough lumber
left over
to build the new dock
that the government wants.
Yeah, but we got
the old dock out.
That was the
main issue.
Harold,
our boats sink.
They don't need to be
tied up to anything.
I don't think you guys
have any idea what you're
doing at all,
or the damage
it's gonna do to the
world as we know it.
If only someone had
said that to your parents.
I'm assuming you have
some plans to build
this tower with.
No, we don't
need plans.
We know a tower is
wide at the bottom
and comes to a
point at the top
so we're designing it
after Moose Thompson.
It doesn't look all
that straight to me.
This could end up being
the leaning tower of PBS.
Look at this!
It's not even secured
to the base.
The weight will
hold it here, Harold.
We used the
water-logged dock boards
for the first platform.
That was
like 1200 pounds
not counting
the zebra mussels.
With that
much weight,
gravity will
hold it in place.
Gravity is our
friend, Harold.
Red: NOTHING
CAN BE MORE RELAXING
THAN BEING OUT FISHING
WITH A BUNCH OF BUDDIES.
ACTUALLY, MAYBE
IT'S TOO RELAXING.
LUCKILY WE LEFT
THE MOTOR GOING.
SO WE COME IN AND TAKE
OUR CATCH OUT OF THE BOAT.
I HAD A PRETTY GOOD
STRINGER OF FISH THERE.
NOT TOO BAD AT ALL.
A LITTLE SUSHI ATTACK
AT THE END OF THE DAY,
BUT I WAS FINE.
WALTER HAD A FAIR NUMBER.
BUT THEY WEREN'T HUGE.
IT'S OKAY,
WE HAVE CRACKERS.
AND BILL -- I'M NOT
SURE WHAT BILL GOT.
HE SEEMED HAPPY ABOUT IT.
IT'S AN UMBRELLA OR
A TV AERIAL, I DUNNO.
SO WE'RE GETTING SET
TO HAVE OUR LITTLE COOKOUT,
BUT HAROLD WANTS
TO TAKE A PICTURE,
YOU KNOW, THE WAY THE
GUYS HOLD UP THE FISH.
IT'S NOT THAT HARD,
BUT WITH HAROLD, SOMETIMES,
IT'S JUST EASIER TO GO ALONG,
GET ALONG...
I WISH HE WOULD GO ALONG.
WATCH OUT, THERE'S A
FLASH ON THAT, HAROLD.
BE CAREFUL.
NO, NO, HAROLD...
GREAT.
WHY DON'T YOU
POINT THE CAMERA
AT WHAT YOU'RE TRYING
TO TAKE A PICTURE OF?
THAT'S ALWAYS A GOOD --
HAROLD?
AH, STUPID...
IN FOR A LONG DAY.
OH, NO, IT'S GOOD.
THEN WALTER DECIDES
SINCE IT'S A PHOTO OP
HE'S GONNA -- MAYBE HOLD IT A
LITTLE CLOSER TO THE CAMERA
IT'LL LOOK A
LITTLE LARGER.
THAT WAS AN
ODD LOOKIN' THING,
AND IT DIDN'T
SMELL ALL THAT GREAT.
TAKE HER OVER
TO THE OTHER SIDE.
THERE WE GO.
OKAY, SO HAROLD'S
GETTIN' SET NOW.
I GUESS HE DIDN'T
TIGHTEN HER UP ENOUGH.
NOW, HE'S -- AND WE'RE
TRYING TO STAY WITH IT.
THEN THE ONE LEG
STARTS TO GO,
AND WE GOTTA
KINDA LEAN OVER.
EVENTUALLY GRAVITY
TOOK OVER.
SO THIS IS JUST NOT --
HAROLD, WATCH OUT FOR THE --
SO THIS IS NOT
WORKING OUT AT ALL.
WE NEED A
DIFFERENT APPROACH,
SO WALTER DECIDES HE'S GONNA
TAKE OVER AS PHOTOGRAPHER.
AND HAROLD -- AWAY YOU GO.
AWAY YOU GO.
NO, JUST GO.
YOU'RE GONNA GET ONE.
HERE IT COMES.
AWAY YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT SO
HAROLD COMES OVER.
NOW WE HAVE TO
GET OURSELVES --
WHO'S GONNA
BE IN THE MIDDLE?
HAROLD'S TALLER, SO MAYBE
HE SHOULD BE IN THE MIDDLE.
I DIDN'T CARE, BUT BILL
WANTED TO BE IN THE MIDDLE.
OKAY, LATER THAT DAY...
WE'RE FINALLY SET TO GO
AND WALTER GOT --
I THOUGHT IT
WAS ALL RIGHT.
BUT HE SAID OUR
EYES WERE CLOSED.
YEAH, I KNOW.
OKAY. OKAY.
THE FISH EYES WE CAN'T DO
ANYTHING ABOUT WALTER, SO...
NOW WE'RE STARTING
TO TAKE PICTURES,
AND WE GOT A
COUPLE OF GOOD POSES.
SOMETIMES WHEN YOU'RE TAKING A
PICTURE YOU'RE FOCUSSED ON --
YOU DON'T SEE WHAT'S
HAPPENING IN THE BACKGROUND.
AND, UH...
APPARENTLY, UH...
WE WERE HAVING
A VISITOR OF SOME --
NOW, BILL SPOTTED HIM.
AND HE WAS
TRYING TO REACT.
AND THEN HAROLD SAW HIM,
AND, UH...
OF COURSE,
THEN THEY'RE GONE.
NOW I'M ALONE,
AND, UH, SUDDENLY
MY FISH ARE GONE.
AND THAT WAS REALLY THE
FIRST TIME I NOTICED
SOMETHING WAS UP.
SO I SAY, HEY, HEY, HEY,
MY FISH ARE GONE.
AND THEY'RE GOIN,
"HEY, IT WASN'T ME."
AND THEN WE ALL
SPOTTED THE BEAR.
AND THEN THE BEAR SPOTS US,
AND THEN WE GO HOME.
[ applause ]
Nothing can pack it in
like a garbage truck.
Except maybe Moose Thompson
at a buffet.
The secret is compression.
And what works for
that garbage truck
can also work
for you.
It's not about squeezing the
crap out of something.
It's about squeezing the
crap into something.
If you're like me,
you like to keep
things in your car,
things that probably should
have gone in that truck
that just left.
But you don't want
to throw something out
that you might
need next week.
Well, here's how you
can keep everything.
First, consolidate.
Okay, now all you need is
an extra rim attached
to your drive wheel
and a piece of chain.
Make sure you leave
the key in the trunk,
just like taxis do.
And just hook the, uh --
Oh, darn.
Okay, just hook the
chain onto something.
There we go.
Then run her across.
Then you just
hook the other end
onto maybe another rust hole
or a door knob.
Oh, here we go.
That looks safer.
And this is how
you turn a mid-size
into a compact.
We're getting there.
She just needs
a little more power.
[ applause ]
[ wind blowing,
wood creaking ]
Okay, we got the
tower finished,
got the dish
mounted on top,
and we're back in business.
And we got it all done
before the playoffs.
Uncle Red, this tower
is over 100 feet tall!
Who authorized that?
Luck.
A lumber truck dropped its
load at Dead Man's Curve.
We took it
as a windfall.
Oh! you almost had
another windfall going.
Every time
the tower sways
we go through a bunch
of channels on the TV.
But I figure it's gonna
save on batteries for
the remote.
I also noticed there's no
lightning rod on top
of this thing.
Do you think that wise?
He asked pointlessly.
Harold, the tower's
made of wood.
Lightning doesn't
hit wood.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay, well...
Well, let's just remember
that tree that was out
by the parking lot,
remember that?
And last year it exploded
in the electrical storm?
Remember that?
If I'm not mistaken,
it, too, was made of wood!
Harold, that
was ironwood.
Oh! Oh! Harold,
gimme a hand.
Ah! Ah!
Spider! Spider!
Never mind, Spiderman,
just grab the darned tower!
[ wood cracking ]
Was that my back?
No I think the tower's
breaking apart.
Maybe we shouldn't have
used the old dock boards.
I told you that!
Come on over to this
side and help me, Harold.
Sure.
Do you think
that's gonna work?
No, but you'll get a
better view of it falling.
[ wood cracking ]
[ loud bang ]
[ applause ]
Well, that was totally
stupid and unnecessary.
Now, don't blame
yourself, Harold.
A lot of good is gonna
come out of this.
Really? Like what?
Well, of course, you were
all wrapped up in yourself
and didn't notice that
as the tower was falling,
we got about 40 channels
we don't even pay for.
[ possum squealing ]
Meeting time.
You go ahead.
I some time to put
a positive spin
on all this.
So you're gonna
be a while.
Um... okay,
if my wife is watching,
uh, the tower fell over,
our dish is in the lake
and our TV set blew up,
but I'm hoping I'll get
a lot better reception
when I get home.
And to the rest of you,
thanks for watching
and on behalf
of myself and Harold
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge,
keep your stick on your ice.
[ cheers and applause ]
Sit down, everybody.
Take a seat.
Sit down.
All rise.
Quando Omni Flunkus Moritati.
RED: Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the man's prayer.
I'm a man,
but I can change,
If I have to...
I guess.
Okay, great news, men.
As a result of our TV tower
falling into the lake,
we now have
a brand new dock
with a covered walkway
all the way up to the Lodge.
And here's the best part...
I found out today our next
door neighbour has cable.
And by tomorrow,
so will we.