WHEN A GUY GOES FISHIHNG,
IT’S NOT ENOUGH TO
CATCH FISH.
YOU HAVE TO CATCH
THE BIGGEST FISH;
IT RIGHT AWAY;
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
YOU HAVE TO DO IT
AROUND PEOPLE WHO
AREN'T CATCHIN' ANYTHING.
IT'S KINDA LIKE TAKIN' YOUR
GIRLFRIEND TO HAROLD'S
CHESS CLUB...
YOU'RE RUBBIN'
IT IN A LITTLE.
LUCKILY THERE'S A GUARANTEED
WAY TO CATCH BIG FISH FAST.
GET YOURSELF A CAN OF
THIS INSULATING FOAM.
WHEN YOU SPRAY THIS STUFF
IT EXPANDS TO 100 TIMES
ITS NORMAL SIZE.
THOSE WERE THE
GOOD OL' DAYS, HUH?
FIRST THING YOU WANNA DO
IS TIE YOUR FISHING LINE
JUST UNDER THE NOZZLE.
THAT WAY WHEN YOU CAST
THE NOZZLE'LL POP OFF,
AND THE FOAM
WILL SHOOT OUT.
BUT FIRST YOU GOTTA
BURY THE WHOLE THING
INSIDE THIS SHINY
MYLAR FISH BALLOON.
YOU CAN GET THESE
WHEREVER THEY SELL THEM.
THEN YOU JUST SEAL IT UP
WITH WHATEVER YOU'VE
GOT AROUND THAT'S HANDY.
THEN YOU JUST SCRUNCH
IT UP REAL SMALL
SO THAT IT LOOKS
LIKE A NORMAL, SHINY LURE.
[ FOAM EXPLODING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
SEE YA!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
TAKE IT EASY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
NO, I APPRECIATE THAT.
ACTUALLY GOT A BIT OF A PROBLEM
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
THE WELL RAN DRY.
THE LOCAL WELL GUY SAYS
WE'VE GOT TO DIG IT DEEPER.
BUT HE WANTS AN ARM
AND A LEG FOR THE JOB.
WE FIGURE WE CAN DO IT
OURSELVES FOR JUST AN ARM.
UNCLE RED! UNCLE RED!
OKAY, ALL RIGHT...
ARE YOU RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS?
NO, YOUR
PARENTS ARE.
HA! HA! HA!
I HAVE BEDHEAD!
THERE'S NO WATER.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO
SHAMPOO, RINSE, REPEAT
AND LEAVE IN FOR
TWO MINUTES WITH NO WATER?
WELL, I SUGGEST
YOU GO JUMP IN
THE LAKE.
I CAN'T.
I'M ALLERGIC.
YOU'RE ALLERGIC
TO WATER?
WATER, NO;
POSSUM LAKE, YES.
JUST RELAX,
HAROLD.
WE'VE GOT THE GUYS
DRILLING THE WELL
DEEPER.
WE'LL HAVE WATER
IN A COUPLE OF DAYS.
COUPLE OF DAYS?
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO STAY CLEAN?
WEAR MORE COLOGNE.
WHY CAN'T WE JUST
HOOK UP THE TOWN WATER
LIKE EVERYBODY
ELSE IN THE AREA?
BECAUSE THEN OUR
TAXES WILL GO UP.
PLUS THEY'LL STICK
A METER IN THERE.
THEN THE GUY COMES BY
ONCE A MONTH TO CHECK IT,
AND HE STARTS
SNOOPIN' AROUND
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
WE'RE NOT ALLOWED TO
STORE OUR GAS CANS
IN THE FURNACE ROOM.
RED, WE'RE HAVING PROBLEMS
WITH THE WELL DRILLING.
MIKE BROUGHT THIS
PORTABLE WELL DRILLER BY,
BUT IT'S ONLY
GOT A 35-FOOT BIT,
THE WELL'S 40 FEET DEEP,
SO MIKE HAD TO HANG
DOWN INSIDE THE WELL
WHILE WE HELD HIM
BY THE HEELS.
MY OH MY, WHAT
COULD HAVE GONE WRONG
WITH SUCH A WELL
THOUGHT OUT PLAN?
GRAVITY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S PRIZE IS THIS
COUPON FOR MUSIC LOVERS,
WHICH ENTITLES
THE WINNER TO RECEIVE
FOUR ACCORDIONS
AND A SLEDGE HAMMER.
NO QUESTIONS ASKED.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
THINGIES, FRANK.
MR. GREEN, YOU'VE
GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET WORLD RENOWNED
HOT DOG EXPERT FRANK KOEPKE
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH,
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND...
GO!
UM, OKAY, FRANK,
UM, THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT MAKES PEOPLE
SMILE OR LAUGH.
WIENERS.
NO, UH -- OKAY, NO.
THIS RHYMES WITH "CHOKE."
SMOKED WIENERS.
NO, FRANK, THIS HAS
NOTHING TO DO WITH WIENERS.
k.d. lang!
[ APPLAUSE ]
NO, NO, THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT PEOPLE LOOK FORWARD
TO DOING AROUND
THE WATER COOLER.
THEY HEAR THIS,
THEN THEY REPEAT IT.
WHO WANTS A HOT DOG?
THIS IS SOMETHING
PEOPLE SAY THAT'S FUNNY.
OH, WHO WANTS A
TUBE STEAK?
NO, THIS IS SOME --
IT SEEMS TO BE ONE THING,
THEN THERE'S A TWIST,
AND IT'S ACTUALLY
SOMETHING ELSE.
A VEGGIE DOG.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
EVERYONE HAS A FEW OF THESE.
SOMETIMES THEY'RE DIRTY.
KIELBASA.
YOU'RE ALMOST
OUTTA TIME, MR. GREEN.
FRANK, CAN YOU STOP
THINKIN' ABOUT WIENERS?
NO, I DON'T THINK I CAN?
WELL, YOU GOTTA.
THERE'S MORE TO LIFE
THAN WIENERS!
GOOD ONE.
THAT'S A JOKE, RIGHT?
THERE WE GO!
announcer: MEET CHERYL.
SHE'S A COMPUTER PROGRAMMER
WHO'S LOOKING FOR A GOOD TIME
AND MAYBE SOMETHING MORE.
[ DOORBELL ]
THIS IS WINSTON,
A SEPTIC SUCKER
WHO'S READY FOR LOVIN'.
LET'S SEE HOW THEY DID.
YOU LOOK, UH,
LOVELY TONIGHT.
MIND IF I DRIVE?
Winston: YOU KNOW, MY TRUCK'S
A VERY SAFE VEHICLE, EH?
NO ONE EVER TAILGATES.
YOU KNOW, PERSONALLY,
I DON'T REALLY CARE FOR
MEXICAN FOOD THAT MUCH.
BUT BOY, IS IT EVER
GOOD FOR BUSINESS!
YOU DONE WITH THAT?
Winston: HANG ON.
OH, YEAH, JUST
WIND AROUND HERE.
SO, UH, WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU HAD YOUR TANK PUMPED?
WHAT DID I SAY?
YEAH, SO I GO ON
THIS OVERFLOW JOB, RIGHT,
BUT INSTEAD OF ONE TOILET
THERE'S LIKE 16 TOILETS!
AND THEY'RE
ALL OVERFLOWIN' --
WELL, ANYWAY, UH...
CALL YOU NEXT WEEK.
THIS IS AN EXOTIC
CAR MAGAZINE?
A LOT OF HIGH PRICED FANCY
VEHICLES IN THIS BABY,
I'LL TELL YOU.
FERRARIS AND TIRAMISUS.
NOW A LOT OF GUYS AVOID
LOOKING AT THESE MAGAZINES
BECAUSE THEY CAN'T STAND
SEEIN' THINGS THEY'LL
NEVER HAVE.
THAT'S ACTUALLY TRUE
FOR ALL MEN'S MAGAZINES.
BUT TO ME, EXPENSIVE
CAN STILL BE DONE CHEAPLY.
THAT'S BECAUSE
I HAVE IMAGINATION.
NOW, THOSE MILLION-DOLLAR,
EUROPEAN, HIGH-PERFORMANCE,
FANCY BOY CARS,
THEY'RE ALL RED,
STAND ABOUT YAY HIGH,
AND THEY HAVE THE ENGINE RIGHT
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE CAR.
SEE, THE MID ENGINE
BALANCES THE CAR
SO SHE CORNERS BETTER.
PLUS IF YOU
SMASH INTO ANYTHING,
MOST OF THE EXPENSIVE,
HIGH-TECH ENGINE PARTS
WILL BE PROTECTED
BY YOUR PASSENGERS.
I COULD NEVER AFFORD
ONE OF THOSE BABIES.
I MEAN, I HAD TO WAIT TILL
PAYDAY TO BUY THE MAGAZINE.
I CAN STILL HAVE
A MID-ENGINE CAR.
OKAY, FROM THE BACK
OF THE CAR TO THE ENGINE
IS EXACTLY...
AROUND 12'11".
BUT FROM THE ENGINE
TO THE FRONT OF THE CAR
IS ONLY 4'9".
SO IF I WANNA HAVE
THE ENGINE IN THE MIDDLE,
I CAN EITHER MOVE THE ENGINE
BACK AROUND 5 FEET,
WHICH WOULD WREAK HAVOC
WITH MY CUP HOLDERS,
OR I COULD LOP 12 FEET
OFF THE BACK END,
BUT THAT WOULD FORCE ME TO
SIT ON THE HOOD ORNAMENT.
SO SIMPLEST OF ALL,
ALL'S I GOTTA DO
IS ADD 8 FEET
TO THE FRONT END.
NOW, IF YOU'RE DOIN'
THIS IN METRIC,
BEST OF LUCK TO YOU.
BOY, THAT WAS
A LOT OF SAWING.
BUT I'VE GOT THE NEW CHUNK
TO STICK ONTO THE
FRONT OF MY VEHICLE.
THE WHEELS EVEN
TURN ON THIS THING.
SAFE OR WHAT?
NOW, I REMOVED THE ENGINE AND
DRIVE TRAIN FROM THE UNIT.
WELL, ACTUALLY, RUST
AND GRAVITY REMOVED THEM.
BUT I DIDN'T FIGHT IT.
I GOTTA FIND SOME WAY
TO FLATTEN THIS ROOF DOWN.
OTHERWISE, IT'S GONNA
LOOK KINDA SILLY.
I'M OUTTA
HACKSAW BLADES, SO...
YOU WANNA USE A FAIR WHACK
OF THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON ON THIS JOB.
I WOULD RECOMMEND
FIVE LARGE ROLLS.
IF THAT'S TOO RICH FOR YOU,
HEY, MAYBE YOU CAN'T
AFFORD TO HAVE
A EUROPEAN-STYLE
MID-ENGINE CAR.
AND FOR THAT
FINISHING TOUCH,
TO MAKE THIS BABY
LOOK EXTRA SHARP,
PUT A PIZZA BOX
OVER THE WHEEL WELLS
TO HIDE WHERE
THE TIRES USED TO BE.
I WOULD RECOMMEND YOU
PUT A REAL GOOD PRIMER
ON THOSE PIZZA BOXES,
BECAUSE WHEN
CARDBOARD GETS WET,
IT LOSES A LOT
OF ITS STRENGTH.
OKAY... SO REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
THIS ISN'T AN
OLD JUNKER ANYMORE.
IT'S A FANCY ITALIAN
MID-ENGINE JUNKER.
AND I'M NOT RED GREEN.
I'M UMBERTO TORTELLINI.
[ CRASH ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
I HAVE A SHOCKING REVELATION
FOR YOU MEN OUT THERE.
THERE ARE PEOPLE
WHO ARE SMARTER THAN YOU.
FOR YOU MARRIED GUYS,
THIS IS PROBABLY NOT THE FIRST
TIME YOU'RE HEARING THIS.
SEE, I'VE ALWAYS KNOWN THERE
ARE SMARTER PEOPLE THAN ME.
BUT THE THING THAT GETS ME
IS HOW THE AGE OF
THE SMARTER PEOPLE
HAS CHANGED OVER
THE COURSE OF MY LIFE.
WHEN I WAS A KID,
MY MIND WAS QUICK AND SHARP.
I'D HAVE TO GO TO UP FIVE,
MAYBE EVEN TEN YEARS OLDER
TO FIND PEOPLE
SMARTER THAN ME.
BY THE TIME I HIT 40,
THE PEOPLE SMARTER THAN ME
WERE ALL AROUND MY OWN AGE.
THAT'S WHEN THE
TROUBLE STARTED.
MY AGE KEPT GOING UP,
BUT THE AGE OF PEOPLE
SMARTER THAN ME
STARTED GOIN' DOWN.
IT BEGAN WITH
A 25-YEAR-OLD WOMAN
EXPLAINING THAT
THE BANK MACHINE
WON'T ALLOW ME
TO WITHDRAW CASH
FROM AN OVERDRAWN ACCOUNT.
THEN A COUPLE
OF YEARS LATER,
IT WAS A 16-YEAR-OLD
SKATE BOARDER POINTING OUT
THAT THE CHEAP GAS
I JUST PUT IN MY TANK
WAS DIESEL.
THEN LAST WEEK,
A 9-YEAR-OLD COMPUTER WHIZ
WAS TELLIN' ME THE REASON
MY MONITOR DOESN'T WORK
IS BECAUSE IT'S
A MICROWAVE OVEN.
BUT MY STUPIDITY CAN
BE OUR LITTLE SECRET.
THAT'S BECAUSE
IN MOST GROUPS
I LOOK LIKE THE SMART ONE.
ALL THESE WRINKLES AND SCARS
FROM DOIN' STUPID THINGS
HAVE GIVEN ME THE
APPEARANCE OF GREAT WISDOM.
THEY ASSUME I MUST
KNOW A LOT OF STUFF.
SO ALL I HAVE TO DO TO COME
ACROSS AS A GENIUS
IS TO JUST KEEP
MY MOUTH SHUT.
IF ONLY I WAS THAT SMART.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLIN'
FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, THIS IS
GETTIN' SERIOUS.
WE'VE GIVEN UP ON
DIGGING THE WELL DEEPER.
AND THIS IS THE LAST
OF OUR DRINKING WATER.
I CAN'T BRING MYSELF
TO BUY THE BOTTLED STUFF,
BECAUSE AFTER I DIE,
I'LL RUN INTO MY GRANDFATHER,
AND HE'S GONNA
GIVE ME A LOT OF GRIEF
ABOUT PAYIN' 12 BUCKS A
GALLON FOR DRINKING WATER.
MIND YOU, IF IT'S HEAVEN,
THERE'S A PRETTY GOOD CHANCE
THAT AT LEAST ONE
OF US WON'T BE THERE.
NOW, HAROLD WANTS US TO
HOOK UP TO THE TOWN WATER,
BUT WE DON'T
WANNA DO THAT.
WE'RE GONNA DRILL
A BRAND NEW WELL.
IN FACT, WE'VE GOT ONE OF
THOSE WATER FINDING EXPERTS
COMING OVER RIGHT NOW.
HEY, RED.
YEAH?
ALL SET TO GO.
GREAT!
WHERE'S THE WATER-
FINDING EXPERT GUY?
IT'S MIKE.
MIKE FELL DOWN THE WELL
AND COULDN'T FIND WATER.
I DON'T THINK YOU
SHOULD USE AN ACCIDENT
AS AN OPPORTUNITY TO
POOH-POOH ME, MR. GREEN.
THE TRUTH IS
WHEN I WAS IN PRISON,
I BECAME VERY PROFICIENT AT
USING A DIVINING ROD
TO LOCATE
UNDERGROUND TUNNELS.
GIVE HIM
A CHANCE, RED.
FEELS LIKE A WASTE
OF TIME TO ME.
WELL, YOU OF ALL PEOPLE SHOULD
BE COMFORTABLE WITH THAT.
OKAY, HERE GOES.
OH, MAN.
THERE!
WOW! LOOK!
GOLLY, THAT'S
CONVINCING.
YOU HAVE WATER
ON THE KNEE.
IT'S A MEDICAL
CONDITION.
HEY!
SO IS THAT!
THERE'S YOUR WATER,
MR. GREEN.
IT'S RIGHT DOWN
UNDER THAT POST.
THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
NO, THE STICK
NEVER LIES.
LOOK DOWN THERE.
IT'S MAYBE 9 OR
10 FEET DOWN,
BUT IT'S THERE
ALL RIGHT.
BUT THERE'S AN ELECTRICAL
OUTLET ON THAT POST.
WOULDN'T THE WATER
SHORT THAT OUT?
NO, NO,
NOT A PROBLEM.
YOU SURE?
NO! NO! NO!
Red: KIND OF AN EDUCATIONAL
FILM ON TONIGHT'S ADVENTURE.
WALTER WAS GONNA SHOW
HAROLD HOW TO MILK A COW.
SO, UH, IN THEY GO.
AND THEY HAD A COW THERE.
A GOOD START.
HAROLD'S A
LITTLE TENTATIVE.
YOU KNOW...
IT'S HIS FIRST DATE.
NO, HAROLD.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
WALTER REALISES HE
HAS TO START FORM SCRATCH.
THIS IS A KIND OF
A SIDEMOUNT UNIT.
JUST EASY.
JUST NICE AND EASY.
NOTHING TO IT.
SEE, HAROLD DOESN'T
KNOW HOW TO REACT.
HEY, WALTER, YOU CAN HAVE A
SNACK WHILE YOU'RE WORKING.
OH BOY!
[ CHUCKLES ]
SO, HAROLD --
AH, NO, NO.
NO, HAROLD.
NO, NO.
YOU EVER HEARD OF
BLOOD FROM A STONE, HAROLD?
SO THAT'S NOT WORKIN'.
WALTER REALISES
HE'S GONNA HAVE TO SPEND
A LITTLE MORE
TIME TEACHING HAROLD,
SO HE JUST HAPPENS TO HAVE A
SURGICAL GLOVE IN HIS
PANTS THERE.
AND HE GETS THAT OUT
AND GONNA FILL THAT WITH MILK
AND USE THAT --
WE KNOW, HAROLD.
WE KNOW. WE KNOW.
COME ON. COME ON.
HE'S GONNA SHOW HIM
IF HE USES THE GLOVE,
JUST TO KIND OF GET
A FEEL FOR IT.
YOU'VE GOTTA BE
FIRM BUT GENTLE.
FIRM... WATCH THIS NOW.
FIRM... BUT GENTLE.
BUT GENTLE.
BUT FIRM.
COME ON NOW.
YOU CAN DO IT.
FIRM BUT GENTLE.
FIRM -- OKAY, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NOT THAT --
OH!
ALL RIGHT, PLAN "B," THE
AUTOMATIC MILKING MACHINE.
THESE THINGS GO
ONTO THE UNIT,
AND THEN, UH, YOU JUST
THROW THE SWITCH
AND THE VACUUM, AND IT MILKS
THE COW AUTOMATICALLY.
THIS SOMETHING EVEN
HAROLD COULD UNDERSTAND.
HAROLD HAS AN
ATTENTION DEFICIT PROBLEM,
AND OF COURSE,
WOULDN'T YOU KNOW IT,
THERE WAS A
FLY IN THE BARN.
SO IT'S COMING AROUND.
HAROLD CAN'T IGNORE THAT.
SO HE'S FLIPPING --
JUST FORGET THE --
HAROLD, FORGET THE --
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT DOESN'T MATTER, HAROLD.
FORGET THE FLY.
THE FLY CIRCLES ANYWAY,
RIGHT DOWN THE CHUTE.
MEANWHILE, WALTER
IS TURNING ON THE UNIT.
AND THOSE THINGS
HAVE A LOT OF ACTION.
AS HAROLD KNOWS.
YOU CAN LOSE
YOUR BRAINS, HAROLD.
WALTER TRIES TO
PULL IT OFF.
UH, WHEN SOMEONE'S IN TROUBLE,
YOU SHOULD JUST STAY AWAY
BECAUSE YOU CAN ACTUALLY
GET HURT YOURSELF...
THERE LIKE THAT.
SO THEN HE REALISES,
WHY DON'T I JUST TURN
THE MACHINE OFF?
THERE THAT SHUT
OFF THE VACUUM,
AND NOW YOU CAN TAKE
THE UNIT RIGHT OFF HIM.
AND HE SHOULD BE FINE.
OKAY. YOU OKAY, HAROLD?
FINE? YOU OKAY?
YOU GOOD? YOU GOOD?
YOU OKAY, HAROLD?
HAROLD?
DON'T LIE TO ME.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AS YOU CAN SEE,
WE'RE WELL INTO THE
WELL DRILLING HERE.
WE'RE ALREADY DOWN
ABOUT NINE FEET.
WE SHOULD HIT WATER
ANY MINUTE.
NOW, WE KNOW ELECTRICITY
AND WATER DON'T MIX.
SO WE'RE USING
A CORDLESS DRILL.
UNCLE RED, I JUST
WANNA GO ON RECORD
SAYING I THINK
THIS IS A BIG MISTAKE.
HAROLD, THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT YOUR DAD SAID IN
THE DELIVERY ROOM.
NO! I'M TALKING
ABOUT PUTTING A WELL
RIGHT INSIDE THE LODGE.
YOU'RE TAKING
AN AWFUL CHANCE.
NO, WE'RE NOT.
THE WELL WILL BE HANDY HERE.
THE WATER WON'T
FREEZE IN THE WINTER.
HAROLD, THIS MAY
BE OUR ONLY CHANCE
TO HAVE INDOOR PLUMBING.
WHAT IF IT ENDS UP SMELLING
LIKE ROTTEN EGGS OR SOMETHING?
IT'LL BE JUST LIKE
A LODGE MEETING.
YEAH! YEAH! YEAH!
WE GOT IT!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
LET'S SEE WHAT
WE'VE GOT, HAROLD.
HUH? HEY?
THAT DOESN'T SMELL
LIKE ROTTEN EGGS.
JUST CLEAN, FRESH
SPRING WATER.
WAIT! WAIT! WAIT!
WAIT! WAIT!
I KNOW THIS TASTE.
YES, YOU DO, HAROLD.
IT'S CALLED CROW.
NO, IT'S
CALLED CHLORINE.
THAT'S CHLORINATED.
YEAH, YOU DIDN'T
MAKE A NEW WELL.
YOU HIT THE
TOWN WATER MAIN.
WHAT'S HE
TALKING ABOUT?
WHERE'S
HE GOING?
WHO CARES?
WHOA!
WHOA! WHOA!
[ APPLAUSE ]
GOOD, HAROLD.
GOOD. GOOD.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GUYS
GO AHEAD.
I'VE GOTTA WAIT
TILL MY PANTS DRY.
WELCOME
TO MY WORLD.
[ APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND THE WATER'S BACK ON,
SO I'LL BE ABLE TO WASH UP.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE STILL
HAVE THAT ANNOYING DRIP.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, GUYS, HAVE A SEAT.
COMING TO ORDER.
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN EVERYONE.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, WE'VE JUST
ACCIDENTALLY HOOKED UP
THE TOWN WATER.
AND TRYING TO GET AN IDEA WHAT
IT'S GOING TO COST THE LODGE.
SO I'VE GOT A COUPLE OF
QUESTIONS FOR YOU HERE.
HOW MANY OF YOU SHOWER
MORE THAN ONCE A MONTH?
WELL, THAT FIGURES.
OKAY, HOW MANY OF
YOU DRINK THE STUFF?
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT WATER.
I THINK WE'LL BE FINE.