YOU KNOW, I’VE SEEN PEOPLE
PUT SOME PRETTY WEIRD
STUFF INTO HAMBURGERS
BREAD CRUMBS, EGG YOLK,
CHOPPED PARSLEY!
MAN, MAYBE IT'S JUST ME,
BUT WHEN A PATTY COMES THAT
CLOSED TO CONTAINING ALL
FIVE FOOD GROUPS,
IT PRETTY MUCH RUINS THE
POINT OF EATING RED MEAT
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
PERSONALLY, I HAVE MY
OWN SECRET INGREDIENT.
IT'S CHEAP, IT'S PLENTIFUL,
AND HERE'S THE BEST PART...
IT WON'T DO A DARNED
THING FOR YOUR HEALTH.
THAT'S RIGHT... POPCORN.
WHAT YOU WANNA DO IS
STICK ABOUT A DOZEN OF THESE
KERNELS INTO ONE SIDE
OF THE PATTY,
AND THEN LAY HER DOWN
ON THE B.B.Q. WITH
THAT SIDE DOWN.
THEN YOU JUST GO RELAX.
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT.
WHILE THE POPCORN DOESN'T
DO MUCH FOR THE TASTE
OR HOLDING
THE MEAT TOGETHER,
I JUST DON'T LIKE
STANDING OVER A HOT
B.B.Q. FLIPPING BURGERS.
[ POPCORN POPPING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE THAT.
I'M JUST ON MY WAY TO
PORT ASBESTOS
TO GET A VIDEO FOR TONIGHT'S
LODGE MEETING.
WE'RE GONNA RENT "FLIGHT
OF THE PHOENIX".
HAVE YOU SEEN THAT ONE WHERE
PEOPLE CRASH THEIR PLANE
IN THE SAHARA
AND THEN BUILD ANOTHER PLANE
OUT OF THE PIECES?
OH, WE LOVE THAT MOVIE.
IT'S KINDA LIKE THE HANDYMAN'S
"GONE WITH THE WIND."
SO WHAT DO YOU
SAY, UNCLE RED?
WELL, I SAY GIVE ME
10 BUCKS WORTH OF
REGULAR UNLEADED.
NO! NO! NO!
IT'S A PILOT'S UNIFORM.
I GOT MY WINGS.
WELL, YOU GOT WINGS,
I'LL GET SOME FRIES,
WE'LL HAVE LUNCH.
NO! NO! NO!
MY REAL WINGS,
MY PILOT'S LICENSE.
I CAN FLY YOU
TO PORT ASBESTOS.
CONGRATULATIONS, YOU'RE
THE FIRST 'RETHE FIRST CUSTOMERN
POSSUM AIR.
THE PROUD BIRD WITH
SKINNY, HAIRLESS TAIL.
DON'T YOU NEED A PLANE
TO FLY ANYBODY ANYPLACE?
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
THAT'S WHY I BORROWED
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S
OPEN COCKPIT
W.W.I. SOPWITH CAMEL.
WAIT A SEC, THAT'S
HIS CHICKEN COOP.
WELL, WE TOOK
THE CHICKENS OUT.
CHICKENS CAN'T FLY.
BUT YOU CAN,
IF YOU'RE NOT CHICKEN.
WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
OH, COME ON,
I DON'T ASK YOU MUCH.
PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLEASE!
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE!
OH, ALL RIGHT!
GET THE
PLANE READY.
YES, SIR!
OH!
OKAY.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TONIGHT'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FOR A GLORIOUS WEEKEND FOR
ONE AT POSSUM LAKE'S
OLDEST INN...
THE DEAD SQUIRREL.
YOU CAN GO NUTS
AT THE DEAD SQUIRREL.
OKAY, COVER YOUR EARS, ED.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30
SECONDS TO GET ED FRID
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH,
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, ED, WHEN YOU
GET A GUT FEELING ABOUT
SOMETHING THAT'S YOUR...
PEPTIC ULCER.
OKAY, NO, THIS IS SOMETHING
YOU DO WITHOUT THINKING.
YOU BECOME AN ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICER.
OKAY, ED, WHEN YOUR DOG
BURIES A BONE IN
YOUR BACKYARD,
WHAT'S KICKING IN?
HIS HIND FEET.
NO, ACTUALLY, THIS
IS SOMETHING THAT YOU
SEE IN EVERY ANIMAL.
OH, TEETH.
NO, NO, THIS IS
DEEP INSIDE AN ANIMAL.
OH, A VETERINARIAN'S ARM.
Winston:
YOU GUYS ARE
RUNNIN' OUTTA TIME, EH.
YEAH, BOY, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I CAN TELL YOU.
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE
GONNA WIN THAT
WEEKEND AWAY.
WELL, THAT'S OKAY, RED.
RI DIDN'T REALLY WANNA STAY
AT THE DEAD SQUIRREL.
THAT INN STINKS.
YES!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING.
JOINING ME TODAY IS LOCAL
WATER TAXI CAPTAIN
HAP SHAUGNESSY.
HAVEN'T SEEN
YOU IN A WHILE, HAP.
WHERE YOU BEEN HIDING?
OH, HOLLYWOOD, RED,
THE OLD DREAM
FACTORY.
YOU A BIG MOVIE
STAR NOW, HAP?
OH, DON'T BE SILLY.
THEY DON'T HAND THOSE JOBS
OUT TO JUST ANYONE, YOU KNOW.
I'M A SCREENWRITER.
YOU WRITTEN ANYTHING
WE MIGHT'VE SEEN?
YEAH, A COUPLE
OF SCI-FI FLICKS.
EVER HEARD OF
"STAR WARS"?
I THOUGHT GEORGE LUCAS
HAD WRITTEN ALL THOSE.
OH, 'LUCKY' LUCAS, NO,
HE JUST DID THE
FIRST DRAFT.
IT WAS MY IDEA TO
SET IT IN OUTER SPACE.
WHERE DID HE
WANNA SET 'EM?
FRANCE.
I JUST DIDN'T THINK
THAT SOUNDED BELIEVABLE.
NO, NO, IT DOESN'T.
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT
ME TO FIX HERE, HAP?
ANSWERING MACHINE.
AN OLD GIRLFRIEND OF MINE
FILLED UP THE TAPE
WITH MESSAGES.
NOW THE REWIND
BUTTON IS BROKEN.
OH, BOY, I DON'T
THINK I CAN FIX IT.
YOU KNOW, I GOT ANOTHER
CASSETTE MACHINE HERE.
I COULD PROBABLY JUST
REWIND YOUR TAPE
USING THAT.
WOULD THAT BE
ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, THAT SOUNDS
GOOD TO ME.
SO THIS GIRL YOU
WERE GOING OUT WITH,
ONE OF YOUR
HOLLYWOOD FRIENDS?
YEAH, YEAH.
GWYNETH PALTROW.
THE GWYNETH PALTROW?
ARE THERE A
LOT OF THEM?
YOU WENT OUT
WITH GWYNETH PALTROW?
YEAH, IT WAS ONE OF THOSE
MAY-DECEMBER THINGS.
DECEMBER OF
WHAT YEAR?
WELL, WOMEN ARE
ATTRACTED TO ME, RED.
THEY FIND ME MYSTERIOUS.
MYSTERIOUS OR DELIRIOUS.
THERE WE GO.
LET'S LISTEN TO THIS.
[ BEEP! ]
[ Hap's voice in
high-pitched tone ]
HI, HAP, IT'S ME AGAIN,
FILM STAR, GWYNETH PALTROW.
PLEASE GIVE ME A CALL.
I MISS YOU, HAP.
WELL, SHE SOUNDS
LIKE SOMEBODY ELSE.
YEAH, SHE'S A
GREAT ACTRESS, RED.
YOU MIGHT WANNA THINK ABOUT
BEING AN ACTOR YOURSELF, HAP.
OH, SURE, I KNOW,
BUT I COULD NEVER GO
INTO THAT LINE OF WORK.
YOU HAVE TO BE
ABLE TO PRETEND YOU'RE
SOMETHING YOU'RE NOT.
THEY'RE
PROFESSIONAL LIARS.
WHAT KIND OF
MAN WOULD I BE,
IF I GOT
PAID TO LIE?
A BILLIONAIRE.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE ALWAYS
LOOKING FOR WAYS
TO RAISE A LITTLE EXTRA
CASH AROUND THE LODGE.
SO I GOT TO THINKING, BOY,
WE GOT A LOTTA FAMILIES
COMING UP HERE.
THEY ALWAYS HAVE A BUNCH
OF KIDS RUNNING AROUND,
DRIVING EVERYBODY NUTS.
SO I DECIDED TO MAKE
A RIDE FOR THE KIDDIES,
LIKE THE ONES THEY USED TO
HAVE AT THE GROCERY STORE.
OR MAYBE IT WAS A LITTLE
CAR OR A FAKE PONY
OR A ROCKET SHIP.
YOU'D STICK STICK
A DIME IN THERE,
AND IT WOULD SHAKE
FOR A MINUTE.
THAT WAS GOOD VALUE,
WASN'T IT?
I FIGURE I CAN MAKE
SOMETHING BETTER THAN THAT
OUT OF THIS OLD COIN-OPERATED
WASHING MACHINE
THEY THREW OUT
AT THE LAUNDRY MAT
AFTER SOMEBODY TRIED
TO WASH MATTRESS IN IT.
WHO KNEW?
AND I'LL TELL YOU,
AT 10 CENTS A POP,
THIS IS THE BIGGEST CASH COW
THE LODGE HAS SEEN SINCE,
WELL, EVER.
NOW ALL WE DO IS ATTACH MY
BAR STOOL TO THE AGITATOR,
AND THAT'LL GIVE US THAT
BACK AND FORTH MOTION
THAT THE YOUNGSTERS
REALLY ENJOY --
UNTIL THEY GET DIZZY AND BARF
ALL OVER EVERYBODY.
BUT FIRST I GOTTA GET THE
AGITATOR OUTTA THERE.
OKAY, I USED THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON
TO ATTACH MY BARSTOOL
POLE ONTO THE AGITATOR.
BUT I TOOK THE
SEAT OFF FIRST,
BECAUSE I REALLY WANT TO
MAXIMIZE THE ENJOYMENT
THAT A YOUNGSTER IS GOING
TO GET OUT OF THIS.
SEE, NOW, IF I MOUNT
THE SEAT NORMALLY,
ALL YOU GET IS THE
NORMAL AGITATOR ACTION.
BUT FOR THAT EXTRA THRILL
YOU WANNA GO OFF CENTRE.
IF THERE'S ONE THING
WE DO WELL AT THE LODGE
IT'S GO OFF CENTRE.
OKAY, I THINK WE'RE READY
FOR A LITTLE DEMONSTRATION.
ACTUALLY GONNA USE A STUFFED
ANIMAL AS MY TEST PILOT
BECAUSE STUFFED ANIMALS
DON'T HAVE PARENTS
THAT'LL SUE YOU.
AS A LITTLE EXTRA
SAFETY FEATURE,
I'M GONNA THROW
A SEAT BELT ON HERE.
THIS WOULD ACTUALLY BE A GOOD
IDEA FOR ALL THE BARSTOOLS
UP AT THE LODGE.
I TELL YOU, THE KIDS'LL BE
LINING UP FOR THIS ONE.
ALL RIGHT,
TIME FOR LIFT-OFF.
ANYBODY GOT A DIME?
YOU GOT A DIME THERE?
GIVE ME A DIME,
WILL YOU?
GIVE ME A DIME.
OKAY, PLEASE GIVE
ME A DIME.
I'LL GET HAROLD TO CLEAN
YOUR WINDSHIELD, ALL RIGHT?
MAN, OH, MAN!
TRUST IN THE WORK PLACE A
THING OF THE PAST,
I'M TELLIN' YOU.
OKAY, LET'S GET
READY TO TUMBLE.
EVERYBODY WINS, SEE?
THE KID HAS FUN;
THE PARENTS HAVE A BREAK;
AND I'M UP A DIME!
GUS, I'LL PAY YOU
BACK, ALL RIGHT?
REMEMBER: IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
AND YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT SOME KID
HOGGING THE RIDE
THE WHOLE DAY,
BECAUSE IF HE STAYS
ON THERE TOO LONG,
SHE KICKS INTO
THE SPIN CYCLE.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
I FIGURE A LOT OF
YOU GUYS OUT THERE
COULD BENEFIT
FROM MY EXPERIENCE.
THAT'S A NICE
WAY OF SAYING THAT IN
THE GREAT RIVER OF TIME,
I'M A LITTLE FARTHER UP THE
CREEK THAN YOU ARE.
NOW, I BET THAT
YOU STILL SEE YOURSELF
AS THAT VIRILE, OUTDOORSY GUY
THAT YOU WERE 20 YEARS AGO.
I'M HERE TO TELL YOU THAT
IS NO LONGER THE CASE,
BECAUSE AS THOSE YEARS HAVE
PASSED, NATURE HAS TAKEN
ITS COURSE,
AND YOU HAVE NOT BEEN KEEPING
UP WITH THE CURRICULUM.
HEADING OUT INTO
THE WILDERNESS AT YOUR AGE
IS ONLY ASKING FOR TROUBLE.
YOU REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
YOU WERE IN WHITE WATER?
WAS IT WHEN YOU SPILLED
YOUR BROMO IN THE HOT TUB?
WHEN'S THE LAST TIME YOU
SAW YOUR HIKING BOOTS?
HECK, WHEN'S THE LAST
TIME YOU SAW YOUR FEET?
REMEMBER YOU USED TO
GRAB THE OL' KNAPSACK
BEFORE HIKING UP
THE MOUNTAIN?
NOW YOU HAVE TO
GRAB A NAP IN THE SACK
BEFORE HIKING UP YOUR PANTS!
SO FORGET ABOUT
THE WILDERNESS.
JUST SETTLE BACK
INTO YOUR La-Z-Boy,
TURN ON THE
NATIONAL GEOGRAPHIC
AND WATCH THE NATURAL
DISASTERS IN COMFORT.
AT OUR AGE, WE DON'T
NEED HIGH ADVENTURE;
WE NEED HIGH FIBRE.
AND IF YOU EAT
ENOUGH OAT BRAN,
YOU MAY JUST GET BOTH.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ ROCK ]
HAVE TO EXCUSE
THE MESS HERE.
THIS IS NOW THE TEMPORARY
DEPARTURE LOUNGE FOR
POSSUM AIR.
THERE'S NOTHING TO DO.
A BOTTLE OF WATER WILL
COST YOU FIVE BUCKS,
AND THE EMPLOYEES
ARE ALL RUDE AND SURLY,
SO IT'S PRETTY MUCH
LIKE A REAL AIRPORT.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
WELCOME TO THE INAUGURAL
FLIGHT OF POSSUM AIR.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR PATIENCE
FOR OUR MECHANICAL DELAY.
WE WILL BE BOARDING
THIS AFTERNOON
STARTING WITH
SEAT NUMBER ONE.
THANK YOU FOR
FLYING POSSUM AIR.
IT'S THE PROUD BIRD WITH THE
SKINNY, HAIRLESS TAIL.
[ TREMBLING ]
[ WHISPERING ]
I'VE JUT BEEN INFORMED
THERE WILL BE ANOTHER
SLIGHT
MECHANICAL DELAY.
WE WILL, UM --
BOARDING WILL COMMENCE --
[ WHISPERING ]
OH! SHORTLY, HA!
COME ON, HAROLD!
IF I'D TAKEN THE POSSUM VAN
I'D BE HALFWAY THERE BY NOW,
IF IT STARTED.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT,
WELL, UM --
YOU KNOW WHAT WE CAN DO?
WE CAN DO OUR SECURITY
AND SAVE TIME ON
THE OTHER END.
ALL RIGHT.
OVER THERE?
WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO DO?
STAND OVER HERE.
AND I'LL JUST SCAN
YOU WITH THIS,
AND THIS WILL TELL ME IF
YOU HAVE ANY METAL
OBJECTS ON YOU.
SPREAD YOUR ARMS!
[ METAL DETECTOR SCREECHING ]
OH! OH! OH!
AH! AH! AH!
AHHH!
OKAY, COULD YOU
JUST EMPTY
ALL YOUR METAL OBJECTS
INTO THIS BUCKET?
OH, SURE, YEAH.
NO PROBLEM.
OKAY. OKAY.
OKAY, NO, THAT'S GOOD.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S JUST ASSUME
YOU'RE CLEAR.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S GOOD, GOOD.
SHE'S READY
TO FLY, CAPTAIN.
I'M PRETTY SURE.
DID HE CALL
YOU CAPTAIN?
OH, YEAH,
I'M THE CAPTAIN.
AND MIKE HERE IS GOING
TO BE YOUR MECHANIC,
CO-PILOT AND STEWARD.
UH, WELCOME ABOARD.
OH, MAN!
Bienvenue.
HERE ARE YOUR
COMPLIMENTARY PRETZELS
AND YOUR PARACHUTE.
Uh, ici, uh, les,
uh, gratis bretzel
et, uh, le chute de,
uh -- hm,
GET OUTTA HERE.
para.
THANKS FOR FLYING
POSSUM AIR.
WE DON'T KNOW
THAT YET.
Red Green: I ASKED WALTER TO
MEET ME BEHIND THE LODGE
BECAUSE I WANTED
TO EMPTY THE VAN.
I NEEDED AN EMPTY VAN FOR
WHAT I PLANNED TO DO.
AND THERE WAS JUST
THE CANOE LEFT IN THERE,
AND I THOUGHT, I CAN PROBABLY
HELP HIM BETTER THIS WAY.
AND WE GOT HER OUTTA THERE,
BUT THE THING IS THE
CANOE WAS FULL OF STUFF,
AND WALTER JUST CAN'T
LEAVE WELL ENOUGH ALONE.
HE'S GOTTA START
SNOOPIN' AROUND.
THOSE ARE ONE OF THOSE
FISHING VESTS THAT HAVE
THE TIE-DOWNS
SO YOU CAN TIE YOUR --
IT'S FOR DEEP SEA FISHING.
YOU TIE THE ROD
RIGHT TO THE VEST,
AND THAT WAY YOU GET SOME
HELP BRINGING THE
BIG ONES IN.
AND THERE WAS
THE DEEP SEA ROD.
BUT WHAT I WAS DOING WAS
I WAS GONNA CUT SOME
TREES DOWN,
DO SOME CHIPPING,
AND JUST EMPTY HER
RIGHT INTO THE VAN.
BOY, THOSE ARE
A BEAUTIFUL MACHINE.
THE POWER IN THAT
THING IS JUST --
OF COURSE, WALTER'S STILL
BACK FOOLING AROUND.
HE SEES A BIG
LURE IN THERE,
A HUGE LURE REALLY.
SO HE'S GOTTA GOOF AROUND.
HE'S GOT THE THING
TIED TO HIS VEST,
MEANWHILE, I'M TAKING SOME
TREES DOWN THAT WERE
IN THE WAY
AND PREVENTING OTHER
TREES FROM GROWING,
IN CASE ANYBODY'S
INTERESTED.
BUT LOOK AT THE
POWER OF THIS UNIT.
YOU JUST FEED 'EM IN THERE,
AND LOOK AT THAT THING.
I MEAN, LOOK AT THAT.
OH, MY GOSH,
JUST RIGHT IN THERE.
I JUST LOOK AT THAT,
I HAVE TO SHAVE.
THAT IS SO --
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
OF COURSE, AS A MAN,
YOU GET IDEAS.
YOU SEE SOMETHING LIKE THAT
AND YOU START THINKING
ABOUT THINGS
YOU PROBABLY SHOULDN'T
BE THINKING ABOUT,
AND I'M LOOKING AROUND
AND THERE'S NOBODY THERE.
AND I'M SAYING,
HEY, THAT'S WICKER.
I WONDER IF ANYBODY WOULD --
I WONDER --
COME ON! YOU KNOW YOU'D
DO THE SAME THING!
THERE'S NOT A MAN
WATCHING THIS
WHO WOULDN'T
WANNA TRY THIS.
AND BY GEEZ, DID SHE
EVER GO IN THERE GOOD.
I WAS JUST RECYCLING WICKER
IS WHAT I WAS DOING.
OF COURSE,
WALTER CASTS THERE,
AND WOULDN'T YOU KNOW IT
HE GETS SNAGGED UP
HIGH IN A TREE,
AND NOW HE CAN'T
GET THE LURE.
AND IT JUST SO HAPPENS
THAT IT'S THE VERY TREE
THAT'S NEXT ON MY HIT PARADE
THERE SO DOWN SHE COMES.
AND I MEAN, THIS IS
A PRETTY GOOD SIZE TREE,
AND TO GET THAT INTO --
I DIDN'T KNOW IF
THE CHIPPER --
HAD SOME RESISTANCE,
BUT I JUST THOUGHT
IT WAS A HEAVY TREE.
I DIDN'T REALISE
I WAS PULLING WALTER.
BUT LOOK AT THE
POWER OF THIS UNIT.
YOU GO IN THERE,
AND UP SHE GOES
AND JUST CRANKS HER
RIGHT IN JUST NO PROBLEM.
IT'S LIKE WATCHING
MOOSE THOMPSON EAT.
AND THEN WALTER'S GETTING
DRAGGED ALONG THE
GROUND THERE,
AND I'M THINKING
EVERYTHING IS GREAT.
I'M REALLY ENJOYING THIS.
I LOVE POWER OF ANY KIND.
AND WALTER FLIPS
AROUND THERE.
'COURSE, HE CAN'T LET GO
BECAUSE IT'S TIED --
OH, THERE GO HIS SHOES.
HE'S GOT HER
TIED TO HIS VEST,
SO HE CAN'T REALLY --
NOW HE'S GONNA TRY --
SHE STARTS TO BOG DOWN.
I FIGURE, WHAT THE
HECK'S GOING ON?
SO I FIGURE RATHER THAN
SEE WHAT THE PROBLEM IS,
I'LL JUST, YOU KNOW,
OPEN UP THE THROTTLE.
SO I GOT HER GOIN'
REAL GOOD NOW.
THERE'S A LOT OF STRESS.
I DON'T KNOW --
OH, THERE WE GO.
SO IN SHE GOES,
AND I HAVE NO IDEA.
SUDDENLY I HAVE BITS OF
SHIRT AND CRAP COMING OUT --
AND FISHING ROD
WENT THROUGH THERE.
AND WALTER COMES OVER.
HE'S GOT SOME BIG STORY.
AND REALLY WHAT HE
WANTS IS A RIDE HOME.
I SAY, WELL, LOOK AT
THE WAY YOU'RE DRESSED.
HEY, COME ON.
NO SHOES, NO SHIRT,
NO SERVICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
DON'T YOU HATE IT WHEN
YOU GO AWAY ON VACATION
AND YOU FORGET TO
CANCEL THE NEWSPAPER?
I MEAN, BURGLARS SEE
ALL THESE NEWSPAPERS
SITTING AROUND HERE,
IT'S LIKE AN INVITATION
TO JUST COME ON IN.
LUCKILY, THE REST
OF THE PLACE SAYS,
WHAT ARE YOU, NUTS?
BUT YOU ALWAYS
WANNA PLAY IT SAFE.
SO WHAT YOU DO IS TAKE
YOUR VACUUM CLEANER
AND HOOK UP ONE OF THESE
ATTACHMENTS RIGHT INTO
YOUR MAIL SLOT.
SEE, LIKE THAT, SEE?
PERFECT FIT.
COINCIDENCE...
PRETTY MUCH, YEAH.
THEN WHAT YOU WANNA DO
IS PLUG THE VACUUM CLEANER
IN TO ONE
OF THESE TIMERS
THAT THEY HAVE TO TURN
THE LIGHTS ON AND OFF.
THESE ARE FOR PEOPLE WHO
THINK THEY CAN FOOL BURGLARS
BY HAVING THEIR LIGHTS
COME ON AND GO OFF
AT EXACTLY THE
SAME SECOND EVERY DAY.
NOW, DON'T JUST PUT THAT
INTO YOUR NORMAL POWER.
YOU WANNA RUN THAT
OFF YOUR STOVE WIRING.
THAT'LL GIVE THE VACUUM
CLEANER A LITTLE
EXTRA PIZAZZ.
OKAY, AND THE
BEAUTY THERE IS
YOU DON'T NEED HER
TO BE ON FOR VERY LONG.
JUST SET IT TO GO,
SAY, ON AT 7:00
AND OFF AT 7:05.
AND REALLY IT
JUST THAT SIMPLE
AND A LOT EASIER THAN ASKING
YOUR NEIGHBOURS TO PICK
UP YOUR PAPER.
PLUS, YOU DON'T NEED
TO BUY A THANK-YOU CARD
FOR YOUR VACUUM CLEANER.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS
THE TOWER SPEAKING.
POSSUM AIR
FLIGHT NUMBER ONE,
YOU ARE CLEAR FOR TAKE-OFF.
Harold:
THIS IS FLIGHT NUMBER ONE
COMMENCING TAKE-OFF.
HOW ARE WE LOOKING, TOWER?
YOU KNOW,
IT'S HARD TO TELL.
I CAN'T SEE
YOU OVER THE HEDGE.
CAN YOU GO UP ANY HIGHER?
[ ENGINE SPUTTERING ]
Harold:
THAT'S WHAT
I'M TRYING TO DO!
[ ENGINE SPUTTERING ]
HOLY SMOKES! THERE'S A
CLOTHESLINE DEAD AHEAD!
WATCH OUT!
HAROLD, PULL UP!
HAROLD, FOR GOD SAKES!
[ HAROLD SCREAMING ]
ARE YOU OKAY?
[ HAROLD SPUTTERING ]
WHAT IS IT?
Harold:
LONG UNDERWEAR!
BUT WE MADE IT.
WE'RE FLYING.
I FEEL FUNNY, LIKE MY
HEAD'S GOING TO EXPLODE.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU'RE FLYING UPSIDE DOWN.
Harold:
THAT EXPLAINS SO MUCH.
[ AIRPLANE ENGINE
ZOOMING BY ]
Harold:
WOW! THAT IS BETTER.
THANK YOU, DALTON.
HOW ARE RED AND
MIKE MAKING OUT?
Harold: I'LL SEE.
AH! DALTON!
THEY'RE GONE!
THEY MUST'VE FELL OUT WHEN
I WAS FLIPPED UPSIDE DOWN.
CAN YOU SEE THEM?
YEAH, THERE THEY ARE NOW.
UH, HAROLD, YOU BETTER
JUST COME ON DOWN.
Harold: ROGER!
[ APPLAUSE ]
GREAT NEWS, YOU JUST
WON 100 AIR MILES!
FREE!
[ HAROLD SCREAMING ]
[ CRASH! ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
- Mike: MEETING TIME.
- Red: YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I'M THINKING
MAYBE THIS WEEKEND
WE SHOULD GO
VISIT YOUR PARENTS.
AFTER WHAT I'VE
BEEN THROUGH TODAY,
I FIGURE I CAN
SURVIVE ANYTHING.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND CAPTAIN HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG OUT
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
COME ON, GUYS.
EVERYBODY IN.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
COME ON, SIT DOWN.
GATHER AROUND.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
YOU ALL REMEMBER HAROLD,
THE PROUD BIRD WITH
THE SKINNY, HAIRLESS TAIL?