♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: HI, THIS IS RED GREEN,
ON TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD IS
GOING TO TELL YOU HOW TO
TALK TO POLICEMEN,
BILL'S BLOWS UP HIS CAMPFIRE,
AND I'M GOING TO MAKE A CABIN
CRUISER OUT OF POP BOTTLES.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: AND HERE'S A MAN WHO
SPENDS HIS WHOLE LIFE OUTSIDE,
OUTSIDE THE HOUSE
OUTSIDE THE NORM
OUTSIDE THE ACCEPTABLE RULES
OF BEHAVIOUR THAT MUCH
I KNOW FOR SURE.
ANYWAY HERE HE IS,
MR. OUTSIDE, RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, THANK YOU.
OF COURSE I WOULDN'T HAVE TO
BE OUTSIDE BEING MR. OUTSIDE
IF MR. INSIDE WASN'T HERE INSIDE
HOW ARE YOU TONIGHT
THERE MR. INSIDE?
>>HAROLD: I'M JUST PEACHY,
OH SO PEACHY.
>>RED: QUITE A FEW PITS
IN THE PEACH I SEE.
WELL IT'S BEEN AN INTERESTING
WEEK UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK,
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK GOT REALLY
TICKED OFF WITH MOOSE THOMPSON
BECAUSE MOOSE HAD WRECKED
HIS TOOL SHED.
BUT MOOSE SAID HEY LOOK,
THE ROOF MUST HAVE BEEN SAGGING
DOWN PRETTY LOW FOR ME TO BE
ABLE TO DRIVE MY CAR RIGHT
UP ON TOP OF IT LIKE THAT.
>>HAROLD: YEAH ACTUALLY I SAW
MOOSE'S CAR UP THERE YOU KNOW,
I THOUGHT IT WAS A WEATHERVANE,
YOU KNOW WITH THE DOORS OPEN
KIND OF SHOWING THE WIND
DIRECTION AND ALL THAT.
>>RED: WELL I MEAN WE HAD TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO GET IT DOWN
THERE BECAUSE IT'S REAL HEAVY
YOU KNOW, SO WHAT WE DID WAS WE
ROLLED UP ALL THE WINDOWS AND
THEN SEALED THEM OFF WITH THE
BATHTUB CAULKING AND THEN
WE FILLED HER WITH HYDROGEN
AND OF COURSE THIS MADE IT
LIGHT ENOUGH YOU KNOW THAT
2 GUYS COULD CARRY IT,
SO MOOSE AND BUSTER WERE
CARRYING THE CAR UP THE DRIVEWAY
AND MOOSE WAS SO EXCITED HE
LIT UP A CIGAR AND BY GOLLY
HYDROGEN BURNS REAL WELL,
AND WHEN THE SMOKE CLEARED
OF COURSE THE CAR WAS GONE.
>>HAROLD: STOLEN?
>>RED: I DON'T THINK SO.
WE DIDN'T KNOW WHERE IT WAS
EITHER TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH
YOU KNOW UNTIL WE LOOKED UP
AND THERE IS WAS WAY UP INTO
THE SKY WITH MOOSE STILL HANGING
ON TO THE BACK BUMPER,
AND SHE'S DROPPING AT 32
FEET PER SECOND, PER SECOND
RIGHT DOWN INTO THE MIDDLE
OF POSSUM LAKE.
>>HAROLD: WOW! HO! HO!
WHOA, WAIT A SECOND,
THAT RUSTY OLD CAR IS
GOING TO POLLUTE THE LAKE,
SO WILL MOOSE ACTUALLY.
>>RED: NO HAROLD I TOLD YOU,
WE HAD SEALED UP ALL THE HOLES
IN THE CAR SO IT JUST FLOATED
LIKE A FISHING BOBBER
AND SO DID MOOSE.
OF COURSE HIS HOLES WERE
SEALED UP FROM FEAR.
THE CAR LOOKED REAL INTERESTING
BECAUSE IT WAS UPSIDE DOWN
YOU KNOW AND IT WAS FASCINATING
WITH THE WHEELS STILL SPINNING
AND THE TIRES SMOLDERING,
A SEAGULL WENT OVER AND DROPPED
A TREAT THROUGH THE HOLE IN
HIS MUFFLER AND WE GOT THE
IDEA TO HAVE OUR OWN REGATTA.
>>HAROLD: A REGATTA?
>>RED: A REGATTA.
>>HAROLD: WELL YOU KNOW
A REGATTA THAT'S LIKE WHEN
ALL THE BOATS GO BY RIGHT?
AND THEN PEOPLE ALL STAND THERE
IN THEIR WHITE SUITS AND
THEY SALUTE YOU KNOW
FROM THE POOP DECK.
>>RED: YEAH WELL WE HAD
THE POOP DECK COVERED YOU KNOW.
♪ THIS IS A LOVE SONG ♪
♪ MORE OR LESS FOR MY WIFE ♪
♪ SHE'S THE BEST THING ♪
♪ OR ONE OF THE BETTER THINGS ♪
♪ ANYWAY THAT'S HAPPENED ♪
♪ TO ME IN MY LIFE ♪
♪ I SAY WHAT I AM ♪
♪ I AM BECAUSE OF HER ♪
♪ BUT SHE WOULDN'T TAKE ♪
♪ THAT AS A COMPLIMENT ♪
♪ I FIND HER TO BE PERFECTER ♪
♪ WELL PRETTY CLOSE IN ♪
♪ A LOT OF WAYS ♪
♪ BUT WELL SHE COULD BACK OFF ♪
♪ ON THE CRITICISM ♪
♪ THAT WOULDN'T HURT AT ALL ♪
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY BERNICE.
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE
GOING TO SHOW YOU SOME WAYS
OF RECYCLING THE OLD
PLASTIC POP BOTTLES.
NOW I KNOW THEY RECYCLE
THESE INTO NEW PLASTIC BOTTLES,
BUT THAT'S GOT TO BE EXPENSIVE
WHEN YOU FIGURE THEY GOT TO HAUL
THEM AWAY IN A TRUCK OF SOME
KIND AND THEN MELT THEM DOWN
AND RINSE ALL THE SPIT OUT
OF THEM AND SO ON.
AND I'M THINKING TO MYSELF,
WHY CAN'T WE COME UP WITH
A BETTER IDEA THAT CAN
USE THE POP BOTTLES
WHERE IS, AS IS.
FOR EXAMPLE WHY DON'T
YOU JUST TAKE A BUNCH OF THEM
AND GLUE THEM ALL OVER YOUR CAR,
DOWN THE DOOR PANELS,
THE FENDERS, THE BUMPERS,
UP OVER THE ROOF BUT
NOT OVER THE WINDOWS
THERE'S A SAFETY TIP THERE.
AND THEN ONCE YOU GOT THEM
GLUED ON, FILL THEM ALL UP
WITH SAND AND WHAT YOU HAVE
IS YOUR VERY OWN PORTABLE
SHOCK ABSORBING CRASH BARRIER.
MIND YOU THEY'RE ABOUT
THE WEIGHT OF A REAL GOOD,
RIPE WATERMELON SO THAT'S GOING
TO CUT INTO YOUR GAS MILEAGE,
BUT YOU GOT TO SAY TO YOURSELF
HEY WHAT IS MY LIFE WORTH?
AND IF THE ANSWER IS MORE THAN
$2 BUCKS A GALLON GO FOR IT.
ANY MORE IDEAS?
WELL I WOULD THINK SO.
WHAT ABOUT JUST CUTTING THE
BOTTOM OFF ONE OF THESE BOTTLES,
THE VARIOUS THINGS YOU CAN DO
WITH THAT, YOU GOT A LOVELY
SOUP BOWL, OR TO MY MIND,
CALL ME CRAZY BUT IF THAT'S
NOT AN ATTRACTIVE PLANT HOLDER
THEN I'M MISSING THE POINT
OF LIFE.
OR YOU KNOW HALF
A HALTER TOP I SUPPOSE.
OR THIS IS I THINK, THIS IS
A DARN GOOD, LITTLE UNIT HERE,
YOU GLUE A LITTLE RIM BRIM ON
THE END THERE AND YOU GOT
YOURSELF A LITTLE BASEBALL CAP
THAT'S THE SAME COLOUR
AS YOUR HAIR.
YOU'D NEED A LITTLE, WEE HEAD
FOR THAT BUT JUST LEAVE HER IN
THE SAUNA FOR AN EXTRA HOUR
OR 2, ONE OF THE INTERESTING
PROPERTIES OF THESE BOTTLES
IS THAT THEY ARE REALLY BUILT
TO HOLD LIQUID IN, WHICH MEANS
THAT THEY WILL ALSO WORK REAL
WELL FOR HOLDING LIQUID OUT.
SO TIGHTEN THE TOP UP REAL GOOD
ON THAT AND CRAM ONE OF THESE
INTO EACH OF THE CORNERS OF ONE
OF THESE POP CASES AND THEN
WHAT YOU DO IS YOU DRAG THAT
UP YOUR ARM AND ADJUST THAT TO
BE THE SIZE AND THE WEIGHT AND
FLABBINESS OF WHATEVER YOU'RE
TRICEPS ARE AND THEN ONCE YOU
GET THEM UP HERE YOU FLIP THEM
UP ON TOP AND THEY'LL
JUST SIT UP HERE.
AND WHAT YOU HAVE IS AN
INCREDIBLE PAIR OF WATER WINGS
AND THEY'RE EXTRA SAFE BECAUSE
IT'S 8 COMPLETELY SEPARATE
FLOATATION UNITS, SO EVEN WHEN
THE KIDS ARE SHOOTING BB'S
AT YOU, YOU'RE PROBABLY GOING
TO BE ABLE TO MAKE IT TO SHORE.
AND OF COURSE ONCE YOU'VE
LEARNED HOW TO SWIM YOU CAN
JUST FILL THEM WITH ICE TEA
AND CROSS THE ENGLISH CHANNEL.
OR WHAT YOU CAN DO IS JUST TAKE
THE ONE BIG, 2-LITRE SIZE AND
PUT THAT INSIDE YOUR BATHING
TRUNKS AND THAT'LL GIVE YOU AS
MUCH FLOATATION AS YOU'LL EVER
NEED AND PROBABLY MORE ATTENTION
THAN YOU'LL EVER WANT.
IF YOU HAVE A BUNCH OF THESE
CASES NOW, YOU COULD STRAP
THEM ALL TOGETHER AND MAKE
YOURSELF A RAFT OR A FLOATING
DOCK OR EVEN A GREAT BIG
PLASTIC ISLAND,
IT'D BE A REAL EYE CATCHER
FOR THE COTTAGERS
LOOKING OUT THE WINDOW,
SEE THAT FLOATING BY DURING
ONE OF THE HEAVIER STORMS.
BUT IF YOU'RE THE KIND OF GUY
WHO'S LIKE ME WHO HAS A WHOLE
LOT OF BOTTLES AND HAS A WHOLE
LOT OF TIME AND DOESN'T HAVE
THE KIND OF JOB WHERE HE
CARES WHAT PEOPLE THINK I'VE
GOT JUST THE PROJECT FOR YOU,
A POP BOTTLE BOAT.
YO HO AND A BOTTLE OF DIET POP!
WHEN YOUR FRIENDS SEE YOU IN
A CABIN CRUISER LIKE THIS
THEY CAN ONLY CALL YOU
ONE THING, POPEYE.
MIND YOU THEY MAY HAVE A FEW
OTHER SUGGESTIONS...
AND THERE IS SOMETHING ELSE
IF YOU DO BUILD ONE OF THESE
OF YOUR VERY OWN YOU GOT TO
EXPECT TO BE PULLED OVER
A FEW TIMES BY THE MARINE POLICE
BECAUSE THEY'LL FIGURE YOU WENT
THROUGH A FAIR WACK OF BOOZE
TO USE UP THIS MUCH MIX.
AND THE OTHER THING,
SOME PEOPLE JUST CAN'T HELP
LOOKING AT A BOAT LIKE THIS
AND JUST ASSUMING THAT ALCOHOL
WAS INVOLVED IN SOME WAY.
NOW AS A BIT OF A SAFETY
PRECAUTION, WHEN YOU GO
TO PICK YOUR ENGINE SIZE,
I WOULD NOT RECOMMEND THAT YOU
PUT THE INBOARD ENGINE IN THIS,
CERTAINLY NOT A V8 OR NOT EVEN
THE BIG 6, IT IS VERY DIFFICULT
TO MY MIND TO SAFELY ATTACH
A 700 POUND ENGINE TO A
POLYETHYLENE POP BOTTLE.
BUT THAT'S JUST MY OPINION,
YOU DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
I WOULD SUGGEST THAT YOU
POWER UP WITH YOUR FAVOURITE
CARBONATED BEVERAGE,
YOU JUST SHAKE HER UP,
PUT YOUR THUMB OVER THE END
AND SHOOT HER OUT THE BACK AND
YOU GOT YOURSELF A JET BOAT,
AND WHEN THE CRUISE IS ALL DONE
YOU GOT ENOUGH BOTTLES LEFT
TO MAKE YOURSELF A FLY BRIDGE.
NOW NEXT WEEK WE'RE GOING TO
SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE A BOAT
TRAILER OUT OF POP CANS.
BUT UNTIL THEN REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY,
TIME FOR ME TO CAST OFF.
(BOAT HORN BLOWING)
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S THE PART
OF THE SHOW WHERE WE EXPOSE
THE 3 WORDS MEN HAVE SUCH
A HARD TIME SAYING,
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE TO PROVE THE POINT ON
THE EXPERTS SECTION OF THE SHOW,
OF COURSE IS MY UNCLE RED
AND HIS GOOD FRIEND,
MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
LETTER NUMBER ONE,
'DEAR EXPERTS, LAST WEEK MY
HUSBAND DECIDED TO SAVE
MONEY BY DOING SOME CAR
REPAIRS HIMSELF,
WHEN HE WAS DONE OUR
CAR WAS RUINED.
AFTER THEY TOWED OUR 64 VALIANT
OFF TO THE JUNKYARD I FOUND THIS
LYING IN OUR DRIVEWAY,
CAN YOU TELL ME WHAT IT IS?'
>>RED: WELL SURE, THAT'S
A DISTRIBUTOR CAP OBVIOUSLY.
HEY EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT
DON'T THEY HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH, THAT'S A
DISTRIBUTOR CAP RIGHT THERE,
THAT'S WHAT THAT IS OBVIOUSLY.
>>HAP: A DISTRIBUTOR CAP,
IF ONLY RED, MAYBE THIS IS
A PROTOTYPE FOR A TOP SECRET
WEAPON DEVELOPED BY THE PENTAGON
DURING THE NIXON YEARS CALLED
ROBO OCTO, IT USE TO BE
WRITTEN ON HERE, ROBO OCTOPUS
MAGNETO TORPEDO.
>>HAROLD: WELL I KNEW IT WASN'T
A REGULAR DISRUPTERCATOR CAP.
>>HAP: THAT'S A DEADLY
WEAPON HAROLD,
IN THE WATER ALL 6 ARMS FLY OUT
SO IT LOOKS LIKE AN OCTOPUS,
AND ALL 6 HIGHLY EXPLOSIVE
CHARGES MAGNETICALLY ATTACH
THEMSELVES TO THE HULL OF
THE ENEMY SUBMARINE AND EXPLODE,
BREACHING THE HULL AND
SINKING THE SUB.
>>HAROLD: THAT'S A ROBO OCTO?
>>HAP: PUS.
>>HAROLD: PUS.
>>HAP: MAGNETO TORPEDO.
>>RED: OH YEAH?
WELL HOW COME THE ROBO OCTOPUS
THING SAYS VALIANT HERE?
>>HAP: IT'S JUST
A CODE NAME, VALIANT.
>>RED: WHAT ABOUT
THE SPARK PLUGS?
OH SORRY, WHAT ABOUT THE
EXPLOSIVE CHARGES, 'AC' DELCO?
>>HAP: 'AC', 'AC' AND 'E'
SUBMARINE CHARGE AND DELCO
ANY 5 YEAR OLD, DELCO SHORT
FOR DELIVERY CONTAINER.
BATTERY SUBMARINE CHARGED
DELIVERY CONTAINER.
ANYWAY THEY DIDN'T END UP
USING IT, THE PENTAGON
DOUBTED THAT IT WOULD WORK.
>>RED: YEAH DOUBT IS A
POWERFUL THING ISN'T IT HAP?
>>RED: IT IS SPRING
WHEN A YOUNG MAN'S FANCY
TURNS TO THOUGHTS OF LOVE
OR FAILING THAT LUST
OR FAILING THAT
WRESTLEMANIA 8.
>>RED: GLEN, GLEN YOU IN THERE?
>>GLEN: THE MARINA'S OPEN,
JUST TAKE WHATEVER YOU NEED,
EVERYTHING IS $100 BUCKS.
>>RED: COME ON GLEN IT'S ME,
I JUST NEED TO BORROW SOME ROPE.
>>GLEN: OH RED JUST HELP
YOURSELF JUST LEAVE $100
BUCKS ON THE COUNTER.
>>RED: WHAT ARE YOU DOING
TO THE R.V. NOW GLEN?
>>GLEN: WELL I'M GOING TO PUT
ONE OF THESE GIZMOS ON HER.
>>RED: ANOTHER TOY EH?
>>GLEN: YEAH.
>>RED: BOY IT'S AMAZING TO ME
HOW YOU FIND THE TIME TO DO
ALL THE WORK ON THE R.V.
AND YOU KNOW RUN THE
BUSINESS AND EVERYTHING.
>>GLEN: RUN A BUSINESS?
>>RED: WELL YEAH THE MARINA.
>>GLEN: OH, OH THE MARINA SURE,
SURE I RUN THE MARINA YEAH,
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS RED?
>>RED: NO.
>>GLEN: THIS HERE IS A MOTION
DETECTOR VIDEO ASSIST
PARKING UNIT.
>>RED: WOW!
>>GLEN: YEAH, WHEN I HAVE TO
BACK INTO A REAL TIGHT SPOT.
>>RED: OH SURE, YEAH.
>>GLEN: WELL THIS THING
HELPS ME OUT, YOU KNOW LIKE
THE EDGE OF THE GRAND CANYON.
>>RED: OH YEAH.
>>GLEN: YOU KNOW OR GOING
THROUGH THE GIANT REDWOODS
IN CALIFORNIA.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>GLEN: YOU KNOW
OR THE BEER STORE.
>>RED: OH YEAH.
BOY YOU HAVE SPENT A COUPLE
OF DOLLARS ON HER HAVEN'T YOU?
>>GLEN: OH YEAH, $7,000 RED.
>>RED: WOW!
>>GLEN: THAT'S JUST
FOR THIS THING.
>>RED: OH.
>>GLEN: YUP, $20,000
I FIGURE OVERALL.
>>RED: OH MY GOSH.
>>GLEN: BUT IT'S WORTH IT.
THIS THING IS, I ONLY PAID
$500 BUCKS FOR IT AND IT
WAS A MESS WHEN I GOT IT.
>>RED: NO KIDDING.
WELL ANYWAY GLEN I JUST NEEDED
THE ROPE BECAUSE WE'RE GOING
TO TIE ALL THE BOATS TOGETHER
FOR THE REGATTA YOU KNOW.
>>GLEN: OH NO YOU DON'T WANT
TO DO THAT RED, NO, NO,
I GOT A WHOLE BUNCH OF OUTBOARD
MOTORS LYING AROUND,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST STICK
THEM ALL IN THE BACK,
I'LL RENT THEM TO YOU
FOR $100 BUCKS.
>>RED: WELL OKAY GLEN
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
YOU THROW A HALF A DOZEN
OUTBOARDS INTO THE BACK OF
THE VAN AND I'LL TAKE THEM OVER
TO THE LODGE AND WE'LL JUST
YOU KNOW SEE WHO WANTS WHAT?
>>GLEN: WELL YOU KNOW RED
I'M REAL BUSY WITH THE
VIDEO ASSIST THING, IT'S GOING
TO TAKE ME A LITTLE WHILE,
SO YOU JUST HELP YOURSELF.
>>RED: NO, NO, THAT'S OKAY,
I CAN WAIT.
>>GLEN: WELL I'VE NEVER PUT
ONE ON RED SO IT MAY TAKE
A COUPLE OF HOURS.
>>RED: YOU TAKE YOUR TIME GLEN.
>>GLEN: YOU SIR ARE
THE LAZIEST MAN ALIVE.
>>RED: WELL GLEN COMING
FROM YOU THAT HAS TO
BE A COMPLIMENT.
>>RED: WELL OUR GONZO REGATTA
HAS GOT EVERYBODY GOING AND
THE IDEA THAT YOU CAN PUT
A MOTOR ON YOUR VESSEL HAS
GOT EVERYBODY PRETTY EXCITED,
MOOSE HAS DECIDED TO TURN HIS
CAR INTO A PADDLE WHEELER.
>>HAROLD: YOU KNOW UNCLE RED,
I SAW BUSTER HADFIELD WALKING
DOWN THERE AND HE HAD LIKE
A REALLY LONG EXTENSION CORD
I WAS JUST HOPING HE'S NOT
GOING TO BUILD A BOAT WITH
AN ELECTRIC MOTOR IS HE?
>>RED: WELL ACTUALLY BUSTER
I BELIEVE IS BUILDING A BOAT
OUT OF 35 USED MAILBOXES.
>>HAROLD: OH?
WHERE'S HE GETTING THOSE?
>>RED: WELL LET'S JUST SAY
THAT NOBODY AROUND POSSUM LAKE
IS GOING TO BE GETTING ANY
BILLS FOR AWHILE.
AND HE'S GOING TO POWER THE UNIT
WITH ONE OF THEM WET/DRY VACUUM
SHOP VAC TYPE THINGS WHICH IS
GOING TO SUCK WATER IN THE BOW
AND BLOW IT OUT THE STERN
VERY REMINISCENT OF MY
GREAT GRANDFATHER ON
MY MOTHER'S SIDE.
>>HAROLD: I DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU'RE ALWAYS CHANGING THINGS,
YOU'RE FOREVER CHANGING
THINGS YOU GUYS, JUST LEAVE
THINGS THE WAY THEY ARE,
YOU'RE ALWAYS SO CREATIVE.
>>RED: YOU GOT ANY MOVING PARTS
IN THAT GIZMO THERE HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: NO I DON'T.
>>RED: NO RUBBER BELTS?
>>HAROLD: NO I DON'T HAVE ANY.
>>RED: WHAT'S THAT THING?
>>HAROLD: NO UNCLE RED DON'T!
I DON'T HAVE ANY!
>>RED: I WANT TO JUST
LOOK AT IT HAROLD,
I WANT TO JUST LOOK AT IT,
HAROLD, I WANT TO LOOK AT IT.
>>HAROLD: DON'T! DON'T!
I HAVE A COLD, I'M JUST GOING
TO GIVE IT TO YOU,
I DON'T EVEN CARE,
>>HAROLD: A HAPPY SONG.
♪ WEAR A SMILE ♪
♪ ALL THE WHILE ♪
♪ AND YOUR FRIENDS ♪
♪ WILL NAME YOU ♪
♪ BUT WEAR A FROWN ♪
♪ WHEN THERE'S A ♪
♪ BAD SMELL AROUND ♪
♪  AND ALL YOUR FRIENDS ♪
♪ WILL BLAME YOU ♪
>>RED: WELL I WASN'T REALLY
IN MUCH OF A MOOD FOR AN
'ADVENTURE WITH BILL'
BUT HE SAID THERE WAS
A LUNCH IN IT FOR ME SO,
AND NOT ONLY JUST LUNCH,
YEAH, YEAH, HI BILL, BUT A BIG,
JUICY STEAK AND OH WELL,
BY GOSH.
(SCRAPING OF FORK ON PLATE)
>>RED: EW, I HATE THAT SOUND!
IT REMINDS ME OF
GRADE 3 BOTH YEARS.
ANYWAY BILL BROUGHT HIS OWN
SECRET STEAK SAUCE AND HE'S
GOING TO PUT THAT ON WITH,
OBVIOUSLY A COUPLE OF HOLES
IN THE SIDE OF THE JAR
THERE BILL, YEAH THANK YOU,
THANK YOU, I THINK I'LL
SKIP THE HOT WAX.
>>GUY: HEY!
>>RED: AND THEN WE'RE GOING TO,
OH, OH, OH, OH, NOW WHAT
WE'RE GOING TO DO IS WE'RE
GOING BUILT OURSELVES A LITTLE
CAMPFIRE AND COOK THE STEAK.
IT WAS A GOOD LOOKING PIECE
OF MEAT AND HE'S GOING TO,
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
CUT THE STEAK SAUCE,
AND HE'S PUTTING THE,
OH, WATCH IT BILL! BILL! BILL!
A LITTLE GARNISH ON THE STEAK
THERE AND HE CLEARED A LITTLE
SPOT AND NOW WHAT HE WANTS
TO DO IS PUT A BUNCH OF
ROCKS AROUND, YOU KNOW TO
KIND OF CONTAIN THE FIRE,
SO WE GOT A FEW ROCKS THERE
AND I'M PITCHING IN,
YOU KNOW THERE AREN'T A LOT
OF ROCKS AROUND THIS PART
OF THE LODGE BECAUSE BILL
HAS DONE THIS BEFORE MAINLY
SO, THERE'S ONE THERE YEAH,
WELL THAT'S KIND OF A BIG
ONE BILL, WATCH WHERE YOU'RE
THROWING IT, WATCH, BILL WATCH,
BILL, BILL, BILL, BILL, BILL,
(PLATTER SHATTERS)
SO HE GOES DOWN BY THE
CREEK THERE, IT LOOKS LIKE
A LOT OF ROCKS DOWN THERE,
YOU KNOW I HEARD A STORY ONE
TIME THAT YOU SHOULD NEVER USE.
>>BILL: OH!
>>RED: BUT ANYWAY YOU SHOULD
NEVER USE ROCKS FROM OUT OF
THE WATER BECAUSE THEY GOT
THE WATER STILL IN THEM.
ANYWAY WE'RE NOT GOING TO WORRY
ABOUT THAT AND SO YOU KNOW
INNOVATION, INNOVATION,
WE'RE GOING TO COOK
THE STEAK OVER THE RAKE.
NOW BILL, NOW BILL,
BILL THAT THING'S GOT HOLES
ALL AROUND THE SIDES OF IT THERE
WHAT? OH ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
YOU'RE GOING TO WRAP IT,
OKAY WRAP THE TOWEL AROUND.
ALL RIGHT MAYBE THAT'LL WORK,
AH NO, APPARENTLY NOT, NO.
THIS WAS ONLY IN THERE BILL,
YEAH, WELL I'LL GET THAT
SAUCE OUT OF THE STEAK ANYWAY,
WELL YOU GOT, BY GOSH YOU
DON'T SEE THAT EVERY DAY
OF THE WEEK THANK GOODNESS.
SO WE'RE GOING TO COOK UP THE,
(ROCK HISSING & SIZZLING)
NOW THE RIVER ROCK IS
STARTING TO...
I DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE THAT,
STARTING TO HUM AND SIZZLE
AND I PUT THE STEAK OVER IT
AND IT'S STARTING TO ROCK AND
APPARENTLY WHEN THESE THINGS
BUILD UP ENOUGH PRESSURE INSIDE.
(LOUD EXPLOSION)
>>BILL: OH!
>>RED: I DON'T REMEMBER MUCH
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED AFTER THAT,
I REMEMBER I KIND OF CAME TO
IN THE BARN AND I CAME UP
AND I THOUGHT TO MYSELF,
WHERE IS THAT WEENIE?
THERE HE IS.
>>RED: AND NOW HERE'S A NEW IDEA
FOR ALL YOU YOUNG KIDS WHO ARE
FORCED TO WATCH THIS STUFF.
>>HAROLD: HEY IT'S ME,
HEAVY, HIP-HOP HAROLD
WITH MY BRAND NEW SHOW,
OKAY I KNOW THERE'S NOT SUPPOSE
TO BE A 'W' IN FRONT OF RAPPING
OKAY, BECAUSE I'M GOING TO
FIX THAT BY NEXT WEEK,
I DON'T WANT YOU TO THINK THIS
IS A SHOW ABOUT WRAPPING GIFTS
WITH SOME GUY BECAUSE IT'S NOT,
IT'S A SHOW ABOUT TALKING
TO POLICEMEN, BUT I DIDN'T
WANT TO CALL IT THAT BECAUSE
OBVIOUSLY VERY UNCOOL.
LIKE WHEN THE POLICEMEN GO
UNDERCOVER, WE STILL KNOW IT'S
POLICEMEN, WE KNOW IT'S THEM,
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW
HOW TO TELL?
OKAY I'LL TELL YOU BECAUSE
I KNOW, THEY GOT THESE LIKE
GREAT BIG, LONG, BLACK SHOES
RIGHT AND THEY GOT SHORT HAIR,
NEATLY TRIMMED MUSTACHES
AND REALLY GOOD POSTURE.
THESE ARE ALL THINGS THAT
I THINK MOST STREET GANGS
ARE LACKING.
SO THE SHOW IS GOING TO
BE CALLED THEN RAPPING WITH
POLICEMEN OR POLICEWOMEN
YOU KNOW, OKAY, OR POLICEWOMAN,
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO CHANGE
THAT TOO, OKAY, SO BY NEXT WEEK
IT'S GOING TO BE CALLED RAPPING
WITH PEOPLE OF AUTHORITY.
YEAH PEOPLE OF AUTHORITY
THAT'S WHAT IT'S GOING
TO BE CALLED, RAPPING WITH
PEOPLE OF AUTHORITY,
OKAY SO.
>>RED: OKAY HAROLD,
NOEL'S OUT OF THE SHOWER NOW,
HE NEEDS HIS UNIFORM BACK.
>>HAROLD: NO, NO, NO, NO.
>>RED: PARDON ME HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: NOTHING, SORRY.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH LONGER
I CAN GO ON DOING A SHOW
WITHOUT A BUDGET.
(GOLF BALL WHIZZING BY)
(SPLASH OF HITTING WATER)
>>RED: CAUGHT YOU PRACTICING
FOR THE POSSUM LAKE
REGATTA THERE BOB?
>>BOB: WHAT, NO, NO RED
I HAPPEN TO BE DOING SOME
WORK FOR THE DEPARTMENT
OF NATURAL RESOURCES.
>>RED: OH YEAH?
>>BOB: YES I HAPPEN TO BE
MEASURING THE GRAVITY OF
THIS SPECIFIC MARSH,
THE WETLANDS ARE AN IMPORTANT
PART OF THE ECOLOGICAL CHAIN,
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU KNEW
THAT RED.
>>RED: WELL I GUESS YOU'RE DONE
FOR THE DAY NOW THAT YOU'VE
DROWNED YOUR INSTRUMENTS.
>>BOB: NO I HAVE ANOTHER
SET OF CLUBS, TOOLS.
WELL WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU RED?
REMEMBER NOW I'VE GOT 36 HOLES
OF WORK AHEAD OF ME.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH.
>>RED: OH BOY.
WELL ACTUALLY BOB I JUST
WANTED TO KNOW IF MAYBE YOU
GUYS DOWN AT THE DEPARTMENT
WANTED TO BUILD
A BOAT FOR THE REGATTA,
I THOUGHT YOU COULD MAKE ONE
OUT OF SAY PENCILS AND COFFEE
CUPS AND THOSE TAX FORMS
YOU'RE SENDING ME EVERY
COUPLE OF MONTHS.
>>BOB: NO THANKS RED, NO TIME,
EVERY MINUTE IS PRECIOUS WHEN
YOU WORK FOR THE CIVIL SERVICE,
IT'S LIKE A WELL OILED MACHINE.
>>RED: REALLY?
MOST OF THE GUYS I MEET
ARE DOWN A QUART OR
THEIR PALMS ARE GREASED.
(GOLF BALL WHIZZING INTO TREE)
>>RED: OH BOY.
>>BOB: HANG ON TO THIS
FOR ME WILL YOU RED?
>>RED: WELL BOB YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO BE ABLE TO PUTT
FROM THE TOP OF A TREE THERE,
WHAT ARE YOU HANDING
ME THIS FOR?
>>BOB: BECAUSE THAT
IS MY FAVOURITE CLUB.
>>RED: BOB? BOB?
>>BOB: (YELLING) OH!
>>RED: WELL WE'VE HAD
A MAJOR RETHINK ON THE
POSSUM LAKE REGATTA
BECAUSE MASS ARREST TENDS
TO DAMPEN THE FUN OF ALMOST
ANY SOCIAL EVENT.
>>HAROLD: WELL I AM ONE PERSON
WHO'S PERSONALLY GLAD THAT YOU
DECIDED TO CANCEL, SMART MOVE.
>>RED: WE'RE NOT CANCELLING
HAROLD, WE'RE JUST GOING TO
MAKE THE BOATS NOT POWERED
OKAY, WE'VE TIED THEM ALL
TO MOOSE'S CAR, WE'RE GOING
TO TAKE TURNS ROWING.
>>HAROLD: HOW DO YOU ROW A CAR?
>>RED: THE CAR IS UPSIDE DOWN
HAROLD, YOU JUST WELD OARLOCKS
TO THE ROCKER PANELS.
>>HAROLD: OH OF COURSE.
>>RED: YEAH AND THIS WAY
IF WE GET STOPPED BY THE
MARINE POLICE AT LEAST
MOOSE'S BOAT IS LICENSED,
HECK IT'S GOT PLATES.
AND THANK GOD THEY'VE MADE
ARRANGEMENTS WITH SOME GUY
AT THE END OF THE REGATTA
WHO'S GOING TO BUY ALL
THE STUFF FOR SCRAP IRON
AND MOOSE WILL GET ENOUGH MONEY,
HE CAN GET HIMSELF A COUPLE
OF USED K-CARS.
>>HAROLD: REALLY?
LIKE ONE TO DRIVE
AND ONE FOR A BOAT?
>>RED: NO, ONE TO DRIVE AND
ONE TO GIVE TO OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
AS A TOOL SHED.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH IT'S THE CRY OF
THE POSSUM, THAT'S MEETING TIME.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT HAROLD YOU
GO ON AHEAD, I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
>>HAROLD: ALL RIGHTY.
>>RED: WELL THAT'S ABOUT IT
FOR OUR SHOW BUT IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING I'LL BE COMING
STRAIGHT HOME AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I FOUND SOMETHING OUT,
THAT COMBINATION WASHER/DRYER
THAT YOUR PARENTS GAVE US
DOES NOT FLOAT ALL RIGHT.
SO I WOULD SAY IT'S PROBABLY
NOT AS TOP OF THE LINE
AS THEY PRETENDED IT WAS.
AND FOR THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
♪ ♪ ♪
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: A COUPLE OF THINGS
GUYS BEFORE WE GET STARTED,
BUSTER HADFIELD IS SELLING
HIS SNOWMOBILE FOR $25 BUCKS,
YOU CAN PAY HIM TONIGHT
AND PICK IT UP TOMORROW,
MAKE SURE YOU BRING
SCUBA EQUIPMENT.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca