[breezy folk music]
♪
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> ONCE AGAIN, IT'S TIME FOR THE
SHOW THAT EVERYBODY'S TALKING
ABOUT, THE SHOW THAT CAUGHT THE
NATION'S ATTENTION, AND IT'S AT
TOP OF THE CRITICS' LIST.
WELL, I DIDN'T SAY WHICH LIST,
SO IT'S REALLY NOT FALSE
ADVERTISING, OKAY?
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW.
AND NOW PLEASE GIVE A WARM
WELCOME TO YOUR HOST WITH THE
MOST AND MY UNCLE, RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH, HAROLD.
THANK YOU, AND WELCOME
TO THE SHOW.
WE GOT A HECK OF A SHOW FOR YOU
THIS WEEK.
WE HAVE A STORY ABOUT--WE HAD
A HE-MAN CONTEST UP HERE AT THE
LODGE WITH FIRST PRIZE BEING
A TRUSS.
AND THEN LATER ON,
WAYNE GRETZKY'S GONNA DROP BY.
>> OH, UNCLE, HE HAD TO CANCEL.
>> WHAT?
I THOUGHT HE WAS DROPPING BY.
>> OH, NO, NO, IT'S JUST--
YOU KNOW, IT WAS ALL TENTATIVE
ON A FEW THINGS.
>> WHAT THINGS?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, LIKE IF WE
COULD GET THROUGH TO HIM, YOU
KNOW, AND HE HADN'T SEEN THE
SHOW, AND, YOU KNOW, JUST HOPING
THAT HE KNEW WHAT HE WAS GETTING
INTO, STUFF LIKE--JUST THINGS.
OKAY?
>> WELL, THIS HERE IS MY NEPHEW,
HAROLD, AND MORE IMPORTANTLY,
MY PRODUCER AND DIRECTOR AND, UP
UNTIL NOW, HAD BEEN IN CHARGE OF
BOOKING THE GUESTS FOR THE SHOW.
BUT ANYWAY.
BUT WE STILL GOT KAREN CANE
COMING.
WE'RE GONNA DO SOME MOOSE
HUNTING.
>> [clears throat] NO, NO, NO.
NO, SHE'S NOT.
WELL, LET'S JUST--WELL, SHE'S
NOT GONNA BE HERE AS YOU MIGHT
THINK, YOU KNOW, LIKE IN PERSON.
>> WHAT HAPPENED, HAROLD?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, THIS AND THAT
AND THOSE AND THEM AND,
YOU KNOW, SHE'S WASHING HER
HAIR AND AMONG OTHER THINGS.
>> [sighs] OH, WELL.
NOT TO WORRY.
YOU KNOW, WE STILL GOT MY STORY
ABOUT THE HE-MAN CONTEST.
>> AND WE ALWAYS GOT THESE
SPECIAL EFFECTS.
HA-HA-HA-HA-HA.
>> YEAH, WELL, I'LL START WITH
THE STORY, AND THEN WE CAN SAVE
THE DIPSY DOODLES FOR WHEN WE'RE
TRYING TO KILL DEAD AIR.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> WELL, MY STORY ISN'T
DEAD AIR, HAROLD.
>> I MADE A JUDGMENT CALL,
UNCLE RED.
[lilting guitar music]
>> ♪ I HAVE AN OLD WOOD STOVE
♪ BELONGED TO MY DAD...
>> ♪ DAD
>> ♪ IT WAS THE BEST DARN
♪ WOOD STOVE THAT HE EVER HAD
>> SURE.
>> ♪ IT HISSES AND CRACKS
♪ AND BURNED THINGS REALLY BAD
♪ IT BELCHES AND SMOKES
♪ BUT THEN SO DID MY DAD
[strums]
DOES THIS SOUND IN TUNE TO YOU?
>> YEAH, EXCEPT WHEN YOU PLAY
IT.
>> THIS WEEK IN HANDYMAN CORNER,
WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU WHAT YOU
CAN DO WITH AN OLD STOVE, AND
I'M NOT REFERRING TO ANY MEMBER
OF YOUR FAMILY HERE.
MAYBE YOU'VE GOT ONE OF THESE
OUT IN THE GARAGE OR IN THE BOMB
SHELTER, OR MAYBE YOU WERE LUCKY
ENOUGH WHERE SOMEBODY DIED
AND LEFT YOU A STOVE.
BUT WHATEVER THE REASON, I'M
GONNA SHOW YOU TODAY SOMETHING
YOU CAN DO WITH THESE, AND I
THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE PRETTY
DARN IMPRESSED WITH IT.
NOW, FIRST OFF, WE HAVE TO
DISMANTLE THE STOVE, SO STEP
NUMBER ONE, OF COURSE, IS TO
LOOSEN ALL THE HARDWARE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW SHE HAS FAILED TO
DECONSTITUTE INTO HER PRIMARY
COMPONENTS, SO I THINK WE'RE
LEFT WITH NO OTHER CHOICE
OTHER THAN TO TAKE THE TORCH
TO HER.
THIS SHOULD DO IT.
[gas hissing]
[clicking]
YOU KNOW, THIS COULD BLOW OUT
THE TUBES OF THE CAMERA WHEN
THIS BABY LIGHTS UP.
YOU GUYS MIGHT WANT TO JUST PAN
OFF TO THE SIDE THERE, AND I
DON'T HAVE ANY PROBLEM THERE.
YEAH.
[hissing and clicking]
[explosions]
WELL, THE TORCH DOESN'T SEEM TO
BE OPERATIONAL.
I GUESS HAROLD WAS FUTZING
AROUND WITH THE SETTINGS ON IT,
SO I GOT TO FIND SOME OTHER WAY
OF TAKING THE STOVE APART.
MIGHT AS WELL JUST--BACK TO THE
OLD-FASHIONED HANDS-ON APPROACH.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, I GOT HER ALL
TAKEN APART.
TOOK THE TOP OFF, TOOK THE BACK
OFF, AND I THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE
SURPRISED WHAT WE GOT HERE.
I GOT A BUNGEE CORD WRAPPED
AROUND THE DOOR, AND LET ME SHOW
YOU HOW THIS WORKS.
DOWN HERE WHAT USED TO BE THE
OVEN DRAWER, THIS IS NOW
A MAGAZINE RACK.
SO WE GET OURSELVES
OUT A MAGAZINE.
OH, BUT NOT THAT MAGAZINE.
THAT'S HAROLD'S MAGAZINE.
HE'S GROWING UP, ISN'T HE?
COME AROUND TO THE FRONT.
WE PICK UP THE CONTROL MODULE.
WE'RE GONNA NEED THAT
IN A MINUTE.
PULL OUT THE OVEN RACK, WHICH IS
NOW GONNA BE A LEG REST.
THERE'S A BIT OF A CLUE THERE.
OKAY.
NOW WE EASE OURSELVES DOWN.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BELIEVE THIS.
ALL RIGHT, LEAN BACK.
WE NOW HAVE A BEAUTIFULLY
COMFORTABLE RECLINING CHAIR.
AND AS AN ADDED FEATURE,
I GO DOWN TO THE CONTROL PANEL,
SET HER FOR BUN WARMER...
AND BY GOLLY, I'M HERE
FOR THE EVENING.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME, REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK AFTER THIS
COMMERCIAL BREAK WITH MORE ABOUT
THE HE-MAN CONTEST STORY.
>> IF YOU HAVE CHILDREN, GET
THEM OUT OF THE ROOM NOW!
JUST IN CASE.
I WOULD.
>> WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
>> BOY, DID YOU SEE THE GAME
LAST NIGHT?
>> I WAS RATHER DISTURBED BY IT.
>> OH, OH, YOU SEE THAT CHECK?
>> YEAH.
>> RIGHT INTO THE BOARDS.
AND I THINK HIS HEAD WAS SPLIT.
HIS--IT HAD TO BE.
BANGED HIS HEAD.
>> IT DEFINITELY WAS.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> BY THE AMOUNT OF BLOOD ON THE
ICE, I WOULD DEFINITELY SAY
SOMETHING WAS WRONG.
>> HE HAD A HEADACHE THERE,
DIDN'T HE?
>> WELL, TODAY'S HE'S GONNA WAKE
UP AND GO, "SOMETHING HAPPENED
LAST NIGHT."
>> YOU WANT TO BELIEVE IT.
>> THERE'S TOO MUCH VIOLENCE IN
SPORTS, UNCLE RED.
AND I DON'T THINK--YOU SEEM
TO BE ADVOCATING--
>> NOW, DON'T.
>> IT'S A FEELING I GET FROM YOU
AND YOUR FRIENDS.
WHEN YOU STAND UP AND CHEER,
"WAY TO GO," I FIGURE YOU LIKE
THAT SORT OF THING.
>> WELL, IT'S A COMMITMENT TO--
YOU KNOW, TO YOUR TEAM.
YOU KNOW, YOU EITHER SUPPORT
YOUR TEAM, OR YOU DON'T SUPPORT
YOUR TEAM.
>> YEAH, BUT I DON'T KNOW WHICH
TEAM YOU LIKE.
YOU LIKE THE TEAM THAT SEEMS TO
BE STRONGER, AND THAT'S SORT OF
A GLADIATOR APPROACH...
>> WELL...
>> TO SPORT.
>> THERE'S A BULLETIN, HUH?
I LIKE THE TEAM THAT'S STRONGER.
WELL, YOU THINK I LIKE A LOSER?
>> NO, I WOULDN'T SAY YOU LIKE
LOSERS, BUT...
>> YEAH.
>> SOMETIMES YOU LIKE THE GUY
WHO GETS HIT INTO THE BOARDS,
AND HE'S THE LOSER.
SO LIKE--
>> I DON'T LIKE HIM.
I DON'T--NO.
NO, I DON'T LIKE HIM.
I THINK THAT IT'S A--YOU HAVE TO
MAKE A COMMITMENT TO A SPORT.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE IN THERE
AND THEY'RE FIGHTING.
IT'S WAR.
THAT'S NOT A SPORT. THAT'S WAR.
>> HOW DO YOU PRACTICE A SPORT
LIKE THAT?
YOU JUST KIND OF SKATE INTO THE
BOARDS?
>> YEAH, WELL, YOU START WITH
YOUR OWN FAMILY, FIRST OF ALL.
>> OH, START SMALL.
>> YEAH.
COME ON, I'LL SHOW YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I THINK YOU BETTER
TAKE YOUR GLASSES OFF.
>> OH, THANKS.
>> IT IS WINTER.
A FRIEND HITS YOU IN THE FACE
WITH A SNOWBALL.
AND AS IT MELTS, YOU BECOME
AWARE THAT HE HAS A NEW PUPPY.
SO AS I WAS SAYING, WE HAD THIS
HE-MAN CONTEST, AND IT'S KIND OF
INTERESTING HOW WE PUT IT
TOGETHER.
WE MADE EACH GUY COME UP WITH AN
EVENT, AND THEN THE RULE BEING
THAT HE HAD TO GO FIRST ON HIS
OWN EVENT, AND THAT WAY THE GUYS
WOULDN'T, YOU KNOW, RIG UP THE
EQUIPMENT SO THAT IT WOULD FALL
APART, AND THEN EVERYBODY ELSE
WOULD GET KILLED JUST SO THEY'D
WIN.
>> UNCLE RED, YOU KNOW, THIS IS
A REALLY INTERESTING STORY,
IT REALLY IS, BUT SOME VIEWERS
MIGHT FIND IT BORING,
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
THEY FIND IT OFFENSIVE,
YOU KNOW.
AND THAT'S NOT BETTER.
SO WHY DON'T WE JUST TELL THEM,
YOU KNOW, THAT THERE WERE SOME
WINNERS AND SOME LOSERS AND SOME
INJURIES, AND THAT WAY, WE CAN
JUST GET RIGHT ALONG WITH THE
NEXT FILM CLIP.
>> YEAH, BUT I THINK THE VIEWERS
WOULD AT LEAST LIKE TO HEAR WHAT
THE EVENTS WERE, HAROLD.
>> OH, YEAH, OKAY.
YEAH, THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
>> WELL, I DIDN'T GET TO TELL
THEM WHAT THE EVENTS WERE.
>> OH, I DIDN'T KNOW YOU MEANT
RIGHT NOW.
>> WELL, WHEN DID YOU THINK I
MEANT, HAROLD?
>> EVENTUALLY.
>> WELL, NOW, HAP, THIS IS
A GREAT DAY FOR FISHING.
IT DOESN'T GET ANY BETTER
THAN THIS.
>> PERFECT WEATHER CONDITIONS,
AS WE BUSH PILOTS USED TO CALL
THEM.
>> BUSH PILOT?
YOU WERE A BUSH PILOT?
>> OH, YEAH, I WAS ONE OF THE
VERY BEST, SO THEY TELL ME.
>> WHAT KIND OF PLANE
DID YOU HAVE?
>> I WASN'T A PLANE PILOT.
I WAS A BUSH PILOT.
I PILOTED BUSHES.
>> WELL, BUSHES DON'T FLY, HAP.
>> YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO TELL ME
THAT, RED.
I WORKED WITH THEM
FOR FIVE YEARS.
IN THE LUMBER COMPANY,
BRITISH COLUMBIA.
THEY'D CUT DOWN THE TREES AND
DRAG THEM DOWN TO THE RIVER.
I'D BUILD A RAFT OUT OF A BUSH,
AND I'D PILOT THOSE TREES DOWN
THE RIVER TO THE SAWMILL.
>> OH, SO YOU WERE A LUMBERJACK.
>> IT WAS DANGEROUS WORK BEING
A BUSH PILOT,
FLOATING DOWN A RAGING RIVER ON
A SHRUB.
AND I GOT MY LOGS DOWN TO THE
MILL INTACT AND DEBARKED
AND READY TO SAW.
>> WELL, THAT SOUNDS LIKE AN
INTERESTING JOB, HAP.
>> YEAH, AND IT PAID WELL.
AND IT TAUGHT ME SOMETHING ABOUT
LIFE--TAUGHT ME HOW TO BE
STRAIGHT AND HONEST WITH PEOPLE.
>> THAT'S A GOOD LESSON.
>> IF I HADN'T LEARNED
TO TELL THE TRUTH, I'D STILL BE
COMING DOWN THE WHITE WATER
WITH MY LEGS WRAPPED
AROUND A DOUGLAS FIR.
WHAT KIND OF LIFE IS THAT?
>> TENUOUS.
>> THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> ♪ I'LL TELL YOU A STORY
♪ ABOUT LUMBER JACK MORT
♪ HE WAS WELL OVER 40
♪ HE'S STOCKY AND SHORT
♪ HE COULD CLEAR
♪ A WHOLE FOREST
♪ IN LESS THAN A WEEK
♪ BUT TAKE AWAY
♪ HIS BULLDOZER
♪ HE'D BE UP [...] CREEK
>> OH, UNCLE RED, YOU'RE GONNA
BE SORRY YOU CAME IN HERE THIS
WEEK.
THE VIEWER MALE IS REALLY
PERSONAL.
FEEL THAT PAPER.
THAT'S NICE PAPER.
FEEL THAT.
>> JUST READ THE LETTER, HAROLD,
WILL YOU?
>> OH, OKAY, 'CAUSE IT'S REALLY
NEAT PAPER.
"DEAR RED, I AM AN OLDER
GENTLEMAN WHO FINDS HIMSELF
LONELY FOR FEMALE COMPANIONSHIP.
[laughing]
HOW DO I MEET A NICE
RESPECTABLE WOMAN WHO SHARES MY
INTERESTS AND IS LOOKING
FOR A SERIOUS ROMANCE?
AND HOW DO I KEEP IT FROM MY
WIFE?"
SIGNED SEÑOR SWINGER.
MUST BE MEXICAN.
>> YEAH, RIGHT, WELL, OKAY, I'M
GONNA TALK DIRECTLY TO THE
VIEWER HERE.
AND IF YOU ARE SINCERE HERE,
IF YOU REALLY ARE LOOKING FOR
A WOMAN WHO'S PROBABLY KIND OF
LONESOME HERSELF, A WOMAN WHO'S
DYING FOR A LITTLE ROMANCE, A
LITTLE COMPANIONSHIP, IF YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR A LADY WHO YOU COULD
LOVE AND WHO COULD LOVE YOU
BACK, WHO IS SERIOUS ABOUT
HAVING A ROMANCE, THEN I SUGGEST
THAT YOU TALK TO YOUR OWN WIFE.
>> WELL, THAT WAS REALLY NICE.
THAT WAS GREAT.
>> YEAH, WELL, I FIGURE THAT HIS
WIFE'S BOUND TO KNOW A LOT OF
WOMEN, YOU KNOW, HER OWN
CRONIES.
>> OH, UNCLE RED!
>> SHE CAN PUT YOU ONTO--IT'S
JUST THAT WHEN YOU DO TELL HER,
JUST SAY THAT YOU'RE ASKING
FOR A FRIEND.
>> OH, UNCLE RED, PLEASE.
I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU WERE TALKING
ABOUT HAVING A BETTER AND
STRONGER RELATIONSHIP WITH HIS
OWN WIFE.
COME ON. JEEPERS!
THAT'S WHERE I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GOING WITH THAT.
>> WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE THE
GUY'S A JERK, AND I WAS JUST
TRYING TO GIVE HIS WIFE A BREAK.
>> OH.
YEAH, OH, I THOUGHT THAT TOO.
DID SO, YEAH.
OKAY, WELL, WE GOT TIME FOR ONE
OTHER LETTER, RIGHT?
SO "DEAR RED, LATELY I'VE HAD
A PROBLEM IN THE MARITAL
DEPARTMENT.
MY WIFE IS AN ATTRACTIVE AND
DESIRABLE WOMAN, BUT IT SEEMS
THAT WHENEVER SHE'S IN THE
LOVING MOOD--"
[cackling]
>> QUIT LOSING IT, HAROLD.
>> OKAY, I GOT A GRIP.
"AND WHEN SHE'S IN THE LIVING
MOOD, I'M NOT.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
WILL THIS GO AWAY?
IS IT THE KIWIFRUIT?"
>> WELL, WE HAD TIME FOR THE
LETTER, BUT UNFORTUNATELY, WE
DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THE ANSWER.
>> YEAH, WE DO.
>> NO, THE NEXT SEGMENT'S COMING
UP RIGHT AWAY, SO--
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> YEP, ANY SECOND NOW, AND IT'S
TOO BAD, TOO, 'CAUSE I REALLY
WANTED TO ANSWER THAT LETTER.
[fire crackling]
[whistling]
WELL, OKAY, MAYBE WE'LL GET
A CHANCE TO ANSWER THAT ONE
NEXT TIME.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
THIS WEEK ON ADVENTURES WITH
BILL, WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU WHAT
WE CONSIDER TO BE A LOST ART,
AND ACTUALLY, THERE MAY BE
A GOOD REASON FOR THAT.
THE FIRST THING BILL DOES IS
WHIP OUT--OH, MY GOD.
THE BIG, UH, THE BIG FELLA.
NOW, BILL'S GONNA USE THAT KNIFE
TO--THIS IS YOUR FIRST CLUE.
HE'S GONNA USE IT TO CUT
THE SNOW.
HAVE YOU FIGURED OUT WHAT THE
LOST ART IS YET?
YEAH, HE'S CUTTING IT KIND OF
IN A RECTANGLE.
A LOST ART.
HE LOST THE WHOLE BLADE OF THE
KNIFE IN THERE, YOU KNOW.
BILL'S EQUIPMENT IS NOT THE
GREATEST.
SO I HUNG ON TO THE HANDLE WHILE
HE WENT SEARCHING FOR THE BLADE.
AND HE FOUND IT.
YOU KNOW, BILL IS NOT CLEVER,
BUT HE'S VERY EFFECTIVE.
HE'S OKAY.
YEAH, HE'S FINE.
HE'S FINE.
YEAH, YEAH.
NOBODY USES ALL THEIR FINGERS
ANYWAY.
WHAT HE WANTS TO DO NOW IS PUT
SOME WATER ON--PUT SOME WATER ON
THERE, BILL, TO KIND OF FREEZE
THE--OH!
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH!
WHAT HE WANTS TO DO IS PUT SOME
WATER ON THE SNOW, IS YOUR NEXT
CLUE, SO THAT IT'S A LITTLE
HARDER, IT'S GOT A LITTLE MORE
TEXTURE TO IT.
THIS TAP WATER WAS FRESHER.
SEE, THE OTHER WATER WAS STALE.
THAT WAS THE PROBLEM.
NOW HE'S GONNA CHECK AND MAKE
SURE IT'S FROZEN.
YEAH, YEAH, IT'S FROZEN.
AND I WAS JUST KIBITZING HERE.
I THOUGHT HE MIGHT HAVE HURT HIS
HEAD, SO I PUT SOME ICE ON IT.
AND THEN WHAT HE WANTS TO DO IS,
HE'S GONNA USE A CHAINSAW TO
CUT--WELL, TO CUT THE SNOW.
OH! OH, MY GOD!
NOW HERE'S ANOTHER IDEA.
THIS IS A PIZZA CUTTER.
YEAH, YEAH.
SEE, IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT YOU
USE.
ONCE YOU GOT THE SNOW FROZEN SO
THAT IT'S GOT SOME TEXTURE TO IT
SO IT'LL STAY TOGETHER, HE GOES
AROUND, CUTTING IT INTO
A RECTANGLE.
NOW, HAVE YOU GUESSED THE LOST
ART YET, BY THE WAY?
IT'S GONNA GET EASIER, I THINK.
WELL, MAYBE NOT.
MAYBE NOT.
AND HE COMPLETES THE RECTANGLE
NOW, AND THEN HE JUST GINGERLY,
VERY--CAREFUL NOW, BILL.
CAREFUL, CAREFUL, CAREFUL,
CAREFUL.
PICKS IT UP.
YEAH, YEAH.
AND THEN, AS I SAY, THIS IS
A--I'LL GIVE YOU ANOTHER HINT.
THIS--YOU SEE THIS MAINLY UP IN
THE ARCTIC, YOU KNOW, WITH THE
INUIT AND THE ESKIMO, AND THEN
THEY GET INTO IT.
YOU KNOW, THE INUIT GET INTO IT.
NOW THIS--CAREFUL NOW.
NOW, SEE.
WELL, HE WASN'T QUITE AS CAREFUL
WITH THAT.
AND BILL IS NOT REALLY AS
PATIENT AS HE NEEDS TO BE.
HAS ANYONE GUESSED WHAT HE'S
DOING?
HE'S BUILT HIMSELF A HOUSE.
ISN'T THAT A BEAUTY?
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT'S NOT IT.
IT'S OVER THIS WAY.
AND YEAH, THERE IT IS.
NOT BAD.
NO, NOT BAD.
I THINK HE SHOULD HAVE
DOVETAILED THE CORNERS, BUT IT'S
A BEAUTY.
AND OF COURSE, YOU KNOW, WE
DIDN'T REALLY NOTICE THE WIND
COMING UP...
WHICH IS UNFORTUNATE.
IT IS WINTER.
MY WIFE SNUGGLES CLOSE.
"PUT A LOG ON THE FIRE,"
SHE WHISPERS.
I DO.
IT SIZZLES AND POPS.
IT CRACKLES
AND SNAPS AND FIZZLES.
IT SHAKES AND YELPS
AND RUNS AWAY, WHIMPERING.
LOG?
I THOUGHT SHE SAID "DOG."
EARLY ON IN THE PLANNING STAGES
OF OUR SHOW, IT WAS SUGGESTED
THAT WE HAVE SOMETHING
DIFFERENT, SOME KIND OF
A FEATURE, YOU KNOW, JUST AS
LONG AS IT WAS UNIQUE.
IT DIDN'T MATTER IF IT WASN'T
ANY GOOD.
>> OKAY, SHOPPING WITH YOUR MOM.
OH, YES, I REALIZE THIS ISN'T UP
THERE, LIKE, WITH WORLD HUNGER
OR PEACE OR, YOU KNOW, WHO'S
BETTER, GRETZKY OR LEMIEUX?
BUT IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME.
NO ONE SHOULD HAVE TO GO
SHOPPING WITH THEIR MOM,
ESPECIALLY SINCE I KNEW THE
SALES GIRL FROM HIGH SCHOOL.
SHE HAD TO MEASURE ME, AND MOM
KEPT SAYING, "HE WEARS SMALL
PANTS."
[squawking]
THAT KILLED.
I DON'T BLAME THE SALES GIRL FOR
LAUGHING, BUT FOR 15 MINUTES?
THERE SHOULD BE A LAW, YOU KNOW.
THERE SHOULD BE, LIKE, SOME
RESPECT FOR PRIVACY.
AND THERE SHOULD BE A LOCK ON
THOSE CHANGING ROOM DOORS SO THE
DOOR DOESN'T BUST OPEN WHEN YOU
BEND OVER TO PICK YOUR PANTS UP.
I DON'T CARE HOW RIDICULOUS THAT
POINT OF VIEW IS.
IT'S MINE.
THANK YOU.
>> WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH LOTS
MORE FUN AND LOTS MORE GUESTS
AND THE EXCITING CONCLUSION OF
THE HE-MAN CONTEST STORY.
>> THERE'S A CHANCE HE COULD BE
EXAGGERATING.
>> HAROLD, I'LL TELL YOU
SOMETHING.
THE WORLD IS IN TROUBLE BECAUSE
WE GOT TOO MANY PEOPLE THAT GOT
A UNIVERSITY DEGREE, AND THEY
DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT LIFE.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> YEAH.
SPEND TOO MUCH TIME IN SCHOOL.
DON'T STAY IN SCHOOL TOO MUCH,
HAROLD.
>> BUT THEN I'D HAVE
NO PLACE TO GO.
>> YOU LEARN HOW TO READ, YOU
LEARN HOW TO WRITE, YOU LEARN
HOW TO COUNT UP TO, SAY, 11,
AND THAT'S ENOUGH.
>> BUT THAT'S NOT EVEN UP TO
A DOZEN.
YOU GOT TO BE ABLE TO COUNT TO
12 'CAUSE THAT'S A DOZEN.
YOU GOT TO KNOW HOW MANY WORMS
YOU GOT IN YOUR BAIT BOX.
>> EAT ONE.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
BUT WHAT ABOUT ALL THE TEACHERS?
THEY WOULDN'T HAVE JOBS OR
NOTHING OR LIKE THAT.
>> WELL, THEY'D HAVE TO FIND,
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING PRODUCTIVE
TO DO.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
THEY'D HAVE TO GO ACTUALLY GO
INTO THE WORLD THAT THEY'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>> WELL, NOW, THERE'S
A STATEMENT, ISN'T IT, EH?
>> UH-OH, I MADE A STATEMENT.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT SEE, I CAN MAKE
STATEMENTS 'CAUSE I WENT TO
SCHOOL.
I KNOW HOW.
>> WELL, STATEMENTS ARE WORTH
YOU KNOW WHAT.
SQUAT.
>> SQUAT STATEMENTS?
LIKE, THEY'RE LITTLE ONES?
>> WELL, YEAH, BUT THEY GET TO
THE POINT.
AND THE THING I HEAR IS THAT YOU
TAKE ONE OF YOUR TEACHERS AND
YOU PUT THEM UP HERE IN THE
LODGE, AND HOW LONG ARE THEY
GONNA LAST?
>> A WEEK?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
JACK, JACK, COME ON UP HERE.
I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE, JACK.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> OH, NOTHING.
I JUST, YOU KNOW, WANTED TO SEE
HOW YOU WERE DOING.
THAT'S ALL.
>> HOW DO YOU MEAN?
>> WELL, I WAS JUST WONDERING
HOW YOU'RE ADJUSTING, JACK, YOU
KNOW, TO GO FROM BEING AN
EXECUTIVE AND A FAMILY MAN TO
BEING A PARANOID CAVE-DWELLING
HERMIT.
>> MY WIFE SENT YOU, DIDN'T SHE?
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING, MAN.
I KNOW PEOPLE ARE LAUGHING AT
ME, A LOT OF PEOPLE, BUT THEY
LAUGHED AT CHRISTOPHER COLUMBUS
TOO.
AND IF IT WASN'T FOR HIM, WE'D
ALL BE ITALIAN.
SO I DON'T MIND THAT PEOPLE ARE
LAUGHING AT ME BECAUSE THEY
LAUGHED AT COLUMBUS.
>> DID THEY?
>> DIDN'T THEY?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> I MEAN, I'M SURE SOME SMUG
JERK DID.
THEY'RE ALWAYS LAUGHING.
YOU KNOW, THEY LAUGHED AT ME
WHEN I CAME UP HERE.
>> YEAH.
>> THEY LAUGHED AT ME WHEN I
WENT INTO ADVERTISING AFTER
COLLEGE.
THEY LAUGHED AT ME WHEN I PLAYED
FIELD HOCKEY IN HIGH SCHOOL.
THAT'S THEIR PROBLEM NOW.
>> YEAH, WELL, I GUESS WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING IS THAT YOU'RE NOT
JUST KIND OF SKULKING AROUND IN
YOUR CAVE FOR THE SAKE OF YOUR
HEALTH, EH?
HUH?
>> I AM NOT SKULKING, RED.
>> OH, ALL RIGHT.
>> I STAND TALL, EXCEPT DOWN
RIGHT AT THE BACK IT'S VERY LOW,
THE ROOF, AND THAT'S MY TV ROOM.
BUT OTHER THAN THAT, I DON'T
SKULK ANYWHERE.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
NO SKULKING.
JACK, THE GUYS AT THE LODGE WERE
WANTING TO KNOW HOW LONG EXACTLY
YOU PLAN ON BEING UP HERE.
>> WELL, BASICALLY, UNTIL THE
RELIGIOUS FANATICS AND
WARMONGERING DICTATORS HAVE
DESTROYED THE WORLD.
SEE, THEN I'LL COME DOWN FROM MY
HOLE IN THE HILL AND BE KING OF
ALL I SURVEY.
>> OH.
>> YEAH, AND THEN I'LL JUST KIND
OF WING IT FROM THERE, DEPENDING
ON WHAT I SURVEY.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> I'LL TELL YOU, THOUGH, IF THE
CITIES ARE STILL IN GOOD SHAPE,
I THINK I'M GONNA TURN THEM INTO
A THEME PARK.
>> OH, WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU'RE GONNA BE UP HERE FOR
A LONG, LONG WHILE.
>> WELL, I HOPE NOT.
I ONLY HAVE ENOUGH FOOD FOR SIX
WEEKS.
YOU KNOW, CHRISTOPHER COLUMBUS,
HE DIDN'T HAVE THESE PROBLEMS.
THE QUEEN GAVE HIM MONEY.
OLD JACK'S DOING THIS
ON HIS OWN.
>> WELL, IF IT WOULD HELP YOU, I
COULD LEND YOU, LIKE, 20 BUCKS
OR SOMETHING, YOU KNOW.
>> I'M SORRY, RED, BUT I NO
LONGER RECOGNIZE YOUR CURRENCY.
IT'S MEANINGLESS PAPER,
YOU KNOW, A USELESS SYMBOL
OF A CIVILIZATION GONE AWRY.
>> OH.
WELL, I HAVE SOME MCDONALDS
COUPONS.
WHAT ABOUT THOSE?
>> SURE.
SURE, THOSE--
>> HELP YOURSELF, EH?
THERE YOU GO.
YEAH.
>> THANKS.
>> OKAY.
>> NOW BUG OFF!
>> JACK, THOSE COUPONS
ARE FOR MCRIBS.
>> DARN!
>> ANYWAY, I JUST WANTED TO TELL
YOU HOW THE HE-MAN CONTEST
WORKED OUT.
IT WAS KIND OF FUN.
THE FIRST EVENT WAS OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK'S TOOTH RACE.
AND THE WAY THAT WORKED WAS,
YOU HAD TO TAKE YOUR TEETH OUT,
PUT THEM ON THE FLOOR, STAND ON
THEM, PICK THEM UP, PUT THEM
BACK IN YOUR MOUTH.
AND ACTUALLY, OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
WON THAT ONE, BUT THEN HE'S THE
ONLY ONE THAT HAS DENTURES.
NOBODY EVEN CAME IN SECOND,
ALTHOUGH MOOSE THOMPSON MANAGED
TO LOOSEN THREE MOLARS FOR AN
HONORABLE MENTION.
AND THEN BUSTER HATFIELD HAD THE
BEER CHUG-A-LUGGING CONTEST,
WHICH WE ALL WON.
THE LAKE WAS THE ONLY LOSER ON
THAT ONE.
AND THEN WE GOT THE KIND OF
INTERESTING EVENT, THE ONE I
COME UP WITH, WHICH WAS 100-YARD
DASH BACKWARDS THROUGH THE WOODS
BLINDFOLDED.
AND STINKY PETERSON WON THAT IN
15 SECONDS FLAT.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE LOST JUNIOR
SINGLETON FOR THE REST OF THE
GAMES.
BUT THAT WAS A HECK OF A DAY.
WE ALL HAD A REAL GOOD TIME, AND
IT WORKED OUT WELL.
I MEAN, JUNIOR SINGLETON IS
ACTUALLY STILL GETTING SOME
FRESH AIR.
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE AT NIGHT,
WE KIND OF HEAR HIM GO BY THE
LODGE.
THAT BLINDFOLD'S ON TIGHT, I'LL
TELL YOU.
ANYWAY, THAT'S ABOUT IT
FOR THIS WEEK.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE HOME SOON.
AND IF JUNIOR SINGLETON'S WIFE
IS WATCHING, HE'S GONNA BE LATE.
OKAY, SO UNTIL NEXT TIME,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND--
>> HAROLD.
>> YEAH, WHATEVER, AND THE REST
OF THE GUYS UP AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.