ALOT OF GUYS MY AGE DRINK
WAY TOO MUCH COFFEE.
IT'S NOT HARD
TO FIGURE OUT.
IF YOU HAVEN'T HAD A GOOD
NIGHT'S SLEEP SINCE 1991,
OR IF YOU HEAR SOMETHING
HUMMING AND THEN YOU
REALIZE IT'S YOU,
OR IF YOU CAN'T AFFORD
TO BE ANYWHERE WHERE THEY
DON'T HAVE BATHROOMS OR TREES,
MAYBE IT'S TIME TO CUT DOWN
ON YOUR COFFEE INTAKE.
NOW, MY WIFE SUGGESTS THAT
I SHOULD DRINK TEA INSTEAD.
YEAH, RIGHT.
MAYBE I SHOULD TAKE UP DANCING
LESSONS AND LEARN HOW TO KNIT.
NO, NO, THE ANSWER IS
JUST TO GIVE UP COFFEE,
BUT THAT COULD
BE TOUGH TO DO.
ANYBODY WHO'S
TRIED TO CUT DOWN
OR LIVES WITH
SOMEONE WHO'S TRIED,
KNOWS THAT
A MORNING WITHOUT COFFEE
IS KIND OF LIKE
A HOCKEY GAME WITHOUT A FIGHT.
WHAT YOU NEED IS
SOME INTERMEDIATE STEP
TO TAKE YOU FROM
TOO MUCH COFFEE
OVER TO NO COFFEE AT ALL.
SO GRAB A STRIP OFF THE OLD
HANDYMAN'S SECRET REHAB.
YOU WANT TO LAY THAT
DOWN ON YOUR WORKBENCH,
OR YOUR DINING ROOM TABLE
OR WHAT HAVE YOU,
STICKY SIDE UP.
THEN YOU WANT TO TAKE SOME
OF YOUR FAVOURITE BLEND,
SPRINKLE THAT RIGHT ON THERE.
OKAY.
NOW WHAT YOU'VE DONE,
YOU'VE MADE A
CAFFEINE PATCH, OKAY.
STICK THAT ON YOUR ARM,
AND NOW THE CAFFEINE WILL
BE RELEASED FROM THE
INSTANT COFFEE
DIRECTLY INTO YOUR --
INTO YOUR --
INTO YOUR BLOODSTREAM.
AND YOU'RE -- AND YOU'RE WELL
ON YOUR WAY TO BEING OFF
THE STUFF COMPLETELY.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
[ WHISTLES AND CHEERING ]
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
MY GOLLY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
YOU KNOW HAROLD AND I
HAVE BEEN ON KIND OF A
RESEARCH PROJECT ALL WEEK.
HE WANTS US TO FIND
SOMETHING INTERESTING IN
THE HISTORY OF THE LODGE
THAT WE CAN USE TO
ATTRACT TOURISTS.
YOU KNOW, I KIND OF HOPED
THAT BY THIS POINT,
WE'D HAVE BUILT UP A CLIENTELE
OF REGULAR CUSTOMERS,
BUT SO FAR THE ONLY
REPEAT BUSINESS WE'VE HAD
IS ONE GUY WHO CAME BACK
WITH A SEARCH WARRANT
'CAUSE HE DROPPED HIS
RAY BANS DOWN THE TWO-HOLER.
UNCLE RED!
OH! UNCLE RED!
LOOK WHAT I FOUND!
FALSE TEETH.
THEY'RE MADE OUT OF WOOD.
I THINK THEY BELONG TO
GEORGE WASHINGTON.
THESE COULD BE OVER,
LIKE, 200 YEARS OLD.
NO, HAROLD, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO.
YEAH.
THOSE ARE OLD
MAN SEDGEWICK'S TEETH.
AHH! AHH! OHH!
HE HAS
WOODEN TEETH?
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
HE SAYS THEY'RE QUIETER.
HE LIKES TO EAT CORN CHIPS
IN THE LIBRARY.
WHAT DOES HE --
WHY DOES HE LEAVE
THEM AT THE LODGE?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
IT WAS MEXICAN NIGHT
AND THE FOOD
WAS SO SPICY,
HE WAS AFRAID
THEY WOULD BURST
INTO FLAME ON HIM.
'COURSE NOBODY WANTS HIM
SHOOTING HIS MOUTH OFF.
BUT DON'T
WORRY, HAROLD.
THERE'S YOUR
TOURIST MAGNET
RIGHT THERE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
UNCLE RED, YOU THINK
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO
COME TO THE LODGE
TO SEE A PADDLE?
WELL, IT'S NOT JUST
ANY PADDLE, HAROLD.
LOOK AT THE
LINES ON THERE, SEE?
AGE SEVEN,
AGE SEVEN AND A HALF,
AGE EIGHT,
AGE EIGHT AND A HALF,
AGE NINE,
AGE --
AGE NINE AND A HALF,
YEAH, OKAY, I GET IT.
YES, YES, IT'S
A STICK MARKING
SOME KID'S HEIGHT.
SO WHAT?
NOT JUST ANY
KID, HAROLD.
A FAMOUS MEMBER
OF THE GREEN FAMILY.
EVER HEARD OF
LORNE GREENE?
YEAH.
SAYS LORNE
UP THERE.
AND I FIGURE HE WAS
MY GRANDPA GREEN'S
SECOND COUSIN BY
A PREVIOUS MARRIAGE
AND A PRIOR
COMMITMENT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
SO I FIGURE
THIS PADDLE PROVES
THAT THE FAMOUS
LORNE GREENE IS
A RELATIVE OF OURS
AND STAYED RIGHT HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE.
WOW!
THE REAL LORNE GREENE?
GREENE WITH THE EXTRA "E"
ON THE END OF IT?
UNLIKE THE UNFAMOUS RED GREEN
WHO HAS NO EXTRA ANYTHING.
[ LAUGHTER ]
ANYWHERE.
HAROLD, WHEN PEOPLE
GO INTO SHOW BUSINESS
THEY CHANGE
THEIR NAMES.
HE ADDED AN "E",
HAROLD, OKAY.
SO I FIGURE THAT WE CAN
CHANGE POSSUM LODGE
INTO AN ATTRACTION
BASED ON LORNE GREENE,
JUST LIKE DOLLY PARTON
DID WITH "DOLLYWOOD".
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELL, DOLLY PARTON HAS
TWO THINGS YOU DON'T HAVE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
BRAINS AND MONEY.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
IT'S THE POSSUM
LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER
RECEIVES A COUPON
FOR A FREE OIL CHANGE
AND CHEESEBURGER
FROM McHANIC'S.
POSSUM LAKE'S FIRST
DRIVE-THROUGH
CAR REPAIR SHOP
AND FAST FOOD RESTAURANT.
HOME OF THE SLOGAN
"DO YOU WANT TIRES WITH THAT?"
OKAY, COVER YOUR --
OH, NEVER MIND.
MR. GREEN, YOU'VE GOT
30 SECONDS
TO GET EDGAR
TO SAY THIS WORD.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND GO.
OKAY, EDGAR,
OKAY, IF YOU WORK WITH C4,
THIS IS WHAT YOU
DON'T WANT TO BE...
IN THE SAME COUNTY.
THAT STUFF'LL BLOW
YOUR CLOTHES RIGHT OFF.
I'VE SEEN ME RUNNING
BACK TO YOUR TRUCK
WITH NOTHING BUT A LITTLE
PLUNGER IN FRONT OF ME
AND HOPING THAT THE
SMOKE WOULD HOLD OUT.
OKAY, NO, NO, NO, NO,
OKAY, OKAY.
UH, WHEN A GUY
WORKS WITH EXPLOSIVES
BUT HE MAKES A
LOT OF MISTAKES,
WHAT WOULD
YOU CALL HIM?
LEFTY.
OKAY, EDGAR, WHEN SOMEONE DOES
WHAT YOU DO FOR A LIVING,
THIS IS SOMETHING THEY
CAN'T AFFORD TO BE...
INSURED?
IF SOMEBODY CALLS YOU
INCOMPETENT, DANGEROUS
AND RECKLESS,
THAT MEANS YOU'RE...
BACK IN FRONT OF THE
LICENSING BOARD AGAIN.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
WHEN A MAN IS
NOT CAREFUL, HE'S...
MARRIED.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF
TIME, MR GREEN.
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW, EDGAR,
I THINK THIS CHEESEBURGER
IS JUST FLYING
AWAY ON YOU HERE.
OH, BIG DEAL.
WITH MY CHOLESTEROL,
I COULD CARE LESS.
YEAH!
[ APPLAUSE ]
HIS NAME IS ROTHSCHILD,
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
WHEN YOUR TANK GOES BAD
AND STARTS TO OOZE
YOU NEED A MAN
WITH RUBBER SHOES
CALL ROTHSCHILD,
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
HE HAS REAL NICE CLOTHES
BUT HE'S HARD ON THE NOSE
STILL HE'S THE ONE
THAT WE ALL CHOSE
'CAUSE YOU KNOW FOR SURE
YOU'LL NEVER GET HOSED
WITH ROTHSCHILD,
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
WHEN YOUR LINE'S
ALL BLOCKED
AND YOU KNOW YOU'RE STUCK
YOU NEED A GUY
WHO'S A WORLD CLASS SUCK
CALL ROTHSCHILD,
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
[ GRUNTING ]
OH, I'M KIND OF
GOING A DIFFERENT WAY
WITH THE HANDYMAN
CORNER THIS TIME.
I THOUGHT I WOULD TAKE
A NORMAL PROBLEM
AND DEMONSTRATE HOW
THE TRUE HANDYMAN USES
INGENUITY AND PERSISTENCE
TO OVERCOME ANY OBSTACLES.
YOU KNOW THE SAME
APPROACH WOULD BRING
SUCCESS IN YOUR PERSONAL
OR PROFESSIONAL LIVES TOO,
BUT I FIND THAT STUFF
PRETTY BORING.
SO WHAT WE HAVE HERE
IS A FLAT TIRE
WITH SOME PRETTY RUSTY
LUGS ON THERE.
OKAY, NOW, I STARTED
WITH BRUTE FORCE THERE,
'CAUSE THAT'S ALWAYS
THE SHORTEST WAY HOME.
BUT WHEN BRUTE FORCE FAILS,
WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO IS
GO WITH MORE BRUTE FORCE.
THIS TIME WE'RE GOING TO ADD
A LITTLE SCIENCE IN THERE,
THE LAW OF THE LEVER,
WHICH IS NOT: "IF YOU DON'T
LOVE HER, LEAVE HER."
[ LAUGHTER ]
I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE EXTRA TORC YOU GET
WHENEVER YOU EXTEND THE
HANDLE OF YOUR TOOL.
[ LAUGHTER ]
NOW, A LOT OF GUYS
WOULD QUIT AT THIS POINT,
BUT THEN THEY'RE NOT ME.
AND WE ALL FEEL
PRETTY GOOD ABOUT THAT.
WE'RE GONNA GIVE UP
ON BRUTE FORCE,
WE'RE GONNA SWITCH OVER
TO TECHNOLOGY.
THIS HERE IS
AN IMPACT WRENCH.
IT USES COMPRESSED AIR
TO DO THE WORK FOR YOU.
SORRY YOU HAD TO
SEE THAT BACK THERE.
YOU KNOW, A HANDYMAN
LOSING HIS TEMPER
IS THE REASON
WE HAVE HOSPITALS.
BUT LOOK AT HOW I HAVEN'T
LET THIS THING BEAT ME.
SEE I TOOK THE SOCKET
OFF THE IMPACT WRENCH,
STUCK IT ONTO THE WHEEL --
ONTO THE WHEEL NUT THERE,
AND THEN I WELDED THIS END
OF THE PIPE ONTO THE SOCKET.
AND NOW TO GIVE ME
THE EXTRA POWER
TO LOOSEN THIS BABY OFF,
I ATTACHED THE OTHER END
OF THIS PIPE
TO THE DRIVE SHAFT
OF THIS CAR.
NOW SHE'S ONLY
200 HORSE,
BUT I FIGURE IN REVERSE
SHE'LL HAVE ENOUGH POWER
TO FIRE THOSE
NUTS OFF NO PROBLEM.
AND THEN WHEN IT COMES TIME
TO TIGHTEN THEM BACK ON,
WELL, I CAN PUT
IT IN DRIVE
AND THEN I'VE GOT
THREE SPEEDS TO CHOOSE FROM.
THE IMPORTANT
LIFE LESSON HERE IS
YOU DON'T EVER GIVE UP,
YOU DON'T EVER GIVE IN
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
YOU DON'T EVER READ
THE OWNER'S MANUAL.
SO REMEMBER...
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[ CREAKING ]
MAN, THOSE NUTS ARE
LEFT-HAND THREAD!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
MOST MEN ARE NOT
NATURALLY NEAT.
WE CAN'T HELP IT;
IT'S GENETIC.
SEE, WOMEN HAVE THE
TWO "X" CHROMOSOMES,
THAT'S A MATCHED SET, OKAY.
WE HAVE AN "X" AND A "Y".
AS FAR AS WE'RE CONCERNED,
ANYTHING GOES WITH ANYTHING.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IN FACT, MAKING A MESS
IS HOW THE HUMAN MALE
MARKS HIS TERRITORY.
AND WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
IT'S -- IT'S A LOT BETTER THAN
THE WAY WE USED TO DO IT.
THE POINT IS ALL YOUR LIFE
YOU'VE THRIVED ON CHAOS.
REMEMBER YOUR
FIRST APARTMENT?
REMEMBER THE FIRST TIME
YOUR MOTHER DROPPED IN
ON YOUR FIRST APARTMENT?
REMEMBER HOW SHE FAINTED?
AND HER FALL WAS BROKEN
BY THOSE EMPTY PIZZA BOXES?
ENOUGH SAID.
BUT LATELY YOU'VE HAD STRANGE
STIRRINGS, HAVEN'T YOU?
UNFAMILIAR YEARNINGS LIKE WHEN
YOU'RE WALKING BY THE SHED
YOU START THINKING, YOU KNOW,
I SHOULD CLEAN THAT UP.
OR YOU'RE THINKING,
LANDSCAPING WOULD MAKE
THIS PLACE A LOT HOMIER.
I KNOW IT'S SCARY,
BUT DON'T PANIC.
IT'S A NATURAL PART
OF THE MATURING PROCESS,
SEE, YOU'VE FINALLY COME TO
THE AGE WHERE YOU'VE ACQUIRED
ALL THE TERRITORY
YOU'RE GONNA CONQUER.
IT'S NOT GONNA
GET ANY BIGGER,
MAYBE YOU CAN
GET IT ORGANIZED.
IT'S NOT BECAUSE YOUR WIFE
HAS FINALLY MANAGED
TO TAKE OVER YOUR MIND
WHILE YOU WERE SLEEPING.
NOW, IF YOU'RE SMART,
YOU'LL ACCEPT THAT
NOW YOU'RE A NEATER PERSON.
AND IF YOU'RE REALLY SMART,
YOU'LL LET YOUR WIFE THINK
YOU'RE DOING IT FOR HER.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU;
WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WHEN A STRONG BLAST FROM
METHANE BURNS THE HAIR
FROM YOUR NOSE,
WHEN IT WEAKENS YOUR KNEES
AND BUCKLES YOUR TOES,
WHEN THERE'S A RISING DAMP
ON YOUR LAWN AND YOUR CLOTHES,
YOU'LL WISH THAT
ROTHSCHILD SEWAGE
HAD BEEN THE
SUCKER YOU CHOSE.
THIS LORNE GREENE IDEA
IS REALLY STARTING
TO TAKE SHAPE.
ALL THE YEARS WE'VE STRUGGLED
TO BUILD OUR OWN POPULARITY
AND ALL WE HAD TO DO
WAS STEAL SOMEBODY ELSE'S.
[ LAUGHTER ]
AND IN ORDER TO CASH IN
ON LORNE GREENE'S SUCCESS,
POSSUM LODGE IS NOW
KNOW AS POSSUM PONDEROSA.
[ LAUGHTER ]
AND I'LL TELL YOU,
IT'S NOT JUST A MONEY MAKER,
IT'S A "BONANZA".
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND WHISTLES ]
YOU ALL REMEMBER
THE VILLAGE PEOPLE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WE'RE JUST TRYING
TO ENHANCE THE LORNE
GREENE EXPERIENCE
BY DRESSING UP LIKE
CHARACTERS FROM THE SHOW.
I DIDN'T KNOW BEN CARTWRIGHT
HAD TWO JACKASSES.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WE'RE HIS SONS.
DALTON IS HOSS.
YOU'RE HOSS?
YEAH, VERY MUCH SO, YES.
HE ALWAYS HAD AN
AIR OF QUIET DIGNITY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELL, YOU HAVE AN AIR
OF LOUD EMBARRASSMENT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
AND WHO ARE YOU
SUPPOSED TO BE,
LIBERACE CARTWRIGHT?
[ LAUGHTER ]
NO, I'M LITTLE JOE.
OH, LITTLE JOKE,
MAYBE.
YOU SHOULD SEE MOOSE THOMPSON.
HE'S HOP SING.
[ LAUGHTER ]
A LITTLE LIGHT ON THE SING,
A LITTLE HEAVY ON THE HOP.
MAYBE THIS WAS
A BAD IDEA.
OH, NO, NO, NO,
UNCLE RED.
WE ALREADY HAVE
60 GUESTS BOOKED
FOR THE FIRST
POSSUM PONDEROSA WEEKEND.
WE'VE GOT TO
MAKE IT LOOK GOOD.
YOU GET TO BE
BEN CARTWRIGHT.
WELL, NOW
YOU'RE TALKING.
OKAY, OKAY,
OKAY, OKAY.
Red (voice over):
YOU KNOW EVERY YEAR AT
THE START OF FOOTBALL SEASON,
THE BIG QUESTION IS...
WHAT DO YOU DO WITH THE
PEOPLE WHO WEREN'T PICKED?
SO I THOUGHT WE'D
HAVE A BIT OF
A FOOTBALL
COMPETITION, THERE.
AND WE HAD SIX FOOTBALLS,
AND I PUT A COUPLE OF
INITIALS ON EACH ONE
SO THERE WAS
TWO WITH A "D",
TWO WITH A "W",
TWO WITH AN "M".
AND SO TAKE THE
TWO WITH THE "D", NO "W",
AND GIVE THOSE TO WINSTON.
WINSTON --
HE'S GONNA THROW.
HE'S GONNA BE THE PASSER.
THEN I TAKE THE TWO WITH
THE "D"s ON THEM
AND I GIVE THEM TO DALTON.
DALTON'S GONNA BE
THE PUNTER.
THE KICKER, THE PUNTER,
THE PUNTER, THE KICKER --
GIVE IT A TRY THERE, DALTON.
HOW IS THE BACK ANYWAY?
NOT GOOD,
NOT GOOD, OKAY.
AND NOW MIKE'S CHALLENGE --
HE'S GOING TO DO
THE PLACE KICKING.
I'M NOT SURE MIKE
REALLY GRASPS
THE WHOLE CONCEPT OF HOW
THAT WHOLE KICKER STANCE --
NOT, NOT --
SO ANYWAY, SO WINSTON'S
GONNA GO FIRST.
SO HE DOES THE
Y.A. TITTLE THING
AND THEN HAD TO
CHANGE HIS PANTS
AND THEN HE CAME OUT
AND THREW THE FOOTBALL.
AND NOT A BAD --
NO, NOT A BAD TOSS.
NOT BAD,
NOT BAD.
OKAY, THERE'S THE "W".
NOW, DALTON, YOUR CHALL --
SEE IF YOU CAN KICK IT
FARTHER THAN WINSTON
THREW IT.
OKAY, OKAY.
CAREFUL ON THE BACK,
NOW, DALTON, CAREFUL.
HERE WE GO,
HERE WE GO.
BACK OKAY?
LOOKS ALL RIGHT.
NO, NO.
OKAY AND -- OKAY, NOW,
THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S GOOD, IT'S NOT
THAT MUCH FARTHER, DALTON.
MIKE, HE PUTS HIS
ON THE TEE THERE,
AND HE'S GONNA --
OH, BOY -- OH.
A LITTLE SOMETHING
HE LEARNED IN PRISON.
AND OKAY, SO,
THEY'RE ALL PRETTY HAPPY,
BUT TO ME, I WAS
A LITTLE DISAPPOINTED
IN THE OVERALL QUALITY
OF THE COMPETITION.
IT'S NOT LIKE THESE
WERE THAT FAR DOWN THE FIELD.
SO OKAY, SO I'M SAYING YOU
GUYS GET ONE MORE BALL EACH.
LET'S PUT A LITTLE
EXTRA INTO IT.
I'LL GET RID OF THIS.
OKAY SO WINSTON
HAS A RAMP
AND DOWN HE COMES
AND JUST REALLY LET'S HER GO.
OH! OH!
OH, BOY, OH!
WE DON'T WANNA --
WE DON'T WANT TO SEE THAT.
WINSTON, I CAN'T EVEN
LOOK AT THAT.
NO, NO, PUT THAT AWAY.
PUT THAT AWAY.
OH, I GOTTA GET
FISH THIS FRIDAY.
AND THEN DALTON
TAPES A SLEDGEHAMMER
TO THE SIDE OF HIS LEG.
I'M NOT SURE THIS IS
NOT COMPLETELY LEGAL.
GIVE HIM A LITTLE
EXTRA OOMPH.
THIS IS LIKE
THE TUNGSTEN EJECTED
TITANIUM GOLF CLUB,
audience: O-O-O-H!
Red (voice over):
SO MIKE DECIDES THAT
HE'S JUST GONNA MAYBE
OVERINFLATE THE BALL
A LITTLE BIT.
HE CRANKS THE COMPRESSOR UP
WELL PAST THE SAFE ZONE,
AND I DON'T KNOW HOW BIG --
OH, THEY GO PRETTY BIG.
YEAH, THEY GO PRETTY BIG.
SO NOW I GUESS THE IDEA IS
WHEN HE MAKES CONTACT WITH
THAT, SHE SHOULD TAKE OFF.
YEAH, OKAY, OKAY,
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, LET 'ER GO,
LET 'ER GO.
AND -- OH, BOY,
OH, BOY.
AND I THINK --
THAT'S THE WHOLE LENGTH --
THAT'S A --
THERE'S A FIELD GOAL.
WELL, THERE'S YOUR --
NOW, SHAKE HANDS,
SHAKE HANDS
WITH EVERYBODY.
C'MON, MIKE, BE A GOOD
SPORT AND SHAKE HANDS --
DON'T SHAKE --
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
WELL, THEN JUST --
WELL, MAYBE --
NO, NO, NO,
MAYBE NOT,
ALL RIGHT,
OKAY.
DON'T WORRY, DALTON.
WE'LL FIX THIS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YEAH, I KNOW I GOT IT.
PEPPERONI, GROUND BEEF
GROUND PORK AND EXTRA CHEESE.
YOU WANT A DOUBLE
BYPASS WITH THAT?
YEAH, YEAH,
IT'S COMING RIGHT UP.
REMEMBER THAT GAME YOU USED
TO PLAY WHEN YOU WERE A KID?
NO, NOT THAT GAME.
THE OTHER ONE WHERE
YOU AND A FRIEND
WOULD SEE WHO COULD
SKIP A STONE
THE FARTHEST OUT
ACROSS THE LAKE?
WELL, HOLD THAT THOUGHT.
THIS IS STINKY
PETERSON'S ISLAND.
THEY SAY NO MAN
IS AN ISLAND,
BUT IN STINKY'S CASE WE'RE
PREPARED TO MAKE AN EXCEPTION.
ACTUALLY STINKY'S AWAY
FOR A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
HE ASKED ME TO LOOK AFTER
HIS BUSINESS FOR HIM,
A PIZZA DELIVERY BUSINESS.
AND STINKY'S GOT
A REAL UNIQUE WAY
OF GETTING THEM OUT TO YOU.
HE SITS THEM IN BETWEEN
A COUPLE OF OLD WHEEL DISCS.
AND THEN HE FIRES THEM OUT
TO YOU ACROSS THE LAKE,
USING THAT SKEET THROWER.
HE CAN ONLY DELIVER, YOU KNOW,
TO HOUSES ON THE LAKE,
BUT THAT PREVENTS
HIS BUSINESS FROM GETTING
SO BIG HE CAN'T HANDLE IT.
THIS PIZZA HERE IS
FOR DALTON'S DAUGHTER,
SO I'VE JUST GOTTA
AIM IT AT HIS PLACE.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
THERE WE GO.
YOU KNOW, STINKY
CALLS IT A PIZZERIA
BUT IT COULD JUST AS EASILY
BE CALLED A SKEET-ZERIA.
AND EVERY PIZZA COMES
WITH A GUARANTEE...
NO MORE THAN 30 SKIPS,
OR IT'S FREE.
AND... PULL.
[ DISCS HITTING WATER ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU'VE MADE
YOURSELF SUCCESSFUL,
SO MANY FRIENDS TO THANK.
IT'S GOOD TO HAVE
A LIFE THAT'S FULL,
BUT NOT A SEPTIC TANK.
COME ON IN,
COME ON IN.
WELL --
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU ALL RIGHT,
HAROLD?
IT'S BEEN THAT KIND
OF A WEEKEND.
WE HIT A FEW SNAGS
WITH OUR PONDEROSA THING.
IT TURNS OUT OUR LORNE GREENE
WASN'T THE REAL LORNE GREENE.
WE ALL GOT CAUGHT WITH
OUR CHAPS DOWN ON THAT ONE.
BUT I FIND THAT WHENEVER YOU
PRETEND TO BE SOMETHING
THAT YOU'RE NOT,
YOU GET YOURSELF
INTO TROUBLE
UNLESS YOUR COMPANY
IS PUBLICLY TRADED.
[ LAUGHTER ]
BUT IT'S OKAY,
IT'S OKAY.
EVERYTHING'S FINE NOW.
THEY DROPPED THE CHARGES.
HAROLD, I CAN'T BELIEVE
ALL THOSE PEOPLE
WERE RELATIVES
OF LORNE GREENE.
OH, NO, THEY WEREN'T.
NO, A LOT OF THEM
WERE LITIGATORS.
YEAH, WE HAD SOME
COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT ISSUES,
SOME LICENSING
VIOLATIONS.
OF COURSE, THERE'S THAT
WHOLE KAFUFFLE ABOUT
WHETHER OR NOT LIVESTOCK
SHOULD BE ALLOWED IN
THE RESTAURANT.
THAT WAS SOMETHING
WE GOT TO LEARN.
YOU KNOW, I FELT THAT
AFTER I SPOKE TO THEM
THINGS KIND
OF SETTLED DOWN.
OH YEAH!
ONCE THEY HEARD
YOU SPEAK, BOY,
THEY REALIZED
WE WERE DOING IT
OUT OF IGNORANCE.
YEAH, THEY WERE JUST
TRYING TO PROTECT
THE REPUTATION OF
LORNE GREENE, THAT'S ALL.
AND WE DID NOT MENTION
BATTLESTAR GALACTICA.
THEY REALLY
APPRECIATED THAT.
THAT HELPED.
WELL, HAROLD,
WHAT NOW?
I MEAN, HOW ARE WE GOING
TO PROMOTE THE LODGE
IF WE CAN'T LIE?
WELL, HOW ABOUT WE
BASE THE CAMPAIGN
ON THE LODGE'S NATURAL
BEAUTY AND SERENITY
AND OF COURSE THE
MAJESTY OF POSSUM LAKE.
WE'RE SO DEAD.
SO DEAD.
WE'RE FINISHED.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD,
HAROLD, OKAY.
OKAY.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
SO IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
THIS OLD COWPOKE WILL BE
BLAZING A TRAIL STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
TODAY I TRIED
TO BE LORNE GREENE,
BUT I FOUND OUT HOW TOUGH
IT IS TO BE A STAR.
THAT'S NOT GOING
TO HAPPEN TO ME;
I'M STAYING IN CANADA.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF, HAROLD
AND THE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OH, HERE WE ARE, OKAY,
TAKE YOUR SEATS, PLEASE.
SIT DOWN, SIT DOWN.
THE MEETING'S ABOUT TO BEGIN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, GUYS, NOW THAT THE
POSSUM LODGE PONDEROSA THING
HAS BEEN CANCELLED, WE GOT A
CHUCKWAGON TO GIVE AWAY
IF ANYBODY'S INTERESTED.
ANYBODY?
OKAY, OKAY, IT'S NOT
ACTUALLY A CHUCKWAGON,
IT'S A '79 K-CAR.
OKAY, AND WE'VE TAKEN
THE SHOCKS OUT OF HER,
SO IT'S REALLY MORE OF
AN UPCHUCK WAGON.
(shouting)
BOB, YOU WANT TO TURN ON
YOUR HEARING AID?