You know, a lot of
the high-end cars
have a navigational system
built right into the dash.
I guess men find it easier
to ask their car for directions
than a total stranger.
But the problem with high-
tech is the high price.
So I'm going low-tech
and low-brow.
See, at my age, I'm not
interested in going anywhere
I've never been before.
So on my last few trips,
I took along this
cassette recorder
and recorded the
directions myself.
Now all I do is pop in
the tape of wherever
I want to go
and presto,
instant directions.
And technically, it's
not asking for help
'cause it's still me.
Like right now, I've got
to go to the post office
so all I've got to do
is get out the post
office cassette.
Beer store,
other beer store,
other other beer --
Here we are... post office.
[ ENGINE REVS ]
RECORDED VOICE:
Okay, I get to the end of
the driveway and hang a left.
And now I'm coming up
to a red mailbox.
Oh, wait, no, that was
the road back there.
I'd better pull a u-ey.
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
Okay, watch out
for that road sign.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
All right.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate it.
A bit of a setback up
at the lodge this week.
Junior Singleton tried out
his one-man water
skiing invention
where he skis behind
an unmanned boat
with the rope tied to the
throttle of the outboard motor.
But you know, no matter
how clever an idea is,
things can go wrong.
As it turns out, Junior's
a lot better at water skiing
than he is at tying knots.
Uncle Red, oh boy.
The Farnsworth's are
going to keep Junior's boat.
Oh, she ran aground
at the Farnsworth's...
Yeah, yeah, during their
daughter's beachfront
wedding reception.
Oh boy.
Yeah, Junior's unmanned boat
came right off the dock,
flattened the
no trespassing sign,
landed right in the buffet.
Oh boy.
The prop pureed an
entire side of pork.
Wow and now they're
being jerks about it?
I know, it's
hard to believe.
You know, some people...
But you know, they say
it landed on their property
so they're keeping it now.
And Mr. Farnsworth, he's
a very successful lawyer.
Well he can't be
that successful
if he has a place up here.
You know what,
maybe a bunch of us
should go over and
see this hotshot lawyer
and drop a torte
in his briefs.
No, no, no, no.
Violence is not the answer.
It's fun, though.
No, it's not.
No, no, no.
Violence only leads
to more violence.
Instead, we should present
our legal position.
Oh yeah, I know.
We sue them
and they sue us
and it goes back and
forth between the lawyers
at 300 bucks an hour
and it comes to court
about nine years later.
We win of course but
then they have an appeal
and by the time the
thing's settled
and we get
the boat back,
we're all in
an old age home
and nobody has
the strength
to pull-start anything.
No, all we have to say
to the town council
is that the Farnsworth's
do not own that beach.
Nobody does!
It's called Riparian rights.
Yeah, that boat is not
on their property.
And you think they're
going to side with us
rather than Farnsworth
who pays taxes?
Uncle Red, all we have
to do is go around the lake
and get our neighbours
to sign this petition.
The town council
cannot argue with that.
That's pretty smart.
Yeah, it's very smart.
It's way better
than violence.
Yeah and if somebody
won't sign it,
I'll just smack 'em one.
[ APPLAUSE ]
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
Today's winner receives
this coupon for a
bucket of chicken
from the Port Asbestos
High Volume Chicken Ranch
where chickens don't
cross the road
because we breed them
not to have any bones.
All right, cover
your ears, Mike.
Red, you've got 30 seconds
to get Mike Hammer
to say this word.
Yeah, all right Winston.
And GO!
Okay, Mike,
when you work,
this is what you make.
License plates.
Okay, this is another
term for the bottom line.
Oh, bikini wax.
No, okay.
This is something that
every CEO is focussed on...
Net?
Stockings.
Do you even know
what CEO means?
How do you spell it?
Okay, let's try
something else.
This is a mysterious person
who knows where you'll
be in the future.
Oh, the judge.
Red, you guys are almost
out of time, here.
Okay, okay.
Mike, say you buy
something for 90 bucks
and then sell it
for 100 bucks.
That difference of
10 dollars is?
Peanuts.
I can acquire the same
object for nothing
and then sell it to
a fence for 50 bucks.
Okay and that gives you a?
Court appearance.
The problem with that is
after I've paid the lawyer
and I rent the suit,
there goes my profit.
There we go!
[ RINGING BELL ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Well tonight, local animal
control officer, Ed Frid
is going to tell us
how he likes to unwind
after dealing with
animals all day long.
Ed?
Well, I like to have
a couple of pops
and get out a
few animal traps.
That's my hobby.
Kind of a strange hobby,
it's a lot like your job.
I mean a hobby is supposed
to help you take a break.
Take a break?
Harold, do you think
grizzly bears take a break?
Huh?
Do you think rattlesnakes
have a social club
where they go to drink
tea and play cards?
Oh no, no, no, no.
Snakes can't shuffle.
They can't shuffle,
they're snakes.
They can't shuffle.
So... what is it
about animal traps
that appeals to you, Ed?
You know, is it that you
feel trapped by your job?
I'd rather not say.
Oh, okay, well maybe you
can tell us about this one
I see your trap is open.
You should talk.
Okay, uh...
this is a leg trap.
It's a Colin & Bronton
1937 Paw Master 75.
Wow, it looks dangerous.
Should you be
handling it like that
if it is dangerous?
Oh, well yeah,
very much so, oh yeah.
But this one
is rusted open.
Yeah, urine will do that.
How do you know
urine did it?
I'd rather not say.
Now here's a very
important trap.
We use this for catching
the cleverest animal
known to man,
the raccoon.
That's a cat.
It looks like a cat.
Like I say, raccoons
are clever.
Now, for a commercial
fisherman,
there are
lobster traps
and this one, this is
one used right here
on Possum Lake.
I thought that lobsters
were saltwater crustaceans.
Yeah but around here,
a fisherman can make
a pretty good living
pulling up snowmobile gloves.
Okay.
Now, say you want
to catch a mouse.
Oh, that'd great because
then we could feed it
to this raccoon.
Okay.
This is the best.
This is the Rat Master 500
and its got a couple... AUUGH!
OWWW! NOT AGAIN!
NOT AGAIN!
You know, a lot of people
don't care for accordion music.
They make jokes about it
like, the difference
between an accordion
and a trampoline
is you take your shoes off
and jump on a trampoline.
Or the definition
of an optimist
is an accordion
player with a pager.
Or, if you play one
more note on that thing
you're going to need
a surgeon to remove it
from your large intestine.
Now, I don't know
anything about music
but I do have an opinion.
It seems that if
something isn't good,
alls they do is
make it real loud.
Like rap music or opera
or the laugh track
on Who's The Boss.
So I'm going to make
my accordion really loud
with a few simple components:
a vinyl folding door,
some parts from
this old toilet
and a late model minivan
with a power sliding
door and a sunroof.
Oh yeah, and of
course, a stool.
I really lucked out
on this minivan.
The salesman said
try it for the weekend
so I am.
Alls I'm doing is I'm taking
the accordion air pump
and putting it on steroids.
I've magnified the bellows
by mounting the folding door
inside the slider opening.
And this is a power unit
so I don't have to
do any work
which is music to my ears.
Now if you've seen the
inside of an accordion,
I hope you've apologized
to the owner
and you also know that
there's a valve on the back
that lets the air in when
the bellows are opened up.
So I got this toilet
flapper valve
mounted over the
hole in the floor
and connected by this chain
to the toilet handle.
So now, every time
the door slides open,
it automatically
flushes the toilet
and lets the new air in.
Okay, I've made the van
completely air tight
using the handyman's
secret weapon
and I mounted the business
side of the accordion
over the sunroof
so that all the air
will pass through it.
Now, I had to rewire
the remote a little bit
so that the side door
would open and close
without stopping.
It's a lot easier
than I thought.
I just put it in the
microwave for a few minutes.
And now, if you'll excuse me,
it's showtime!
[ ACCORDION MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ BAD ACCORDION SOUNDS ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
The other day I was thinking
back to when I was a teenager
as a way of getting ready
for my second childhood.
We had an expression
back then...
Whenever you went on a date,
your friends always wanted
to know if you got lucky.
You know... well, you know.
I mean that was big.
Any guy that could get lucky
must be really something.
We had one guy, Brett,
he never played baseball
but he got a lot of home runs
if you know what I mean,
most of them inside the park.
Well, I ran into Brett
a couple of weeks ago
and I would say that his
luck has kind of run out.
It's tough to be a playboy
when you don't have the
magazine or the mansion.
He has the fancy scarf,
though, you know, the ascot.
In fact, he's had
it caught many times.
So there he is,
sitting at the bar
with a dyed moustache
and a bad toupee
trying to pick up
flight attendants
but all the gates are closed
and the seatbelts
are securely fastened.
Meanwhile, Bernice and I
are in the restaurant
having a ribeye steak
and a baked potato
and when dinner's over,
I know where she'll
be spending the night.
I can't give you
any more information
about what's going
to happen after that
because after all these years,
I still don't have a clue.
But the point is,
for all you guys
who struck out as
teenagers like I did,
take a look at
your life now.
Funny how much good fortune
can come from
not getting lucky.
Remember, I'm
pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
If you're watching
what you eat
while you're sitting
at the kitchen table,
that's fine.
But if you're watching
what you ate
while you're looking
out the backyard window,
call me.
Well, we had no luck
getting any of our neighbours
to sign the petition
and some of them
can read and write.
But nobody wanted to
question the ownership
of Farnsworth's beach
because that would lead
to questioning the ownership
of their own waterfront.
It's like being a
turkey at Thanksgiving.
You've got a whole
different attitude
when you've got
something to lose.
Speaking of turkeys...
You know, the cottages
on this lake,
they've got a thing of two
to learn about diplomacy.
One of them told me where
I could stick my petition
then tried to put it there.
Don't you worry
about that, Harold.
I have a little something
called plan "B".
Oh no...
It's not violent is it?
Not yet.
No, we're going to walk all
the way around Possum Lake
with a whole whack
of these signs.
We're going to
stick them
in front of
everybody's property
to let them know the beach
doesn't belong to them...
especially Farnsworth.
Our slogan is, let's get
the sign of a beach.
That's a very civilized way
to get your message across.
Do you think Farnsworth
is going to give
Junior's boat back?
Oh, I think so, yeah.
Really?
Yeah, a big, important
lawyer like that,
you think he's going
to be intimidated
by a bunch of old guys
walking around with signs?
Oh, no, Harold, we're
not going to be walking.
It's too far to be
walking around Possum Lake.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
It was raining outside
and Bill came in
and he was ready for a
supernatural adventure
with some investigations
into bad luck and superstition.
First of all, you never
open an umbrella indoors.
So put that away and there's
your first sign --
first sign things
are not going well.
And now you've --
Bill, you're under a ladder.
You're actually, okay
there comes the bat.
Okay Bill, get rid
of the umbrella.
Get rid of the umbrella.
Get calm, get calm.
Now look for something to --
There we go.
And... okay.
Okay, now, Bill,
stay calm, stay calm.
Bill, Bill,
c'mon now Bill.
Okay, take it easy.
Take it easy.
Easy now.
You're not doing that
well with the bat.
Okay, it's about
Love-200 by now.
All right, you know what,
let's just --
let's get rid of
the tennis racket.
Get rid of it.
There we go.
Okay now, plan B,
maybe the bat's gone
that could be.
Oh he's going to
get a pillowcase.
Oh, this is more humane.
Get the pillowcase.
Oh, it's Old Man
Sedgewick's teeth.
He puts them all there
hoping for the tooth fairy.
And, okay, the bat has landed
right on top of the
little dresser there
and Bill is going to
just scoop him up
and just scoop him up
there Bill... shhh.
Go! Go!
Go now! Go!
There he got him.
Easy now, easy,
easy, easy, easy.
Holy cow!
Take it easy,
take it easy.
Bill!
Bill he's only a little bat.
Bill! Bill!
There's the bat.
What's in the bag?
Oh, it's the clock.
Okay, so...
All right, the bat's
still there and unfortunately
Bill has another plan.
So he grabs a firearm --
Oh, that's not an
indoor toy, Bill.
Oh, easy, easy.
Bill, the aim.
Bill, the aim, Bill.
Bill, oh my gosh,
that's an heirloom.
Okay, thank goodness
he's out of ammo.
No, no, no,
no, no, no.
Okay, he's just going
to try and just --
You're not going to
grab the bat are you?
Bill, the bat's probably
going to defend himself.
Bill, no Bill.
No, no, no, no!
Oh, oh, oh...
Bill, then a strange
thing starts to happen.
Bill seems to change and
starts getting ideas.
He gets the umbrella out
and I don't know what
he's got in mind here.
He starts cutting
the umbrella up.
What are you doing, Bill?
What are you doing?
Oh, wings.
Oh boy, okay.
All right, this is getting
into kind of a fantasy world.
Boy, that's an
odd look isn't it?
Oh, there he is.
Wow, he's looking good.
He kind of looks
like John Travolta.
And he's whipping around,
he's eating mosquitoes
like crazy, lots of mosquitoes
and then... it was
all a strange dream
but he's still got
mosquitoes in his teeth
he can't figure out.
Oh, those aren't mosquitoes,
they're mesquite wings.
Oh...
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Got kind of a
two-part lesson
for all of you
handymen out there.
Last spring I had to
re-seed the lawn
out where the lodge members
park all of their cars.
The grass was all killed
from the various fluids
leaking out all
over the ground.
Some of it from the vehicles.
Now, this job needed
a lot of grass seed
because we're talking
about a pretty big lawn.
The problem is we're trying
to do this on a budget
but it's too big
a job for one guy
especially if
that guy is me.
Then I thought, hey,
I don't shovel snow,
why should I
shovel grass seed?
Okay, that's the first
part of today's lesson.
Be creative.
The second part, always
clean up your tools.
[ LAUGHTER ]
Mission accomplished...
sort of...
Well I see you're
back from the front.
Actually, I can almost see
your front from the back.
You know what friendly
fire is Harold?
Yes, I'm sorry, okay.
How did things go?
Things went well?
Well we made it most of
the way around the lake
but in a way we realized
how many of the residents
had incorporated
the beachfront
into their landscaping.
We're talking hedges?
Hedges, barbed wire,
electric fences, stone walls,
gazebos, bunkhouses,
doghouses,
we took a lot of hits.
I believe it's called flak.
Well, you would know.
But we made
our point, Harold.
We got Junior's
boat back.
All right, okay!
That's great!
Where is it?
Under the tank.
[ POSSUM SQUEALS ]
Meeting time.
Yeah.
Time for the de-briefing.
Why don't we
start with yours?
Okay, all right, okay.
Okay, if my wife
is watching
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting
and I learned an important
lesson this week.
Things that I
have belong to me
and things that you
have belong to you
but it's way more
fun when we share.
And to the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of
myself and Harold
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge,
keep your stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
C'mon hurry up and sit down.
Sit down there.
All rise.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the man's prayer.
I'm a man
but I can change
if I have to
I guess.
All right men, apparently
the beachfront doesn't
belong to anybody
which limits the liability
of all the land owners
including the lodge.
So from now on whenever
you see something
that looks like it's
going to blow up,
take her down to the dock.