[quirky upbeat music]
[chain saw buzzing]
[gunshots]
[glass shatters]
THE TIME FOR DECISIONS HAS
COME AND GONE.
WELL, WE DIDN'T MAKE ANY, AND
IT'S PRETTY MUCH TOO LATE NOW.
SO SIT BACK OR SIT UP.
PRETTY MUCH SIT ANY WAY
YOU WANT TO.
IT'S REALLY NONE OF MY BUSINESS.
BUT ANYWAY, IT'S TIME FOR THE
SHOW LIKE NO OTHER SHOWS TO THE
EXTENT, YOU KNOW, THAT THIS IS
OUR SHOW, MEANING, YOU KNOW, ME,
MYSELF, AND MY UNCLE,
WHO HAPPENS TO BE THE STAR
OF THE RED GREEN SHOW,
RED GREEN.
[applause]
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
AND A SPECIAL THANK YOU TO OUR
VIEWERS FOR BUCKING THE TREND.
SPEAKING OF WHICH, HAROLD, COME
ON OVER HERE, MAN.
HAROLD IS PRODUCER, DIRECTOR,
AND MY NEPHEW ON THE SHOW.
AND HE'S GOT THIS LITTLE MACHINE
HERE, AND HE'S ABLE TO REALLY
KEEP THINGS MOVING ALONG FOR US.
IT'S A VIDEO EFFECT MACHINE.
IT GOES LIKE THIS.
[keyboard clacking]
[chicken bawks]
THAT WAY I CAN BAIL OUT OF
A BORING SEGMENT INTO A MORE
INTERESTING ONE, YOU KNOW, IF
THE NEED SHOULD ARISE, WHICH I'M
SURE IT DOESN'T.
WELL, ANYWAY.
GOLLY, WE HAD A HECK OF A TIME
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
WE SAT AROUND, AND WE STARTED
DISCUSSING WHAT IT MEANS TO BE
A REAL MAN.
AND FUNNY, WHAT IT CAME DOWN TO
WAS, YOU'VE GOT TO BE LOUD,
STRONG, AND SMELL LIKE GAS.
AND OF COURSE, TO US, THAT MEANT
YOU HAD TO HAVE AN OUTBOARD
MOTOR.
OR A VIDEO EFFECT MACHINE.
WELL, WE DECIDED RIGHT THEN
AND THERE, WE WERE GOING TO HAVE
THE BIGGEST OUTBOARD MOTOR ON
THE LAKE, WHICH MEANT THAT WE
HAD TO BUILD IT OURSELVES.
NOW, HAROLD, DO YOU HAPPEN TO
KNOW WHAT A 427-CUBIC-INCH
ENGINE IS?
NO.
WHY DON'T WE GO TO THE NEXT
SEGMENT, AND WE'LL HAVE A CHANCE
TO LOOK IT UP?
[keyboard clacking]
WELL, I CAN TELL YOU WHAT IT
IS, HAROLD.
OH.
IT'S TOO LATE.
DARN.
[spoons clicking]
[strumming guitar tune]
ON A CLEAR SUMMER NIGHT
WHEN THE WARM SUMMER BREEZE
COMES DOWN TO THE WATER
AND RUSTLES THE TREES
A BUNCH OF US MEET THERE
AND STRIP TO THE BUFF
BECAUSE BOYS WILL BE BOYS
AND ENOUGH IS ENOUGH
WE GO SKINNY-DIPPING
SKINNY-DIPPING
OFF AND FLIPPING
WHEN NATURE'S CALLING
WE GO CANNONBALLING
HEART RATE RISES
THE SPIRIT SOARS
THE MOON YOU SEE
MIGHT EVEN BE YOURS
SKINNY-DIPPING
SLAPPING MY BUTT ON THE LAKE
I WOULDN'T DRINK THE WATER.
NOW HE TELLS ME.
[quirky upbeat music]
THIS WEEK AT THE HANDYMAN
CORNER, WHAT I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
IS HOW TO OPERATE THIS POWERFUL
ELECTRICAL DEVICE.
THIS RIGHT HERE IS A--
IT'S A BELT--A BELT SANDER.
BUT I WOULDN'T ADVISE YOU
SANDING YOUR BELT WITH IT UNLESS
YOU ARE REALLY INTO
THE CELIBACY THING.
ANYWAY, LET ME SHOW YOU HOW THIS
WORKS WITH THIS LITTLE PIECE OF
WOOD I GOT RIGHT HERE.
[belt sander whirring]
AH, THAT REMINDS ME.
I WANTED TO TALK ABOUT
SAFETY GOGGLES.
ANYWAY, I'LL SHOW YOU SOMETHING
ELSE YOU CAN DO WITH A SANDER.
IT'S GOOD FOR SANDING A BIG-
A BIG, FLAT SURFACE
LIKE A DOOR HERE.
[coughs]
NOW, WITH A DOOR, THE FIRST
THING YOU HAVE TO DECIDE IS,
WHICH WAY IS THE GRAIN GOING?
ALL RIGHT.
THE GRAIN IS GOING THAT WAY.
SO WE--WE SAND AGAINST
THE GRAIN.
NOW YOU HOLD HER LEVEL, A LITTLE
BIT NOSE UP, KEEP HER STEADY,
AND BRING HER DOWN
ONTO THE DOOR.
[belt sander whirring]
[loud clattering]
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S RIGHT TOO.
I FORGOT.
YOU HAVE TO SAND WITH THE GRAIN.
SO WHAT I'LL DO IS JUST SWING
THE DOOR AROUND.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW GET THE SANDER GOING AND
DROP HER DOWN ONTO THE DOOR.
[belt sander whirring]
crash!
I'M OBVIOUSLY NOT GOING TO BE
ABLE TO FINISH THIS JOB UNTIL
I GET A LONGER WORKBENCH.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME, REMEMBER:
IF WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[applause]
YOU'LL WANT TO COME RIGHT BACK
AFTER THE BREAK AND HEAR MORE
ABOUT THE OUTBOARD MOTOR UNLESS
I MISS MY GUESS.
WHICH IS QUITE POSSIBLE,
IN MY OPINION.
[quirky upbeat music]
IT IS WINTER.
CHILDREN'S LAUGHTER
AT THE FRONT DOOR.
THEY TUMBLE INTO THE HOUSE,
BOOTS OFF, HATS OFF, SWEATERS,
SNOWSUITS, SCARVES, AND MITTENS
ARE PEELED AWAY.
HEY, THESE AREN'T YOUR KIDS.
AS I WAS SAYING ABOUT BUILDING
OUR OWN OUTBOARD MOTOR, WE WERE
LUCKY ENOUGH TO GET OUR HANDS ON
A 427 ENGINE WHICH FELL OUT OF
A FRIEND'S CAR WHEN BUSTER
HATFIELD DID AN OIL CHANGE
ON IT.
THE INSURANCE PAID FOR
EVERYTHING, SO WE ENDED UP WITH
THE MOTOR.
WE FIGURED IT WOULD BE IDEAL TO
BUILD AN OUTBOARD AROUND THAT.
SO NEXT THING WE NEEDED WAS A
DRIVE SHAFT.
WE DECIDED TO USE OUR SHOWER ROD
BECAUSE WE WEREN'T USING IT
BECAUSE WE DON'T HAVE A SHOWER
CURTAIN BECAUSE WE DON'T HAVE
SHOWERS BECAUSE WE DON'T HAVE
HOT WATER BECAUSE WE DON'T HAVE
WATER.
SO WHEN YOU GET A MOTOR THAT
SIZE, IT'D JUST BE WASTED ON
A NORMAL-SIZED PROP.
SO WE HAD TO THINK OF SOMETHING
A LITTLE BIGGER, LIKE
A CEILING FAN.
SO WE PUT A WHOLE RIG UP THERE
AND PUT IT ALL TOGETHER WITH THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON, DUCT
TAPE, AND THEN WE MOUNTED HER ON
THE BACK OF THE ALUMINUM BOAT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, GOLLY, THAT
WEIGHT DISTRIBUTION WAS KIND OF
OFF ON THAT.
SO WE ENDED UP TURNING THE WHOLE
FRONT HALF OF THE BOAT INTO
A GAS TANK.
UNCLE RED, THE NEXT SEGMENT'S
ALL READY.
WELL, I DON'T CARE, HAROLD.
OH, OKAY.
[keyboard clacking]
WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR?
WELL, YOU SAID
YOU DIDN'T CARE.
MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
GEEZ.
RED GREEN?
YEAH?
IS THAT REALLY YOU OR IS JUST
ANOTHER HALLUCINATION?
NO.
NO, IT'S NOT A HALLUCINATION.
HALLUCINATIONS DON'T HAVE
PROFESSIONAL TV CAMERAMEN
FOLLOWING THEM AROUND.
THAT'S RIGHT.
[laughter]
WELL, PLEASE EXCUSE THE MESS.
I'VE BEEN CHANGING THINGS AROUND
A LITTLE.
YEAH, YOU HAVE CHANGED IT
A BIT HERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY.
A CHANGE IS AS GOOD AS A
VACATION, AND I HAVEN'T HAD A
VACATION IN 13 YEARS.
AND I FIGURED,
WHY NOT HAVE A CHANGE?
GOSH, 13 YEARS
WITHOUT A VACATION.
BOY, WHAT--THAT'S SOMETHING.
THERE'S A WORD FOR THAT, ISN'T
THERE?
WHAT--WHAT IS IT?
DEDICATION?
SURE.
YEAH, YEAH.
DEDICATION AND LONELINESS.
[sobbing]
OH.
SORRY, MAN.
[sobbing]
I'M SORRY.
NO, THAT'S OKAY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MISS THE
MOST?
WHAT?
TV.
MY FAVORITE TV SHOWS, YOU KNOW.
LAVERNE AND SHIRLEY,
WELCOME BACK, KOTTER;
HAWAII FIVE-0.
SOMETIMES I'LL ACT OUT ALL MY
FAVORITE SCENES, PLAY ALL THE
ROLES, YOU KNOW.
YEAH.
EIGHT IS ENOUGH IS THE
TOUGHEST.
WHAT DO YOU DO TO STOP
YOURSELF FROM GOING CRAZY
UP HERE, GORD?
WELL, I TRY TO KEEP MYSELF
BUSY.
YOU KNOW, I TAKE ALL KINDS OF
CORRESPONDENCE COURSES.
MAKES SENSE.
YEAH.
RIGHT NOW, I'M LEARNING
BRICKLAYING BY MAIL.
YOU KNOW WINSTON CHURCHILL
ENJOYED LAYING BRICKS?
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
YEAH.
AND I'M LEARNING A SECOND
LANGUAGE: BEAVER.
YEAH.
IT'S A GREAT LANGUAGE THAT I'M
PICKING UP FROM BEAVERS DOWN BY
THE RIVER.
OKAY.
YEAH.
AND BEAVER'S EASIER TO LEARN
THAN GERMAN.
WHEREAS GERMAN WILL HAVE THREE
GENDERS, BEAVER ONLY HAS ONE.
SO IT'S A LOT LIKE ENGLISH IN
THAT WAY.
AND A LOT OF THE WORDS ARE
SIMILAR.
THE BEAVER WORD FOR
THUNDERSTORM, FOR INSTANCE,
IS...
[smacking teeth]
THAT IS CLOSE.
YEAH, DO YOU KNOW THERE
ARE OVER 40 DIFFERENT BEAVER
WORDS FOR TREE STUMP?
GOSH, THAT'S--
NO, IT'S A RICH LANGUAGE,
RED, ESPECIALLY WHEN IT COMES TO
TREES AND BARK AND RUTTING.
OR, AS WE SAY,
[smacking teeth]
[laughs]
HUH?
ISN'T THAT GREAT, EH?
WELL, AND THE BEAVERS DON'T
HAVE A WORD FOR TRANSMISSION.
NO, THEY DON'T.
BUT THEY DON'T CARE.
NO, THEY WOULDN'T.
NO.
LIKE, THE BEAVERS HAVE A SAYING.
[smacking teeth]
WHAT DOES THAT TRANSLATE AS?
LET'S CHOP DOWN THIS TREE
AND DRAG IT TO THE RIVER.
OKAY, GORD, I THINK WE'VE
GOT TO GET GOING HERE.
BUT THANKS A LOT FOR YOUR TIME.
WE WANT TO GET YOU BACK
TO YOUR WORK.
>>PLEASE DON'T--PLEASE DON'T GO.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL COME BACK ANOTHER TIME.
OKAY.
HOW ABOUT SATURDAY, THEN?
HUH?
WELL, WE'LL SEE.
YEAH?
IS 4:00 OKAY WITH YOU?
WELL, I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
GET BACK TO YOU ON THAT, GORD.
OKAY?
ALL RIGHT.
JUST SLAP YOUR TAIL ON THE
WATER.
YEAH, I'LL LOOK FORWARD
TO THAT.
BYE.
[spoons clicking]
[upbeat guitar music]
GO DOWN TO THE SWAMP
IN THE SUMMERTIME
COVER YOUR THIGHS
WITH SLUDGE AND SLIME
SLAP THEM TOGETHER
IN 3/4 TIME
NOW YOU'RE DOING
THE MERCY BOG JIG
THERE'S NEVER BEEN A DANCE
EVER THIS BIG
NEVER, NEVER
YOU DON'T NEED LESSONS
JUST JOIN RIGHT IN
BUT IT HELPS IF YOU'RE
PRETTY WELL HAMMERED
OH, UNCLE RED,
THIS IS GREAT.
EXCELLENT.
IT'S MALE BAG TIME.
YOU KNOW, BUT I FOUND THE
LETTERS A TAD REPETITIVE BASED
ON THE DEMOGRAPHICS.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE SKEWING 40-PLUS.
SO I SELECTED SOME LETTERS FROM
SOME TEENAGERS TO GIVE
THE SEGMENT MORE OF A NOW FEEL
TO IT, YOU KNOW?
[laughs]
WE DON'T HAVE TO.
JUST READ THE LETTERS,
HAROLD, WILL YOU?
HERE'S LETTER NUMBER ONE FROM
OUR VIEWERS.
DEAR RED, I'M A 14-YEAR-OLD
GIRL WHO'S NEVER SEEN YOUR SHOW
BECAUSE IT'S, LIKE, TOTALLY
GROSS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF NEW KIDS ON
THE BLOCK?
ARE THEY EXCELLENT OR WHAT?
SERIOUSLY, WHAT'S SO GREAT
ABOUT MATH?
I THINK IT'S, LIKE, TOTALLY
GROSS.
WHO'S THE NERDY GUY WHO SAYS
HE'S YOUR NEPHEW?
THE GUY IS, LIKE, A MAJOR
DOOFUS.
SIGNED, AMANDA.
WHAT'S A DOOFUS, HAROLD?
OH, A DOOFUS IS LIKE A STUD,
LIKE A REALLY COOL-LOOKING GUY.
DOOFUS.
OKAY, WELL, AMANDA, I DON'T
KNOW IF THERE WAS A QUESTION IN
YOUR LETTER.
I CERTAINLY DIDN'T HEAR ONE.
BUT IF THERE WAS,
THE ANSWER IS NO.
THAT'S EXCELLENT.
COMMUNICATING WITH THE YOUNG
PEOPLE OF TODAY.
THAT'S EXCELLENT, UNCLE RED.
LETTER NUMBER TWO FROM ANOTHER
TEENAGE VIEWER.
DEAR RED, WE ENJOY THE RED
GREEN SHOW EVERY WEEK.
WE NEVER MISS AN EPISODE.
MANY TEENAGERS THINK YOU'RE AN
OLD FOGEY, AND THEY MAKE FUN
OF YOU.
BUT WE THINK THE RED GREEN
SHOW IS ENTERTAINING AND
INFORMATIVE ABOUT THINGS THAT
CONCERN YOUNG PEOPLE.
SIGNED, DOUG HOLES, JIM NASIUM,
AND I.P. DAILY.
THAT'S GREAT.
THAT'S EXCELLENT.
THEY'RE LISTENING TO YOU.
YOU'RE GETTING TO THE PEOPLE OF
TODAY.
THAT'S EXCELLENT.
YEAH.
WELL, MAYBE SOMEDAY I'LL BE A
DOOFUS, EH, HAROLD?
I CAN HELP.
[wistful guitar music]
[grunts]
BILL AND I WENT OUT ON THE
LAKE THERE AND SHOT
THIS LITTLE FILM.
REALLY WANTED TO--WANTED TO SHOW
YOU WHAT IT WAS LIKE TO TRY AND
PORTAGE A CANOE.
BUT OF COURSE FIRST, WE HAD TO--
[clearing throat]
FIRST WE HAD TO LAND THE CANOE
BEFORE YOU CAN ACTUALLY DO THE
PORTAGING.
SO LUCKILY BILL HAD THE ROPE.
MAYBE HE SHOULD HAVE
UNTANGLED THAT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HE HAD IN MIND
THERE.
I TRIED TO PADDLE THE DOCK OUT
TO BILL AS HE BRINGING
THE CANOE IN.
GOD, IT WAS A BEAUTIFUL DAY.
OH, WE JUST FINALLY JUST GOT HIM
UP THERE SOMEHOW, I GUESS.
HE TRIED TO PULL HER UP
THIS WAY.
NOW, INTERESTINGLY ENOUGH, WATER
GOES INTO THE BACK OF THE CANOE
AND, BY GOD, SHE GETS KIND OF
HEAVY.
I'VE GOT TO HAND IT TO BILL
BECAUSE YOU REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S IN THAT WATER.
I KNOW THERE'S A LOT OF DEAD
CATTLE IN THERE AND SOME
VEHICLES AND I THINK A COUPLE OF
OLD LODGE MEMBERS ARE DOWN
THERE.
ANYWAY, WE EVENTUALLY
GOT HER UP.
I THOUGHT WE WOULD JUST PULL IT
RIGHT UP ON THE DOCK FROM THE
SIDE, LITTLE DIFFERENT ANGLE,
AND THEN WE'D HAVE TO WORK
WITH--WELL--
MAYBE A LITTLE WIDER DOCK MIGHT
HAVE BEEN--ANYWAY WE DECIDED
BILL WOULD JUST PADDLE THE CANOE
UP TO THE BEACH AREA AND FORGET
ABOUT THE DOCK FOR THE TIME
BEING.
YOU KNOW, THE BOTTOM'S GOT A LOT
OF SPONGY, STICKY KIND OF--
YEAH.
[clears throat]
THAT'S THE KIND OF THING THAT
CAN HAPPEN.
ANYWAY, LUCKILY WE HAVE 700 OR
800 PADDLES.
YEAH, BILL.
I DON'T THINK WE'RE GONNA SEE
THAT ONE AGAIN.
BUT HE GOT HER UP
MUCH FURTHER.
KIND OF AN INTERESTING
TECHNIQUE.
BILL AND I JUST KIND OF GET
FIXING THERE, YOU KNOW.
SO NOW TO GET READY FOR THE
PORTAGE, WHAT YOU'VE GOT TO DO
IS, YOU'VE GOT TO--YOU SEE WHAT
HE'S SAYING THERE IS, YOU'VE GOT
TO PICK THE CANOE UP.
SO I'M GOING TO HELP HIM PICK
THIS THING UP.
TRYING TO GET STUFF IN THERE,
YOU KNOW.
BUT OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
OH.
WELL, HE'S ALL RIGHT.
SO NEXT THING WE DO IS, WE'RE
GOING TO PICK IT UP FROM THE
SIDE RATHER THAN FROM THE END,
AND WE'VE GOT A LOT OF THE CRAP
OUT OF THERE.
OH, BILL.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE JUST NOT
MAKING THE CANOES THE WAY THEY
USED TO.
THEY'RE A LOT STRONGER NOW.
YOUR OLD BIRCH BARK THERE WOULD
JUST, I THINK, COLLAPSE UNDER
THAT KIND OF STRAIN.
BUT IT'S GOT THE ALUMINUM OVER
THE FIBERGLASS.
YOU KNOW, BILL WILL VOUCH FOR
THE STRENGTH OF THESE THINGS.
ANYWAY, YOU KNOW, HE'S GOT A LOT
OF RECUPERATIVE POWERS.
AND WE GET THE CANOE UP ONTO HIS
HEAD THERE AND, OF COURSE,
THE PROBLEM NOW IS, HE CAN'T SEE
WHICH WAY THE WATER IS,
YOU KNOW.
I'M TRYING TO DIRECT HIM,
YOU KNOW, BACK THAT WAY, BILL,
KIND OF DEAL.
IT WAS A LOT OF FUN--
DANGEROUS, DANGEROUS, BUT FUN.
IT IS WINTER.
DOWN THE HILL YOU RACE, FLAT ON
YOUR BACK, SCREAMING, EYES
CLOSED, ON A TOBOGGAN.
UP THE HILL YOU GO, FLAT ON YOUR
BACK, SCREAMING, EYES CLOSED,
ON A STRETCHER.
IN THIS PART OF THE SHOW, I GIVE
HAROLD A CHANCE TO TALK ABOUT
THE THINGS THAT ARE BOTHERING
YOUNG PEOPLE BECAUSE THEY SEEM
TO TRUST HIM OR AT LEAST NOT
FEEL THREATENED BY HIM.
HAROLD?
WHAT?
OH, YEAH, OKAY.
[laughs]
OKAY, SEX EDUCATION.
[moos]
YOU MIGHT WANT TO GET THE KIDS
OUT OF THE ROOM OR, LIKE, YOU
KNOW, MAKE CLEARING YOUR THROAT
NOISES OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
ASK THEM HOW SCHOOL WENT.
GET THEM DISTRACTED, RIGHT?
OKAY?
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
SEX EDUCATION.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE ALL MODERN
ABOUT IT AND STUFF, BECAUSE
IT'S, LIKE, THE '90s, RIGHT?
YEAH, IT IS.
OKAY.
SO IN SCHOOL, RIGHT?
THEY TEACH US, LIKE,
DON'T BE ASHAMED.
DON'T BE EMBARRASSED BY IT
OR NOTHING.
YOU KNOW, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S NATURAL.
BUT YET OUR PARENTS WON'T EVEN
TALK ABOUT IT WITH US,
AND WE KNOW THEY DO.
WE KNOW BECAUSE, LIKE, EVERY
TIME THEY HAVE AN ANNIVERSARY,
THEY SEND THE KIDS TO THE MOVIES
FOR THE NIGHT.
THEY DON'T EVER DO THAT, RIGHT?
SO WE KNOW.
WE KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
WE KNOW.
WE DO.
AND THEY TEAR ALL THE GOOD
ARTICLES OUT OF THE READER'S
DIGEST BEFORE WE GET A CHANCE
TO READ THEM.
REAL GOOD ONE LIKE
I WAS JOE'S PROSTATE.
THAT'S A GOOD ONE TOO.
SO MY POINT IS, I JUST WANT TO
SAY THAT I'M GLAD I'M NOT LIKE
ADULTS AND HAVE HANG-UPS ABOUT,
WELL--WELL, YOU KNOW.
[laughs]
DON'T GO AWAY.
I CAN'T WAIT TO FINISH MY STORY
ABOUT THE OUTBOARD MOTOR.
I'LL MAKE SURE
THAT HE HAS TO.
[singing] STAYING ALIVE
[singing] OOH, OOH, OOH, OOH
WELL, THIS IS CERTAINLY ONE
OF MY FAVORITE ASPECTS OF BEING
A HUMAN BEING, AND THAT IS, YOU
KNOW, NOT TO BE QUITE SO
SELFISH AND NOT TO JUST THINK OF
YOURSELF AND SPENDING TIME WITH
PEOPLE LIKE YOURSELF IF THERE
HAPPEN TO BE ANY
BUT TO ACTUALLY TAKE SOME TIME
AND SPEND SOME OF YOUR VALUABLE
TIME WITH SOME OF THE YOUNG
PEOPLE, SOME OF THE GREAT, GREAT
YOUNG PEOPLE OF THIS COUNTRY.
MAYBE YOU HAVE A NEPHEW--
HOPEFULLY NOT LIKE HAROLD--
MAYBE THERE'S A KID DOWN
THE STREET OR, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE JUST YOU GET INVOLVED
WITH THE BIG BROTHERS
OR WHATEVER OR MAYBE YOU JUST,
YOU KNOW, HAD THE BAD LUCK
TO HAVE YOUR OWN KIDS.
WHATEVER IT IS.
I HAVE MY FRIEND HERE--
DAVID.
AND DAVID AND I ARE GONNA DO
SOMETHING TOGETHER TODAY
JUST, YOU KNOW, BUDS.
WE CALL IT BUDS, HUH?
HUH?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO
TODAY, DAVID?
WE'RE GONNA PLAY A GAME OF
CROQUET.
YOU KNOW WHAT CROQUET IS?
NO, NOT REALLY.
OH, WELL, NOW, THIS IS A
THRILL FOR ME BECAUSE NOT ONLY
AM I SPENDING SOME TIME, I'M
TEACHING HIM A NEW TYPE OF SPORT
THAT OBVIOUSLY DAVID OTHERWISE
WOULD NEVER BE EXPOSED TO.
DAVID, THE GAME OF CROQUET IS,
YOU PUT THESE LITTLE METAL HOOPS
INTO THE LAWN AND THEN YOU HAVE
MALLETS AND YOU KNOCK BALLS
THROUGH THE HOOPS.
IT'S AN AWFUL LOT OF FUN, AND
YOU CAN HIT THE OTHER PERSON'S
BALL, AND YOU CAN JUST KNOCK THE
LIVING BEJEEBERS OUT OF IT AND
SMASH IT TO BITS IF YOU WANT,
YOU KNOW.
SOUNDS LIKE YOUR KIND OF GAME.
YOU KNOW, GOLLY, THE PROBLEM
WE'RE GONNA HAVE HERE, DAVE, IS,
I BELIEVE THIS GRASS MAY JUST BE
A TAD LONG FOR A REAL GOOD GAME
OF CROQUET.
AND IF WE'RE GONNA PLAY CROQUET,
WE MIGHT AS WELL PLAY A GOOD
ROUND OF CROQUET, RIGHT?
YEAH.
SO YOU KNOW WHAT WE NEED?
WHAT?
ONE OF THESE.
WATCH YOUR FEET THERE.
YOU WANT TO PUSH IT ALONG WHILE
I'M DOING THIS, AND WE'LL GET
THE LAWN CUT?
[lawn mower whirring]
ALL RIGHT, THERE YOU GO.
SO THE BEAUTY OF IT IS,
YOU'RE SPENDING TIME WITH
A YOUNG PERSON.
THEY'RE LEARNING
A WHOLE NEW GAME.
OH, GOD.
HE'S GONNA BE ALL DAY
DOING THAT.
I'M THINKING I GOT TO GET A NEW
OUTBOARD MOTOR.
THIS ONE KIND OF SMELLS.
IS THAT OIL?
IS THAT OIL I SMELL IN THAT?
DON'T ASK ME, RED.
I LOST MY SENSE OF SMELL FOR OIL
WHEN I WORKED ON THAT
OFFSHORE RIG.
YOU WORKED ON ONE OF THEM
OIL RIGS?
BOY, THOSE THINGS ARE HUGE,
AREN'T THEY?
8 1/2 TRILLION TONS.
REALLY?
TRILLION?
AND WE WEREN'T DRILLING
FOR OIL.
WE WERE DRILLING FOR GUNPOWDER.
WELL, THAT'D BE A LITTLE
DANGEROUS, WOULDN'T IT?
DRILLING FOR GUNPOWDER?
WELL, THE WATER HELPS, AND
IT'S UNDER A LOT OF PRESSURE.
THIS WAS A DEEP PART
OF THE OCEAN.
I'D SAY MAYBE, OH, 20,000
LEAGUES UNDER THE SEA.
THAT'S DEEP.
WELL, NEVER FIGURE IT OUT.
A LEAGUE IS OVER SIX FEET.
NO, THAT'S A FATHOM.
[chuckles]
RED, A LEAGUE IS
A METRIC FATHOM.
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT, HAP?
I NEVER HEARD THAT BEFORE.
ANYWAY, ONE DAY I WAS RUNNING
THE DRILL.
WE HAD MAYBE 21,000 LEAGUES OF
PIPE GOING STRAIGHT DOWN, AND I
HIT THE MOTHER LODE, PURE
GUNPOWDER.
AND SHE BLEW.
BOOM.
NOT COMPLETELY, BUT BIG.
THAT PIPE BLEW STRAIGHT UP.
21,000 LEAGUES OF PIPE SHOT
STRAIGHT UP AND OUT INTO SPACE.
TRAVELING EVEN 15 TIMES THE
SPEED OF SOUND, IT TOOK 9
MINUTES FOR THE END OF THAT PIPE
TO PASS BY ME.
NOISY?
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE THE RACKET.
AFTER THAT, GUNPOWDER MINING WAS
DECLARED UNSAFE.
WHERE'D THE PIPELINE
COME DOWN?
MARS.
NOTHING PERSONAL, HAP, BUT
I'M HAVING A REAL PROBLEM
BELIEVING THIS STORY.
DOESN'T BOTHER ME IF YOU
BELIEVE IT OR YOU DON'T.
YOU WEREN'T THERE.
NO, BUT AT LEAST I'M WILLING
TO ADMIT IT.
SO AS I WAS SAYING, WE GOT THE
OUTBOARD MOTOR ALL MOUNTED ON
THERE, AND WE GOT THE BOAT ALL
GASSED UP AND EVERYTHING,
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT WAS STILL TOO
HEAVY AT THE BACK END,
SO WE PUT MOOSE THOMPSON
IN THERE.
BUT THEN ALL THE WEIGHT WAS UP
AT THE FRONT, AS IT IS
ON MOOSE TOO.
SO IT TURNED OUT THAT BUSTER
HATFIELD HAD TO BE
OUR TEST PILOT.
SO HE GOT IN THERE, AND WE KIND
OF POINTED THE BOAT OUT TOWARDS
THE CENTER OF THE LAKE.
IT TOOK US A WHILE TO GET IT
GOING, THOUGH, BECAUSE A 427 V8
IS NOT ALL THAT EASY TO
PULL-START.
BUT WE DID GET HER GOING.
AND BUSTER HIT THE THROTTLE,
AND IT BROKE OFF RIGHT IN HIS
HAND, YOU KNOW.
BUT NOT BEFORE IT HAD JAMMED
WIDE OPEN.
SO IT WAS, I GUESS, ABOUT
THREE SECONDS THAT MOTOR WAS
DOING 80 MILES AN HOUR.
UNFORTUNATELY, THE BOAT WAS ONLY
DOING 75.
SO SHE BROKE OFF THROUGH THE
TRANSOM AND STARTED TO WORK HER
WAY UP, YOU KNOW, THROUGH THE
BOAT, UP OVER THE SEATS, AND IN
BETWEEN BUSTER'S LEGS AND SO ON.
AND, GOLLY, IT WAS REALLY
SOMETHING.
IT TURNED OUT, YOU KNOW,
LUCKILY, THAT BUSTER'D ONLY
DAMAGED HIS PRIDE, OR I SHOULD
SAY HIS PRIDE AND JOY.
HE TRIED TO JUMP OVER
THE SPINNING BLADES, AND, GOLLY,
HE ONLY MISSED BY A HAIR.
BUT ANYWAY, IF MY WIFE IS
WATCHING, I'LL BE COMING HOME.
BUT I THINK I'M GONNA STAY UP
AND READ A LITTLE BIT TONIGHT,
SO MAYBE YOU COULD LEAVE THE
COMIC SECTION ON THE FRIDGE.
ANYWAY, THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR
TUNING US IN.
AND ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND...
[sniffs]
HAROLD.
HAROLD AND THE REST OF THE
GANG UP HERE AT THE LODGE, UNTIL
NEXT TIME AROUND, KEEP YOUR
STICK ON THE ICE.
SORRY, HAROLD.
[applause]