IF YOU’RE LIKE ME, YOU
PROBABLY HAVE
A DRAWER FULL OF ODD-SOCKS
SOMEWHERE
AND YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO WITH THEM.
OH, SURE, YOU MAY HAVE A
PEA-HEAD LIKE OLD MAN SEDGWICK,
AND YOU CAN USE
'EM AS TOQUES.
BUT FOR THE REST OF US
MAY I HUMBLY SUGGEST
A SOCK TOOL BELT.
IT'S SO SIMPLE
IT'S BREATHTAKING.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
HAD KIND OF A LIFE CHANGING
EXPERIENCE LAST WEEK.
BERNICE AND I WENT INTO
TOWN TO GET SOME NAILS,
AND I JUST STARTED
LOSIN' IT.
I STARTED YELLIN' AT EVERY
OTHER CAR ON THE ROAD,
AND THAT WAS WHEN I WAS
WALKIN' DOWN THE SIDEWALK.
AND THEN IN THE HARDWARE STORE,
I'M GIVING THE CLERK GRIEF
BECAUSE HE'S FORCIN' ME
TO BUY A WHOLE BOX OF NAILS
WHEN I ONLY NEED THREE.
I GO OUT IN THE PARKING LOT,
I START HASSLING SOME
SQUEEGEE KID.
YOU KNOW, I GOT REAL UPSET
THAT HE'S POINTING OUT
DIRT ON MY WINDSHIELD,
WHEN HE HASN'T HAD
A BATH SINCE '93.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
I'M GOIN' CRAZY.
THEN I GET INTO THE VAN,
AND I PEEL RUBBER RIGHT
OUTTA THE PARKING LOT.
I'M JUST -- I'M BLOWIN'
A GASKET HERE,
AND BERNICE SAYS,
"SETTLE DOWN.
SETTLE DOWN."
SHE GIVES ME THIS CARD
TO HELP PEOPLE LIKE ME
THAT HAVE TO IMPROVE
THEIR BEHAVIOUR.
KINDA MAKE YOU SETTLE DOWN,
BE NICER, YOU KNOW.
THIS HELPS YOU.
YOU LOOK AT THE
TIPS ON HERE.
HELPIN' ME BE A "KINDER,
GENTLER, MORE FORGIVING
"AND MORE HELPFUL FRIEND
TO ALL THAT I MEET."
SEE, THE IDEA IS
YOU HELP PEOPLE OUT.
YOU BE KIND TO PEOPLE,
AND THEN YOU RECEIVE "AN
ABUNDANCE OF REWARDS,
"BOTH SPIRITUAL AND PHYSICAL."
RIGHT HERE
ON THE CARD.
HEY, RED.
YEAH.
FINISHED WITH THE POSSUM VAN.
THANKS FOR LENDIN' IT TO ME.
WELL, UH,
NO PROBLEM, WINSTON.
"IF I CAN HELP YOU,
I'M HAPPY TO DO THAT."
OKAY.
I GOTTA TELL YOU, I CAN'T
BELIEVE HOW MUCH THAT VAN HOLDS.
YOU KNOW I GOT EVERY ONE OF MY
SEWAGE PUMPS INSIDE OF IT?
"I'M GLAD IT WAS
TO YOUR LIKING."
ANYWAY, I'D SUGGEST AIRING
IT OUT FOR THE NEXT
COUPLE OF DAYS.
THERE WAS
SOME SPILLAGE.
OH, MAN.
"TREASURE YOUR --"
YOU DIDN'T LEAVE ANY
TREASURES IN THERE --
NO, NO.
BUT HERE'S 20 BUCKS.
THANKS FOR
THE TROUBLE.
WELL, THERE'S A PHYSICAL
AND SPIRITUAL REWARD
RIGHT THERE.
Mr. GREEN,
CAN I BORROW THE VAN
TILL TOMORROW?
OH, SURE
YOU CAN, MIKE.
"YOU DON'T EVEN
HAVE TO ASK."
WELL, YES, I DO.
IT SOUNDS BETTER IN COURT.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE YOU GO.
UH, YOU MIGHT
WANNA DRIVE WITH THE
WINDOWS OPEN FOR AWHILE.
OKAY.
I JUST RETURNED
THE VAN TODAY.
I BORROWED IT
YESTERDAY.
THAT'S AN
INTERESTING ANECDOTE.
I GAVE RED 20 BUCKS
TO SHOW MY APPRECIATION.
WELL, I DON'T APPRECIATE
THINGS AS MUCH AS YOU.
YOU KNOW, MIKE,
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THAT.
I'M HAPPY TO
HELP YOU OUT,
AND YOU DON'T HAVE
TO PAY ME ANYTHING.
THE LEAST
YOU COULD DO IS
PAY FOR THE GAS.
OKAY, I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT I'LL DO,
I'LL FILL THE GAS TANK
UP BEFORE I RETURN IT.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
SOUNDS GOOD
TO ME.
SEEMS FAIR.
DEAL?
YEAH.
OKAY.
WELL, IT'S TIME TO PLAY THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
AND TODAY WE'RE ON LOCATION
IN RANGER GORD'S FIRE
WATCHTOWER.
AND RANGER GORD, HE'S GOING
TO BE PLAYING FOR THE
GRAND PRIZE OF
THE POSSUM CALENDAR GIRL.
CAN I
SEE THAT?
YEAH, OF COURSE.
I'M GLAD YOU LIKE
THE PRIZE, GORD,
BUT ARE YOU GONNA BE ABLE TO
CONCENTRATE ON THE GAME?
YOU GONNA BE ALL RIGHT
WITH THE GAME, GORD?
GORD,
THE GAME.
WHAT?
WE GOTTA PLAY THE GAME.
GOTTA A GAME TO PLAY.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, SURE.
WHAT ARE THESE
CALLED AGAIN?
WHAT ARE
WHAT CALLED?
THESE BEAUTIFUL
THINGS.
WHAT?
THIS AND THIS
AND THIS.
WHAT, THE WOMEN?
WOMEN!
YES.
CAN I TAKE THE CALENDAR BACK,
AND WE CAN JUST GET ON WITH --
GIMME THE --
GIMME THE CALENDAR.
GONNA GIVE ME
A PAPER CUT.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET RANGER GORD TO SAY
THE FOLLOWING WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
HAROLD.
GO!
ALL RIGHT, GORD,
THE BODY RETAINS
90% OF THIS.
UH, LIGHTENING.
NO.
OKAY, THIS IS
SOMETHING YOU DRINK.
OH, UH,
VINEGAR AND SAP.
OKAY, NO.
THAT'S MY FAULT.
UM, NOT YOU,
THIS IS SOMETHING
NORMAL PEOPLE DRINK.
OH, BEER.
YUP, OKAY.
BUT THIS HAS
NO TASTE TO IT.
OH,
AMERICAN BEER?
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
ALMOST OUTTA TIME,
UNCLE RED.
ALL RIGHT, GORD,
WHAT IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT WEAPON WHEN
YOU'RE FIGHTING A FOREST FIRE?
YES, SPOTTING IT
BEFORE IT SPREADS.
OKAY, I KNOW THAT.
YOU THINK I DIDN'T KNOW THAT!
I WAS TIRED,
ALL RIGHT?
I HADN'T SLEPT
ALL WINTER.
I DOZED OFF.
WAKE UP,
NEXT THING I KNOW,
50 SQUARE MILES
ON FIRE.
YOU THINK I MEANT TO
LEAVE THE HOT PLATE ON?
WELL, LET ME TELL YOU
SOMETHING, ALL RIGHT.
I PUT THAT ALL
BEHIND ME NOW!
ALL RIGHT?
THAT IS WATER
UNDER THE BRIDGE!
[ BELL RINGING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ HAROLD MAKING BEEPING SOUND ]
HEY, HAROLD.
HOW'S IT GOIN', HUH?
OH,
UNCLE RED, HI.
IT'S GOIN' --
HEY, YOU'RE ALL
DRESSED UP.
LOOKS SHARP.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YOU GOIN'
TO COURT?
OH, NO, NO, HAROLD.
NO, NO, NO.
BIG DAY TODAY, HUH?
WASN'T THERE KINDA
A SPECIAL EVENT?
MAYBE, LET'S SEE,
ABOUT 19 YEARS AGO, EH?
I WONDER WHAT THAT
EVENT COULD BE, HUH?
MY NINTH
BIRTHDAY.
YOU MEAN YOU'RE OLDER
THAN 19, HAROLD?
YOU'RE 19 PLUS NINE?
TWENTY-EIGHT.
TWENTY-EIGHT!
TWENTY-EIGHT, WOW.
YOU MEAN IT WAS
28 YEARS AGO TODAY
I WENT OVER TO THE HOSPITAL TO
HELP YOUR PARENTS THROUGH
THE DISAPPOINTMENT?
THEY WERE HAPPY
TO HAVE ME.
WELL, THEY DIDN'T
HAVE ANY MORE.
WHAT DOES THAT
TELL YOU, HAROLD?
I KNOW YOU'RE TEASING.
I APPRECIATE
IT TOO.
I REALLY APPRECIATE YOU
GETTING DRESSED UP
BECAUSE WHEN YOU SHOW UP
IN LODGE WEAR,
I GET VERY
EMBARRASSED.
OH, I ALMOST
FORGOT, HAROLD.
GOT A GIFT FOR YOU.
GIFT?
THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
I LOVE GIFTS WHEN
THEY'RE FOR ME.
IT'S MY VIDEO EFFECTS
SWITCHER FROM THE SHOW.
I DO NOT KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
DON'T SAY ANYTHING, HAROLD.
HIT THE AUDIO BUTTON.
[ MUSIC INTRO ]
WAIT TILL YOU
HEAR THIS, HAROLD.
OH, HA -- HA -- HA --
NO, NO, NO.
[ EVERYONE SINGING OUT OF TUNE ]
SECURITY.
DESK FOUR,
SECURITY, PLEASE!
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYIN'.
JOININ' US TODAY
IS DALTON HUMPHREY.
WHAT DO YOU GOT
FOR US, DALTON?
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT ELECTRONICS, RED?
OH, SURE, WITH THE
TRANSISTORS AND THE DIALS
AND THE PRINTED CIRCUIT BOARDS
WITH THE MICROCHIPS THERE.
YEP.
YEAH, I DON'T EITHER.
OH, COME ON.
GIVE ME A CHANCE.
I MIGHT FLUKE ONE,
YOU KNOW.
YEAH, WELL, OKAY.
I BROUGHT IN MY
REMOTE CONTROL.
NO, DON'T TAKE IT OUTTA
THE PAIL THERE, RED!
NO, DON'T DO THAT.
HOW COME?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
IT WON'T TURN OFF.
IT'S SENDIN' OUT A
SIGNAL ALL THE TIME.
IT'S GOT ALL THE GARAGE DOORS IN
THE NEIGHBOURHOOD OPENING,
TURNING ALL THE
MICROWAVE OVENS ON.
THE GUY ACROSS THE STREET
HAS GOT A PACEMAKER.
HAVEN'T SEEN HIM
IN A COUPLE OF DAYS.
AS LONG AS IT STAYS
IN THE METAL PAIL,
IT'S SAFE.
WHAT I'LL DO, JUST TAKE
THE BATTERIES OUTTA HER.
THAT'LL SHUT THE
WHOLE UNIT DOWN.
HOW'D THIS
HAPPEN ANYWAY?
WELL, YOU KNOW, I WAS IN THE
LIVING ROOM WATCHING TV,
AND ANN MARIE WAS IN
THE KITCHEN MAKING DINNER,
AND I WAS WATCHIN'
MASTERPIECE THEATRE
AND THE MONSTER TRUCK PULL
AND THE THREE BALL GAMES
AND THE W.W.F.
JUST --
YEAH, YOU HAD THAT REMOTE
HUMMIN', DID YOU, DALTON?
BOY, I WAS WORKIN'
THAT BABY.
TILL ANN MARIE YELLED,
"PICK ONE AND WATCH IT!"
BOY, DO I KNOW
THAT ONE.
AH, GEEZ.
WHAT DID YOU SAY TO THAT?
WELL, NOW, THIS IS WHERE THE
DISCREPANCY COMES IN, RED,
BECAUSE I BELIEVE
THAT I SAID,
"OKAY, SORRY, HONEY."
BUT, APPARENTLY,
WHAT SHE HEARD WAS,
"MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS."
I SEE.
YEAH.
AND THAT'S WHEN SHE CAME IN
AND GRABBED THE REMOTE
AND TOOK IT.
SEEMS TO HAVE A FAIR
BIT OF GOO ON HERE.
YEAH, THAT'S ANN MARIE'S
SPECIAL CLAM CHOWDER.
OH, YEAH.
YOU THINK YOU CAN
FIX THAT, RED?
NO, YOU KNOW,
I THINK MAYBE YOU SHOULD
GET ANNE MARIE TO CHANGE THE
CHANNELS FOR YOU FROM NOW ON.
I'M GUESSIN'
AT THIS POINT,
SHE'S A LITTLE REMOTE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
HEY, HEY, HEY.
DON'T TELL HER
I SAID THAT.
I LAUGHED.
YOU KNOW,
WHEN I WAS A KID,
WE ATE CHOCOLATE BARS,
CANDY, BUBBLE GUM,
THAT KIND OF THING.
WHEN YOU ATE THAT STUFF, YOU
KNEW IT WAS BAD FOR YOU.
THAT WAS MOST OF THE APPEAL.
WELL, NOW THEY'RE
MAKING CANDY LIKE THIS.
OUT OF FRUIT.
FRUIT.
FRUIT ISN'T
BAD FOR YOU.
WHERE'S THE
FUN IN THAT?
BUT THERE IS SOMETHING
INTERESTING HERE.
THE WAY THEY MAKE THIS STUFF.
I FIGURE ALL THEY DO IS SQUISH
THE LIVING DAYLIGHTS
OUTTA FRUIT
AND TURN IT INTO
A VINYL-LIKE SHEET.
VERY SIMILAR
TO PREHISTORIC TIMES,
WHERE THE DINOSAURS WOULD SIT
ON COAL WITH SO MUCH PRESSURE
THEY'D TURN
IT INTO DIAMONDS.
DINOSAURS ACTUALLY HAD A
FASCINATION WITH DIAMONDS,
WHICH IS WHY SO MANY OLD PEOPLE
WEAR ALL THE JEWELLERY.
SO IT'S ONLY LOGICAL THAT IF I
COULD SQUISH SOME FRUIT,
LIKE, SAY, THESE APPLES,
WITH ENOUGH FORCE,
I COULD PAVE
MY DRIVEWAY.
WELL, THEY TELL ME IT
TAKES ABOUT A MILLION
TONS OF PRESSURE
TO TURN COAL
INTO DIAMONDS.
I HAVEN'T ACTUALLY EXPERIENCED
THAT MUCH PRESSURE
SINCE I MET MY
WIFE'S PARENTS.
BUT I DO HAVE
AN OIL DRUM HERE.
IN FACT, I'VE GOT
FIVE OF THEM.
THEY'RE
45 GALLONS EACH.
I FILL THEM UP WITH WATER.
I FIGURE THAT'S
500 POUNDS A PIECE,
BUT THERE'S FIVE OF 'EM.
AND THEN, OF COURSE,
THE WEIGHT IS CONCENTRATED
ON THE SMALL PART OF THE EDGE
THAT TOUCHES THE GROUND.
SO YOU TAKE
THE TOTAL WEIGHT,
DIVIDE IT BY
THE COSINE OF THE TANGENT...
WELL, YOU DO THE MATH.
I HAVE NO IDEA.
NOW, I NEEDED A HANDLE TO
ATTACH THIS OIL DRUM TO
THE FRONT BUMPER,
SO I JUST RIPPED
ONE OFF MY LAWN MOWER
AND SPREAD IT
OUT A LITTLE BIT.
IT MEANS I CAN'T
CUT THE LAWN NOW,
BUT I'LL GET OVER IT.
THEN I JUST DUCT TAPED THE WHOLE
UNIT TO THE FRONT BUMPER.
ACTUALLY, THAT WAS
THE HARD PART.
THE OTHER OIL DRUMS WERE
A LOT EASIER TO MOUNT.
AND I'VE ALREADY FILLED
THEM UP WITH WATER,
SO WE'RE PRETTY
WELL READY TO GO.
YOU WANNA USE
LOW GEAR ON THIS
BECAUSE YOU'VE ADDED ABOUT
SEVEN TONS TO THE GROSS
VEHICLE WEIGHT.
ACTUALLY, WITH THAT
MUCH WEIGHT,
YOU CAN TURN ANY
FRUIT INTO ASPHALT.
BANANAS MIGHT BE, YOU KNOW,
A LITTLE SLIPPERY,
BUT WITH THE PEACHES
YOU'RE GONNA GET KIND
OF A COBBLESTONE EFFECT.
I DECIDED TO
GO WITH APPLES
BECAUSE I HAVE APPLES.
AND IN A MINUTE, I'M GONNA TURN
THEM INTO APPLESAUCE YOU
CAN DRIVE ON.
SO REMEMBER THAT IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
AND NOW, AS THE BRITISH USED
TO SAY WHEN THEY RODE
INTO SCOTLAND,
LET'S GO CRUSH
SOME MACINTOSHES.
I WANNA TALK TO YOU
OLDER GUYS OUT THERE.
YOU KNOW,
AS THE YEARS GO BY,
YOU END UP LOOKIN'
INTO THE BATHROOM MIRROR
LIKE YOU'RE LOOKIN' UNDER
THE HOOD OF A USED CAR.
YOU SEE A LOT OF
OLD PARTS, LOOSE JOINTS,
AND A TIRED POWER PLANT THAT
USES UP AN AWFUL LOT OF FUEL
FOR WHAT YOU GET
OUT OF IT.
NOW, MOST GUYS JUST PUT LOWER
WATT BULBS INTO THE BATHROOM,
BUT SOME GUYS ARE
ACTUALLY GOING OUT
AND GETTING A FACELIFT.
PLEASE, PLEASE,
THINK TWICE ABOUT THAT.
YOU'RE ONLY
FOOLIN' YOURSELF.
NO MATTER HOW MANY WRINKLES YOU
TAKE OUT OF THE BODY WORK,
YOU WON'T STOP THE
TRANSMISSION FROM SLIPPING,
PLUS YOU ARE MESSIN'
WITH A GOOD THING.
YOU SEE, THE WORLD DOES NOT
EXPECT MUCH FROM US
MIDDLE AGED GUYS.
AS LONG AS WE CAN
SIT UP AT THE TABLE,
TAKE OUT THE GARBAGE,
MAYBE SHOW UP AT WORK
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE,
WE PRETTY MUCH
CARRY OUR OWN WEIGHT.
ONCE YOU START LOOKIN' 25,
PEOPLE ARE GONNA EXPECT
THINGS FROM YOU THAT
YOU CAN'T DELIVER;
THINGS LIKE
ENERGY, AMBITION
OR ANY KIND OF
A CLUE ABOUT ANYTHING.
SO I SAY JUST LET THE WRINKLES
AND THE JOWLS AND THE
EYE BAGS COME
BECAUSE WHEN YOU LOOK
LIKE A BASSET HOUND,
EVERYBODY'LL LEAVE
YOU ALONE.
AND LET'S BE HONEST.
THAT'S ALL WE
REALLY WANT.
IF YOU WANNA LOOK YOUNGER,
TRY SMILING.
IT'S CHEAP AND IT'LL LIFT A LOT
MORE THAN YOUR FACE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLIN'
FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, I'M NOT DOIN' TOO BAD ON
THE BEHAVIOR MODIFICATION PLAN.
I HAD THE ONE SLIP UP.
THE WAITRESS MADE A
MISTAKE AND BROUGHT ME
A WHEATGERM SHAKE
AND A TOFU BURGER,
AND, UH, IT SOMEHOW
GOT AIRBORNE.
BUT I DID CLEAN IT UP
AS BEST I COULD.
THERE'S ONLY SO MUCH YOU CAN
DO WITH THAT GRASS CLOTH
WALLPAPER, YOU KNOW.
Mr. GREEN,
THANKS FOR
THE VAN.
OH, NO PROBLEM.
I LEFT IT PARKED
OUT BACK.
OH, HERE'S AN EXTRA
TEN BUCKS FOR YOUR TROUBLE.
WELL,
THANKS, MIKE,
BUT I THOUGHT YOU WERE
JUST GONNA FILL IT UP
WITH GAS INSTEAD.
OH, I FILLED UP
THE GAS TANK.
YEAH, SURE.
THAT'S A BONUS.
AND THE REWARDS
JUST KEEP ON COMIN'.
SO WHAT'D YOU PUT IN 'ER,
REGULAR OR HI-TEST?
I'M NOT SURE.
WHATEVER WINSTON
USES IN HIS TRUCK.
Mr. GREEN, DO YOU SUPPOSE
I COULD BORROW THE VAN
AGAIN TONIGHT?
SAME DEAL.
CASH PLUS.
SURE.
NO PROBLEM.
GREAT.
OKAY.
OH, I GOTTA GO.
WHAT'S
HIS PROBLEM?
HE'S GOT GAS.
SO HOW MUCH OF THE PRIZE
MONEY DID HE GIVE YOU?
WHAT PRIZE MONEY?
THE 100 BUCKS
HE WON LAST NIGHT
DRIVING YOUR VAN IN THE
DEMOLITION DERBY.
WHAT!
OH, YEAH.
THERE'S ANOTHER
ONE TONIGHT.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I'M ENTERING THE
SEPTIC TRUCK INTO IT.
AND THE YOU-KNOW-WHAT'S
GONNA FLY.
I GOTTA STOP HIM!
MIKE!
WAIT.
COME ON.
Red:
HAD SOME HEAVY PIPE
AND PROPANE TANKS AND WHATNOT
TO GET OUT OF THE OF
THE WAREHOUSE.
IT WAS UP ON THE SECOND FLOOR
IN TOWN THERE.
SO WALTER WAS GONNA HELP ME.
IT WAS VERY HEAVY,
VERY HEAVY.
THE CAST-IRON, UH,
THE CAST-IRON PIPE --
WELL, I CAN'T PICK 'EM UP.
ONCE I GET 'EM UP --
OKAY, YOU HAND IT TO ME.
I'LL BE ALL RIGHT NOW.
OH, THAT'S --
OH, THAT'S  --
LOT OF WEIGHT TO THAT.
WHY DON'T I SET THAT
DOWN OF THE SHELF
AND PUT ON MY TRUSS HERE.
OH!
ALL RIGHT, NO.
WE NEED A BETTER PLAN.
HERE'S A WAY --
HERE'S A WAY TO USE YOUR BRAI
AND ALSO TEACH THE
KIDS ABOUT PHYSICS.
C'MON, WALTER.
C'MON.
I GOT A BETTER --
JUST LEAVE IT, WALTER.
WALTER, LEAVE IT.
LEAVE IT.
C'MON.
BETTER IDEA.
WE'RE UP ON THE SECOND FLOOR,
AND THAT'S THE TRUCK I
WANNA PUT 'ER IN.
SO WE GOT A PULLEY --
SEE WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WE GOT A PULLEY,
WE GOT A CRATE,
AND WE GOT A HUNK OF ROPE.
THIS IS JUST USIN' YOUR BRAIN
INSTEAD OF YOUR BRAWN.
SO GET WALTER --
WALTER, YOU GO DOWN THERE,
AND I'LL TOSS YOU
DOWN THE ROPE,
AND THE CRATE,
WE'LL BRING THE CRATE UP.
WE'LL PUT THE STUFF
IN THE CRATE,
AND TAKE HER
DOWN THAT WAY.
MAKE THAT A GOOD
KNOT THERE, WALTER,
AND HERE COMES THE ROPE.
SEE, KIDS, THIS IS
THE WHOLE THING.
NEWTON'S -- NEWTON'S LAW THAT
NOTHING'S WORTH A FIG.
AND HAUL THAT UP THERE.
WALTER'S VERY, VERY STRONG.
LOT OF UPPER BODY STRENGTH.
I HAVE MORE OF THE LOWER BODY
STRENGTH FROM SITTING, I THINK
OKAY, I'LL PULL THAT IN THERE
AND YOU JUST STAY CALM FOR
A MINUTE, WALTER.
I'LL LOAD UP THE STUFF,
PROPANE TANKS IN THERE.
BOY, THOSE ARE HEAVY UNITS.
IT'S THE CAST-IRON PIPES THAT
REALLY HAVE THE WEIGHT TO THEM
BY GOLLY.
SO I'M GETTIN' THEM IN THERE.
ALL RIGHT, I THINK YOU GOT A
PRETTY GOOD LOAD.
YOU THINK YOU CAN
HAUL THAT, WALTER?
YEAH, SHOULD BE ALL RIGHT.
SHOULD BE FINE.
BOY, I HOPE HE WEIGHS ENOUGH.
OH, NO.
OH!
APPARENTLY NOT.
AND I'VE JAMMED HIS
FINGERS UP INTO THE --
NOW, THE PROBLEM IS THERE'S TO
MUCH WEIGHT IN THE CRATE,
SO I TAKE THE WEIGHT
OUT OF THE CRATE...
THIS SHOULD HELP.
MAYBE ONE MORE.
ONE MORE SHOULD DO IT.
JUST KIND OF EASE --
SHE'S GETTIN' LIGHTER.
NO, ONE MORE, I GUESS.
THAT SHOULD DO IT.
NO, OKAY, ONE MORE.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, THAT'S
TOO MUCH MAYBE.
OH, OH, OH, OH!
OKAY, UH --
OKAY, I TOOK TOO MUCH
WEIGHT OUT OF THAT.
LET'S GET THE
REST OF THE STUFF.
OH, HERE IT COMES.
HERE WE GO.
OKAY, NOW,
TELL ME, WALTER,
WASN'T THAT EASIER?
I THOUGHT SO.
BACK IN THE 1930s,
MULTIPLE BIRTHS WERE RARE.
EVERYBODY KNEW ABOUT
THE DIONNE QUINTUPLETS
AND THE CASH COW
THAT HAD BEEN,
SO IT WAS NO SURPRISE WHEN OUR
LOCAL TOWN COUNCIL
TRIED TO DRUM UP INTEREST IN THE
BIRTH OF THE MANNING TRIPLETS.
BORN TO CARLOTTA AND MAX MANNING
ON AUGUST 24, 1932,
WAS A SET OF TRIPLETS,
THE MANNING TRIPLETS.
ALL IDENTICAL,
ESPECIALLY IN LOOKS.
THEY WERE ALL BOYS.
THEY WERE NAMED
SNAP, CRACKLE, AND POP.
THAT WAS THE WINNING ENTRY
IN A CONTEST SPONSORED BY
OUR LOCAL PAPER,
"THE POSSUM LAKE
DAILY MOVEMENT."
THE TOWN BUILT AN ADDITION
ON THE FAMILY HOME
TO HOUSE THE NEW ARRIVALS
AND TO SEAT THE 150 PAYING
CUSTOMERS ON BLEACHERS
INSIDE THE THE HOUSE.
THE FAMILY GOT THE HOME,
AND THE TOWN GOT ALL
THE GATE RECEIPTS,
PLUS ALL THE MERCHANDISING
RIGHTS AND FUTURE
CONSIDERATIONS
IF THE PARENTS CRAZY ENOUGH
TO TRY THIS STUNT AGAIN.
WELL, IT WAS A DISASTER.
NOBODY CAME.
I MEAN, WHO WOULD COME TO SEE
THREE IDENTICAL BOYS
WHEN YOU COULD DRIVE
A FEW A HOURS MORE
AND GAWK AT FIVE
IDENTICAL GIRLS,
PLUS GET A CHANCE TO SEE WHAT
FRENCH PEOPLE LOOK LIKE?
THEN THE STORY CAME OUT THAT
Mr. MANNING HAD BEEN IN EUROPE
WHEN THE BOYS WERE BORN,
PLUS HE'D BEEN ABROAD FOR THE
ENTIRE YEAR BEFORE THAT.
YOU KNOW,
IT KINDA TOOK THE HEARTWARMING
LUSTRE OF INNOCENCE OFF
THE STORY,
IF YOU GET MY DRIFT.
Red:
WHEN MAYOR DENNIS FLAHERTY
WAS NAMED BY Mrs. MANNING
AS THE BOYS' FATHER,
HE CONFESSED AND IMMEDIATELY
SUED FOR HALF THE
GATE RECEIPTS.
HE WAS TURFED OUT OF OFFICE
LATER THAT DAY.
MANY YEARS FROM THEN,
A BROKEN MAN,
HIS DYING WORDS WERE,
"BAD THINGS
COME IN THREES."
GROWING UP, THOSE MANNING
TRIPLETS DID ALL KINDS
OF SPORTS.
THEY ALWAYS DID
THEM TOGETHER,
STARTING WITH BASEBALL.
THEY PLAYED FIRST, SECOND,
AND THIRD BASE
FOR THE POSSUM LAKE
MARKER BOYS.
THEY EVEN GOT THEIR NAMES
IN THE RECORD BOOK
AS THE ONLY TRIPLETS TO TURN A
TRIPLE PLAY IN THE NINTH GAME
AT HOME ON NATURAL GRASS
PRIOR TO THE FIFTH INNING.
WHEN ALL THE TROUBLE
STARTED IN TURKEY,
THE THREE MANNING BROTHERS
AND I WENT DOWN AND ENLISTED
IN THE POSSUM COUNTY LIGHT
DRAGOON HIGHLANDERS
OF FOOT RIFLES.
NOW, THEY NEVER SAW ANY COMBAT
ACTIONS SINCE THEY WERE
PRETTY GREEN,
AND FUNNILY ENOUGH, OUR COUNTRY
WASN'T INVOLVED IN THE TURKISH
WAR IN ANY WAY.
IRONICALLY, THEY WOUND UP
IN THE ARMY POSTAL CORPS,
SORTING OVERFLOW MAIL
FOR THE DIONNE QUINTS.
'COURSE, THAT INVOLVED
A LOT OF HEAVY LIFTING.
ALL THREE BROTHERS
INJURED THEIR BACKS
AND HAD TO BE INVALIDED
OUT OF THE SERVICE.
THIS LED TO THE FAMOUS
MANNING RULE
THAT WOULD NEVER AGAIN ALLOW
MEMBERS OF THE SAME FAMILY
TO SORT MAIL IN
THE SAME UNIT.
USING THEIR HONOURABLE
MEDICAL DISCHARGES,
ALL THREE BROTHERS WENT
TO WORK FOR THE POST OFFICE,
WHERE THEY IMMEDIATELY
WENT ON COMPENSATION
UNTIL THEIR
RETIREMENT IN 1987.
THE MANNING TRIPLETS
ARE STILL ALIVE TODAY,
AND THEY ARE WORKING ON THREE
SEPARATE VOLUMES OF THEIR
AUTOBIOGRAPHY CALLED
"IS THIS A GREAT
COUNTRY OR WHAT?"
COME ON.
BRING IT IN.
WELL, I'M BACK.
Mr. GREEN --
NOT NOW, MIKE!
NO, NO, NO, THAT TOLERANT
DO-GOODER STUFF IS OKAY
FOR SOME PEOPLE,
BUT IT WAS
KILLING ME.
I THINK I PICKED UP
ALL THE PARTS.
I WOULD JUST
LIKE TO APOL --
THERE'S TIME FOR
THAT LATER, MIKE, OKAY.
NO, NO, IT'S GOOD TO
BE NICE TO PEOPLE
AND EVERYTHING,
BUT IF ALL YOU'RE DOIN'
IS KEEPING THE
ANGER INSIDE,
YOU WILL EVENTUALLY
TURN INTO A SPLEEN.
YOU KNOW WHAT
IS GOOD IS GOIN' TO
THE DEMOLITION DERBY.
I THINK THERE'S SOMETHING
CATHARTIC ABOUT SEEING
THAT MUCH DESTRUCTION.
UNLESS, OF COURSE, IT'S
HAPPENING TO YOUR OWN VAN!
I'LL FIX THE VAN.
I'LL PUT IT ALL TOGETHER.
OR IF MY PAROLE OFFICER
LETS ME GO TO THE CITY,
I'LL GET YOU
ANOTHER ONE.
NO, NO, NO, YOU JUST
PUT MY POSSUM VAN
BACK TOGETHER.
OKAY, YOU GOT IT.
AND I TELL YOU WHAT,
I WON'T EVEN
CHARGE YOU, OKAY?
WELL, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
OH, WELL, HERE HE IS,
THE WINNER OF THE DEMOL --
I GUESS I GOTTA GIVE YOU
SOME CONGRATULATIONS,
EH, WINSTON?
NO, NO, I DIDN'T WIN.
HUH?
OH, NO.
IT WAS BETWEEN ME
AND MY SEPTIC TRUCK
AND MOOSE THOMPSON
AND HIS '73 GREMLIN.
MAN!
YOUR TRUCK COULD CRUSH
THAT GREMLIN IN
A HEARTBEAT.
WELL, YOU'D THINK,
WOULDN'T YOU?
SO I'M LINING HIM
UP FOR THE KILL,
AND I RAN
OUT OF GAS.
NOW, I DON'T GET IT
BECAUSE I JUST
FILLED UP THAT TRUCK
A COUPLE OF DAYS AGO.
WELL, YOU MUST
HAVE A LEAKY TANK.
YEAH, YOU CAN PROBABLY
FIX IT WITH A LOCKING
GAS CAP.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, MEETING TIME.
LET'S GO.
YEAH, YOU GUYS
GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN
A MINUTE.
UH, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
I'LL BE STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND, UH, I GAVE THE KINDER
GENTLER THING A REAL GOOD TRY,
BUT, YOU KNOW, I WAS AFRAID OF
GETTING TO BE SO NICE
THAT YOU'D THINK
I WAS CHEATING ON YOU.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND THE
WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR
STICK ON THE ICE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
closed captioning performed
by INTERCAPTION CANADA
www.intercaption.com
ALL RIGHT,
SIT DOWN, PLEASE.
EVERYONE SIT DOWN.
HERE WE GO.
SIT DOWN.
OKAY, ALL RISE!
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.