[quirky upbeat music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> AND NOW IT'S TIME FOR THE MAN
WHO IS KNOWN TO MILLIONS AS MY
UNCLE, THE RUSTIC STAR OF
THE RED GREEN SHOW [laughs].
THAT WAS A BIG HINT THERE, THAT
ONE, AND A HECK OF A HUMAN
BEING, CONSIDERING ALL HE'S BEEN
THROUGH IN HIS LIFE,
YOU KNOW, JUST THE CAR ACCIDENTS
ALONE--
ANYWAY, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
BOYS AND GIRLS, OLD PEOPLE
AND SIAMESE TWINS--I THINK I
PRETTY MUCH GOT EVERYBODY THERE.
PLEASE WELCOME RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH, HAROLD,
AND THANK YOU FOR TUNING US IN.
WE'VE GOT A HECK OF A SHOW FOR
YOU THIS WEEK.
WELL, ACTUALLY, IT'S PROBABLY
WITHIN 5% OR 10% OF LAST WEEK'S
SHOW, BUT WE CERTAINLY
APPRECIATE YOUR PATIENCE.
WE HAD A HECK OF A SET-TO UP AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
YOU GONNA INTERRUPT ME?
>> SORRY?
SORRY, UNCLE RED.
I WAS JUST--WAS JUST MAKING
MENTAL CROSSWORD PUZZLES.
WHAT'S A THREE-LETTER WORD FOR
"SHOEHORN?"
>> HE USUALLY INTERRUPTS ME.
OKAY, ANYHOW, THE WATER PUMP
BROKE DOWN AT THE LODGE AND NONE
OF US WANTED TO GO UNDER THE
LODGE AND FIX IT.
SO STINKY PETERSON GOT THE IDEA
WE SHOULD--WE SHOULD BUILD A
WATER TOWER, YOU KNOW, AND NOT
JUST A WATER TOWER ON THE ROOF,
BUT MAYBE UP INTO THE TREES ON
THE RIDGE SO WE CAN, YOU KNOW,
REALLY GET A LOT OF--LOT OF
POWER AND JUICE AND A LOT OF
TORQUE AND PULL DOWN AND--COME
ON OVER HERE A MINUTE, HAROLD.
I'M SORRY, BUT--HAROLD, HE
USUALLY MY INTERRUPTS MY STORIES
AND THROWS ME RIGHT OFF AND HE'S
GOT THIS MACHINE HERE, AND IT
DOES LIKE THAT KIND OF THING AND
TAKES US INTO THE NEXT SEGMENT,
AND JUST THAT REALLY THROWS ME
OFF.
>> WELL, NOT TODAY UNCLE RED.
TODAY I'M JUST YOUR DIRECTOR AND
YOUR NEPHEW.
I PROMISE I'M NOT GONNA
INTERRUPT YOU.
I'M NOT GONNA BOTHER YOU.
I'M NOT GONNA BREAK THE FLOW
FROM ANY PART OF YOU.
I'M NOT GONNA BRING OUT FILM
CLIPS.
NOTHING.
[laughs]
JUST STAND HERE QUIETLY.
ONLY IF THINGS GET REALLY,
REALLY BORING WOULD I EVER TOUCH
THESE BUTTONS.
>> WELL, THANK YOU HAROLD.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
[folksy guitar and spoons music plays]
>> LATE IN THE EVENING WHEN
THE FIRE'S ALMOST OUT
THE BOYS START COMPARING
AND YOU KNOW WHAT
THAT'S ABOUT
WHO'S BIGGER
AND WHO'S STRONGER
AND ON AND ON IT GOES
UNTIL THE BIGGEST TEST
OF ALL
WHO HAS THE OLDEST CLOTHES
WHO HAS THE OLDEST CLOTHES?
CAN'T TELL WITH YOUR EYES
YOU CAN ALWAYS USE YOUR NOSE
STINKY HAS A PAIR A SOCKS
OLDER THAN HIS SON
BUSTER HAS A VEST HE SAYS
HE GOT FROM THE GRAVE
OF ATTILA THE HUN
WHEN PEOPLE SEE OUR WARDROBE
THEY OFTEN WONDER WHY
IT'S NOT THAT WE LIKE
OLD CLOTHES SO MUCH
IT'S JUST THAT WE PREFER
WEARING THINGS THAT OUR
WIVES DIDN'T BUY
THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU SOMETHING
THAT YOU CAN DO WITH YOUR OLD
CAR.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, THIS IS AN OLD
CAR, BUT THERE'S STILL SOMETHING
ABOUT IT THAT GETS MY HEART
POUNDING.
I THINK IT'S THE LACK OF BRAKES.
YOU KNOW, WE ALL GOT TO GO
SOMETIME, AND FRANKLY, I'D
RATHER--I'D RATHER GO WITH
SOME KIND OF A HEAD-ON INTO THE
GUARDRAIL RATHER THEN SPEND MY
DECLINING YEARS IN A RETIREMENT
HOME.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I GOT OFF ON
THAT.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S THE--
I GET STARTED AND THEN I GO OFF
ON A CRAZY ANALOGY AND--AND
THAT'S THE WAY I AM WITH THE
CAR, TOO.
I GOT THE CAR AND I JUST CAN'T
LEAVE WELL ENOUGH ALONE WITH IT.
WHAT I WANTED TO DO TODAY WAS I
WANTED TO TURN THIS DOOR AND THE
OTHER DOOR INTO--INTO THE GULL
WING.
YOU KNOW THE GULL WING DOOR TYPE
OF STYLE, WHICH THEY HAD ON THE
OLD MERCEDES, I BELIEVE, AND
BROOKLYN HAD THE GULL WING AND I
THINK--I BELIEVE GULLS HAVE
THEM.
I'M NOT SURE ON THAT ONE.
ANYWAY, THE FIRST THING YOU GOT
TO DO IS YOU GOT TO REMOVE THE
DOOR, WHICH IS NOT AS EASY AS IT
SOUNDS.
UH, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WHAT I'VE--WHAT I'VE
DONE HERE IS I'VE POKED A LITTLE
HOLE IN THE--IN THE ROOF, BUT
I'M GONNA NEED THAT FOR LATER,
SO THAT'S--THAT'S ACTUALLY A
TIMESAVER.
OKAY.
BY GOLLY, THIS IS REALLY ON--
ON THERE.
AH, THERE IS A BETTER WAY.
OKAY.
WHERE THERE'S A VAN, THERE'S A
WAY.
NOW, ALL I'VE GOT TO DO IS GET
THIS UNIT UP HERE.
[groans]
PUT HER ON HERE.
NOW, WHAT I...
WHAT I HAVE TO DO IS CREATE
A HINGE NOW THROUGH OUR--
THROUGH OUR PRE-DRILLED HOLE,
AND I'M GONNA USE A HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
AND YOU WANT TO PUT ON TWO OR
THREE LAYERS OF DUCT TAPE ON
THIS, JUST SO YOU'RE STREET
LEGAL.
YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T WANT THE
COPS PULLING YOU OVER.
AND YOU WANT IT SECURE THERE,
'CAUSE THERE'S NOTHING MORE
INCONVENIENT THAN HAVING TO PULL
OFF THE HIGHWAY AND GO BACK AND
GET YOUR DOOR.
ANYWAY, I THINK THAT'S PRETTY
SECURE THERE.
WE'VE GOT ENOUGH TAPE FOR THE
OTHER DOOR, SO NOW I'M GONNA GO
AND HOOK UP THE MECHANISM THAT
WILL ACTUALLY OPEN THE GULL WING
DOOR.
GETTING EXCITING, ISN'T IT?
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT.
IF THAT DOESN'T SCREAM
"ITALIAN," THEN YOU'RE NOT
LISTENING.
WHAT I DONE WAS I GOT A GARAGE
DOOR--DOOR OPENER THERE.
I GOT IT FROM MY NEIGHBOR'S
PLACE WHILE THEY WERE OUT, AND I
RAN THE CHAIN FROM THE DOOR
OPENER--IT'S MOUNTED ON THE--
ON THE SEAT, AND I RAN THE CHAIN
UP THROUGH AND HOOK HER ON TO
THE DOOR AND THE DUCT TAPE HERE
WILL JUST HOLD HER, AND THEN I
GOT THE WIRELESS REMOTE FOR THE
GARAGE DOOR OPENER, AND I WALK
UP TO MY CAR AND I JUST FEEL
LIKE MARCELLO MASTRO--MASTRO--
YOU KNOW.
SO ANYWAY, UNTIL NEXT TIME,
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
LET'S GIVE OUR GULL WING DOOR A
SHOT.
[sniffs]
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE
FEATURES AND MORE FROM OUR
REGULAR GUESTS.
>> AND WILL WE HEAR THE ENDING
OF THE WATER TOWER STORY?
>> OH, WE MAY NOT HAVE TIME.
>> OH, I'M THE DIRECTOR.
WE'LL FIND TIME.
>> IT IS AUTUMN.
THE SQUIRREL IS FAT FOR THE
COMING WINTER.
THE BEARS ARE PLUMP AS THEY
READY FOR HIBERNATION.
THE MUSKRAT, THE PORCUPINE, THE
RACCOON ARE ROLY-POLY, TO SEE
THEM THROUGH THEIR LONG WINTER
SLEEP.
WHAT'S YOUR EXCUSE?
SO ANYWAY, WE WERE GETTING INTO
THIS BUILDING THIS WATER TOWER
THING, AND WE DIDN'T WANT TO
MAKE IT OUT OF WOOD OR METAL.
WE THOUGHT WE'D JUST GET A
GIGANTIC PLASTIC BAG AND STRING
IT BETWEEN SOME OF THE TREES AND
THEN IT WOULD FUNNEL THE WATER
DOWN TO THE LODGE.
OF COURSE THE PROBLEM IS, WHERE
YOU GONNA FIND A PLASTIC BAG 90
FEET BY 90 FEET THAT WILL HOLD
15 TONS OF WATER WITHOUT
RIPPING?
NOW LUCKILY MOOSE THOMPSON HAD
ONE IN HIS VAN.
YOU'RE GOING TO INTERRUPT ME,
AREN'T YOU?
>> NO.
I WANT THE PEOPLE TO HEAR THIS
STORY, UNCLE RED.
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
>> YES, I DO, I REALLY DO.
HONEST INJUNS.
STAMP ON IT.
CHERRY ON TOP.
SUPERMAN SAYS SO.
ON A STACK OF BIBLES.
>> YOU THINK THE STORY IS
STUPID.
YOU THINK WHAT WE DID WAS
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> WELL, THEN WHY DO YOU WANT ME
TO TELL THE STORY?
>> WELL--WELL, TO BE HONEST
WITH YOU, I'VE BEEN GETTING A
LOT OF NEGATIVE FEEDBACK FROM
OUR VIEWERS.
WELL, OKAY, MOSTLY FROM MEN FROM
AROUND HERE, BUT THEY ALWAYS SAY
"HOW COME--HOW COME YOU ALWAYS
INTERRUPT RED'S STORIES WHEN
HE'S TELLING THE STORY?
HOW COME YOU DO THAT?" AND I'LL
SAY, "WELL, BECAUSE, THAT'S
WHY." AND THEY SAY "WELL, LET
HIM FINISH ONE ONE TIME, SEE IF
IT'S GOOD."
I FIGURE, OKAY, YOU FINISH ONE
OF YOUR STORIES AND THEN PEOPLE
WILL KNOW WHY I INTERRUPT YOU.
SO YOU GO AHEAD.
YOU GO AHEAD.
YOU TELL ONE OF YOUR STORIES
ABOUT WHAT YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS
DID.
GO AHEAD, RIGHT IN THERE, TELL
THEM.
[laughs]
>> WHAT?
I DIDN'T THROW IT.
I DIDN'T EVEN SEE IT.
IT WAS STILL ROLLING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> RACCOONS.
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU, RED?
DO YOU WANT TO PLAY THROUGH?
IS THAT IT?
>> NO, NO, NO, BOB.
I CUT DOWN A TREE AT THE LODGE--
>> OH, YEAH.
>> AND HAROLD SAYS THE
GOVERNMENT'S GONNA, YOU KNOW,
AUDIT ME OR RIP OUT MY
FINGERNAILS, OR SEND ME TO
PRISON OR SOMETHING.
I THOUGHT SINCE YOU'RE WITH THE
NATURAL RESOURCES PEOPLE AND
YOU'RE A LODGE MEMBER, MAYBE YOU
COULD KIND OF STRAIGHTEN THINGS
OUT FOR ME.
>> OH, THAT'S OK.
SURE, RED, I'LL DO THAT.
>> GREAT.
>> EXCEPT I'M WORKING RIGHT NOW.
>> OH.
>> YEAH, THIS IS GOVERNMENT
WORK.
>> REALLY?
>> OH, YEAH.
I'M MARKING TREES.
>> OH, REALLY.
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
YOU SEE THAT TREE OVER THERE?
YOU SEE THAT LITTLE MARK ON
THERE?
SEE THAT?
>> OH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> YEAH, I DID THAT.
>> OH.
>> THAT TAKES A LOT OF TIME AND
CONCENTRATION.
>> YEAH.
>> I FIND GOLF HELPS ME WITH
THAT.
YEAH.
>> WELL NOW THE TREE I CUT,
IT WAS--IT WAS A BEECH TREE,
BOB, AND I SWEAR IT WAS NO MORE
THAN 6 INCHES IN DIAMETER,
AND IT COME DOWN REAL EASY,
YOU KNOW.
>> MM-HMM.
WELL, I WOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> OH.
>> NO, YOU KNOW, THE GOVERNMENT,
THEY'RE NOT TOO CONCERNED WITH
ONE TREE.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU FLATTENED A
WHOLE FOREST.
YOU DIDN'T DO THAT, DID YOU?
>> NO, NO.
>> THERE YOU GO.
SEE, THAT'S THE SECRET.
>> YEAH.
>> MODERATION.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> IT'S MUCH LIKE GOLF.
OH, I PLAY ABOUT, WELL, FOUR OR
FIVE ROUNDS OF GOLF A WEEK.
>> REALLY.
>> WELL, MAYBE--MAYBE ABOUT
EIGHT OR NINE ROUNDS OF GOLF A
WEEK.
BUT YOU KNOW, IF I DON'T WATCH
IT, I COULD PLAY AS MUCH GOLF AS
I WANTED AND IT COULD BECOME A
REAL PROBLEM.
>> SURE.
>> OH, YEAH.
OR IS IT 10 OR 12 ROUNDS?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KEEP COUNT.
FORE!
OH, DAMMIT!
HEAD DOWN.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S THE WHOLE THING, YOU
KNOW.
HEAD DOWN.
THIS THING, DOWN.
IT'S ALL PART OF THE GAME, YOU
KNOW.
>> YOU WENT RIGHT INTO THE--
RIGHT INTO THE WATER THERE.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
>> NO.
>> YEAH.
>> AH, GEEZ.
>> IS THAT GOOD?
>> NO, NO, IT'S NOT GOOD.
WELL, IT'S GOOD FOR THE BALLS.
IT'LL WASH THEM OFF,
BUT IT'S HEAD DOWN.
THAT'S THE WHOLE THING, YOU
KNOW.
GOT TO KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN.
THAT'S IMPORTANT.
GOT TO DO SOME GOVERNMENT WORK.
>> OH.
>> I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
>> NO, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> HEAD DOWN.
>> ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, PAL?
>> HUH?
OH, I'M FINE.
NO PROBLEM.
HEAD DOWN.
>> SEEM A LITTLE BIT UPSET
THERE.
>> NO.
YOU KIDDING?
>> HEAD DOWN.
>> BOB.
>> DOWN.
DOWN.
HEAD DOWN.
>> BOB.
>> HEAD DOWN!
BOB.
FLIES IN THE SUGAR BOWL
TWO BY TWO
WHAT AN UNUSUAL THING TO DO
NOT THE FLIES
BUT THE TWO BY TWO
YOU DON'T OFTEN SEE
INSECT'S INFORMATION
>> [laughs]
UNCLE RED, W-WE'VE GOT SOME FUN
LETTERS TODAY.
THIS ONE'S GREAT.
THIS IS A FROM A VIEWER,
I THINK--I THINK HE'S A REAL
KIDDER, YOU KNOW, MORE LIKE A
TEASER.
[laughs]
>> JUST READ THE LETTER, HAROLD,
ALL RIGHT?
>> I WAS BORN READY.
"DEAR RED, ARE THERE ANY
EXPLOSIVES THAT CAN BE MADE FROM
A CAKE MIX?
THIS IS FOR A SURPRISE PARTY, SO
PLEASE REFER TO ME BY THE NAME
'RALPH' RATHER THAN MY REAL
NAME, WHICH IS ALSO 'RALPH,'
BUT SPELLED WITH AN 'F.'"
>> WELL HAROLD, AS THE
PROCTOLOGIST SAID TO THE JOCKEY,
"WE'RE GETTING INTO A SENSITIVE
AREA HERE."
I'M REALLY KIND OF RELUCTANT
TO TALK ABOUT EXPLOSIVES
ON THE AIR, YOU KNOW.
>> NO, UNCLE RED, I DON'T THINK
THE VIEWER MEANT IT THAT WAY.
HE JUST WANTS AN EXPLOSIVE
EFFECT FROM HIS CAKE, YOU KNOW?
SOMETHING THAT HE JUST WON'T
HAVE TO STIR NITROGLYCERIN IN
WITH HIS RECIPE.
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
AT LEAST THAT'S HOW I READ IT.
>> WELL, YEAH, OKAY, HAROLD, BUT
YOU KNOW THERE ARE A LOT OF
EXPLOSIVES THAT CAN BE MADE WITH
THINGS YOU FIND RIGHT IN YOUR
KITCHEN.
>> OUR KITCHEN OR ANYBODY'S
KITCHEN?
>> NO, I MEAN ANYBODY'S KITCHEN.
>> OH, YEAH?
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
>> OH, YEAH.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF, YOU KNOW,
MIXING THE VARIOUS BAKING GOODS
IN A CERTAIN PROPORTION.
I'VE SEEN A BRAN MUFFIN TAKE OUT
A WHOLE SEPTIC SYSTEM.
>> [laughs]
WELL MAYBE WE SHOULD ANSWER THIS
VIEWER BY MAIL, 'CAUSE WE DON'T
WANT THIS INFORMATION GETTING
INTO THE WRONG HANDS, YOU KNOW,
LIKE A TERRORIST BAKER OR
SOMETHING.
>> MAYBE WHAT I SHOULD I DO IS
JUST INVITE HIM UP HERE AND GET
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK TO SHOW HIM.
HE MAKES A BIRTHDAY CAKE THAT
BLOWS OUT ITS OWN CANDLES.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
WOULD HE CHARGE THE VIEWER FOR
THAT?
I WOULDN'T IMAGINE IT WOULD BE
TOO EXPENSIVE OR NOTHING.
>> NO.
MIGHT COST HIM A COUPLE OF
EYEBROWS.
>> THAT'S NOT BAD.
>> BEAUTIFUL DAY UP AT THE LODGE
AND BILL AND I THOUGHT WE'D DO A
LITTLE FISHING.
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OOH, OH,
OH.
ANYWAY, BILL HAD GOT A NEW, ONE
OF THESE, WHAT THEY CALL THEM?
TROLLING MOTOR.
JUST A SMALL LITTLE THING, BUT,
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE KIND OF FUN
AND THEY'RE--THEY'RE IDEAL FOR
TROLLING, WHICH IS WHY THEY'RE
CALLED A TROLLING MOTOR.
BILL TURNED IT ON, SHOW ME HOW
IT WORKED, AND BY GOLLY, YOU
KNOW, THEY HAVE A LOT OF TORQUE
TO THEM.
A LOT OF POWER.
LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT,
LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT--OH.
I, YEAH, YEAH, HE GOT LUCKY
THERE.
HE'S OKAY.
SO THE FIRST THING HE WANTED TO
DO WAS TAKE OFF THE OUTBOARD.
YOU DON'T NEED THAT, 'CAUSE
BELIEVE OR NOT, THAT LITTLE
TROLLING MOTOR WILL DO ALMOST
THE SAME JOB.
THAT--THAT--THE COVER'S LOOSE.
OH, WELL.
THAT WAS MOOSE THOMPSON'S MOTOR
ANYHOW.
SO BILL HOOKS HER ON THERE AND
HE TOLD ME TO BRING HIM
HALF-DOZEN OR EIGHT OR NINE
FISHING POLES, AND HE HAD THESE
C-CLAMPS, AND HE SAYS "START
C-CLAMPING THE FISHING POLES TO
THE SIDE OF THE BOAT."
AND HE HAD SOME, NOT ONLY DUCT
TAPE, BUT THE BLACK DUCT TAPE,
WHICH IS THE BIG DOLLAR--
WENT THE BIG DOLLAR ON THIS,
AND HE DECIDED
THIS IS THE BEST WAY TO FISH.
YOU GOT BASICALLY TEN, 11, 12--
QUITE A FEW RODS IN THE WATER,
AND NOW WE'RE JUST GOING
ON THE--ON THE TROLLING MOTOR,
AND SEE, THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
IT'S GOT THE POWER TO PULL US
ALONG THERE, AND BEAUTIFUL DAY.
BEAUTIFUL DAY.
STILL A BEAUTIFUL--HAVEN'T
CAUGHT ANYTHING YET--BUT BILL,
WAIT, BILL, BILL, BILL.
YOU GOT ONE THERE.
BILL, YOU GOT ONE.
YOU GOT ONE, BILL.
AND, IT STARTED, YOU KNOW, THIS
IS THE BAD THING ABOUT HAVING
ALL THE FISHING RODS, WELL,
AND I HADN'T--HONESTLY HADN'T
NOTICED THAT HE--WHAT I SHOULD
HAVE DONE PROBABLY THERE WAS I
PROBABLY SHOULD HAVE TURNED OFF
THE--TURNED OFF THE TROLLING
MOTOR OR MAYBE UNCLIPPED
THE BATTERY.
BUT IT JUST DIDN'T--DIDN'T OCCUR
TO ME THAT THE FISH WOULD BE
ABLE TO PULL BILL QUITE THAT
HARD.
>> [yelling]
>> BUT IT DID.
ANYWAY, HE WAS OKAY, FLOATING--
ALL OF A SUDDEN HE STARTING
GETTING PULLED.
WE COULDN'T FIGURE OUT WHAT WAS
GOING ON, AND THEN HE REALIZED
THAT ALL HIS FISH HOOKS HAD
GOT HIM.
SO I JUST TOOK OUT THE PROP OUT
OF THE WATER AND THAT STOPPED
THE PULL, AND HE WAS OKAY.
SO WE GOT--GOT OVER THAT
EMERGENCY AND THEN UNFORTUNATELY
ALL THE LINES WOUND AROUND THE
PROP AND STARTED TO--
>> [yelling]
>> YANKING ON HIM, AND IT WAS--
I THOUGHT HE WAS GONNA, YOU
KNOW, REALLY--
SO I TRIED TO UNHOOK--AND HE'S
GETTING THE PROP--AND HE'S--
IN HIS FACE, AND WORSE AND--
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN, THEN I GOT
IT OFF AND HE WAS FINE SO I JUST
HAD TO CUT THE WIRE AND LET HIM
GO.
BEAUTIFUL DAY.
IT IS SUMMER.
NINE NUTBALLS RACE UP THE LAKE
ON THOSE NOISY BOATS THAT LOOK
LIKE SNOWMOBILES.
WHAT DO THEY CALL THEM?
SEA MOBILES?
WATER SLEDS?
SURF SKIS?
WHAT ARE THEY CALLED?
THEY NEED TO KNOW FOR THE
CORONER'S REPORT.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME, AREN'T YOU
HAROLD?
INFLATABLE SHOES?
>> YEAH.
THEY'RE CALLED "PUMPS."
YOU GOT TO--YOU PUMP THEM UP.
THEY'RE LIKE--THEY'RE LIKE
SNEAKERS OR RUNNING SHOES, YOU
KNOW?
THEY'RE FOR PEOPLE WHO LIKE TO
PLAY SPORTS OR, YOU KNOW, JUST
PEOPLE WHO LIKE TO LOOK LIKE
THEY PLAY SPORTS.
YOU PUMP 'EM UP.
THEY DON'T GET REAL BIG OR
SOMETHING, UNCLE RED.
THEY'RE NOT LIKE AIR MATTRESSES.
THEY JUST ENSURE A PROPER,
SNUG FIT.
>> WELL, WHY DON'T YOU JUST BUY
THE RIGHT SIZE IN THE FIRST
PLACE?
>> I DON'T KNOW, YOU COULD--
YOU SEE, YOU COULD DO THAT BUT
WHERE'S THE MARKETING SCHEME IN
THAT, YOU SEE?
I MEAN, WHEREAS WITH THESE,
"THE PUMP."
YOU SEE?
IT'S JUST SOMETHING NEW.
THAT'S ALL IT IS.
AND YOU KNOW, THEY COST TWICE AS
MUCH AS REGULAR SHOES.
>> TWICE AS MUCH?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> HOW COME?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, INFLATION.
[laughing]
>> WE'RE GONNA COME RIGHT BACK
AND FINISH OFF THE SHOW WITH A
LOT OF SPECIAL STUFF, SO STAY
TUNED.
>> AND STAY TUNED FOR THE
EXCITING CONCLUSION OF THE WATER
TOWER STORY.
>> I FORGOT IT.
>> I DON'T.
>> IF ANY OF YOU HAVE ANY
TEENAGERS IN THE HOUSE, YOU
MIGHT WANT TO VIDEOTAPE THIS
PART SO THAT YOU CAN ERASE IT
LATER.
I'M GOING TO TALK ABOUT WHAT
THEY CALL "FREE LOVE."
NOW I'M NOT SAYING WHAT'S RIGHT
AND WHAT'S WRONG, BUT GOLLY,
IT'S A--IT'S A BAD THING.
SO, ALL YOU TEENAGE GIRLS THERE
IN PARTICULAR, WHENEVER YOU GET
A REQUEST FROM A BOY OF THE
OPPOSITE SEX ALONG THE FREE LOVE
LINE, I'M ASKING YOU TO JUST SAY
"NO."
THAT'S--THAT'S ONLY FAIR TO--
TO THOSE OF US FROM AN OLDER
GENERATION WHO GREW UP WHEN
THINGS WERE REAL UPTIGHT AND
CELIBATE AND CELIBACY AND SO ON,
AND YOU WEREN'T ALLOWED TO DO
ANYTHING.
SO WE DON'T ENJOY YOU BEING
ALLOWED TO ENJOY THINGS THAT WE
WEREN'T ALLOWED TO ENJOY.
IT'S JUST--IT'S NOT ENJOYABLE.
I THINK JUST TO SAY "NO" IN THE
INTERESTS OF FAIR PLAY.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY TO GO.
I KNOW I CAN'T TELL YOU WHAT TO
DO.
ALL RIGHT, YOU DO WHATEVER YOU
WANT TO DO, BUT I'LL TELL YOU
ONE THING.
UP AT THE LODGE, OUR ATTITUDE
TOWARDS FREE LOVE IS "YOU GET
WHAT YOU PAY FOR."
>> [yelling]
OKAY, IT'S JUST A GAME!
JUST A GAME.
RED, IS IT A GAME?
>> YEAH.
>> JUST BREATHE DEEP.
BREATHE DEEP, BOB.
HEAD DOWN.
>> BOB.
>> HUH?
>> SO THIS, THE THING WITH THE
TREE AND THE GOVERNMENT?
SO I'M NOT GONNA BE IN ANY KIND
OF TROUBLE THERE WITH THE--
WITH THE TREE THING?
>> OH, RIGHT.
NO.
YOU--YOU PLAY GOLF, RED, OR--
>> NO, I'M PRETTY RELAXED
ALREADY.
>> OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
WELL, YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
IT'S A GREAT GAME.
>> YEAH, WELL.
>> YESIREE, GREAT GAME.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I'D BE--
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE A SHOT?
>> NO, NO, NO, THANK YOU, NO.
IT'S, NO, NO.
>> NO, NO, IT'S EASY.
GO ON.
TAKE A SHOT.
>> I GOT TO GET BACK TO THE
LODGE, YOU KNOW, AND THE GUYS--
>> TAKE A SHOT.
>> YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
NO PROBLEM.
JUST GO AHEAD.
>> OH, YEAH.
NOW YOU'RE HAVING FUN, HUH?
YOU'RE HAVING FUN, BUDDY?
>> YEAH, SURE.
>> GOOD.
KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN.
FORE!
>> SO, I'M NOT IN ANY TROUBLE
AT ALL THEN, EH, SO JUST--
I'M NOT GONNA WORRY ABOUT IT.
I SAY HAROLD'S BLOWING SMOKE AND
EVERYTHING IS GONNA BE JUST
FINE.
>> LOOK AT THAT.
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> YOUR HEAD WAS DOWN.
THAT WAS THE WHOLE KEY.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU KNOW, RED, I WOULD LOVE
TO PLAY A FEW ROUNDS OF GOLF
WITH YOU.
>> WELL, GOLF'S NOT REALLY MY
GAME, YOU KNOW, BOB,
I DON'T THINK.
>> OH, IT'S NOT?
>> I DON'T THINK SO, NO.
>> THAT'S--THAT'S TOO BAD.
SO, TELL ME SOMETHING RED.
HOW OLD WAS THAT TREE THAT YOU
CUT DOWN?
DIDN'T HAVE A MARK ON IT, DID
IT?
WAS IT MARKED FOR CUTTING?
YOU DIDN'T GET--YOU DIDN'T GET
APPROVAL TO--
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY,
YOU JUST TALKING THERE, AND
SUDDENLY IT OCCURRED TO ME I
THINK I COULD FREE UP NEXT
TUESDAY IF YOU WANTED TO HAVE A
GAME OF GOLF.
>> WONDERFUL.
GREAT.
WELL, WE TEE OFF AT 6:30 IN THE
MORNING AND 1:00 IN THE
AFTERNOON.
>> 6:30 AND 1:00.
>> MM-HMM.
>> TWO ROUNDS.
>> OH, YEAH, WELL--
>> I'M GONNA GO REST UP.
>> ALL RIGHT, AND I NEED TO GET
ANOTHER CLUB.
>> I'LL SEE YOU ON TUESDAY.
>> ON TUESDAY, YOU BET.
DON'T WORRY, I'VE GOT LOTS OF
THESE CLUBS.
LOTS OF THESE BABIES.
>> ENOUGH FOR ME AND--
>> FOR BOTH OF US.
ALL RIGHT, SEE YOU THEN.
>> OKAY
>> FABULOUS.
[laughs]
FORE!
[groans]
>> WELL, ANYWAY.
THAT ABOUT DOES IT FOR THIS
WEEK, SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME
TONIGHT, AND I'LL WARM MY TOES
BEFORE I GET INTO BED.
AND AS FOR THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING AND
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG HERE AT THE
LODGE, KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE
ICE.
>> UNCLE RED, WHAT ABOUT THE
WATER TOWER STORY?
FINISH THE WATER TOWER STORY.
>> WELL, WE DON'T HAVE TIME FOR
THAT THIS WEEK, HAROLD.
>> [laughs]
YOU FOLKS SHOULD HAVE SEEN IT.
IT WAS GREAT.
THEY GOT THIS HUGE BLACK GIANT
PLASTIC BAG, RIGHT?
AND THEY PUT IT UP BETWEEN TWO
TREES.
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED THEN?
[laughs]
IT STARTED TO RAIN.
JUST, LIKE, IT POURED FOR LIKE
TWO OR THREE DAYS, RIGHT,
AND THE BAG FILLS UP.
AND THEN YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE TREES STARTED TO BEND LIKE
THIS.
THEY WERE ALL HUNCHED OVER WORSE
THAN OLD MAN SEDGEWICK.
[laughs]
AND THEN YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
THEN?
NOTHING.
NO WATER WAS COMING OUT THE
BOTTOM OR NOTHING AS THEY HAD
PLANNED.
YOU KNOW WHY?
[laughs]
THEY FORGOT TO PUT A HOSE IN IT.
YEAH.
SO, STINKY PETERSON--HE'S THE
BRAINS OF THE GROUP, RIGHT?
HE GETS THIS IDEA.
HE FIGURES "HEY, LET'S THROW A
LAWN DART AT IT."
[laughs]
NOW, FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO DON'T
KNOW THE WORD "FLOOD,"
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED.
WE LOST ALL THE TREES, FOUR
OUTBUILDINGS, AND 3 INCHES
OF TOPSOIL.
[laughs]
SEE, UNCLE RED?
IT WAS A GOOD STORY.