♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN,
IN TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD'S
RUNS FOR STUDENT COUNCIL,
BILL RUNS FOR COVER,
AND I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO MAKE A WHOLE
HAIRDRESSING SALON.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: AND NOW HERE'S
THE HEAD HONCHO AND
THE STOMACH HONCHO.
THE C.E.O. OF THE I.P.B.
IF YOU LIKE A MAN OF LETTERS,
NOT THAT HE READS THEM,
MY UNCLE, THE STAR OF THE SHOW,
RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
THANKS FOR TUNING US IN.
HELLO HAROLD, WAS THERE ANYTHING
YOU'D LIKE TO SAY BEFORE WE
GOT STARTED, MAYBE AN APOLOGY?
>>HAROLD: NO THANK YOU,
I'LL LET MY ELECTRONIC EDITORIAL
EFFECTS MACHINE DO ALL
THE TALKING.
>>RED: AMAZING THAT HE'D
DO THAT WHILE I'M HOLDING
A HAMMER ISN'T IT?
BIG, BIG WEEK UP AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK, OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
HAS ANNOUNCED THAT HE WANTS TO
GET BACK TO NATURE AND WE'RE
ALL IN FAVOUR AND THE
SOONER THE BETTER.
>>HAROLD: OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
IS LEAVING THE LODGE?
THAT OUGHT TO BRING THE AVERAGE
AGE DOWN BY ABOUT 90 YEARS.
>>RED: YEAH AND IT WILL HAVE
THE EXACT OPPOSITE EFFECT
ON THE AVERAGE I.Q.
BUT HE'LL STILL BE AROUND
HAROLD, HE'S BOUGHT A COTTAGE
UP ON ROCK REEF POINT.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED THERE ARE NO
COTTAGES UP ON ROCK REEF POINT,
THERE'S JUST LIKE, WELL ROCKS
AND THAT REEF AND THAT
LITTLE POINT.
>>RED: JUST LIKE
YOUR HEAD HAROLD.
NO HE'S HAVING THE
COTTAGE BUILT.
>>HAROLD: BY WHO?
>>RED: ANYBODY WITH A TOOL.
YEAH HE BOUGHT ONE OF THEM
PREFAB KIT COTTAGES,
THE COTTAGE COMPANY COME UP
THERE AND THEY DUMPED OFF A
WHOLE LOAD OF LUMBER AND
INSULATION AND SHINGLES AND
A LITTLE BAG OF SILICA GEL
WITH A NOTE SAYING SOME
ASSEMBLY REQUIRED.
>>HAROLD: THAT'S GREAT!
OH THIS IS GREAT YOU KNOW
BECAUSE WE CAN HAVE LIKE A BARN
RAISING THING YOU KNOW THE WAY
THE QUAKERS USE TO DO,
ONLY WITHOUT PORRIDGE.
>>RED:YEAH ACTUALLY WE FIGURED
WE'D GET ALL THE GUYS UP THERE,
WE'D GET THE COTTAGE UP
IN MAYBE LESS THAN A DAY.
AND WE INVITED THE WIVES TO
COME UP AND BAKE PIES YOU KNOW
BUT OF COURSE THEY'RE ALL
AWAY IN LAS VEGAS AT
A NETWORKING SEMINAR.
>>HAROLD: I HOPE YOU READ
THE INSTRUCTIONS THIS TIME,
JUNIOR SINGLETON STILL HAS
THE SCARS FROM THE HOT TUB KIT.
>>RED: OH HAROLD THE
INSTRUCTIONS ARE A BOOK,
AT OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S AGE
HE DOESN'T HAVE THAT KIND
OF TIME, WE'D END UP JUST
BUILDING ONE CLOSET AND
THEN BURYING HIM IN IT.
>>HAROLD: I DON'T KNOW UNCLE RED
WE END UP WITH NOTHING BUT
TROUBLE WHEN YOU GUYS DO THINGS
BY THE SEAT OF YOUR PANTS
OR IN THE SEAT OF YOUR PANTS.
>>RED: AH YOU WORRY TOO
MUCH HAROLD, IN A COUPLE OF
HOURS THERE'S GOING TO BE
A COTTAGE UP ON ROCK REEF POINT
THAT'LL KNOCK YOUR EYE OUT.
>>HAROLD: I'M SURE IT'LL KNOCK
SEVERAL PEOPLE'S EYES OUT.
♪ I REMEMBER ONE MORNING ♪
♪ I AROSE FROM MY BUNK ♪
♪ EVERYBODY THOUGHT ♪
♪ I'D BEEN SPRAYED BY A SKUNK ♪
♪ THEY GOT THE TOMATO JUICE ♪
♪ AND SCRUBBED ME TO DEATH ♪
♪ BUT IT TURNED OUT ♪
♪ TO BE MY BREATH ♪
>>RED THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' I GOT
SOMETHING A LITTLE
BIT DIFFERENT FOR YOU,
I GOT AN ANNIVERSARY COMING UP
AND I WANTED TO DO
SOMETHING SPECIAL,
SO I THOUGHT I'D MAYBE CREATE
SOME SPECIAL GIFTS THAT YOU
COULD GIVE TO SAY YOUR WIFE
OR MAYBE YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
OR EVEN THAT VERY SPECIAL WOMAN
IN YOUR LIFE OR ALL 3 YOU KNOW.
SO I'M THINKING TO MYSELF,
WELL FOR STARTERS MAYBE WE
CAN CREATE OUR OWN SPECIAL
KIND OF LADY SHAVER,
COME ON IN HERE A MINUTE
HAROLD WILL YOU?
AND I'M THINKING TO MYSELF,
WHY DON'T WE JUST USE DUCT TAPE
TO SAY SHAVE A LEG BECAUSE IT
TAKES A LONG TIME TO SHAVE
A LEG DOESN'T IT HAROLD?
JUST KIDDING YOU, ALL RIGHT,
SO YOU GET A PIECE OF DUCT TAPE
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN YOU
GOT NO CREAM TO WORRY ABOUT,
NO SHARP BLADES AND
NO MESSY CLEANUP,
YOU JUST STICK HER ON THERE
AND JUST SNAP IT RIGHT
OFF LIKE THIS,
THAT DIDN'T HURT DID IT?
>>HAROLD: NO.
>>RED: BOY IT LOOKS
LIKE A THRILL RIDE.
(HAROLD SCREAMING IN PAIN)
>>RED: OH WELL.
HOW ABOUT MAKING YOURSELF
A PROFESSIONAL SALON
STYLE HAIRDRYER?
ALL YOU NEED IS AN OLD TV SET
BUT YOU GOT TO GET THE PICTURE
TUBE OUT OF HER THERE,
AND YOU NEED A SCREWDRIVER
FOR THAT CASE AND UNSCREW
IT AT THE BACK,
(LOUD SHATTERING OF TUBE)
DONE.
ALL RIGHT, SAVE ALL THE
ELECTRONIC COMPONENTS THERE
BECAUSE NEXT WEEK WE'RE GOING
TO BUILD A LAPTOP COMPUTER.
AND YOU'RE ALSO GOING TO NEED
AN OLD TOASTER BUT YOU NEED
ALL THE STUFF OUT OF THE INSIDE,
KEEP THE CASE BECAUSE WHEN
WE BUILD THE COMPUTER THIS WILL
BE OUR DUAL FLOPPY DRIVE.
ALL RIGHT ONCE WE GET THE
HEATER AND THE TIMER OUT OF
THE TOASTER, GET THEM MOUNTED
INSIDE THE TV SET,
WE PUT THAT WHOLE DEAL ONTO
THIS FANCY LOOKING DESK LAMP
AND WHAT WE HAVE THERE IS
A VERY PROFESSIONAL
LOOKING HAIR DRYER,
THAT THING YOU SEE IN
THERE IS THOSE REAL SUPER
DUPER SALONS THAT SMELL KIND
OF FUNNY, SO I'M JUST GOING TO
GO AHEAD AND KEEP ON WORKING
ON THIS, YOU GUYS GET BACK TO
THE SHOW AND WHEN WE COME BACK
IN HERE MAYBE WE'LL TRY THIS
WHOLE RIG OUT ON HAROLD,
I THINK IT'LL BE
VIDAL BASSOON LOOK OUT.
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S THAT
PART OF THE SHOW WHERE WE GET
TO EXPOSE THOSE 3 LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND TODAY CLAIMING TO BE EXPERTS
ARE MY UNCLE RED AND OF COURSE
AND MR. DOUGIE FRANKLIN.
'DEAR EXPERTS, I'M HOPING YOU
CAN ANSWER A QUESTION WHICH
HAS BEEN TEARING MY FAMILY
APART AND DESTROYING
MY MARRIAGE,
THE QUESTION IS THIS,
WHAT WAS THE BEST CAR
EVER BUILT?'
>>DOUGIE: WHOA BOY,
THAT IS A TOUGH ONE YOU KNOW,
THAT REALLY IS I THINK ONE OF
THE CORE QUESTIONS OF OUR TIME.
THAT STRIKES DEEP INTO
THE HUMAN PSYCHE,
BOY I DON'T KNOW
THAT'S A TOUGH ONE.
>>HAROLD: WHICH WAS
THE BEST CAR?
>>RED: OH YEAH HAROLD,
A PERSON'S CHOICE OF CAR IS
A WINDOW TO THEIR SOUL,
NOW I HAVE THE POSSUM VAN.
>>DOUGIE:I GOT MY MONSTER TRUCK.
>>RED: AND YOU GOT
YOUR ROLLERBLADES.
>>DOUGIE: OH YEAH,
YOU KNOW I THINK IT WAS
JEAN-PAUL SARTRE WHO REALLY
KIND OF BEST EXEMPLIFIED
THE EXISTENTIALIST VIEW.
NOW OF COURSE HE HAD ONE
OF THEM RENAULT KIT CARS,
YOU KNOW THE ONES THAT YOU
BUILD YOURSELF YOU KNOW,
KIND OF AN ATTEMPT TO KNOW
THE UNKNOWABLE YOU KNOW,
AND IT COME WITH THESE
INSTRUCTIONS THAT HAD KIND
OF A TOPOLOGICAL LOGIC LOOP,
SO YOU KNOW HE NEVER DID
FINISH THE REAR SUSPENSION
ON THAT BABY, BUT YOU KNOW
HE DID COME TO THE CONCLUSION
THAT ESSENCE PRECEDES EXISTENCE
THEREFORE YOU KNOW I MEAN,
'BEST' IS REALLY WHAT
YOU'D HAVE TO SAY IS A
SUBJECTIVE MEASUREMENT BASED
ON THE OBSERVER'S FRAME
OF REFERENCE.
>>RED: RIGHT.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH.
WELL SO?
>>DOUGIE: SO THE BEST VEHICLE
FOR RED HERE WOULD BE THE
POSSUM VAN, FOR ME IT WOULD
BE THE MONSTER TRUCK AND FOR
YOU IT'D BE THEM WATER WINGS.
>>HAROLD: ROLLERBLADES.
BUT ALL YOU SAID KIND OF MAKES
YOU WONDER SOMETHING LIKE,
WHAT WOULD PLATO DRIVE?
>>DOUGIE: A BUICK LESABER.
>>RED: IT IS AUTUMN,
WE WALK HAND IN HAND
MY WIFE AND I,
OUR LOVE IS LIKE MUSIC
NOW AND THEN A STRING BREAKS
AND WHAT ONCE WERE SHARPS
ARE NOW FLATS,
OUR LOVE IS LIKE
A FRETLESS BASE,
WE'VE BEEN PLAYING IT
SO LONG WE KNOW EXACTLY
WHERE TO PUT OUR FINGERS.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT IT'S TIME
TO MAKE BEAUTIFUL HAIR.
NOW I'VE USED SOME OF THE
OLD 9 VOLT BATTERIES HERE AS
THEY MAKE DANDY HAIR CURLERS
AND I PUT THEM ON WITH
DUCT TAPE BUT YOU COULD USE
SAY HAIRPINS OR A GLUE GUN
OR SCREWS YOU KNOW.
IS YOUR HAIR WET THERE HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: NO IT IS NOT.
>>RED: NO I DIDN'T THINK SO.
(BATTERIES SIZZLING)
NOW JUST IMAGINE THAT WAS
A $50 CUT, CREAM RINSE AND SET.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED
MY HEAD'S TINGLING,
WERE THOSE BATTERIES DEAD?
>>RED: DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT
HAROLD, I'LL JUST SET THE HEAT
ON THE TOASTER NOW AND
POP HER DOWN, THERE WE GO,
NOW EASY HAROLD, EASY, EASY,
SET HER RIGHT IN THERE,
BEAUTY, NOW ALL WE HAVE
TO DO HAROLD IS WAIT.
DO YOU WANT YOUR LEGS
SHAVED WHILE WE'RE WAITING?
>>HAROLD: NO THANK YOU!
(TOASTER WHIZZING)
>>RED: OKAY YOU'RE DONE.
(LOUD POPPING OF SPARKS)
ALL RIGHT, OKAY, THAT'S GOOD,
OH, OH, HOLD ON THERE HAROLD
HOLD ON.
>>HAROLD: HOW DO I LOOK,
I LOOK OKAY RIGHT?
>>RED: WELL LET ME PUT
A LITTLE MOUSSE ON THAT.
>>HAROLD: WHAT DID
YOU DO THAT FOR?
>>RED: WELL I WAS FROSTING
YOUR TIPS HAROLD THAT'S ALL,
WELL THERE YOU HAVE IT.
SO REMEMBER IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
>>HAROLD: IS THAT WATER
STILL DRIPPING?
>>RED: NO THAT'S BATTERY
ACID HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH.
>>RED: I WENT TO ASK JOSHUA
FOR HELP BUT HE WAS ALL TIED
UP ON SOME LAND DEAL.
WELL I GUESS THAT MEANS YOU'RE
GOING TO BE TOO BUSY TO HELP
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK,
HE'S BUILDING A COTTAGE UP
ON ROCK REEF POINT YOU KNOW?
>>JOSHUA: ROCK REEF POINT IS
NOT ZONED FOR COTTAGE RED,
IT'S A BIRD SANCTUARY.
>>RED: WHAT, ARE YOU SURE?
>>JOSHUA: YEAH I TRIED TO BUY
IT ONCE FOR A LANDFILL SITE,
THE LAWYERS WERE ALL OVER ME.
IF HE TRIES TO BUILD ANYTHING
UP THERE THE ECHO FREAKS WILL
JUST MAKE HIM TEAR IT DOWN.
>>RED: BY GOLLY I BETTER
GO TELL HIM.
>>JOSHUA: MMM HMM.
>>RED: HOW DO I GET
OUT OF HERE?
>>JOSHUA: OH NO!
>>RED: OH I'LL HELP YOU.
>>JOSHUA: MAN I NEED
A SECRETARY REAL BAD.
>>RED: WELL BEFORE I COULD
STOP HIM, OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
AND THE GUYS HAD THE
WHOLE COTTAGE BUILT,
HE EVEN HAD A ROOF ON HER.
IT WASN'T ON THE TOP BUT
IT WAS ON THERE SOMEWHERE.
>>HAROLD: WHAT A MESS TOO,
BOY THERE WAS A CHIMNEY THAT
ALL ZIG-ZAGGED OUT THE DOORWAY,
AND THERE WAS WIRES IN THE
BOTTOM OF THE TUB WHICH WAS
OUT ON THE FRONT PORCH
WHICH WAS IN THE BASEMENT.
HOW'S A GUY SUPPOSE TO CLOSE
THE WINDOW WITH ALL THE
PLUMBING COME OUT OF
IT LIKE THAT?
>>RED: WELL THEY'RE JUST
NOT ALL THAT GOOD AT
READING THE BLUEPRINT.
>>HAROLD: WELL MAYBE
IF THEY LOOKED AT IT,
IT MIGHT BE A GOOD FIRST STEP.
I THINK THE REAL PROBLEM
CAME THOUGH IS WHEN THEY
DIVIDED THE GUYS INTO 2 TEAMS
AND MADE A RACE OUT OF IT,
BOY THAT'S WHEN THEY REALLY
STARTED CUTTING CORNERS THERE.
>>RED: YEAH I THINK THAT'S
WHY SO MANY OF THE ROOMS
ARE TRIANGULAR.
BUT DON'T FORGET THESE ARE
VOLUNTEERS HAROLD AND IN
THE LONG RUN VOLUNTEERS
ARE THE MOST EXPENSIVE WORKERS
YOU'LL EVER HAVE.
SO ANYWAY AFTER THEY INSTALLED
THE SHOWER IN THE KITCHEN,
IN THE ATTIC,
THEY WANTED TO FIRE UP THE GAS
WATER HEATER AND WHEN THEY
TURNED EVERYTHING ON WATER WAS
COMING OUT OF THE GAS LINE BUT
NOTHING WAS COMING OUT
OF THE WATERLINE,
SO JUNIOR SINGLETON WENT
DOWN INTO THE BASEMENT TO SEE
WHO HAD HOOKED UP THE GAS
AND AS SOON AS HE HIT THE SWITCH
HE REMEMBERED THE ANSWER
WAS NOBODY BECAUSE THE
WHOLE PLACE EXPLODED.
>>HAROLD: IS THAT WHAT THAT WAS?
I THOUGHT THEY WERE BLASTING
IN THE QUARRY AGAIN,
OF COURSE I DID WONDER WHEN
I LOOKED UP AND I SAW
THAT COTTAGE IN THE SKY.
>>RED: YEAH YOU DON'T
SEE THAT TOO OFTEN.
>>HAROLD: WELL IT'S ONLY
THE SECOND TIME THIS YEAR.
>>RED: BUT THERE'S A GOOD SIDE
BECAUSE NOW OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
DOESN'T HAVE TO TEAR THE
COTTAGE APART JUST TO COMPLY
WITH THE ZONING BYLAW
ALTHOUGH THEY MAY CHARGE
HIM WITH LITTERING.
>>HAROLD: THE POOR OLD GUY,
I GUESS HE'S REALLY UPSET HUH?
>>RED: WELL HE'S NOT
A QUITTER HAROLD,
IF HE WAS HE WOULD OF
DIED LONG AGO DURING THE
WAR OF 1812.
BUT AS HE WAS SITTING THERE
IN THAT BIG PILE OF SPLINTERED
WOOD WITH LITTLE TUFTS OF
PINK INSULATION AROUND HIM,
BLOWING PIECES OF SHINGLE
OUT OF HIS NOSE, A BIG BLUE
HERON FLEW OVER AND DROPPED
A WAKEUP CALL ON HIS BALD SPOT
AND HE GOT AN IDEA,
HE'S THINKING, OKAY IF ROCK REEF
POINT HAS BEEN MADE INTO A
BIRD SANCTUARY WHAT HE'LL BUILD
AS A HOME IS A GREAT, BIG NEST.
♪ WE LIKE BURGERS ♪
♪ AND BEEF RIBS ♪
♪ AND RUMP ROAST AND STEAK ♪
♪ WE LIKE SIRLOIN ♪
♪ AND T-BONE MAKES US GO SNAKE ♪
♪ WE ALSO LIKE LEATHER ♪
♪ FOR SHOES AND FOR BELTS ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS HURT ♪
♪ THE ONE YOU LOVE ♪
♪ WE ARE OBVIOUSLY ♪
♪ QUITE FOND OF COWS ♪
♪ OR WE WOULDN'T BE ♪
♪ SLAUGHTERING THEM SO BAD ♪
>>RED: I NOTICED MY THUMBNAIL
WAS REAL LONG SO I THOUGHT
I'D GET SOME OF THE BIRD
DROPPINGS OFF THE TOP OF VAN
AND THEN BILL CAME OVER.
NEVER MIND BILL I'M FINE,
YEAH I'LL BE RIGHT THERE
SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING.
IT'S TIME FOR
'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'.
NOW WHAT BILL WANTED TO SHOW US
ABOUT THIS WEEK WHICH I DIDN'T
REALIZE WAS HOW TO SURVIVE
IN YOUR CAR,
AND BELIEVE ME SURVIVING
IN BILL'S CAR IS A CHALLENGE.
WE WENT WAY BEHIND THE LODGE,
GOT INTO THE BUSH THERE,
I DON'T THINK BILL WAS,
OH, OH, OH, OH, ALL RIGHT,
SO NOW WHAT WE'RE SAYING
IS YOU'RE STUCK,
WELL WE'RE NOT SAYING IT,
WE ARE...
ANYWAY BILL IS SAYING YOU
CAN SURVIVE STUCK IN A CAR,
YOU CAN, ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN RUB YOUR STOMACH,
NO, NO, I SEE YOU CAN
FEED YOURSELF,
YOU GET A DRINK, OH, OH, OH,
YOU GET A DRINK OUT OF THE
RAD APPARENTLY, SO YOU JUST
REACH OVER AND UNDO THE
THING THERE, IT MIGHT
BE HOT THOUGH BUT..
(BILL CHOKING & GAGGING)
>>RED: NO IT SEEMS FINE.
AND YOU PUT THE STRAW IN THERE
HE SAYS THAT WORKS,
I DON'T KNOW THOUGH IT
DOESN'T SEEM, WELL YOU GOT
A BIT OF A SHORT STRAW
ON THAT ONE BILL.
>>BILL: EW!
>>RED: BUT YOU WANT TO BE
SPOTTED FROM THE AIR
THAT'S THE BIG THING,
NOBODY IS GOING TO COME DRIVING
BY OUT IN THE FIELDS,
SO YOU PUT LIKE A SIGN
LIKE THIS ON YOUR RADIO
AERIAL HERE, THIS SAYS YEAH
HELP, IT'S RIGHT IN MY FACE,
I CAN'T SEE, OH, ALL RIGHT,
WELL MAYBE IF YOU CAN'T PUT IT
ON THE RADIO AERIAL THEN PUT
IT ON YOUR DOOR HANDLE,
SOMEWHERE WHERE AGAIN IT
CAN BE SPOTTED.
OH, YOU WANT TO BE DOING
THIS WITH A BETTER CAR I THINK.
NOW BILL'S GOING TO COOK US UP,
HE'S GOT SOME CORN THERE,
HE JUST WRAPS IT UP IN THE TIN,
WE GOT SOME FISH AND SOME
ASSORTED CANS OF STUFF
AND MORE FISH AND SOME PA...
WHAT ARE THOSE?
OH THOSE ARE WIENERS OKAY.
HE'S PUTTING EVERYTHING IN THERE
THAT'S A RUNNING SHOE THERE BILL
AND HE GETS THAT ALL IN THERE
AND STUFFS IT ALL AROUND
THE ENGINE, THE PARTS THAT
GET HOT WHEN YOU TURN
THE ENGINE ON AND
THE IDEA IS HE'S GOING TO
TO START HER UP, WHAT'S THAT?
OH BANGERS AND MASH.
HE'S GOING TO PUT THAT IN THERE
AND NOW WHEN HE STARTS HER UP,
THE MANIFOLDS AND WHAT HAVE YOU
OH, YEAH, YEAH, WELL YEAH,
ALL RIGHT SO, OH BOY, OH BOY,
OH BOY, OH BOY, GOOD THING
HE'S GOT THE RUBBER PANEL
IN THOSE COVERALLS.
AND HE GETS IN THERE AND
HE STARTS HER UP AND SHE'S
RUNNING REAL GOOD,
WELL 2 OF THE CYLINDERS
ARE ANYWAY...
AND THE ENGINE'S GETTING REAL
GOOD AND HOT AND I OPEN HER UP,
WHOA! WHOA! IT'S MOVIE TIME!
AND BY GOLLY WE HAVE BEEN
SPOTTED FROM THE AIR,
AND ALL THIS TIME I THOUGHT
BILL HAD NO IDEA WHAT
HE WAS DOING.
YOU'RE A GENIUS BILL,
YOU ARE A GENIUS.
>>RED: THIS NEXT PART OF THE
SHOW IS FOR THE YOUNG PEOPLE
WHO APPARENTLY CAN STOMACH
THIS KIND OF THING,
HERE'S HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: GOOD EVENING AND
WELCOME TO THE FIRST EPISODE
OF A 52 PART SERIES ENTITLED
'QUEST FOR THE PRESIDENCY'.
♪ HUMS TRUMPET TUNE ♪
OKAY, YES I KNOW IT SAYS
GUEST FOR THE PRESIDENCY
BUT YOU KNOW I COULDN'T
FIND A 'Q' SO I HAD TO
USE A 'G' OKAY, DON'T.
OKAY, I MEAN GUEST FOR
THE PRESIDENCY WOULD BE
PRETTY STUPID RIGHT?
SO, OKAY, WELL THEN JOIN
ME OVER THE NEXT 52 WEEKS
AS I WILL BE THROWING
MY HAT INTO THE RING,
WELL IF I HAD A HAT I WOULD
THROW IT INTO THE RING
AND AT THAT TIME I'LL BE
RUNNING FOR THE PRESIDENCY
OF MY VERY OWN HIGH SCHOOL,
AND PERHAPS YOU MORE ADVANCED
STUDENTS WILL BE ABLE TO LEARN
FROM MY MISTAKES AS I RUN
THROUGH THE PRIMARIES
WHICH WILL INCLUDE JUNIOR
KINDERGARTEN RIGHT UP TO THE
STUMP ON THE ELECTION DAY WHERE
I WILL CONVINCE THE ELECTORATE
THAT I AM TRULY THE ONLY
CANDIDATE WITH ENOUGH BLANKS
IN MY SOCIAL CALENDAR TO HANDLE
SUCH A HIGH, HIGH OFFICE.
SO LET ME SAY THIS ABOUT...
>>RED: HAROLD YOU'LL NEVER
MAKE IT WITH YOUR MARKS OKAY,
PRESIDENTS HAVE TO HAVE
A HIGH EDUCATION.
>>HAROLD: WHAT ABOUT ABE LINCOLN
HE WASN'T MUCH OF AN
EDUCATED GUY.
>>RED: HE WAS
ASSASSINATED HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: GOOD POINT.
>>RED: YUP.
>>HAROLD: WELL MAYBE I COULD
BE GUEST FOR THE PRESIDENT.
>>RED: I GUESS IT MUST BE
PRETTY CONFUSING TO BE A
TEENAGE BOY IN THIS DAY AND AGE
WITH ALL THE TV ADS SAYING SEX,
SEX, SEX, AND YOUR FRIENDS
SAYING SEX, SEX, SEX, AND THE
MUSIC VIDEOS SAYING SEX, SEX,
SEX, AND YOUR PARENTS SAYING
HOW WAS SCHOOL TODAY?
WELL I REMEMBER IN MY DAY,
YOU KNOW IN MY DAY THE GIRLS
WORE SKIRTS AND DRESSES
AND IF YOUR GIRLFRIEND SAID
THE 'F' WORD IT WAS FIANCÉE.
WE PUT GIRLS UP ON A PEDESTAL
AND IT WASN'T JUST TO
LOOK UP THEIR DRESSES,
BUT I GUESS WE WERE WRONG
BECAUSE THE LAST 20 YEARS
WOMEN HAVE GONE FOR THE
EQUALITY THING AND THEY'VE
ALMOST WORKED THEIR WAY
DOWN TO OUR LEVEL, ALMOST,
ALTHOUGH I HAVE YET TO SEE A
WOMAN ACTUALLY SCRATCH
HERSELF AT THE TABLE.
I DON'T GET IT THOUGH
BECAUSE BEING EQUAL TO SAY
A MEMBER OF POSSUM LODGE
IS PRETTY MUCH AN INSULT,
BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT
THEN AGAIN IF I UNDERSTOOD WOMAN
I WOULDN'T BE WHERE I AM TODAY.
>>RED: THOUGHT I'D DROP IN
ON RANGER GORD AND ASK HIM ABOUT
THIS NEST BUSINESS AND MAKE SURE
THAT HE DIDN'T PANIC WHEN HE
SAW OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S COTTAGE
BLOW UP THIS MORNING.
WHAT DID YOU THINK WHEN
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S PLACE
EXPLODED UP AT ROCK REEF POINT
THIS MORNING?
>>GORD: EXPLODED?
>>RED: OH YEAH, DIDN'T YOU
SEE THE FLAME AND THE SMOKE,
IT BURNED FOR OVER AN HOUR.
>>GORD: YOU CAN'T
CATCH THEM ALL.
>>RED: NO, I GUESS.
ANYWAY ON THIS NEST THING,
YOU KNOW THAT BIRD,
THE BLUE HERON THERE,
WHAT DO THEY DO TO THEIR NEST
TO GET IT READY FOR THE WINTER?
>>GORD: WELL MOST BIRDS WILL
ONLY BE IN THE NEST IN THE
SPRINGTIME FOR MATING,
CAN I SAY MATING ON TV?
>>RED: OH YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
WELL IF A NEST IS ONLY
FOR MATING I DON'T THINK
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK NEEDS
ONE OF THEM, NO.
>>GORD: NO, NO, NO.
I DON'T SEE HIM HAVING
A WOMAN IN HIS LITTLE NEST,
I CAN'T SEE HIM DATING
A REAL, LIVE WOMAN.
NO HE'S OUT THERE ALONE,
STARING AT THE CLOUDS UNTIL
EVERY CLOUD REMINDS HIM OF
A WOMAN NAMED GRETCHEN,
(SOBBING) OH GRETCHEN!
>>RED: ALL RIGHT GORD,
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
>>GORD: GRETCHEN!
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
>>GORD: SHE COULD HAVE SHARED
HIS NEST AND LAID HIS EGGS
AND HATCHED HIS CHICKS.
(GORD SOBBING)
>>RED: ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
WELL NEVER MIND, GO ON.
ALL RIGHT GORD, WELL DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, OKAY GORD THANKS
VERY MUCH, THAT WAS VERY
HELPFUL AND LISTEN,
WE'LL SEE YOU AGAIN SOON.
>>GORD: HOW SOON?
>>RED: SOON.
>>GORD: WHEN EXACTLY?
>>RED: SOON THAT'S ALL,
SOONER THAN NEVER HOW'S THAT?
>>GORD: OKAY, I CAN
LIVE WITH THAT.
>>RED: VERY GOOD AND
I'LL SEE MYSELF DOWN.
>>GORD: YUP.
>>RED: DON'T FOLLOW ME GORD.
>>GORD: I'LL WATCH YOU GO.
>>RED: WELL OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
HAS RUN INTO A FEW PROBLEMS
BUILDING HIS BIG NEST,
HE'S BEEN STUDYING THE HERON
AND TRYING TO IMITATE HIM
EXACTLY BUT HE'S FOUND THAT
HIS FALSE TEETH MAKE IT REAL
HARD TO PICK UP SOME OF
THE BIGGER 2 BY 4'S.
>>HAROLD: DID HE NOT THINK
TO USE HIS HANDS,
DID THIS NOT OCCUR TO HIM?
>>RED: WELL HE'S A BIT OF
A PUREST YOU KNOW HAROLD,
HE WANTS HIS NEST TO BE
AUTHENTIC YOU KNOW FOR
RESALE VALUE.
AND IF THE HERRING IS BUILDING
HIS WITH A BEAK AND ABOUT
THE SAME SIZE BRAIN,
HE SHOULD BE ABLE TO DO IT TOO.
SO HE TOOK THE FALSE TEETH OUT
TO GET HIMSELF A BETTER GRIP
WITH HIS GUMS AND THE HERRING
SWOOPED DOWN, PICKED THE TEETH
UP AND FLEW OFF,
AND GOLLY THERE IS NOTHING
SO UNNERVING AS SEEING A
LARGE WATER BIRD FLYING OVER
THE LODGE WITH A BIG
TOOTHY GRIN.
>>HAROLD: YOU KNOW UNCLE RED
I HEARD THAT OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
CAME TO HIS SENSES AND HE'S
COMPLETELY ABANDONED
THIS NEST IDEA.
>>RED: WELL YOU'RE HALF RIGHT,
HE ABANDONED THE IDEA
BUT HE'S GOING TO BUILD HIMSELF
A WHOLE NEW DIFFERENT
TYPE OF HOME.
IT'S GOING TO BE ALL SEASON,
ALL YEAR AROUND AND STILL
KEEPING WITH THE BACK TO
NATURE THEME, HE'S GOING TO
BUILD A GREAT BIG BEEHIVE.
>>HAROLD: WELL WHY DOESN'T
THAT SURPRISE ME?
>>RED: AND IF THAT DOESN'T WORK
OUT HE'S GOING TO GET 90 MILES
OF YARN AND SPIN A COCOON,
OR HE MAY END UP DIGGING
AN ANTHILL.
>>HAROLD: MAN OH MAN
LETS JUST HOPE HE'S NEVER
HEARD OF A DUNG BEETLE.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH THERE'S THE
CALL OF THE MEETING UNCLE RED.
>>RED: YEAH YOU GO AHEAD HAROLD,
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
>>HAROLD: OKEY DOKE.
>>RED: WELL ON A PERSONAL NOTE
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
YOU KNOW I TAKE A LOOK AT
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK AND I
HAVE TO THINK HOW LUCKY
I AM YOU KNOW TO BE MARRIED
AND TO HAVE A REAL NICE HOME
AND NOT TO BE ANYTHING LIKE HIM,
AND I REALLY FEEL THAT I HAVE
YOU TO THANK FOR THAT
AND I WANT TO JUST SHOW
MY APPRECIATION, SO RIGHT AFTER
THE MEETING I'M GOING TO COME
STRAIGHT HOME AND I'M GOING
TO BUILD JUST FOR YOU
A COMBINATION GARDEN SHED
AND BIRD FEEDER OUT OF WAFFLES
DON'T MENTION IT.
OKAY, SO THE REST OF YOU THANKS
VERY MUCH FOR WATCHING,
ON BEHALF OF HAROLD AND MYSELF
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
♪ ♪ ♪
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUONDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: SIT DOWN.
WELCOME TO THE MEETING
AND I'D LIKE TO TELL YOU
THAT DON AND GORD AND CLAUDE
AND BARRY HAVE FINISHED
COMPLETELY REWIRING THE
BASEMENT OF THE LODGE,
LET'S HEAR IT FOR THEM.
(EVERYONE APPLAUDS)
(CRACKLING OF ELECTRIC CIRCUITS)
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca