I FIND THE TOUGHEST JOB
AROUND THE HOUSE
IS THE CLEAN-UP
AFTERWARDS --
OTHER THAN THE APOLOGY
TO THE NEIGHBOURS
AND THE TRIP
TO THE POLICE STATION.
BUT FOR MOST MEN,
WATERING THE LAWN
OR TAKING DOWN THE CHRISTMAS
LIGHTS IS DRUDGERY ENOUGH
WITHOUT HAVING TO PUT
EVERYTHING NEATLY AWAY
WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
BUT THEN THE NEXT TIME YOU
GO TO USE ANY OF THAT STUFF,
THERE'S A PROBLEM.
I'M THINKIN' THERE'S
GOTTA BE A BETTER WAY.
PUT A FEW EXTRA
RIMS ON THIS BABY,
MADE MYSELF A 120
HORSEPOWER SIDE WINDER.
ONE RIM FOR EACH ITEM
I'M TRYING TO WIND UP, SEE.
THAT WAY IT KEEPS
THEM ALL SEPARATE.
ALLOWS ME TO CLEAN UP ANY
PROJECT IN TWO SECONDS FLAT.
I TURNED THE IDLE
UP TO ABOUT 2200 rpm.
THAT'LL GIVE ME ENOUGH POP TO
TAKE THE KINKS OUT OF THE HOSE.
NOW ALL I HAVE
TO DO IS REACH INSIDE
AND TAP HER INTO GEAR.
OKAY. OKAY.
THAT'S IMPORTANT.
DON'T USE A
FRONT WHEEL DRIVE VEHICLE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
IT'S THE END OF THE MONTH.
THAT'S WHEN THE
BILLS COME IN,
YOU KNOW, THE ENVELOPES
WITH THE WINDOWS IN THEM --
OR AS WE CALL THEM,
LAND FILL.
OH, LOOK AT THIS ONE, EH?
FINAL NOTICE.
THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
I WAS AFRAID THEY'D
NEVER GIVE UP.
LA-LA-LA, LA-LA-LA
LA-LA-LA
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
STOP.
YOU KNOW HOW IT WORRIES
ME WHEN YOU'RE HAPPY.
WELL, IT HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH BUGGING YOU.
I'M JUST REALLY HAPPY
BECAUSE SOMETHING SPECIAL
ARRIVED IN THE MAIL TODAY.
WELL, I'M NOT HELPING
YOU INFLATE IT.
NO, LISTEN TO THIS.
LISTEN TO THIS.
"DEAR FRIEND...
"THIS LETTER COMES TO YOU
FROM SOMEONE WHO WANTS
TO PASS ON
"THE GOOD FORTUNE
THEY RECEIVED FROM IT.
"ALL YOU HAVE
TO DO IS SEND IT OFF,
"WITHOUT CHANGING
ANY OF THE TEXT,
"TO 10 FRIENDS
WITHIN 24 HOURS
"AND THEN GREAT THINGS
WILL HAPPEN TO YOU!
HAROLD, YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS IS?
THIS IS A
CHAIN LETTER.
THIS IS ALL BALONEY.
CHAIN LETTERS ARE RIGHT
UP THERE WITH HOROSCOPES,
PALM READERS AND
EXTENDED WARRANTIES.
NO, IT SAYS IF
I DON'T RETURN IT
TERRIBLE THINGS
WILL HAPPEN TO ME, THOUGH.
YEAH, HAROLD, YOU KNOW,
IN MY LIFE I'VE RECEIVED,
I DUNNO, HUNDREDS OF THESE
DARNED CHAIN LETTERS.
I'VE NEVER SENT ONE OUT,
AND LOOK AT ME.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S PRIZE IS
FROM PORT ASBESTOS VIDEO.
GOOD FOR ONE RENTAL OF
ABSOLUTELY ANY MADONNA MOVIE!
THE RENTAL IS FREE,
BUT IF YOU WANNA BRING IT BACK
IT'LL COST YOU FIVE BUCKS.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE,
COVER YOUR EARS.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS TO
GET MIKE TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, MIKE, EVERY CHRISTMAS
YOUR FAMILY GETS TOGETHER
BECAUSE IT'S...
WHEN THEY ALL
GET A DAY PASS?
NO, OKAY.
NO, OKAY, LIKE,
MY MOTHER MAKES CRANBERRY
SAUCE EVERY THANKSGIVING.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING YOUR
MOTHER DOES EVERY YEAR,
AND THAT'S CALLED A...
WEDDING?
NO, OKAY. OKAY.
BUT YOUR MOTHER DOES
THAT SO OFTEN
BECAUSE IT'S
ONE OF SOCIETY'S...
LEGAL LOOPHOLES.
YOU CAN'T TESTIFY
AGAINST A SPOUSE.
OKAY, NO, BUT CARRY ON
WITH THE WEDDING THING.
THE BRIDE WEARS A WHITE DRESS
BECAUSE IT'S A...
NAIVE GROOM!
UH, RED,
ALMOST OUTTA TIME.
OKAY, OKAY.
OKAY, MIKE,
YOU KNOW THESE C.E.O.s, THEY
MAKE THEIR BIG MONEY GRAB,
AND THEY HEAD OFF
TO THE GRAND CAYMANS, RIGHT?
THAT'S BECAUSE
FOR THEM IT'S A...
IT'S A CRIMINAL'S PARADISE.
HOW DO YOU FIGURE THAT?
NO EXTRADITION TREATY!
I HEARD IT!
WELCOME TO THE EXPERTS
PORTION OF THE PROGRAMME,
WHERE WE ADDRESS
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
OKAY, HERE'S THE LETTER...
"DEAR EXPERTS:
MY QUESTION IS
"SHOULD I HEAT MY HOUSE
WITH GAS OR ELECTRICITY?
"NOW THAT THE NIGHTS
ARE GETTING COOLER
"WHAT'S BETTER FOR SLEEPING,
"TURN UP THE THERMOSTAT
OR GET AN ELECTRIC BLANKET?"
NO, NO, NO, ELECTRIC
BLANKETS SCARE ME.
WELL, THEY'RE OKAY,
UNLESS THEY GET WET.
YOU KNOW, IN PRISON THEY KEEP
THE TEMPERATURE
AT 70 DEGREES FAHRENHEIT,
ALL DAY, EVERY DAY.
IT'S KINDA LIKE
CALIFORNIA,
EXCEPT WITH NO BEACHES
OR PALM TREES.
OR MOVIE STARS.
OH, YOU'D
BE SURPRISED.
PLUS, IN PRISON,
YOU HAVE MORE OPTIONS.
YOU HAVE GAS, ELECTRIC
OR LETHAL INJECTION.
I DON'T THINK THE GUY
WANTS TO SLEEP THAT LONG.
PERSONALLY, I'D RECOMMEND
THE FURNACE OVER THE
ELECTRIC BLANKET,
BECAUSE THEY HAVE THESE
PROGRAMMABLE THERMOSTATS.
THEY CAN BE SET
TO BE CONSTANTLY ADJUSTING
THE TEMPERATURE
IN THE HOUSE.
OH, YEAH.
AROUND HERE
THEY'RE CALLED HUSBANDS.
THERE IS
ANOTHER OPTION!
YOU KNOW, BACK IN THE
'70s THERE WAS THIS
ROCK 'N' ROLL GROUP
AND THEY WERE CALLED
THREE DOG NIGHT.
YOU GOT ANY IDEA WHERE
THEY GOT THAT NAME FROM?
A FRAT PARTY?
NO. NO.
FROM AUSTRALIA.
'CAUSE SOMETIMES
THEY SLEEP WITH DOGS.
SURE SOUNDS LIKE
A FRAT PARTY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
FORGET ABOUT GAS.
FORGET ABOUT ELECTRICITY.
THE CHEAPEST WAY
TO STAY WARM
IS JUST TO WEAR
MORE CLOTHES TO BED.
HA!
YEAH, OKAY, BUT WHAT
ABOUT WHEN YOU WANNA...
WHAT?
YOU KNOW...
YOU KNOW.
OH, I KNOW I KNOW.
I'M JUST NOT SURE YOU KNOW.
I'M TALKING ABOUT...
I'M TALKING ABOUT WHEN
YOU WANT TO DO
SOMETHING,
BUT YOU HAVE
ALL THOSE CLOTHES ON.
WELL, YOU JUST KEEP YOUR
SLIPPERS NEAR THE EDGE
OF THE BED,
AND DON'T TAKE THE FLAP
DOWN TILL YOU GET THERE.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE THESE
CENTRAL VAC UNITS IN
THEIR HOMES,
BUT I GOT TO THINKING,
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING THIS GOOD
SHOULDN'T BE WASTED ON
HOUSECLEANING.
AND I USED TO GO DOWN TO THE
BIG EATON STORE IN TORONTO.
AND THEY HAD
VACUUM TUBES THERE
FOR TAKING MESSAGES FROM
ONE AREA TO ANOTHER.
LIKE MAYBE CHECKING ON
THE PRICE OF SOMETHING
OR GETTING YOU YOUR BILL
OR TELLING THE MANAGER THERE
WAS A 9-YEAR-OLD KID IN
A FLANNEL SHIRT
TRYING TO STEAL
FISHING LURES.
SO THIS TIME ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
TO TURN YOUR CENTRAL VAC
INTO AN IN-HOUSE, TWO-WAY
MESSAGE DELIVERY SYSTEM.
FIRST THING YOU WANNA DO IS
RE-WIRE THE RECEPTACLE
SO THAT IT'S CONTROLLED
BY THIS WALL SWITCH.
LIKE THIS...
SO THAT'S WHERE THEY GO.
NEXT YOU NEED A
COUPLE OF MAILBOXES.
YOU CAN ACTUALLY
GET THESE CHEAP,
AS LONG AS IT'S DARK AND
YOU'VE GOT A STRONG
FRONT BUMPER.
THESE ARE GOING TO
BECOME OUR MESSAGE CENTRES.
TO HOOK THE UNIT UP TO THE
CENTRAL VAC SYSTEM,
YOU NEED SOME PVC PIPE
AND A COUPLE OF ELBOWS.
AND THAT WAY ANYTHING THAT'S
TRAVELING THROUGH THE SYSTEM
WILL BE DEFLECTED
INTO THE MAILBOX.
NOW, SENDING MESSAGES, WELL,
THAT'S A LITTLE TRICKIER,
BECAUSE YOU NEED SOMETHING THAT
WILL FUNNEL EVERYTHING
INTO THE PIPE.
I'M ACTUALLY GOING TO USE
PIECES OFF THESE HIGHWAY
SAFETY CONES.
YOU CAN ACTUALLY GET THESE
WHILE YOU'RE GETTING
THE MAILBOXES.
YOU NEED TO GET
TWO OF THESE UNITS
SO THAT YOU AND YOUR WIFE
CAN EACH HAVE ONE, SEE,
AND THEN WHEREVER
YOU ARE IN THE HOUSE
YOU JUST PLUG IT INTO THE
NEAREST CENTRAL VAC OUTLET.
THE ONLY OTHER DETAIL IS
CONTROLLING THE AIRFLOW.
SEE, I PUNCHED A HOLE IN
THE SIDE OF THE MAILBOX,
AND IN THE RECEIVE POSITION,
THE HOLE IS COVERED
BY THIS PLUG THAT
I TOOK OUR OF OUR BATHTUB.
IT MEANS BERNICE AND I
CAN ONLY TAKE SHOWERS NOW,
BUT THAT'S FINE.
I MEAN, THE TWO OF US
HAVING A BATH TOGETHER
LOOKS LIKE THE MANATEE
EXHIBIT AT MARINELAND.
BUT RIGHT NOW I WANNA SEND
BERNICE A MESSAGE.
SO WHAT I DO IS
I MOVE MY DISPATCH ARM
INTO THE SEND POSITION.
THAT MOVES THE BATHTUB
PLUG AWAY FROM THE HOLE
AND ALLOWS AIR TO FLOW
INTO THE SYSTEM,
BECAUSE AIR IS KINDA
LIKE A MARRIED MAN...
IT'LL ALWAYS TAKE THE
PATH OF LEAST RESISTANCE.
OKAY, BERNICE IS UPSTAIRS
IN THE HOUSE SOMEWHERE.
I'M JUST GONNA SEND HER
THIS LITTLE MESSAGE.
NOW I JUST SWING THE ARM DOWN
INTO THE RECEIVE POSITION.
THERE WE GO.
WONDER WHAT SHE SAID?
[ APPLAUSE ]
I THINK I FIGURED OUT
THE EXACT MOMENT
WHEN MEN STARTED
TO GO HORRIBLY OFF TRACK.
IT WASN'T THE
FIRST SUPERBOWL
OR A VILLAGE PEOPLE CONCERT
OR WHEN THEY INTRODUCED
BOTTOMLESS DRINKS
AT THE TOPLESS BAR.
IT WAS THE DAY SOMEBODY
INVENTED AUTOMATIC
TRANSMISSION.
THAT CHANGED US FOREVER.
SUDDENLY DRIVING
A CAR WAS EASY.
THAT'S A BAD THING.
MEN ONLY LIKE TWO
THINGS TO BE EASY...
EXAMS AND WOMEN.
AND WE DON'T STUDY
FOR EITHER ONE OF THEM.
DRIVING NEEDS
TO BE DIFFICULT,
BECAUSE IF A MAN
IS DOING SOMETHING
THAT DOESN'T TAKE
BOTH HANDS AND BOTH FEET,
HIS MIND WILL WANDER, AND IT
DOESN'T STOP AND ASK
FOR DIRECTIONS.
AND IF YOU ASK ME,
WOMEN WOULD PREFER
TO DATE A GUY
WHO HAS STANDARD
TRANSMISSION,
'CAUSE IF HE'S A YOUNG MAN,
YOU KNOW HE'S GOTTA KEEP
HIS HANDS TO HIMSELF;
AND IF HE'S AN OLD GUY,
THERE'S LESS CHANCE THAT
HIS LEG WILL FALL ASLEEP.
SO THE NEXT TIME
YOU BUY A CAR,
GET ONE WITH A CLUTCH
AND A GEAR SHIFT.
LET'S GET BACK TO THE DAYS
WHEN OUR CAREERS WERE MOVING
FORWARD AND OUR CARS
WERE STALLING,
RATHER THAN
THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
REMEMBER I'M
PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
EVEN IF YOU'VE BEEN LIVING
A THREE-PLY LIFESTYLE
ON A TWO-PLY BUDGET,
DON'T SKIMP ON YOUR
SEPTIC MAINTENANCE.
THAT'S ONE PLACE
YOU DON'T WANNA BE
OVER YOUR HEAD.
WELL, I GOT A
CHAIN LETTER FROM HAROLD,
WHICH IS NOT
A BIG SURPRISE,
BUT HEY, WAIT A MINUTE,
WHAT'S THIS?
A CHAIN LETTER
FROM WINSTON, HUH?
I AM HAVING A SPECIAL
KIND OF DAY, AREN'T I?
HEY, RED,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WELL, YOU DON'T THROW
CHAIN LETTERS IN
THE GARBAGE!
OH, NO, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, I EXPECTED A CHAIN
LETTER FROM HAROLD,
BUT NOT FROM YOU, WINSTON.
LOOK, RED, YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO SEND CHAIN LETTERS
TO 10 PEOPLE YOU KNOW.
IN A TOWN THIS SIZE,
YOU'RE BOUND TO GET
SOME OVERLAP.
YEAH, WELL,
YOU KNOW, WINSTON,
I DON'T MIND YOU GETTIN'
INVOLVED IN THIS CHAIN
LETTER THING,
OH, I SENSE A BIG
"BUT" COMING HERE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WELL, I WAS HOPING
I'D FIND YOU TWO HERE.
I'VE GOT A LITTLE
CHAIN LETTER HERE
FROM YOURS TRULY
TO EACH OF YOU.
DALTON, ISN'T THE
STAMP A LOT CHEAPER
THAN YOU DRIVING
ALL THE WAY OVER HERE?
YEAH, BUT IT'S
NOT AS FAST.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S NOT ALWAYS
ABOUT MONEY, RED.
YOU KNOW, RED'S TOTALLY
AGAINST THIS CHAIN
LETTER THING, EH?
HE FEELS THAT PEOPLE
SHOULD GIVE UP ALL HOPE
OF EVER TRYING TO
IMPROVE THEIR SITUATION.
WELL, EVERY YEAR I LOOK
AT THE FORTUNE 500 LIST,
AND I NEVER SEE ANYBODY
ON THERE WHO MADE IT
BY SENDING OUT
CHAIN LETTERS.
WELL, THAT'S
THE WAY I FELT,
BUT LOOK AT WHAT
HAPPENED TO HAROLD.
NOTHING HAPPENED TO HAROLD.
HE'S ALWAYS BEEN LIKE THAT.
NO, NO, NO.
THE LETTER.
THE CHAIN LETTER!
AND THE NEXT DAY HE
GOT $100 BILL IN THE MAIL.
$100!
FOR NOTHING.
JUST LIKE THAT!
A HUNDRED
DOLLARS!
I GOT LETTERS TO DELIVER.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER!
YEAH, ME TOO!
Red: WE WERE TRYING TO GET A
LITTLE IRRIGATION GOING
OUT BEHIND THE LODGE.
IT WAS PRETTY
DRY BACK THERE.
[ CHUCKLING ]
SORRY, WALTER.
SORRY. SORRY. SORRY.
JUST A LITTLE ACCIDENT.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
HEH, HEH. OH, BOY.
OKAY, THAT WASN'T.
THAT'S NOT AN ACCIDENT.
THAT WAS JUST A --
NO, THAT'S JUST PURE FUN.
AND THEN -- NOW, THE TROUBLE
WITH THAT IS
NOW MIKE'S TRYING TO
KEEP THE BOX DRY AND SO ON.
AND YOU'RE A LITTLE
DAMP THERE, MIKE.
MIKE HAD BROUGHT THESE
UNDERGROUND SPRINKLER SYSTEMS.
THIS IS A GREAT THING.
SO MEANWHILE THEY'RE TRYING
TO GET THIS THING --
SO I'M SAYING WHY ARE THEY
BOTHERING WITH THE REGULAR --
THE REGULAR
SPRINKLER ON THERE?
[ RED CHUCKLING ]
SORRY, GUYS.
SORRY. SORRY. SORRY.
SO WE GET THE IRRIGATION --
AND MIKE LET THE COIL GO,
AND THAT
KNOCKS WALTER OVER,
AND THEN, UH --
OKAY, THAT'S NOT MY FAULT.
IT'S JUST A --
A VALVE JUST WENT.
THERE'S NOTHING I --
NO, DON'T KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED THERE.
SO GUYS, I THINK YOU'RE
DIGGIN' HER A LITTLE DEEP.
UH, YOU ONLY GO
DOWN ABOUT SIX INCHES.
BUT LIKE I SAY --
BOY, THE GROUND
IS SO HARD.
SO I FIGURE FROM HERE ON OUT,
YOU KNOW WHAT WE'LL DO?
JUST KINDA PILE
THE GRASS OVER IT.
I DIDN'T REALISE
THAT THEY HAD ACTUALLY
BURIED QUITE A BIT
OF THE PIPE WAY DOWN THERE,
BUT I HAD DONE MY PART,
AND I FIGURED WHY NOT JUST
RELAX FOR A MINUTE OR TWO?
AND WALTER AND MIKE WERE JUST
GONNA GO AND GIVE IT A TRY.
TRY OUR NEW SPRINKLER SYSTEM
AND SEE HOW SHE WORKED.
BUT THEY TURNED HER ON,
AND THEY'RE LOOKIN' FOR THE
LITTLE HEADS TO POP OUT
BUT THERE'S NOTHIN' --
NOTHIN' HAPPENIN'.
THEY CAN'T QUITE FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S GOIN' ON,
BUT YOU COULD HEAR THERE WAS
WATER RUNNING SOMEWHERE.
AND I'M STARTIN'
TO GET A --
I'M DREAMING I'M ON
THE TITANIC AT THIS POINT,
AND THEY'RE LOOKIN' AROUND,
TRYING TO FEEL
WHAT'S GOIN' ON.
AND WE GOT A PROBLEM.
AND THEY DOWN
REAL CLOSE THERE,
ALL OF A SUDDEN THEY GET
THE ONE HEAD TO POP UP,
BUT IT'S JUST NOT --
IT'S NOT --
THERE'S WHERE
THE WATER IS.
SHE'S CAUGHT IN
SOME KIND OF A --
BOY, A BIG JELLY
THING THERE,
AND WALTER DECIDES TO
JUST NAIL THAT WITH THE AXE
AND JUST RELEASE
THE PRESSURE,
AND UP COMES THE WATER.
GUESS WHO GOT IT ALL?
AS CONNIE FRANCIS
WOULD SAY...
WHO'S SORRY NOW?
.
YOU KNOW WHAT REALLY
FRENCHES MY FRIES?
BORROWING SOMEONE'S CAR
AND THEN FINDING OUT
IT DOESN'T EVEN
HAVE POWER STEERING.
I MEAN, DRIVING'S SUPPOSED
TO BE PLEASANT AND RELAXING.
IF I WANTED
A WORKOUT, I'D --
WELL, I WOULDN'T
WANT A WORKOUT.
DON'T PANIC.
THERE'S ALWAYS A BETTER WAY.
GET YOURSELF ONE OF THESE
HEAVY DUTY STEERING
WHEEL COVERS HERE.
MAKE IT AN EXTRA LARGE.
YOU CAN GET THESE OFF A BUS
WHILE THE DRIVER'S IN
THE MEN'S ROOM.
WE'RE GOING TO SLIP THAT OVER
THE STEERING WHEEL ITSELF
BUT YOU NEED IT EXTRA BIG
BECAUSE WE'RE GONNA POWER IT
WITH THIS CORDLESS DRILL.
OKAY, THE KEY HERE IS THE RATIO
BETWEEN THE DIAMETER OF THE
STEERING WHEEL
AND THE SIZE OF THE PULLEY
THAT'S GOING INTO THE
CHUCK OF THE DRILL.
I FIGURE 500:1
IS THE CORRECT RATIO.
SO IF THE STEERING
WHEEL IS 17 INCHES,
ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS DIVIDE THAT BY 500.
YOU KNOW, MATHEMATICAL
FORMULAS MAY BE FINE
FOR SOME PEOPLE,
BUT I PREFER
TRIAL AND ERROR --
EVEN THOUGH IT SOMETIMES
LEADS TO TRIAL BY FIRE
AND OCCASIONALLY
TRIAL BY JURY.
SO I JUST TRIED A BUNCH OF
DIFFERENT THINGS.
STUCK 'EM INTO THE
CHUCK OF THE DRILL.
FOR EXAMPLE, TRIED
A BABY CARRIAGE WHEEL.
TOO BIG.
WENT WITH A SCREW NAIL,
TOO SMALL.
WHAT I AM GOING WITH IS
A GHERKIN PICKLE.
THIS BABY WORKS
LIKE A CHARM.
CHECK THIS OUT.
WHAT'S THAT YOU SAY?
WHAT IF I WANT
TO TURN THE OTHER WAY?
WELL, HEY, THIS IS
A REVERSING DRILL.
WELL, THE WHOLE LODGE
IS REALLY GETTIN' BEHIND
THIS WHOLE
CHAIN LETTER THING.
THIS IS THE
INCOMING PILE.
NOT TOO EXCITED
ABOUT THAT.
IT'S THE LETTERS GOING OUT
THAT WE'RE FOCUSSING ON.
GET THE LEAD OUT OF
THERE, DALTON, EH?
I'M TRYING TO MAKE
THE 5:00 MAIL PICK-UP.
AND RATHER THAN PITCH IN,
YOU'VE CHOSEN TO USE
HARSH WORDS?
WHERE AM I,
AT HOME?
Winston:
YEAH, COME ON, RED.
HELP OUT HERE.
I'VE GOT SO MUCH GLUE
ON MY T-T-TONGUE
I CAN'T EVEN --
TALK?
MORE CHAIN LETTERS.
WHERE SHOULD I PUT THEM?
IN THE GARBAGE CAN.
UH, IT'S
UNDER THE PILE.
I OWE YOU GUYS
AN APOLOGY.
I SHOULD NEVER HAVE
DRAGGED YOU INTO THIS
STUPID CHAIN LETTER.
OH, DON'T BE CUTE,
HAROLD.
WE ALL KNOW ABOUT
YOUR LITTLE WINDFALL.
OH, THAT.
WELL, I TOOK
SOME BEANO.
I THINK IT PRETTY
MUCH BROKE IT UP.
NO, NO, NO!
THE M-M-MONEY YOU GOT
IN THE M-M-M --
MAIL.
I DIDN'T GET ANY
MONEY IN THE MAIL.
THE $100 BILL,
HAROLD.
I DIDN'T
GET A HUNDRED --
I DIDN'T GET $100 BILL;
I GOT A BILL FOR $100.
OVERDUE
LIBRARY BOOKS.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO ASK US
FOR THE MONEY.
NO, I ALWAYS EXPECT
SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
SO I ALWAYS PUT A LITTLE
BIT OF MONEY AWAY EACH
WEEK IN MY CASH BOX.
OH, BOY.
OKAY.
WE BETTER GO.
UNCLE RED!
YES, HAROLD?
DO YOU HAVE AN EXPLANATION
I'M EXPECTED TO BELIEVE?
UH, YES, I DO,
HAROLD.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU STARTED THE
WHOLE CHAIN LETTER THING,
WHICH I BELIEVE INTRODUCED
THE CONCEPT OF GETTING
SOMETHING FOR NOTHING,
AND THAT WAS JUST
A SLIPPERY SLOPE
FOR US TAKING MONEY OUT
OF YOUR CASH BOX
TO COVER OUR COSTS HERE.
SO IN A WAY,
THIS IS YOUR FAULT.
OKAY, NO, OKAY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'LL PAY YOU BACK.
IN CASH?
WELL, CASH IS GOVERNMENT
CURRENCY, RIGHT?
YES, IT IS.
SO ARE STAMPS.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
AWAY YOU GO.
I THINK WE'RE EVEN.
SO IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I LEARNED A LITTLE
LESSON TODAY.
NAMELY THAT YOU DON'T NEED A
CHAIN LETTER TO GET LUCKY,
BUT AGAIN,
THAT'S YOUR CALL.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
COME ON, GUYS,
HAVE A SEAT.
MEETING'S COMING TO ORDER.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
EVERYONE SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO
I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
THIS WHOLE CHAIN LETTER FIASCO
HAS POINTED OUT WE HAVE
A REAL SMALL GENE POOL
IN OUR AREA, AND WE GOTTA
WARN THE YOUNG PEOPLE
THAT IF YOUR
GIRLFRIEND LOOKS LIKE YOU,
THERE'S A PRETTY GOOD CHANCE
YOU'RE EACH GIVING
THE SAME GIFT
TO THE SAME GUY
ON FATHER'S DAY.