IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
AND NOW, HERE'S THE REASON
GOD CREATED NO-FAULT INSURANCE,
THE ALL-FAULT GUY,
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WELL, SHE'S A BIG DAY
FOR A SPECIAL YOUNG MAN
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE.
HAROLD,
YOU GOT AN
ANNOUNCEMENT?
NO.
OH, COME ON NOW.
HE'S A LITTLE SHY.
HAROLD HAS GOTTEN
HIS DRIVER'S LICENSE.
HE'S WELL ON HIS WAY
TO BECOMING A MAN,
BECAUSE NOW HE HAS
A REASON TO GET A VEHICLE.
ONCE HE GETS THAT VEHICLE,
HE WILL BE A MAN,
UNLESS IT'S, LIKE,
AN '87 SUNBIRD.
OK, OK, YEAH, OK, YES,
I TOOK THE DRIVING TEST.
BUT I HAD SOME MISHAPS,
SOME MISCUES,
AND PROPERTY DAMAGE.
YOU FLUNKED AGAIN?
YEAH.
I HAD THE SAME
DRIVING EXAMINER AS LAST TIME.
THERE'S ONLY ONE
DRIVING EXAMINER
IN THE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
I SHOULD HAVE EXPECTED THAT.
SHE GAVE ME
THE BENEFIT OF THE DOUBT,
UNTIL I RAN OVER HER FOOT --
I DIDN'T SIGNAL.
YEAH, I KNOW.
SAME FOOT AS LAST TIME --
SHE WAS TICKED.
YOU GOT TO GET RIGHT BACK UP
ON THAT HORSE.
YOU GOT TO GO THERE TOMORROW
AND TAKE THE TEST AGAIN.
NO, I CAN'T DO THAT.
WHY NOT?
THERE'S VARIOUS REASONS,
BUT NUMBER ONE IS THAT
THE TEST CAR DOESN'T COME BACK
FROM THE AUTOBODY SHOP
TILL NEXT WEEK.
THAT WILL SLOW ME UP SOME.
SHE SAYS I HAVE TO TAKE LESSONS
BEFORE I CAN RETEST.
NOBODY IN THEIR RIGHT MIND
WOULD GIVE YOU DRIVING LESSONS.
YOU WILL? -- THANK YOU.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MAIN MESSAGE BEING,
FOR GOSH SAKES,
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
IF ANY OF YOU
ARE DRIVING INSTRUCTORS,
I'LL TELL YOU,
YOU ARE ALL UNDERPAID.
IT SAYS "DRIVER WILL COME TO
A COMPLETE STOP
"FOUR METERS PRIOR TO
THE INTERSECTION,
"CREEP FORWARD,
COME TO
ANOTHER
COMPLETE STOP,
"PRIOR TO ENTERING
SAID INTERSECTION."
THERE ARE TWO KINDS OF PEOPLE,
THOSE WHO DO THINGS,
AND THOSE WHO WRITE MANUALS.
A ROLLING STOP IS FINE.
(Laughing)
ROLLING STOP DOESN'T MEAN
ROLLING OVER.
WE WERE AROUND THAT CORNER
ON TWO WHEELS.
THE POSSUM VAN ONLY HAS
TWO GOOD WHEELS.
BESIDES,
THERE WAS NOBODY COMING.
SO YOU STOP
WHEN YOU SEE CARS COMING?
YEAH...
IF IT'S GOT LIGHTS ON THE ROOF.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO,
IF YOU'RE GOING TO TEACH ME
TO DRIVE, IT HAS TO BE BY
PROPER TRAFFIC RULES.
IN 35 YEARS,
I'VE NEVER HAD A PROBLEM.
YOU HAVEN'T,
BUT EVERYONE ELSE SURE HAS.
DO YOU WANT TO BE ON THE ROAD
DRIVING WITH PEOPLE
WHO DRIVE LIKE YOU?
I THOUGHT NOT.
(Red): LATER ON WE'VE GOT
AN ADVENTURE WITH BILL
FEATURING TENNIS, OBVIOUSLY.
HE'S JUST WARMING UP A BIT.
GIVE ME THE RACQUET.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
OW, OW, OW.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
SO, HE'S GOT THE WARM-UP BALLS
THERE, AND THE VARIOUS
ANIMAL-TRAP CONTAINERS THERE.
AWAY YOU GO, BILL.
GET OVER THERE.
GO ON, GET OVER THERE.
AWAY YOU GO.
GET OVER THERE.
HE MAY NOT BE QUITE FIT ENOUGH
FOR THIS...
TENNIS HAS A LONG HISTORY
OF PEOPLE
WHO SHOULDN'T BE PLAYING IT.
SO WE'RE RIGHT IN LINE
WITH THAT.
IT'S MORE OF
AN OLDER PERSON'S GAME.
OH, YOU GOT YOUR BOUNCER.
OH!
IT WAS A POOR CHOICE.
BUT HE'S ALL RIGHT.
OH, OH, GOLLY!
THE RACQUETS
ARE MUCH BIGGER THESE DAYS.
I GUESS BILL DIDN'T KNOW--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU JUST NEED A COUPLE.
YOU NEED
JUST A COUPLE IN THERE.
OH.
IT'S LIKE THAT BIG BUCKET
OF FRIED CHICKEN.
SERVES 20.
OH BOY.
HE'S STARTING TO LOOK
A BIT LIKE A CHICKEN, ISN'T HE?
WOW.
WAY YOU GO, WAY YOU GO.
OH, MAN, MISTER AGILITY.
MAKE A WISH.
THERE WE GO.
HE CAN'T HANDLE THE HEAT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, ALL RIGHT.
NO, THAT'S AN APPLE.
BILL, BILL.
THAT'S AN APPLE.
OH, BOY, HE'S GOT
A WICKED SLICE.
OH, WELL, THERE'S AN UP SIDE.
OHHH
MY UNCLE
HAS A DAIRY FARM
A MAN
WHO LIKES TO PUTTER
HE SLIPPED AND FELL OFF
THE ROOF ONE DAY
AND LANDED IN THE BUTTER
HE FLIPPED AND FLOPPED
FOR AN HOUR OR MORE
TILL HE WAS RESCUED
BY HIS WIFE
SHE WARNED HIM THAT BUTTER
IS BAD FOR HIS HEALTH
BUT HE CLAIMS
IT SAVED HIS LIFE
THIS IS FOR THE BIG ONE,
A WATER-BALLOON LAUNCHER
AND 40 AIR-SICK BAGS.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. FRANKLIN
TO SAY THIS WORD.
CANADA.
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT,
DOUGIE,
A COUNTRY.
THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA.
OK, THIS IS AMERICA'S
LARGEST TRADING PARTNER.
THE DALLAS COWBOYS.
NO -- I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE SECOND BIGGEST COUNTRY
IN THE WORLD.
IT'S GOTTA BE TEXAS.
THINK COUNTRY, OK?
THIS IS A COUNTRY
DIRECTLY NORTH OF AMERICA.
ALASKA.
THE LONGEST UNDEFENDED BORDER
IN THE WORLD
IS BETWEEN THE U.S.A. AND...
FRANCE,
I BELIEVE.
(Laughing)
MONSIEUR.
DOUGIE, I WAS BORN
IN THIS PLACE.
HOME FOR UNWED MOTHERS.
(Laughing)
I'M TALKING ABOUT
WHERE WE ARE RIGHT NOW.
WHERE ARE WE, RIGHT HERE?
OH, OH,
ONTARIARI--
NO, NO, NO.
MANITOULIN--
NOVA SOMETHIN'.
THOSE ARE PROVINCES.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
WE'RE OUT OF TIME.
WAY TO GO.
OH, THAT'S STILL A COUNTRY?
(Laughing and applause)
THIS WEEK
WE'RE GONNA MAKE A PROJECT
THAT'S GOING TO MAKE YOU
POPULAR WITH THE KIDS.
WE'LL BUILD OUR OWN
AIR-HOCKEY GAME.
YOU GOT TWO BASIC PRINCIPLES:
HOLES, AND YOU GOT WIND
GOING THROUGH THEM.
WE'VE ALL BEEN THERE.
YOU NEED A COUPLE OF DRYERS.
YOU CAN PICK THESE UP
AT A GARAGE SALE,
OR IF YOU STAY UP LATE,
YOU CAN HOIST A COUPLE
OUT OF A LAUNDROMAT.
THE DRYERS ARE FREE,
BUT THE QUARTERS
TO KEEP THEM RUNNING
WILL EVENTUALLY BREAK YA.
PLUG UP THE EXHAUST
SO THAT THE AIR WILL GO
WHERE YOU WANT IT TO GO.
THE VENT IS IN THE BACK.
PLUG HER UP WITH A BALL
OR A SMALL HOUSEPLANT.
THESE UNITS ALREADY HAVE
A FAIR AMOUNT OF LINT BUILD-UP.
THAT WILL DO THE JOB FOR US.
SOMEBODY MUST HAVE DRIED
A CAT IN THERE.
PUSH THESE DRYERS TOGETHER.
AND THEN KEEP THEM TOGETHER
USING THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
THERE'S ALWAYS ONE, ISN'T THERE?
HA, HA, HA, HA, HA!
SO THAT'S WHERE THEY GO!
HOCKEY IS A REAL PHYSICAL GAME
WITH THE SLAP SHOTS
AND THE CROSS-CHECKING,
AND THE INEVITABLE FIST FIGHTS.
SO MAKE SURE
YOU HORSE THESE BABIES DOWN.
OK, REMEMBER THAT WE PLUGGED UP
ALL THE EXHAUST VENTS.
SO NOW WE PUNCH SOME HOLES
IN THE TOP
SO THE AIR WILL BLOW UP.
NOT BLOW UP -- BOOM.
BLOW UP -- PHHHT.
THIS COULD TAKE
LONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
THERE WE GO.
BOY, THAT'S A LITTLE ROUGHER
THAN WHAT I...
WHAT YOU DO NOW, OF COURSE, IS
YOU ADD ANOTHER LAYER ON THAT.
OK, OUR NEW SURFACE NOW
WILL BE PEGBOARD.
YOU'LL PROBABLY FIND A HUNK
OF THIS OVER YOUR WORK BENCH.
I NEVER USED IT ALL THAT MUCH
ANYHOW.
ACTUALLY, I DATED A GIRL
NAMED PEG BOARD.
SHE ENDED UP MARRYING
A REAL TOOL.
WHEN YOU PUT THE PEGBOARD ON,
MAKE SURE YOU'VE GOT
THE SMOOTH SIDE UP.
THIS IS WHAT THEY CALL
GOOD-ONE-SIDE.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
SO WAS THE GIRL I DATED.
WE GOT HER ALL SET.
I GOT A JAR LID.
THAT'S MY PUCK.
AND I GOT BOWLS
TO HIT IT WITH.
THE BEAUTY OF USING A DRYER
IS YOU'VE GOT THE TIMER.
EVEN GET A BUZZER THAT GOES OFF
WHEN THE GAME'S OVER.
YOU CAN BE ANY TEAM.
IF YOU WANT TO BE
A EUROPEAN TEAM,
JUST SET HER ON DELICATE.
REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
IT'S HOCKEY NIGHT IN CANADA.
(Crashing)
WOW, MY FIRST BREAK-AWAY.
WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
I WANT TO TALK TO
YOU OLDER FOLKS
ABOUT A LITTLE SECRET
THAT WE ALL SHARE.
IT'S ABOUT SOMETHING CALLED
WISDOM.
WE MAY NOT HAVE AS MUCH OF IT
AS YOUNG PEOPLE THINK WE DO.
NOW, I KNOW WE ALL KNOW
THE FASTEST ROUTE
TO THE COTTAGE
AND THE BEST FOOD AND
THE BEST MUSIC AND T.V. SHOWS.
THAT'S MORE A SIGN OF OUR MINDS
NARROWING, NOT DEEPENING.
WHEN I WAS LITTLE, I THOUGHT
ALL OLD PEOPLE WERE WISE,
UNTIL THEY'D OPEN THEIR MOUTHS.
THEN I'D REALIZE,
"WHAT A STUPID OLD COOT."
(Laughing)
SO AS YOU GET ON IN YEARS,
LEARN TO FAKE WISDOM...
WITH SILENCE.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE
A KNOWING BRAIN,
FAKE IT WITH A KNOWING SMILE.
WHEN YOU NOD AND SMILE,
PEOPLE WILL THINK, WELL...
EXACTLY.
IN EXTREME CASES, YOU CAN ADD
A WINK AND A CHUCKLE.
'CAUSE YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT SAYS.
WELL, THAT SAYS...
(Chuckling)
(Laughing)
REMEMBER, I'M PULLIN' FOR YA,
BECAUSE, WELL...
(Chuckling)
(Coughing)
THAT WASN'T TOO BAD, HAROLD.
OLD LADY BENKMAN YELLED A LOT
BUT I THINK THOSE SHRUBS
WERE ALREADY DEAD.
OH, THAT POSSUM VAN'S BIG, HUH?
OOH, THAT'S GOT
SOME POWER THERE, I'LL TELL YA!
YEAH, YEAH.
I MEANT TO TELL YOU.
IT WILL GO FASTER
THAN SEVEN MILES AN HOUR.
I WAS MAINTAINING
A SAFE SPEED LIMIT.
IT'S NOT A GOLF CART.
WHEN YOU STOP FOR A HITCHHIKER
AND THEY SAY, "NO, I'M IN
A HURRY," THAT'S A CLUE.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
IF YOU CAN SMELL
YOUR OWN EXHAUST, THAT'S NATURE
SAYING, "PICK UP THE PACE."
OK, THAT'S GOOD, OK.
I CAN PICK UP THE PACE.
HOW WERE THE TURNS?
UH, INTERESTING --
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE LETTING GO
OF THE STEERING WHEEL
SOON ENOUGH...
UNLESS YOU MEANT TO MAKE
THE U-TURN IN THE TUNNEL.
AGAIN, A GOOD POINT.
I'LL TRY TO REMEMBER THAT.
PICK UP THE PACE,
WORK ON THE TURNS...
I GOT BRAKES DOWN COLD, THOUGH.
YOU SLAPPED THE BINDERS ON.
THE WINDSHIELD'S HARD,
ISN'T IT?
HOW'S YOUR HEAD?
I'M GONNA HAVE
A LUMP, YEAH.
OHHH!
ALL RIGHT, WELCOME TO
"AUTO BIOGRAPHY", WHERE, UH...
... MEMBERS OF POSSUM LODGE
GET TO HAVE REMEMBRANCES
OF CARS GONE BY.
WE GOT MIKE HAMAR HERE.
MIKE'S GONNA TELL US ABOUT
HIS FAVOURITE CAR OF ALL TIME.
AW, THAT'S EASY, MR. GREEN.
CORVETTE STINGRAY.
WHAT A SET OF WHEELS.
WHO COULD RESIST A 'VETTE?
NOT ME.
NO.
THAT WAS A BEAUTIFUL CAR, MIKE.
I REMEMBER THE FIRST 'VETTE
I TOOK FOR A SPIN.
IT WAS PARKED IN FRONT
OF THE CONVENIENCE STORE...
KEYS IN THE IGNITION,
THERE... IDLING.
MAN!
SO YOU DIDN'T ACTUALLY OWN
A CORVETTE.
WELL, NO, BUT, YOU KNOW,
FOR AN HOUR IT WAS MINE.
OH.
AND FAST? SHE COULD OUTRUN
ANY POLICE CRUISER ON THE ROAD.
THAT WAS ONE GREAT CAR.
I KNEW GUYS
WHO USED TO BOOST A 'VETTE
AND THEN SELL IT FOR PARTS.
TO ME, THAT IS CRIMINAL.
IT'S CRIMINAL.
CUTTIN' UP
A 'VETTE.
I MEAN, HUH!
YOU KNOW, MR. HAMAR,
YOU MIGHT REMIND OUR VIEWERS
THAT CAR THEFT OF ANY KIND
IS A BAD THING TO DO.
A BAD THING TO DO.
(Audience laughing)
OH, YEAH, WELL, YEAH, FOR SURE.
YOU KNOW, I LOVE 'VETTES,
BUT I NOW KNOW
THAT A FEW HOURS OF FUN
IS NOT WORTH TWO TO FIVE
IN MINIMUM SECURITY.
SO I WOULD SAY IF YOU WANT
A CORVETTE, BUY ONE.
YEAH, BUT THEY ARE EXPENSIVE,
ARE THEY NOT?
YEAH, THEY ARE EXPENSIVE,
BUT IF YOU FIND THE RIGHT BANK,
LIKE ON A FRIDAY
WHEN THEY GOT A LOT OF CASH...
(Audience laughing)
MIKE, NOW, REMEMBER
HOW THAT
ENDED?
OH, YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT, MR. GREEN.
I DON'T DO THAT NO MORE.
MAYBE YOU NEED
TO WORK HARD, SAVE YOUR MONEY,
BUILD UP A CREDIT RATING.
THEN YOU CAN GET
YOUR OWN CORVETTE,
ONE YOU ACTUALLY OWN.
THEN SOME LOSER SWIPES IT
FOR A JOY RIDE?
NO, THANKS.
(Audience laughing)
(Red): AS I TRIED
TO WARN YOU EARLIER,
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL"
THIS WEEK
IS AT THE TENNIS COURT.
I FIRE ONE UP--
OH! OHHH! OHHH!
ALL THE BALLS
CAME OUT OF HIS PANTS.
MAYBE THOSE ARE GALLSTONES.
COULDN'T CARE LESS,
TO BE HONEST.
I'LL FIRE A FEW AT BILL.
TRY THIS, BILL, TRY THIS.
JUST TRY AND RETURN
THE SERVE -- TRY THIS.
NO CHANCE!
NO CHANCE.
WHAT? WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU WUSS, GET BACK IN THERE
AND TAKE IT LIKE A MAN.
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'?
OHHH!
ALL RIGHT.
I'M STILL HERE.
(Laughing)
YEAH, I KNOW, YOU'RE GONNA
JUMP UP AND DOWN.
TRY THIS.
NO CHANCE.
(Laughing)
BOY, TENNIS IS
A FUN, FUN, FUN GAME.
WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
OH! UH-OH!
UH-OH!
HE'S GOT AN IDEA.
AHHHH!
OK, I SEE.
HE'S GONNA TAKE HIS RACQUET...
YOU NEED SOMETHING
TO ATTACH THAT WITH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'?
NOTHIN' IN THERE YOU CAN USE.
DON'T USE--
BILL, DON'T USE THAT.
BILL... BILL... BILL?
TENNIS IS A CLASS GAME.
USE YOUR SHOELACES.
YOUR SHOELACES... YEAH,
YOUR SHOELACES.
ALL RIGHT,
SO YOU DON'T HAVE SHOELACES.
LOOK WHAT YOU GAINED.
(Laughing)
MAN! NOW, THERE'S A RACQUET.
NICE HIT!
BEAUTIFUL! WHAT? OH!
OH!
(Bill): OHHHH!
(Red): OHHH!
BY GOLLY.
SEE WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU TRY
TO CHEAT, BOYS AND GIRLS?
I'LL GET THE TIN MAN
BACK TO THE LOCKER ROOM.
AWAY YOU GO.
(Squeaking)
(Red): THANKS TO JIM JACKSON
FOR THIS CARVIN' OF HAROLD.
WE GOT THE VAN DOWN
OFF THE GAZEBO.
WE CAN GO AGAIN IF YOU'RE SURE
WHICH PEDAL IS WHICH NOW.
I PANICKED!
I PANICKED, OK?
IT'S YOUR FAULT -- YOU TOLD ME
ALPHABETICAL ORDER.
BRAKES, GAS --
I THOUGHT YOU MEANT
ACCELERATOR, BRAKES!
EVEN IF IT IS ACCELERATOR,
"E" COMES AFTER "B"!
COME ON,
LET'S GO.
NO MORE DRIVING FOR ME.
I'M GONNA CONCENTRATE
ON THE MANUAL.
YOUR TEST IS
IN TWO HOURS.
YEAH, I KNOW,
SO HELP ME WITH THIS ONE.
"TWO DRIVERS APPROACH
AN UNMARKED INTERSECTION
"AT THE SAME TIME.
"WHO HAS THE RIGHT OF WAY?"
THE GUY IN
THE BIG TRUCK.
NO, THE GUY ON THE RIGHT
ALWAYS HAS THE RIGHT OF WAY.
UNLESS THE OTHER GUY
HAS THE BIG TRUCK.
CHECK THE MANUAL.
CHECK THE
CEMETERY.
(Audience laughing)
A LOT OF YOU KIDS
ARE LOOKIN' FOR PART-TIME WORK.
GET YOURSELF EXTRA MONEY,
BUY SOMETHING
YOUR PARENTS THINK IS STUPID.
UNFORTUNATELY, YOU'LL COME
FACE TO FACE
WITH A SAD FACT OF LIFE --
MINIMUM WAGE.
YOU'RE EXPECTED TO GIVE UP
ALL YOUR FRIDAY NIGHTS
AND WEEKENDS
FOR A PAPER HAT, FRENCH-FRY
BASKET, AND FOUR BUCKS AN HOUR.
IF IT WAS UP TO ME, I'D
GIVE YOU FIVE TIMES THAT MUCH
FOR WEARING THE DORKY UNIFORM,
BUT IT'S NOT UP TO ME.
MINIMUM WAGE IS ONE OF THOSE
THINGS LIFE THROWS AT YOU.
IT'S A DOOR
WE ALL PASS THROUGH.
IT MAY BE THE ONLY DOOR
YOU PASS THROUGH,
SO WORK HARD, TOUGH IT OUT.
IN NO TIME, YOU'RE MAKING
20, 30, MAYBE 40 CENTS
ABOVE MINIMUM WAGE.
YOU'LL BE ON EASY STREET.
WELCOME TO MY FAVOURITE PORTION
OF THE SHOW,
WHERE WE EXAMINE THOSE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
(Audience):
"I DON'T KNOW!"
EXCELLENT! WAY TO GO!
ON THE EXPERT PORTION,
JOINING MY UNCLE RED GREEN
IS HIS BEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE ROOM,
MR. DALTON
HUMPHREY!
(Applause and cheering)
OUR LETTER GOES, "DEAR EXPERTS,
I WANT TO COOK VEGETARIAN
"BUT MEAT IS ALL
MY HUSBAND WILL EAT.
"HOW CAN I GET HIM TO EAT
A BALANCED DIET?"
AHHHH!
YOU GOTTA REMEMBER THERE ARE
TWO MAJOR FOOD GROUPS.
THERE'S MEAT AND THERE'S SALT,
SO YOUR HUSBAND'S ALREADY
HALF-WAY THERE.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
HAVEN'T YOU FORGOTTEN,
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
DAIRY AND FRUITS
AND VEGETABLES AND GRAINS?
WE HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN THEM.
IF YOU CAN'T SAY ANYTHING GOOD
ABOUT SOMETHING--
AMEN.
YEAH.
(Humphrey): YEAH,
FOR A HEALTHY,
BALANCED MALE DIET,
YOU WANT TO VARY
YOUR KINDS OF MEAT.
VARIETY OF CUTS,
VARIETY OF GRADES,
VARIETY OF BARBECUE SAUCE.
YOU KNOW,
AROUND OUR HOME,
WE WILL HAVE AS MANY
AS 17 DIFFERENT KINDS
OF MEAT IN A WEEK.
(Audience laughing)
17 DIFFERENT KINDS OF MEAT?!
(Laughing)
WHAT BUTCHER SHOP
ARE YOU GOIN' TO?
YOU DON'T NEED A BUTCHER SHOP
WHEN YOU LIVE NEAR THE HIGHWAY.
(Laughing and applause)
OHHH...
NO, NO.
SO, UH, YOU'RE EATIN'
THE ROAD-KILL, ARE YOU, DALTON?
WE'RE EATING ALL-NATURAL,
ORGANICALLY RAISED,
FREE-RANGE, AUTOMOTIVELY
PROCESSED FOOD PRODUCTS.
SO, UH, DALTON, LIKE, UH...
HOW DO YOU COOK, YOU KNOW,
THE ROAD-KILL THING?
WELL, IT'S NOT HARD.
MOST OF IT'S ALREADY GRILLED.
(Audience laughing)
(Laughing)
BUT THAT'S GOTTA BE TOUGH.
SOME TOUGH
MEAT, THERE.
YEAH, SOME OF IT'S ALREADY
BEEN POUNDED TO PEMMICAN
BUT AT THE POINT
OF IMPACT, IT'S ALWAYS
PRETTY TENDER,
AND WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS
PRESENTATION,
BECAUSE THERE'S NOTHING LIKE
PRESENTATION--
OH, THAT'S TRUE.
... TO ENHANCE THE FLAVOUR.
WHAT WE DO,
WE'LL PAINT A WHITE LINE
DOWN THE CENTRE
OF THE DINING ROOM TABLE...
AND WE'LL SERVE OUR MEAL
SOMETIMES ON A HUBCAP.
I CAN JUST PICTURE
YOUR WHOLE FAMILY
BOWIN' THE HEADS FOR GRACE.
"LOOK BOTH WAYS
BEFORE YOU CROSS."
EH?
YEAH, I THINK SO.
YEAH, YEAH, BUT, YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES WE'LL SING
A COUPLE OF VERSES --
(Laughing)
WELL, I HOPE YOU TWO CLOWNS
REMEMBER YOU ARE WHAT YOU EAT.
WELL, THAT'S TRUE, HAROLD.
TELL US MORE
ABOUT YOUR VEGETABLES.
(Audience laughing)
HAROLD WENT DOWN
FOR HIS DRIVIN' TEST
SO I WOULD THINK THE EXAMINER
WILL BE SUBMITTING HER
RESIGNATION ANY MOMENT NOW.
I GOT IT!
I GOT IT, I GOT IT!
I GOT IT -- WHAT'S THAT? IT!
I GOT IT, IT, IT, IT!
(Audience laughing)
HOW DID IT GO?
I GOT IT.
OH.
I GOT 61% ON THE WRITTEN TEST.
THE EYE EXAM WAS BAD,
BUT I WAS LOOKING
INTO THE COFFEE MACHINE.
CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GOT YOUR
LICENCE -- CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU, YEAH!
YOU'RE A BIG PART OF THIS.
I HAVE YOU
TO THANK.
HAVING A GOOD TEACHER
CAN MAKE ALL THE DIFFERENCE.
MY THIRD YEAR IN GRADE 9
WAS A WHOLE NEW WORLD.
THE HEAD DRIVING EXAMINER,
HE FIGURED
IF I GOT MY LICENCE,
I'D BE DRIVING INSTEAD OF YOU.
SAID IT WAS THE LESSER
OF TWO EVILS, AND I GOT IT.
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME, MEETING TIME.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SHOW THE GUYS.
(Laughing)
I GOT IT!
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M GONNA LET HAROLD DRIVE ME
SO YOU MIGHT DUCT-TAPE
SOME TIRES
TO THE FRONT OF THE HOUSE...
WAIT UNDER THE BASEMENT STAIRS
TILL I GIVE YOU THE ALL-CLEAR.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND MR. UNSAFE-AT-ANY-SPEED,
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): I GOT MY LICENCE.
I GOT A LICENCE.
I'LL BE DRIVING,
NOW THAT I GOT A LICENCE.
ANYBODY NEEDS A RIDE SOMEWHERE?
I GOT MY LICENCE.
(Red): HAROLD! HAROLD!
(Harold): I GOT ONE OF THOSE.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
MEETING TIME! MEETING TIME!
YOU NEED A LICENCE
TO HAVE A MEETING.
(Red): SHUT UP, HAROLD.