THERE'S NOTHING WORSE THAN
ACCIDENTLY NAILING AN ANIMAL
WHEN YOU'RE OUT DRIVING
IN YOUR VEHICLE.
THE GRIEF YOU TAKE FROM THE WIFE
AND THE GREENPEACERS.
IT'S EVEN WORSE IF YOU'VE
GOT THE KIDS ON BOARD.
THEY GET SOBBING AND YOU'VE GOT
TO MAKE THEM FEEL BETTER.
YOU SAY: DON'T WORRY
THERE'S A SPECIAL SKUNK HEAVEN.
AND IT SMELLS LIKE
WE'RE NOT IN IT.
THE WORST PART IS SCRAPING ALL
THE GUNK OFF THE FRONT
OF YOUR CAR.
SO I GOT TO THINKING.
I PRE-SPRAY THE BARBEQUE
BEFORE I COOK DEAD ANIMALS,
WHY NOT DO THE SAME THING
WITH THE VAN?
OH YEAH, EVEN BUGS
FLY RIGHT OFF HERE.
YOU COULD T-BONE A MOOSE
AND AS LONG AS YOU DUCK
THE ANTLERS,
YOU CAN KEEP RIGHT ON TRUCKING.
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW.
AND NOW HERE'S A MAN WHO HAS
NO QUALMS ABOUT USING
THE WORD QUALM,
YOUR HOST AND HERO,
AND MY UNCLE:
RED GRE-E-E-N!!!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG NEWS
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
ACTUALLY, IN THE NEWS, YES SIR.
POSSUM LODGE MADE THE FRONT PAGE
OF THE PORT ASBESTOS
DAILY MOVEMENT.
A REPORTER WAS HERE YESTERDAY,
KIND OF SNOOPING AROUND,
SNAPPING PHOTOS AND
DOING INTERVIEWS,
IT WAS PRETTY EXCITING STUFF.
I THINK YOU HAVE TO LEARN
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
GOOD PRESS AND BAD PRESS.
THAT REPORTER WASN'T
UP HERE DOING A PLEASANT
HUMAN INTEREST STORY.
OH NO?
OH NO!
HE WAS ASKING LODGE MEMBERS
SOME PRETTY TOUGH QUESTIONS.
ABOUT THE FLOATING FURNITURE
OUT ON THE LAKE, THERE.
ALL THE PETROLEUM STAINS
ON THE GROUND.
WHY IS THAT SNOWMOBILE PILE
SMOULDERING LIKE THAT?
YOU WOULD KNOW THESE THINGS
IF YOU DIDN'T LOCK YOURSELF
IN THE POSSUM VAN.
NONE OF THAT STUFF
MATTERS, HAROLD.
AS LONG AS THEY SPELL
OUR NAMES RIGHT.
DID YOU EVEN BOTHER
TO READ THE ARTICLE?
THE TOWN WANTS TO
DEMOLISH THE LODGE.
HAROLD, THEY PUT THOSE
SENSATIONAL HEADLINES
IN THERE LIKE...
"MAN MARRIES HIS
OWN SISTER."
THEN, YOU READ THE ARTICLE
AND THE GUY'S A MINISTER
AND HE MARRIED HIS SISTER
TO SOME OTHER GUY, YOU KNOW.
SEE, LOOK IT, LOOK IT.
THEY TRY TO MAKE
US LOOK WORSE.
RIGHT BESIDE
OUR ARTICLE,
THEY'VE GOT A PICTURE OF
A SCRAPYARD, FOR GOSH SAKES.
THAT'S AN AERIAL VIEW
OF THE LODGE.
TIME TO PLAY
"THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME"
AND TODAY, LOCAL ROOFER,
MR. ARNIE DOGAN, IS PLAYING
FOR A FANTASTIC PRIZE
OF AN ANT FARM.
AND THE BEST PART IS IT COMES
WITH A COLONY OF ANTS.
YOU CAN SEE THEM
INSIDE THERE.
YOU CAN'T SEE THEM NOW,
THEY MUST BE HIDING
OR CAMERA SHY.
BUT, THEY'RE ALL THERE.
[laughter]
UNCLE RED.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS TO GET
MR. ARNIE DOGAN TO SAY
THIS WORD:
GO!!!
ALL RIGHT, ARNIE,
SOMEONE YOU SEE A LOT.
THE AMBULANCE DRIVER.
AFTER WORK, YOU GO OUT
FOR A DRINK AND YOU TAKE A...?
NECK BRACE.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE PERSON YOU'RE WITH.
OH, MY ORTHOPAEDIC SURGEON.
THIS IS A VERY SPECIAL
PERSON IN YOUR LIFE.
A KIDNEY DONOR.
NEVER LEAVES YOUR SIDE.
MY I.V. BAG.
ALWAYS THERE FOR YA, BUDDY.
OH, BED PAN.
ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
UNCLE RED.
CAN YOU GET YOUR MIND
OFF THE DOCTORS AND
HOSPITAL EQUIPMENT?
HEY RED, THE MEDICAL PROFESSION
IS THE BEST FRIEND I EVER HAD.
[bell ringing]
BAD PRESS WILL KILL YA,
I'M TELLING YA.
THE TOWN COUNCIL HAS GOT
A COURT ORDER THAT SAYS
IF WE DON'T CLEAN UP THE LODGE,
THEY'RE GOING TO TEAR IT DOWN.
ON TOP OF THAT, I'VE GOT THIS
WEIRD CULT THAT'S SHOWN UP
BECAUSE THEY LOOKED AT
THE PICTURE AND THEY SEE
A SACRED IMAGE OR SOMETHING,
I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, THEY'RE NUTS.
THEY WEAR STRIPED ROBES AND
SAY THEY'RE FROM OUTER SPACE.
SO, I SENT HAROLD OUT
TO TALK TO THEM.
[laughter]
I TALKED TO THEM,
I TALKED TO THEM.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING,
BUT I DIDN'T JOIN THE CULT,
OR ANYTHING.
I'M INFILTRATING THEM.
YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH, I'M GAINING
THEIR CONFIDENCE.
YOU'RE LOSING
MINE, HAROLD.
THEY'RE REALLY COOL,
YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY.
THEY SAY THEIR ANCESTORS
CAME HERE FROM THE PLANET
GORGON IN A DISTANT GALAXY.
YOU SURE IT WASN'T IN
A FORD GALAXY, HAROLD?
I BELIEVE THEM,
I BELIEVE THEM.
THEY SAY THEIR MOTHERSHIP
IS COMING BACK FOR THEM
REAL SOON, YOU KNOW,
AND THEY BELIEVE THAT
POSSUM LODGE IS THEIR
DEPARTURE LOUNGE.
HAROLD, COME ON,
THESE ARE NOT
RATIONAL PEOPLE.
THESE ARE WEIRDOS,
THESE ARE LOSERS.
YOU GO RIGHT
BACK OUT THERE
AND YOU TELL THEM THAT
THE LAST BUS FOR GORGON
LEFT ABOUT THREE WEEKS AGO
AND MAYBE THEY SHOULD WARP
THEMSELVES UP TO PORT ASBESTOS
AND GET SOME DILITHEUM CRYSTALS.
YOU GO TELL THEM THAT.
THEY CALL YOU
"THE GRAND MASTER."
WHAT? PARDON ME?
THEY SAID BECAUSE YOU'RE
THE LODGE LEADER,
YOU MUST BE ALL KNOWING,
ALL POWERFUL AND ALL SEEING.
THEY'LL DO YOUR BIDDING,
YOU'RE THE "GRAND MASTER."
SHOULDN'T YOU BE BOWING
WHEN YOU SPEAK TO ME?
OH YEAH, SORRY,
"GRAND MASTER."
I'LL GO TALK TO THEM.
HAROLD, EITHER DO
THE BACK UP OR PUT
SOME PANTS ON.
OH, THE TORTOISE AND THE HARE
HAD A RACE ONE DAY
TO SEE IF SLOW COULD
EVER BEAT FAST
THEY WERE NECK AND NECK
'TIL THE TRUCK WENT BY
AND THEY BOTH
ENDED UP DEAD LAST
THIS MAY LOOK LIKE FUN
TO SOME OF YOU YOUNGSTERS,
BUT, AS YOU GET OLDER,
THE IDEA OF SPENDING A SATURDAY
TRYING TO PULL START THE OLD
LAWN MOWER WEARS A LITTLE THIN.
[crashing sounds]
THE BEST SOLUTION, OF COURSE,
IS TO GET ONE OF THOSE
NEW FANGLED RIDING MOWERS
WITH THE ELECTRIC START AND
EIGHT GEARS ON HER BIG,
WIDE MOWER BED.
BUT THOSE BABIES WILL COST YOU
OVER A THOUSAND BUCKS.
HOW DOES THAT COMPARE WITH
PICKING UP A PREVIOUSLY ENJOYED
FULL SIZE AUTOMOBILE FOR $100.
OKAY, THIS PONTIAC MAY
NOT BE STREET LEGAL,
BUT, HEY, NEITHER IS
THE RIDING MOWER.
THINK OF THE FEATURES.
YOU GOT A ROOF OVER YOUR HEAD,
YOU GOT A RADIO, YOU GOT HEAT,
YOU GOT AIR CONDITIONING,
AND WHILE YOU'RE
CUTTING THE LAWN,
YOU CAN EVEN HAVE
SOME PASSENGERS,
AS LONG AS THEY HAVE
A HIGH BOREDOM THRESHOLD.
I'D RATHER SPEND A FEW BUCKS
TURNING THIS BABY INTO
A RIDING MOWER,
THAN TO TAKE ONE
RIGHT OFF THE LOT.
ALL I HAVE TO ADD IS
SOME KIND OF ROTATING BLADE.
[crashing noises]
HOW ABOUT A CEILING FAN?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BUY A NEW ONE,
JUST WAIT 'TIL A TALL GUY
HAS A GARAGE SALE.
HE'LL BE UNLOADING ONE OF THESE
AND YOU'LL BE ABLE TO GET
A GOOD DEAL ON IT,
ESPECIALLY IF HE'S WEARING
A HEAD BANDAGE.
ALL WE'VE GOT TO DO IS
CUSTOMIZE THESE FAN BLADES,
SO THAT THEY REALLY ARE BLADES.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS ATTACH
SOME KNIVES TO THE FRONT EDGE
OF THE BLADE USING
THE "HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON"
DUCT TAPE.
I THINK THESE KNIVES ARE
THE KIND YOU SEE ON T.V.
WHERE THEY CUT THE TOMATOES
AND THE TIN CANS,
AND THAT'S GREAT 'CAUSE I HAVE
A LOT OF THOSE ON MY LAWN.
YOU WANT TO ATTACH THIS UNIT TO
THE UNDERSIDE OF YOUR VEHICLE.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO STAY AWAY
FROM THE DRIVE SHAFT.
NO SENSE DOING
ANYTHING DANGEROUS.
THEN, ALL YOU'VE GOT TO DO
IS HOOK UP THE POWER.
NOW, THE PROBLEM THERE IS
THE FAN IS A 110-VOLT UNIT
AND THE CAR IS ONLY A 12-VOLT.
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA NEED IS
A SPECIAL LITTLE GIZMO
I'VE GOT INSIDE.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
ONE OF THESE THINGS?
IT'S ONE OF THOSE
POWER ADAPTER THINGS,
SO, YOU CAN RUN YOUR CDS
AND WALKMANS AND STUFF
INSIDE YOUR HOUSE.
WHAT THIS DOES IS IT CONVERTS
110 VOLTS INTO 12 VOLTS.
SO, IF YOU HOOK IT UP BACKWARDS,
IT'S PROBABLY GOING TO TURN
12 VOLTS INTO 110.
THAT'S THE KIND IF THINKING
THAT MAKES ME WHAT I AM.
AND HERE'S A NIFTY
LITTLE WRINKLE,
I'M ACTUALLY TAKING
MY POWER SUPPLY OFF THE BACK
OF THE BRAKE LIGHT SWITCH,
SO, THE FAN DOESN'T GET ANY
POWER UNTIL THE BRAKE IS OFF.
AS SOON AS YOU STEP
ON THE BRAKE PEDAL,
THE FAN STOPS AUTOMATICALLY.
TALK ABOUT SAFETY.
AND GOLLY, YOU KNOW,
FOR LESS THAN 150 BUCKS,
WE'VE MADE A CUSTOMIZED,
CLIMATE CONTROLLED,
EXTRA WIDE, RIDING LAWN MOWER.
WE GOT HEAD LIGHTS ON 'ER
AND WE GOT WINDSHIELD WIPERS.
IT COULD RAIN DURING AN ECLIPSE
AND WE'D STILL GET THE LAWN CUT.
AND THAT, MY FRIEND,
IS HOW YOU TURN A PONTIAC
INTO A "LAWNDIAC."
A "LAWNDIAC."
HA! HA!
SO, REMEMBER...
" IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME...
[engine choking]
[engine starting]
...THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY."
[laughter and applause]
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU OLDER GUYS
WHO MAY NOTICE SIGNS OF AGING
WHEN YOU GO BY
THE BATHROOM MIRROR
OR WHEN YOU'RE LOVED ONE SAYS:
"BOY, YOU'VE REALLY LET
YOURSELF GO, HAVEN'T YOU?"
THAT'S WHEN YOU TELL YOURSELF,
I'VE GOT TO START EATING RIGHT
AND START EXERCISING.
IT'S GOING TO BE ROUGH,
BUT I GUARANTEE YOU,
YOU GET ON TO A HEALTHY DIET
AND A VIGOROUS EXERCISE PROGRAM
AND BY THE END OF THREE DAYS,
A WEEK AT THE MOST,
YOU'LL REALIZE:
IT'S NOT WORTH IT!
BUT, THAT'S OKAY.
SEE, YOUR BODY IS YOUR HOME.
IF YOU'RE HOME SUITS YOU,
WHY RENOVATE?
SO WHAT, IF THE FOUNDATION
IS SETTLING,
OR MAYBE THE ROOF IS SAGGING.
OKAY, THE WIRING BLOWS A FUSE
EVERY NOW AND THEN, HUH?
ALL RIGHT, MAYBE YOUR PIPES
ARE ALL CLOGGED UP,
BUT AS LONG AS YOU STILL
GET A TRICKLE,
THAT'S ALL YOU REALLY NEED.
YOU'RE NOT A BROKEN DOWN HOVEL.
WHY, YOU'RE A CHARMING HOME
WITH CHARACTER AND HISTORY.
OH, YOUR WIFE MAY NOT LOVE
THE CREAKS AND GROANS EVERY
TIME THE WIND SHIFTS,
BUT AS LONG AS SHE CAN LIGHT
A FIRE AND CURL UP IN THE
WARMTH, SHE'LL BE FINE.
YEAH, YEAH, SHE MAY DROOL OVER
THE NEW DREAM HOMES SHE SEES
IN THE MAGAZINES,
BUT I BET SHE'LL NEVER MOVE
FROM THAT COSY LITTLE BUNGALOW
SHE MARRIED.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YA.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
[laughter]
WHAT IS THAT, HAROLD?
THAT WAS A SEMIPHOR
FOR LIGHTEN UP,
YOU'RE TAKING THIS
WAY TOO SERIOUSLY.
WELL, I'VE GOT A LOT OF
RESPONSIBILITY HERE, HAROLD.
I GOTTA GET MY PEOPLE
BACK TO GORGON
AND I'VE GOT TO PREVENT
THE LODGE FROM BEING DEMOLISHED,
BUT IF YOU'RE SAYING
I'M TAKING IT TOO SERIOUSLY...
THEY'RE NOT GOING BACK
TO THE PLANET GORGON.
YOU KNOW THAT.
YOU'RE JUST
TAKING ADVANTAGE
OF THESE PEOPLE.
THAT'S WHY I'M
THE GRAND MASTER
AND YOU'RE JUST A GUY
IN A STRIPED BAG.
I TOLD THEM TO CLEAR
THE WHOLE AREA AROUND
THE LODGE
TO USE AS A LAUNCHING PAD
FOR THE MOTHERSHIP.
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE
THE LODGE CLEANED UP
AND THE TOWN OFF
MY BACK IN NO TIME.
DON'T YOU JUST THINK
YOU ARE SO CLEVER?
I DON'T THINK
THE GRAND MASTER
APPRECIATES THAT TONE.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE OUTSIDE
WITH THE OTHER GORGONITES
PITCHING IN AND
CLEANING UP HERE.
I'M NOT A GORGONITE
AND I'M NOT A SLAVE.
I'M MY OWN PERSON
AND YOU KNOW WHAT,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I QUIT.
I DON'T HAVE TO DO
ANY OF THAT STUFF
BECAUSE I'M AN INDIVIDUAL
AND I CAN THINK FOR MYSELF,
IF THAT'S OKAY
WITH EVERYBODY.
AS YOU KNOW,
IT'S NEW MEMBER NIGHT
AND EDGAR MONTROSE
HAS BROUGHT A FELLOW,
HE WANTS TO PRESENT
AS A NEW MEMBER.
LOOKS LIKE ANOTHER FLOAT
IN A PARADE OF WANNABES.
[laughter]
AH, THANKS, RED.
THIS GUY I'M PRESENTING
FOR YOUR CONSIDERATION
IS A REAL GOOD GUY.
A FRIEND OF MINE,
MY PAL, STAN...
SOMETHING OR OTHER.
I WAS UP AT STAN'S PLACE
DOING A LITTLE DYNAMITE WORK
ON A RUSTED OUT OLD LINCOLN
THAT WAS TAKING A LITTLE
TOO LONG TO EVAPORATE.
OH, BY THE WAY,
IF ANY OF YOU EVER TRY
TO LAUNCH A TOWN CAR
INTO THE LAKE,
THE TRUNK LID CAN FLY OPEN,
EXPOSING THE GAS TANK AND
IT CATCHES THE BRUNT OF
THE EXPLOSION,
AND WHAT YOU GOT
IS A TWO-TONNE,
OUT OF CONTROL,
SURFACE TO AIR AND
BACK TO THE SURFACE,
INCENDIARY DEVICE.
WHICH BRINGS ME
TO HOW I MET STAN.
HE LIVES AT THE CEDAR LOG HOUSE
AT THE NORTH END OF THE LAKE.
WELL, IT'S NOT SO MUCH
CEDAR LOG ANY MORE,
BUT IT'S STILL A PLACE.
IT'S EASY TO FIND BECAUSE
IT'S STILL SMOKING.
OKAY, THE SHORT VERSION:
WE LET STAN JOIN THE CLUB,
WE HELP HIM REBUILD HIS HOUSE,
HE DROPS THE CHARGES
AND I GET MY TRUCK BACK.
ALL THOSE IN FAVOUR?
ANYBODY WHO VOTES YES CAN HELP
THEMSELVES TO SOME VERY NICE
CEDAR KINDLING.
[lodge members]
YEAH!!!
[narration by Red]
BILL SAID HE WANTED TO PLAY
SOME STREET HOCKEY,
SO I BROUGHT MY ROLLER BLADES.
WELL, NOT WITH SKATES.
HE'S TRYING OUT FOR THE FLAMES.
COME ON, OH BOY.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE, BILL?
I'M FIRING A FEW SHOTS IN AND
BILL'S GOT HIS ROLLER BLADES ON.
OOPS, OH BOY.
I'VE GOT TO HELP HIM, I GUESS.
NEED SOME HELP?
OH!!!
WELL, HE SEEMS TO HAVE GOTTEN
THE PADS ON AND I'M PROBABLY
NOT IN THE BEST MOOD.
BILL, MAYBE JUST LET ME
CHECK THOSE PADS.
HERE, TAKE THE STICK.
HOW ABOUT THIS FRONT UNIT?
HERE'S AN IMPORTANT ONE.
THEY LOOK A LITTLE THIN
AROUND THE BACK, THERE.
BODY CHECK!
BY GOLLY, LOOK AT HIM GO.
HE'S GOOD ON THOSE THINGS.
OH, LOOK AT THAT.
HE'S GOT THE MOVES, AIN'T HE?
LOOK AT THAT GUY GO.
OH, MY.
THOSE WHEELS ARE GREAT,
AREN'T THEY?
LIKE BEING IN A PINBALL MACHINE.
OH, YOU'RE FINE, BILL.
HAVING THE TIME OF HIS LIFE.
OH, OH.
HE'S ON A BREAKAWAY.
I BETTER HOP ON IT.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON, COME ON.
DON'T WORRY, DON'T WORRY.
HE'S COMING IN, HE'S COMING IN.
GETTING CLOSE, GETTING CLOSE.
HE SHOOTS... HE SCORES!
[applause]
THEY DO ANYTHING I WANT.
IT'S GOOD TO BE KING.
WOW! THE GROUNDS ARE SPOTLESS.
WHY, THERE'S NO GARBAGE,
THERE'S NO PILE OF TIRES,
THERE'S NO OLD,
RUSTY WATER HEATERS.
IT'S SO TIDY,
I COULD BARELY FIND
THE FRONT DOOR.
SO, WHAT ARE THE GORGONS
GOING TO DO WITH ALL THOSE
OLD CARS, APPLIANCES AND STUFF?
I TOLD THEM
THAT THE MOTHERSHIP
CRASHED HERE YEARS AGO
AND THAT THOSE
WERE THE PARTS.
ALL THEY'VE GOT TO DO IS
GET THEM BACK TOGETHER
AND GET THE WHOLE UNIT
UP ONTO A FLATBED,
TOW IT UP TO PORT ASBESTOS
FOR A SAFETY INSPECTION
AND THEY'RE BACK
IN BUSINESS.
SO, YOU'RE LYING TO THEM
JUST TO GET WHAT YOU WANT?
YEP, I'M A BORN
LEADER, HAROLD.
WELCOME TO "THE EXPERTS"
PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THAT PART OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE EXAMINE THOSE
THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY:
[studio audience]:
"I DON'T KNOW."
THAT WAS GREAT!
JOINING MY UNCLE RED
IS HIS BEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE WIDE ROOM:
WATER TAXI CAPTAIN:
MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSEY.
[applause]
OUR LETTER IS FROM MARYLAND.
"DEAR EXPERTS..."
LA, LA, LA.
MY DOCTOR HAS ORDERED ME
TO GET SOME EXERCISE,
BUT I'M NOT
INTO SPORTS.
IS THERE SOMETHING SIMPLE
I CAN START WITH,
TO BUILD UP MY STAMINA
AND MUSCLE STRENGTH,
BEFORE I ATTEMPT A MORE RUGGED
SPORT LIKE HACKEY SACK?
WELL, ACTUALLY, THAT'S
A VERY GOOD QUESTION.
PERHAPS YOU'D LIKE TO GO ON
THE SAME FITNESS PROGRAM
AS MY UNCLE RED.
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
YOU'RE ALLERGIC TO BEER.
[laughter]
I WOULD SUGGEST THE VIEWER GET
ONE OF THOSE EXERCISE MACHINES.
WHAT DO YOU CALL THEM?
THE ONE WITH THE HANDLES
AND YOU SIT ON THEM?
THE NAUTILUS MACHINE.
NO, NO, NO.
THE ONE WITH
THE WHEELS AND
THE CHAIN.
THE... AH...
THE MOTORCYCLE.
YOU CAN TRY
MOTOR CYCLE JUMPING.
THAT WILL START
YOU OUT EASY ENOUGH.
BY ONLY EXERCISING
YOUR WRISTS
AND YOU LEARN TO DEVELOP
YOUR SENSE OF BALANCE
AND IF ANYTHING
GOES WRONG,
IT GIVES YOUR WHOLE BODY
A RELAXING ASPHALT MASSAGE.
SO, YOU WERE A MOTORCYCLE
STUNT JUMPER, MR. SHAUGHNESSEY?
YOU NEVER HEARD OF
"ODYSSEY SHAUGHNESSEY?"
I HAD A 1200 HORSEPOWER NORTON.
IT HAD SEVEN GEARS.
AND HE'S GIVING US
ALL OF THEM, RIGHT NOW.
[laughter]
YEAH, I WAS THE BEST.
I WAS ALL SET TO JUMP OVER
THE FOUNTAIN AT CAESAR'S PALACE,
THIS WAS LONG BEFORE
EVEL KNIEVEL.
I HAD THE NETWORKS
LINED UP TO COVER IT,
BUT I BACKED OUT
AT THE LAST MINUTE
ON THE INSISTANCE
OF MY GIRLFRIEND.
I'M SURE SHE WAS
JUST AFRAID FOR YOU.
MORE FOR HERSELF, HAROLD.
SHE WAS IN THE SIDECAR.
[laughter]
BYE.
WELL, THAT'S THE END OF THAT.
THE OLD CULT IS ON THE WAY
TO THE PROMISED LAND.
HOW DO YOU FIGURE
PORT ASBESTOS IS
THE PROMISED LAND?
BECAUSE A GUY THERE
PROMISED ME THAT
WHEN THEY SHOW UP
WITH THE SPACESHIP,
HE'S GOING TO OUTLAW IT.
YOU KNOW, ITS WEIRD,
BUT I'M GOING TO MISS THEM.
DON'T DO THAT.
CULTS ARE FULL OF FOLLOWERS.
THEY HAVE NO
INDEPENDENT THOUGHT.
THEY GO TO THESE
POINTLESS MEETINGS,
THEY HAVE MEANINGLESS CHANTS.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THEY ALL DRESS THE SAME.
[loud Laughter]
[applause]
HOW DO YOU THINK
THE GORGONITES ARE
GOING TO RESPOND
WHEN THEY FIND OUT
THEIR FLYING SAUCER
DOESN'T EVEN FLY?
I GUESS THE FOLKS
AT GORGON ARE GOING TO
HAVE TO SEND DOWN A LOANER.
[mysterious noise from outside]
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
WELL, THAT'S NOT
THE POSSUM SQUEAL.
[noise increasing]
[engine whining]
DID I JUST SEE
A '53 BUICK
WITH A WASHER AND DRYER
DUCT TAPED TO THE SIDE
SHOOT INTO OUTER SPACE?
[loud laughter]
NO, NO.
OH, THANK HEAVENS.
THAT WAS A '54 BUICK.
[squeal of the Possum]
THAT'S THE POSSUM.
YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING HOME
STRAIGHT AFTER THE MEETING
AND THERE'S A CHANCE
I COULD BE ABDUCTED
BY ALIENS LATER TONIGHT.
IF YOU HAVE ANY ROMANTIC PLANS,
WE BETTER GET AN EARLY START.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE.
"KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE."
ALL RISE.
[lodge members]:
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
OKAY, WE'VE GOT SOME GOOD NEWS,
THAT WEIRD CULT IS FINALLY GONE.
THEY'RE HEADED BACK TO
THE PLANET GORGON IN
THEIR '54 BUICK.
[loud crashing]
A VEHICLE NOT KNOWN FOR
ITS GREAT GAS MILELAGE.