I asked five of my friends
to come out here
and give me a hand cutting
down this dead tree.
They all said sure.
Of course, none of
them showed up.
Makes me glad
I never showed up
when they asked me to help
them out with a chore.
Serves them right
in advance.
But now what I am
supposed to do?
I mean this this is a
two-man saw, right?
This thing wobbles more
than a politician
at a paternity test.
And I can't just hack
it up into a one-man saw,
it's mine.
Hmm.
I got it!
I may not have friends
and I may not have pants,
but I have imagination.
You've heard
of a belt sander?
Hey, I made
a saw-suspender.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Thank you very much.
Appreciate it.
Big, big week up
at the lodge this week.
Harold wanted to
have a big theme weekend
to attract
tourists up here
so we thought we'd go
with a Baffin Island deal.
We're going to
have tusk carving,
and everybody gets a little
bag of blubber to chew on.
Moose Thompson is doing
laps of Possum Lake
while people try
to harpoon him.
Uncle Red!
You have to
clear all your
announcements through me.
I thought we settled
that after the
All You Can Eat
Roadkill Barbeque.
Well, that's
a dumb outfit for
the Baffin Island
Festival, Harold.
You're going to freeze
your clam diggers off.
No, no, not
the Baffin Island,
the Big Island.
What?
You mean Alcatraz?
No, Hawaii!
Hawaii?
Oh, Hawaii!
Good and how are you?
What are the rules
for justifiable
homicide again,
Harold?
Uncle Red,
we're going to have
hula dancers
and surfers,
and we're going
to be serving poi.
Poi?
What's that,
pie from New Jersey?
No, no, no,
no, no.
No, it's a
Hawaiian dish.
People are going to
swear they're in Waikiki.
Harold, convincing
tourists
that Possum Lake is
Waikiki is impossible
unless it's nighttime
during a lunar eclipse
and they've got
no sense of smell.
No, Uncle Red,
we're having a
Hawaiian-themed weekend,
and that's all
there is to it.
Please allow me to
present you with this lay.
Harold, you know,
there's something wrong
when two guys
are getting lays,
and one of them's married
and the other one's you.
It's time for
the Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Today's prize is one free
landscaping job
from the Possum Lake
Correctional Facility
Gardening Co-op.
Where we give gas-powered
lawn equipment
to hardened criminals
and turn them loose
in your backyard.
All right, cover your
ears there, Edgar.
Edgar?
We're good.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Okay, Red,
you've got 30 seconds
to get Edgar Montrose
to say this word...
Yeah, all right,
Winston.
And... go!
Okay, Edgar!
Edgar!
Town Council
sent you a letter
telling you you're
making too much...
Road damage.
Okay, but up
around your place
I would imagine you
get a lot of traffic...
Well, not after
the road damage.
Okay, okay, no, okay.
This is a scary sound
coming from the
basement at night.
Grandpa?
No, okay.
This is something you're
not allowed to make
in the library.
Oh, bombs.
No, okay.
No, no.
In some monasteries
they vow not to make...
Whoopie?
Okay, Edgar, you know
when people are startled,
they'll yell,
"what's that..."
Man doing with
the high explosives?
Almost out of time, Red.
Yeah, yeah. Okay.
Okay, Edgar, whenever
you do a demolition job
the main complaint
you get is,
there's just
too much...
Collateral damage.
You know, that
really annoys me.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
RED: So what do
you guys think
of those reality
television shows?
DALTON: Reality television,
what's that?
MIKE: Weird, eh,
reality television?
Sounds like
an oxen-moray.
DALTON: An oxenmoray?
It means two things
that don't go together,
like oxen and
moray eels.
DALTON: Oh, I think you
mean oxymoron.
What's
an oxymoron?
Well, that's when
Harold needs
his pimple cream
on his nose.
Reality TV!
People don't
want to see real.
They want to see
a bunch of
attractive,
smart, young people
wearing skimpy clothing.
I mean REAL
reality television
would show a bunch of ugly,
middle-aged guys in flannels
sitting around
complaining about stuff.
Who would want
to watch that?
Actually, I've been
on quite a lot
of reality television.
Crimestoppers and then
later on Court TV.
No, I'm talking
about these shows
that take a
bunch of people
and put them
on a desert island,
and they get them
swinging from vines
and eating
raw spiders,
and then one of them
pretends to be a
millionaire,
but he's actually a
backhoe operator,
and so the bachelorettes
will face all their fears
and end up getting
hired by Donald Trump.
You know, reality.
DALTON:
That sounds good.
MIKE:
I'll watch anything.
RED:
No, no, but I'm saying
they call that
a reality show.
It doesn't sound like
reality to me.
DALTON:
Well, so what?
Anne Marie and I,
we got reality.
It's bad enough to
watch it in person.
I certainly wouldn't want
to watch it on television.
Well, I think
you're wrong.
I think you
and Anne Marie
can do a great
reality show.
So do I.
Now, where would
that show run,
Dalton,
on Discovery or on
the Nature channel?
You know, based on past
experience with Anne-Marie,
I'd have to go
with pay-per-view.
[ THEY CHUCKLE ]
All right,
50 cents,
but that's my
final offer.
Bye.
Anything else?
You sure?
You know when
you were a kid
you were a
bit of a sucker
for any type
of sales pitch,
so you end up with
a whole bunch of stuff
you never use,
like life jackets
or hard hats
or a thighmaster
or these things
you're supposed to
stick on your
steering wheel.
Oh sure, you tried it
for a couple of weeks,
but then you realized
putting an anti-theft
device in your car
is like posting an
armed guard at the
city dump.
So now you're stuck
with all this stuff,
but what do you do?
You tried
the yard sale,
but unfortunately,
people today
are not as gullible
as you were.
Luckily,
on Handyman Corner,
we like to show
that useless things
can have a purpose too.
That's an important message
for your wife and kids.
For example, this tool box is
something I never use.
It's way too small
for the number
of tools I carry,
and the tool boxes
that are big enough,
I can't lift.
Instead, I just
let my tools
roll around in the back
of the Possum Van.
It's safe as long
as I don't stop too fast
and with the brakes
on that unit,
that's no worry.
But rather than throw
this tool box into the lake,
I keep it here
by the fireplace
full of all the
assembly directions
and instruction manuals
I don't have time
to sit down and read
and never will.
With these babies,
I can start a fire
in four
different languages.
Maybe you've got
a couple of kids
who are always stealing
food from each other
at the dinner table.
It's usually 'cause they're
sitting too close together.
So you need an anti-theft
device keeping them apart.
And did you notice
my tablecloth?
Just an old road map out
of the glove compartment.
It's cheap
but it looks good
and it encourages
dinner conversation.
Cause when you
look at the local towns
and recreation areas,
it reminds you of the
hilarious stories
and how you
avoided arrest.
And when it gets dirty,
you just crumple it up,
and it can hit
the road.
You know those smoke detectors
you have in the ceiling,
the ones where you haven't
changed the batteries
since the '80s?
Well, they make
dandy doorstops.
And you know how the kids
go out the screen door
and never close it?
Well, hey, that's what a
thighmaster's for.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Now, if you're the
kind of handyman I am,
you probably also
have a hard hat that
you never use,
because protecting
your head is, again,
like posting an armed
guard at the city dump.
Instead, fill it up
with water.
makes a dandy bird bath.
And a pair of
safety goggles
makes a real
good bird feeder.
As for those life jackets
that never leave the
boathouse,
wrap them around
the cooler.
They add to
the insulation,
and if you ever get hit
with a flash flood,
at least the
beer'll be safe.
For me, nothing
says summer
like hearing a thighmaster
making my screen door slam,
while the birds are
swimming in my hard-hat
and I enjoy a brewski
lying safely in my hammock
made of seat belts.
[ APPLAUSE ]
There comes a time in the
life of almost every guy
when he's gonna
need glasses.
He's usually the last one
to see it coming.
Along with the stop sign,
the elderly crossing guard
and the lawsuit.
You can tell if
you need glasses.
If you squint so often
your wife keeps asking
if you're constipated,
that's a clue.
And when it comes,
choose your frames wisely.
Some frames complement
your face,
others crack
a joke about it.
Very disappointing to
purchase a pair of bifocals
and the first thing
you can see clearly
is everybody
laughing at you.
Now, you can't tell
what's good and bad
until you see
them on you.
A big pair
of black frames
might make your buddy
look like Henry Kissinger,
but they make you look
like Orville Redenbacher.
Or those small,
round frames
make your brother
look like John Lennon,
but make you
look like that granny
who carries
Tweety Bird around.
You want to choose the
frames based on the
shape of your head.
You may even need
a range of different styles
because maybe your
head changes shape,
after a compliment
or a party
or a skiing accident.
Only get frameless glasses
if you have a shapeless head.
The best thing,
consult your wife.
You're going to get her
opinion anyway, right?
You get a lot more points
if you ask for it first.
But whatever you do,
don't get contact lenses.
I mean, at our age
the fingers aren't steady
enough to cut a bagel.
You really don't want to be
touching the eyeball.
Remember,
I'm pulling for you.
We're all
in this together.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Wow, the big
Hawaiian-themed weekend
is really starting
to take off.
We changed the name
of Possum Lake to
Alottalakawata.
And tonight's
the big luau
where we cook a pig
in the ground there.
Picking the spot
is the tricky part
because most of the holes
on the lodge property
used to have an
outhouse over them.
Oh, Uncle Red,
Yeah?
They brought
the pig over.
Yeah.
I mean, it's dead,
but it's got a
head and everything!
I mean everything.
It's got it all.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, I think
it's going to sit up
and suddenly go,
[AS PORKY PIG ]
that's all, folks!
Everything!
Harold it's not
the lodge mascot,
it's dinner, okay?
The pig prefers
to be dead.
I wouldn't be surprised
if it committed suicide.
Well, that's
another thing,
you don't know
how to cook a luau pig.
I never missed
one episode of
Hawaii Five-O, Harold.
You dig a hole.
You stick the
pig in there.
We're going to
drain the oil out
of Buster's '74 Aries,
crank her at full
throttle until the
motor blows up,
drop the red hot
engine parts in
the pork,
cover the whole
shebang with our
wet bathing suits.
What do you got
to say about that?
Book em, Dan-o.
That reminds me,
Junior Singleton recommended
this Hawaiian girl singer.
I think she's a distant
relative of Don Ho.
Remember that
Hawaiian crooner?
Tiny bubbles,
in the bath
Remember that guy?
Oh, that'd great,
that'd great.
You know who I booked?
[SHUDDERING]
I got a hula dancer.
Oh boy,
oh boy, oh boy.
Yeah, she's going
to be dancing
with the dancing stuff.
Harold, Harold.
She's got all
the stuff --
Harold, you're supposed
to watch the hands.
I know.
Yeah, I know.
I'm going to
videotape her dancing
so I can watch
the hands later.
All right, then.
Yup.
Harold, Harold.
Yes?
Don't tell me
you're the surfer.
Girls love those guys.
Have you ever
surfed before, Harold?
I surf the Internet
all the time.
Okay, but don't
hit the dock,
or you'll be spam.
It's true.
RED: Pretty windy day
out behind the lodge, but --
Watch your head.
Ooh!
Walter and Bill are going
to do a little mini-putting.
We got the --
we got the one hole.
You do one hole 18 times,
it's a lot cheaper.
And I'm not sure if this
is going to work out.
I was just trying
to cut the lawn,
but I noticed the
grass is blowing away
as fast as
I was cutting her.
So Walter's going
to give it a try
and just as
he putted up there,
a gust of wind came along,
blew up the end
of the mini-putt.
That was unfortunate.
So I guess now
it's Bill's shot.
Just get him out
of the way there and --
So Bill's going
to try her again,
and now he's kinda expecting
another gust of wind
might come along so he ducks
and thinking that was
a good move.
Not so.
So now the wind
is really coming up.
Tornado warning,
I'm thinking to myself,
are you serious?
Apparently, yes.
So I say to the guys,
hey guys, forget the game.
There's a tornado coming
and we got stuff everywhere.
We got to get the
yard all cleaned up,
and I think
the best thing --
Walter, Walter,
you clean up the yard.
Bill and I will go
and hide somewhere.
C'mon, Bill.
So Walter starts
picking --
Now the wind
is really starting,
and you can feel it just
starting to twist and
turn a little bit.
Then --
watch out for the rake.
Oh, boy.
And he gets as much
as he can get,
and he's heading
for the shed,
and boy, it's getting
serious there now.
There it's coming
right across the field.
Wow!
And so Bill and I are going
to go into the barn there --
Bill is beating on the --
What's his problem?
I open the door
and let him in,
but he didn't seem
interested,
so to heck with it.
It's not locked, Bill.
There we go.
And the wind just
took it right off.
That's gone.
And Walter, he decided to
abandon the lawn chairs
and the barbeque
and everything
and just get inside the --
unfortunately,
with this shed,
it has a lock
on the outside only.
And the tornado's
getting real close now.
It's getting
pretty scary,
and you've never seen
anything like this.
Bill was shocked.
Shocked to the point that he
brought his video camera out
and got a little footage.
And it picked up
the lawn mower
and dropped it right
down on the lawn
and started cutting the
lawn as if there was --
it was just spooky.
And then suddenly
it was quiet,
which I didn't
mind actually.
We come out round
looking for Walter.
Where's Walter?
Then we realize,
he's in the shed
and Bill wanted
to let him --
And I said hang on
a minute, wait, wait.
Hold it, Bill.
Wait, wait.
Hold it, whoa, yeah.
We got - the lawn's
been cut up here.
Let me try
this golf ball.
Let's see if I can
undo it with a golf ball.
Oh, look at that,
unbelievable.
So we're all safe.
We think
everything is good.
But we had forgotten
about the lawn mower.
Excuse us a minute.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Reminds me of that time
I parked in Moosejaw.
You know, defrosting
your freezer
is like picking spaghetti
off the ceiling.
The longer you leave it,
the harder it gets.
You single guys know
what I'm talking about.
What we need here
is a solution
that's just like the
girls you dream about...
quick and easy.
I'm just kidding,
Bernice.
Because at my age,
the only thing I find
that's quick and easy
is a microwave oven.
You get yourself one
of these smaller units.
Oh.
And then just gently
remove the door.
Next you want
to jam something
into the locking
mechanism
on the front
of the unit
so the machine will think
the door is actually closed.
Ah, here we go.
I suggest you use
something plastic, eh?
We want this
to be safe.
Okay, I set the
timer for five minutes
and plugged her in,
that's all you --
Oh, by the way, remember
a couple of weeks ago
I tried to make
a tanning bed
by putting a microwave
into a freezer?
Doesn't work,
she won't brown.
[ BELL RINGS ]
Oh, mission accomplished.
[ APPLAUSE ]
You know, when you try
new things you
learn stuff.
For example,
I never realized that
a pig was that
flammable.
Of course, all those
engine parts
covered in transmission
fluid didn't help,
and that old oak tree
took a lot of fire damage.
Oh, no,
it's fine, Harold.
Shouldn't you
be out surfing?
I'm not leaving
until that fire's out.
What do you care?
You're on Possum Lake.
That's what's
on fire!
No, Harold,
I put it out.
You're fine.
Way you go.
Yeah?
They're waiting for you.
They love you.
The girls love
that, Harold.
Oh, boy.
Meanwhile, our luau pig
was a bit of a burn out.
Once she cools down,
I figure we'll have
700 pounds of pork rinds.
Hopefully we had
better luck with
the entertainment.
Our clientele has
no appreciation of art.
What happened to the
real hula dancer,
Mike?
Well, there was
a contract dispute.
She wanted one.
I bet the
audience was a
little disappointed.
Yeah!
They all boo'ed
and hissed me,
and then one smart guy
came at me with a weed whacker.
Oh, boy.
I hope you didn't
let him get away
with that.
Oh no, I sent him a
very clear message.
But in keeping with
the Hawaiian motif,
I said it all
with my hands.
Very good.
Actually it was
just one finger.
Okay, okay.
All right.
Away you go,
away you go.
Away you go down
to the meeting.
Away you go.
Better get that off,
it's crab grass season.
More trouble, Red.
What?
You had a misunderstanding
with the girl singer.
The one related
to Don Ho?
Yeah, no.
That was only your
interpretation.
The message
said she's a ho.
[ CREAKING SOUND ]
Oh, I think
that big oak's going
to fall in the lake.
Ah, doesn't matter.
It won't hurt anybody.
Except Harold.
He's still out there
on that surfboard!
Yeah, but the tree's
not going to hit him.
No, but the
tidal wave might!
[ HUGE CRASH AND SPLASHING ]
Oh, man!
Surf's up!
So's the surfer!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Meeting time.
Yeah, I think Harold's
already down there.
Okay, if my wife
is watching,
I'll be coming straight home
after the meeting,
and I'm going to try and
keep the luau going.
I'm hoping you'll have
a little milkshake,
or as they call it in Hawaii,
a tiny muu-muu.
And to the rest of
you thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself
and Harold
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge,
keep your stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Guys, c'mon in. Sit down.
Everybody, meeting's
coming to order.
Everybody, sit down.
All rise.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
RED: Sit down.
Bow your head
for the Man's Prayer.
I'm a man,
but I can change
if I have to...
I guess.
Okay, men.
We're going to abandon the
Hawaiian thing
and we're going for
a Jamaican theme,
because we got the pork,
and we got the jerk.