HERE'S HOW TO KEEP KIDS
OUT OF THE HOUSE.
HANG A TIRE FROM A TREE;
TELL THEM TO SWING IN IT.
TH'S CHEAP...IN A GOOD WAY.
WHY STOP AT TIRES --
IF YOU MUST HANG A CAR
PART AND CONVINCE THEM
IT'S FUN, WHY STOP AT TIRES?
HOW ABOUT A WINDSHIELD, EH?
HANG THAT, EH, AND THE KIDS CAN
PRESS THEIR FACE AGAINST IT.
LOOK AT THAT. ISN'T THAT GREAT?
KIDS LOVE THAT.
[laughing]
HOW ABOUT THIS?
YOU KNOW HOW KIDS LOVE
THOSE MEXICAN PINATAS.
WELL, HOW ABOUT USING
A CAR GAS TANK, EH, AS A PINATA?
TAKE THEM ALL SUMMER TO BREAK
THIS BABY OPEN.
UNLESS THEY HIT IT WITH
A THREE OUGHT THREE.
OR HANG A BUMPER ON THERE.
GIVE YOU KIND OF A NIFTY
TEETER-TOTTER SWING THING.
ALL RIGHT, OR A...
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THEY'D DO WITH THIS.
BUT WHY NOT GO FOR
THE WHOLE ENCHILADA, HEY?
HANG A WHOLE CAR FROM A TREE.
[crashing]
OH, YEAH, REMIND THEM TO WEAR
THEIR SEATBELTS.
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW!
HA, HA, HA.
AND NOW HERE HE IS,
THE MAN WHO BEAT THE ODDS
EVEN THOUGH HE'S ONE OF THEM,
YOUR HOST AND HERO,
BUT HE'S MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
[cheering]
YEAH.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE IT.
IS THERE ANYBODY OUT THERE
WHO HAS A USED HEAVY-DUTY
12-VOLT TRUCK HORN, EH...
AT A REASONABLE PRICE?
I TELL YOU, I'D BE
INTERESTED IN THAT.
DID YOU BURN OUT THE HORN
ON THE POSSUM VAN AGAIN?
UH...
YOU KNOW,
I BELIEVE I DID, HAROLD.
YOU THINK SO? THAT'S
THE FOURTH HORN THIS YEAR.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
BACK OFF ON THE HORN HONKING.
YEAH? WELL, MAYBE YOU
OUGHT TO JUST BACK OFF.
WHOA.
I'M JUST SAYING THAT HORNS
ARE USED FOR EMERGENCIES.
THEY'RE NOT SUBSTITUTES
FOR TURNING SIGNALS AND BRAKES.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE BOTHERING
OUR VIEWERS WITH THIS, EITHER.
GO TO McCLINTOCK'S SALVAGE YARD.
HE'S GOT LOTS OF HORNS.
DRIVE YOURSELF THERE,
PICK UP ONE OF HIS HORNS.
HAROLD, HOW CAN
I DRIVE WITHOUT A HORN?
HOW ARE THE OTHER DRIVERS
GOING TO KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE DOING WRONG?
HANG YOUR HEAD OUT THE SIDE
AND JUST YELL AT 'EM.
HONK! HONK! HONK!
HEY, HEY, WHY DON'T
YOU COME ALONG?
YOU CAN BE
MY HORN.
I DON'T WANT-- HOW AM I GOING
TO KNOW WHEN YOU WANT TO HONK?
YOU'LL FEEL THE TINGLE.
YOU'LL BE ON THE WIRES.
COME ON.
IT'S TIME TO PLAY
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
AND TONIGHT'S CONTESTANT
IS MR. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
OF THE ROTHSCHILD SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
AND TONIGHT MR. ROTHSCHILD
IS PLAYING FOR THE FANTASTIC
GRAND PRIZE OF AN ENTIRE BAG OF
AFTER-DINNER MINTS, HA, HA, HA.
AN ENTIRE BAG OF MOTHBALLS.
ACK-ACK.
UNCLE RED...
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS TO GET
MR. ROTHSCHILD TO SAY THIS WORD:
SMELL...SMELL.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
HAROLD.
OK, GO.
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON,
WHEN YOU DRIVE
YOUR SEWAGE TRUCK
INTO TOWN, THE GUYS
ALL SAY,
"WHAT'S THAT..."
WORTH?
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE THING
THAT MAKES THEIR EYES WATER.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, ENVY.
HEH.
OK, WINSTON, I KNOW YOU
PUT A LOT OF TIME
AND EFFORT
INTO YOUR BUSINESS, RIGHT.
BUT SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO STOP
AND SOMETHING THE ROSES.
FERTILIZE.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
YOU GOT FIVE SENSES:
SIGHT, HEARING,
TASTE, TOUCH AND...
DIRECTION.
OSCAR WILDE WAS TALKING
ABOUT BAGPIPES -- HE SAID,
"THANK GOD THERE'S NO..."
SPIT VALVE.
ALMOST OUT OF TIME, UNCLE RED.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
OH, I KNOW.
REMEMBER YOU GOT
THE CONTRACT TO
PUMP OUT ALL THE SEPTICS AT
THE PORT ASBESTOS PRUNE FAIR?
WHAT DID YOU CALL THAT?
THE SWEET SMELL OF SUCCESS.
[ringing]
I'VE NEVER BEEN SO EMBARRASSED
IN ALL MY LIFE.
THAT WAS INCREDIBLE --
YOU WERE CUTTING PEOPLE OFF,
YOU DROVE THROUGH INTERSECTIONS,
YOU DROVE THROUGH A DITCH
JUST TO PASS BUSTER HADFIELD.
WELL, HAROLD, I
MEAN, HE WAS GOING
SO SLOW -- THE
SPEED LIMIT IS 60,
AND HE WAS ONLY
DOING ABOUT 80.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU GOT?
KNOW WHAT YOU GOT?
ROAD RAGE, YEAH.
YOU GOT A BAD TEMPER,
THAT AIN'T NORMAL.
I DON'T HAVE A BAD TEMPER.
MAYBE NOT, BUT
YOU'RE A CARRIER.
YOU NEED HELP, UNCLE RED.
WELL, I KNOW,
I KNOW THAT, HAROLD.
AND I'VE TRIED, BUT I CAN'T
GET AN INSTITUTION TO TAKE YOU.
[laughing]
YEAH, OK, I KNOW,
WE JOKE AROUND A LOT
AND EVERYTHING,
BUT YOU HAVE A SERIOUS PROBLEM
MANAGING YOUR ANGER.
I KNOW ALL THESE THINGS, 'CAUSE
I JUST FINISHED WRITING A PAPER
FOR MY PSYCH CLASS 101, AND YOU
HAVE THE SYMPTOMS OF A PERSON
WHO MUST LEARN HOW TO MANAGE
THEIR ANGER -- I CAN HELP YOU.
I DON'T NEED TO MANAGE MY ANGER.
I NEED PEOPLE TO STOP
TICKING ME OFF.
WHY CAN'T PEOPLE
JUST SMARTEN UP?
GIVE ME SOME SPACE, YOU KNOW?
HOW ABOUT THIS?
WHY DON'T THEY JUST STAY INDOORS
WHEN I'M DRIVING?
IT'S NOT THEM, IT'S YOU.
YOU CAN CHANGE IF YOU WANT TO.
YOU SOUND LIKE MY WIFE,
YOU KNOW THAT?
NO, I THINK WE SHOULD
JUST GO SOMEWHERE PRIVATE
AND TALK ABOUT
THIS SORT OF THING --
LIKE WHAT MAKES YOU ANGRY?
STUPID MORONS.
STUPID MORONS, OK.
CAN YOU NAME ANY STUPID MORONS?
HOW MUCH TIME HAVE YOU GOT?
SEE, THAT'S YOUR PROBLEM,
IS THAT YOU DON'T RESPECT
OTHER DRIVERS -- THEY CAN'T
ALL BE STUPID MORONS.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT I KEEP HOPING.
ONE OF THE GREATEST LESSONS
I LEARNED FROM MY MOTHER IS
YOU DON'T THROW SOMETHING OUT
JUST BECAUSE IT'S USELESS.
SHE WAS TALKING ABOUT DAD.
BUT I'D LIKE TO APPLY
THE SAME PRINCIPLE...
TO THIS OLD CHAIR.
IT GOT BROKEN
WHEN BUSTER HADFIELD
LEANED BACK ON IT,
NOT REALIZING IT
WASN'T A RECLINER
EVEN THOUGH HE IS.
SO THIS WEEK
ON THE HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
A WAY TO PUT
FANCY BACKS ON ALL
OF THESE OLD CHAIRS.
BUSTER'S A BIT
OF A SLOW LEARNER.
THIS IS A STYLE YOU DON'T
SEE THAT MUCH OF ANY MORE.
IT'S CALLED CANING.
THEY USED TO DO A LOT OF THAT.
THE WORKERS WOULD CANE
THE CHAIRS AND THE BOSSES
WOULD CANE THE WORKERS.
THIS IS WOOD HERE, AND THEY BEND
THAT INTO A SHAPE LIKE THAT,
WHICH, TO ME,
LOOKS VERY DIFFICULT
AND EXTREMELY TIME-CONSUMING,
WHICH ARE TWO NO-NOs
FOR MY KIND OF HANDYMAN.
NOW, I SUPPOSE YOU COULD TRUDGE
THROUGH THE WOODS
UNTIL YOU FOUND A TREE
THAT WAS GROWING
THE EXACT SHAPE OF A CHAIR BACK,
BUT I PREFER TO USE MATERIAL
A LITTLE EASIER
TO WORK WITH THAN WOOD.
I'M THINKING GARDEN HOSE.
NOW HERE YOU COULD CUT THE HOSE
INTO THE EXACT LENGTHS
THAT YOU NEED,
BUT I PREFER TO JUST DO
KIND OF A RANDOM
SLICE-O-MATIC THING
AND THEN JUST ADAPT
TO WHATEVER I GET.
I LOVE A CHALLENGE.
[motor whirring]
YEAH, ALWAYS WEAR YOUR GOGGLES
WHEN YOU REACH
INTO A LAWN MOWER -- SAFETY.
OK, NOW WHAT YOU
WANT TO DO IS TAKE
YOUR VARIOUS PIECES
OF YOUR GARDEN HOSE,
AND YOU WANT TO RE-CREATE
THE CANE-BACK LOOK EXACTLY.
AND YOU WANT TO ATTACH
THAT ON THERE USING
THE FURNITURE BUILDER'S
SECRET WEAPON...DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT, WE GOT OUR BASIC
SHAPE DONE THERE,
AND I'LL TELL YOU,
ONCE YOU COVER THAT WITH
THE VINYL WOOD-GRAINED
TRIM THERE, I DEFY ANYBODY
TO TELL THAT
FROM THE ORIGINAL, HUH?
OH, RIGHT, YEAH, YEAH,
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
MM-HMM, MM-HMM, YEAH,
I FORGOT ONE THING.
UM, THEY'RE
A BIT TOO FLIMSY, YOU KNOW.
BECAUSE VERY FEW GARDEN HOSES
WERE EVER DESIGNED TO HOLD
THE WEIGHT OF AN ADULT HUMAN.
SO, WHAT WE NEED TO DO IS
WE GOT TO REINFORCE THE UNIT
BY FILING THE HOSES
WITH CEMENT, EH?
I JUST, UH, POUR THIS CEMENT
DOWN THE INSIDE OF THE...
HOSE THERE -- YOU MIGHT
HAVE TO SHAKE HER DOWN.
IT MIGHT TAKE A MINUTE
OR TWO TO SLIDE DOWN THERE.
ALL RIGHT, ACTUALLY, ACTUALLY,
TO GET THE CEMENT DOWN THERE,
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS YOU
WANT TO WIPE THE END OF THE HOSE
LIKE THAT, AND THEN YOU
WANT TO ACTUALLY BLOW ON,
YOU WANT TO BLOW ON THAT.
I'M ALONE. ALL RIGHT.
JUST BLOW ON THAT
AND BLOW THE CEMENT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, ACTUALLY TO GET
THE CEMENT DOWN THERE,
IT'S PRETTY-- IT'S PRETTY THICK.
SO YOU GOT TO BLOW
REALLY, REALLY HARD.
REALLY...
[inhaling]
OK, AND ONCE THE CEMENT
HAS HARDENED INSIDE THE HOSES,
ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS --
AS I SAID BEFORE --
COVER THEM WITH THE VINYL
FAKE WOOD STUFF,
AND YOU GOT YOURSELF
A BEAUTIFUL CHAIR.
IT'S EVERY BIT AS GOOD
AS THE ORIGINAL.
IN FACT, THESE CHAIRS ARE
STURDIER, THEY'RE STRONGER...
THEY'RE HEAVIER.
YEAH, WELL, THE CEMENT IN THE
BACK, THEY HAVE
A TENDENCY NOW
TO FALL OVER BACKWARDS.
SO, WHAT YOU COULD DO THERE
IS JUST EITHER BOLT THEM DOWN
OR JUST...SIT IN THEM ALL DAY.
HEY, AS IF YOU NEED AN EXCUSE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME...
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU OLDER GUYS
THAT HAVE NO WAR STORIES.
YOU KNOW, YOU WERE TOO YOUNG
FOR KOREA
AND TOO OLD FOR DESERT STORM.
YOU KNOW, YOU GET
TO A CERTAIN AGE,
PEOPLE REALLY EXPECT YOU
TO HAVE A WAR STORY.
SO HERE'S WHAT YOU DO,
ALL RIGHT?
YOU TAKE THE CRAPPIEST EVENT
IN YOUR LIFE...
MAYBE A CRUMMY JOB
OR A GOOFY FRIEND,
HOW ABOUT YOUR FIRST WEDDING?
AND YOU TURN THAT
INTO YOUR WAR STORY.
AH, YEAH,
I WAS IN THE WAR, YEAH.
AH, YEAH, THE BIG ONE.
GASOLINE PRICE WAR OF '69.
I'D LIED ABOUT MY AGE
TO GET A SUMMER JOB
PUMPING GAS AT LLOYD'S TEXACO.
THEN ALL SHELL BROKE LOOSE.
THE DUTCHMAN DROPPED
HIS PRICE BY A NICKEL.
WE HAD TO FIGHT BACK.
SO WE TOOK THE BIG HIT, AND WE
DROPPED OURS DOWN BY SIX CENTS.
WAR WAS ON.
WHY, WE STARTED HANDING OUT
HOT DOGS AND BALLOONS
JUST TO KEEP THE CUSTOMERS.
BY THE END OF AUGUST, THE WHOLE
STATION WAS UNDER SIEGE.
CARS LINED UP OUTSIDE,
FIRING OFF THEIR HORNS,
SCREAMING FOR FREE TUMBLERS.
AND NOBODY TO HOLD THEM OFF
EXCEPT ME AND ONE-LEGGED LLOYD.
BUT WE DID IT, AND WE WON.
AND IT MADE A MAN OUT OF ME.
AND I GUESS THAT EXPLAINS
THE STAIN ON MY PANTS.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
ALL SET?
YEAH.
YOU ARE A NOTHING!
YOU ARE A ZERO!
YOU ARE LESS THAN ZERO, YOU ARE
A ZERO-A-MATIC -- YOU HAVE
NOTHING, YOU DO NOTHING!
YOU ARE A NOTHING!
YOU MAKE ME SICK!
[spitting and coughing]
YOU DID REALLY WELL.
I'M VERY PROUD OF YOU.
I THINK, I THINK
I'M OVER
THE HUMP
ON THIS.
YEAH, SO YOU'VE BEEN DOING
YOUR DETACHING AND PROJECTING
AND TRANSFERRING EXERCISES.
DETRACTING FROM THE NOW,
PROJECTING INTO THE PAST
AND TRANSFERRING INTO
A POSITIVE EMOTION.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT
I DID, I'LL TELL
YOU WHAT I DID.
I CONCENTRATED.
I THOUGHT ABOUT--
A FEW MINUTES AGO, I WAS
OUT WALKING AROUND THE LODGE.
AND I WENT BY YOUR CABIN.
AND I WENT INSIDE,
AND I PICKED UP
ALL YOUR STUFF,
AND I DETACHED, PROJECTED
AND TRANSFERRED
IT ALL INTO THE LAKE.
YEAH!
WELCOME TO
THE EXPERTS PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THIS IS WHERE WE LIKE TO EXAMINE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY:
I DON'T KNOW.
YEAH.
HA, ALL RIGHTY,
JOINING MY UNCLE RED TODAY
IS MR. DALTON HUMPHREY OF
THE HUMPHREY EVERYTHING STORE.
WE'VE GOT STUFF...
MAYBE BUY SOME.
[cheering]
SIMPLE YET SIMPLE.
OK...
[laughing]
A VIEWER IN KANSAS CITY
WRITES US TODAY, AND THEY WRITE:
"DEAR EXPERTS,
MY FRIENDS OR FAMILY"
"DO THINGS THAT REALLY BUG ME."
"IS IT ME OR WHAT?"
SOUNDS LIKE
IT, YEAH.
NO, NO, NO, NOT
NECESSARILY TRUE, YOU KNOW.
I USUALLY FIND IT'S THEM.
BUT YOU CAN FORCE
PEOPLE TO CHANGE.
IT'S NOT EASY,
BUT YOU OWE IT TO THEM.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF THE TERM "CONTROL FREAK"?
OH, YEAH.
OH, YEAH, MY BROTHER-IN-LAW'S
ONE OF THOSE.
I'M WORKING ON
CHANGING HIM, THOUGH.
YOU CAN WORK AS HARD
AS YOU WANT ON TRYING
TO CHANGE PEOPLE, BUT YOU'LL
SPEND A LOT OF TIME DOING THAT;
THE MINUTE YOU LEAVE THE ROOM,
THEY'LL REVERT TO THEMSELVES.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST
LEARN TO ACCEPT PEOPLE
FOR WHO THEY ARE
AND BE FORGIVING.
I THINK I'D BE TALKING
TO YOU THERE, BERNICE.
YOU KNOW, THAT IS
SUCH A COP-OUT.
WHAT KIND OF FATHER WOULD
I BE IF I DIDN'T REMIND
PEOPLE TO USE COASTERS
AND TO TUCK IN
THE SHOWER CURTAIN
AND TO LOAD THE DISHWASHER
PROPERLY -- BIG PLATES
AT THE BACK, BOWLS ON THE RIGHT,
SAUCERS ON THE LEFT.
IMAGINE THE CHAOS.
HUH? AND WHEN MY DAUGHTER
GOES OUT WITH
HER BOYFRIEND FOR A DRIVE,
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN
IF I DIDN'T YELL OUT,
"DRIVE CAREFULLY!"
"DON'T HAVE AN ACCIDENT!" --
WHAT THEN, HUH?
I'VE SEEN HIM DRIVE.
HE'S A PRETTY SAFE DRIVER.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, RED.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
SO YOU DON'T TELL ME THAT WE
SHOULDN'T HELP OUT THE PEOPLE
AROUND US BY POINTING OUT
WHAT THEY'RE DOING WRONG.
I'M GLAD YOU FEEL THAT WAY,
'CAUSE I FEEL YOU'RE TOO BOSSY,
YOU'RE TOO NOSY
AND YOU ALWAYS LIKE--
WHAT? I DON'T
HAVE TO TAKE THAT FROM YOU.
EXCUSE ME.
DID I SAY
SOMETHING WRONG?
I DON'T THINK SO.
HE LEFT, DIDN'T HE?
[ RED ]: BILL HAD ASKED ME
TO MEET HIM IN THE WOODS.
OH, THERE HE IS.
I'M RIGHT HERE, BILL.
OH, OH.
NOW HE'S HERE.
OH, NO, THAT'S YOUR BIKE, BILL.
I THINK YOU'LL NEED
A BIKE YOURSELF.
I DON'T QUITE KNOW.
OH, HE'S FINE, HE'S FINE.
HI, THERE...
COUPLE OF BRANCH OFFICES THERE.
YEAH, I'M FINE, I'M FINE.
WHAT'S UP? WHAT ARE WE DOING?
THAT'S NOT A HILL.
THAT'S A MOUNTAIN, MAN.
THAT'S A MOUNTAIN.
I'M NOT GOING UP THERE.
I GOT TO WALK UP?
WE'RE GOING TO RACE?
OH, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
OOH, MUST HAVE HIT
THE POINT THERE, BILL.
AH, ALL RIGHT, OK, I'M NOT
GOING TO WALK, BUT I'LL RACE.
YOU WALK; I'M GOING
TO GO ON MY BIKE.
NO PROBLEM, NO PROBLEM.
I'M UP FOR IT.
WATCH THE SEAT. IT LOOKS LOOSE.
THE SEAT LOOKS LOOSE, UH-OH.
OH, OH,
THAT'S GOT TO--
OH, THERE'S A LITTLE BRANCH.
THERE'S A BRANCH HERE.
WATCH OUT FOR THBRANCH, BILL.
BILL, THERE'S A BRANCH, BILL.
THERE'S A BRANCH.
CAN YOU SEE THE BRANCH?
[ THUDDING ]
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
OH, BOY.
NO, IT DIDN'T QUITE MAKE IT --
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT.
YEAH, YOU'RE FINE.
OH!
SO, I'M,
I'M MAKING GOOD TIME, AND START
AGAIN, BILL. WAY YOU GO.
THERE I AM AT THE TOP THERE.
I MADE IT. I GUESS I WIN.
COME ON, BILL. YOU COMING?
HERE HE COMES, HERE HE COMES.
OH, HERE'S A CLASSIC MOMENT --
YOU CAN FEEL IT, EH?
LOOK AT THAT. HUH?
OH, OH, OH!
I DIDN'T KNOW
WE WERE RACING BACK DOWN.
OH, OH, OH!
DOES THIS MEAN I LOST?
OH, NO, HE LOST.
YOU ALL RIGHT, BILL?
NOW HE'S FINE.
OH!
RANGER GORD ASKED ME IF HE COULD
COME ON HERE AND SING
A NEW SONG ABOUT HIS HOBBY.
HE'S GOT A NEW HOBBY APPARENTLY.
AND, YOU KNOW, BEAR IN MIND, WE
HAVE A WHOLE HALF HOUR TO FILL.
SO I'M THINKING...
I'M THINKING, YEAH.
THAT'S GREAT,
RANGER GORD,
YOU'RE GOING TO
PLAY THE GUITAR.
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU COULD EVEN
PLAY THE GUITAR.
REALLY, HAROLD, I'M SHOCKED.
WHAT ABOUT ALL THOSE TIMES
WE SAT AROUND THE CAMP FIRE
SINGING CAMP FIRE SONGS --
REMEMBER THAT?
I HAD A BEARD AND POT BELLY,
SORT OF SOUNDED LIKE THIS.
REMEMBER THAT?
THAT WAS
UNCLE RED AND I.
YEAH.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT, OK.
OK, WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
INSTEAD OF A SONG,
I'M GOING TO DO A POEM
ABOUT MY NEW HOBBY, OK?
NOT ALL POEMS
HAVE TO RHYME, DO THEY?
NO, NO, POEMS
DON'T HAVE TO
RHYME AND THEY
BE DIRTY, BUT
PEOPLE PREFER IT.
ALL RIGHT, OK.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING NOW?
I THINK WHAT I'M GOING TO DO
IS MORE OF A SPEECH
ABOUT MY NEW HOBBY, OK?
AW, SPEECHES
ARE GREAT.
SPEECHES ARE GOOD.
THAT'S VERY BRAVE OF YOU.
MANY PEOPLE DISLIKE PUBLIC
SPEAKING, SO IT'S BRAVE -- GO.
REALLY? WHY?
WHY?
[giggling]
IT'S PUBLIC SPEAKING.
YOU'RE SPEAKING TO THE PUBLIC;
THEY'RE ALL WATCHING YOU.
WHAT IF YOU FAIL?
SEE WHAT THEY'RE
DOING, EH?
THEY'RE
JUDGING YOU.
YOU.
YEAH.
THEY'RE SAYING,
"IS HE INTERESTING OR WHAT?"
AND THIS IS WHY WHEN
YOU GET UP THERE...
THEY JUDGE YOU.
JUST YOU.
AND SOMETIMES
THEY THINK YOU'RE BAD.
REAL BAD.
THAT'S WHY PEOPLE GET NERVOUS.
REAL NERVOUS.
TERRIBLE.
NERVOUS LIKE...
CAN'T TALK.
W-W-WAHHH!
WEIRD.
ANYWAY, OK, HERE'S MY SPEECH.
AHEM.
I COLLECT SPIDERS
IN MY SPARE TIME.
THE END.
OK, I GUESS THERE'S TIME
FOR SOME QUESTIONS.
YOU KNOW, EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE
I HAVE TO ADMIT THAT HAROLD
DOES KNOW WHAT
HE'S TALKING ABOUT.
THIS ANGER MANAGEMENT PLAN
HE'S GOT ME ON
IS WORKING OUT GREAT -- TURNS
OUT MY PROBLEM WAS I WASN'T
DELEGATING ENOUGH
RESPONSIBILITY.
SO NOW I GOT HAROLD DEALING
WITH ALL THE LODGE MEMBERS
AND RUNNING ERRANDS FOR ME.
I HAVE NEVER FELT BETTER.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH THESE PEOPLE!
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT IS IT -- IS THERE A PRIZE
FOR BEING THE STUPIDEST IDIOT IN
ALL OF POSSUM LAKE --
IS THAT IT?
IS THAT WHAT IT IS --
BECAUSE I'M TELLING YOU,
IT'S LIKE TRYING TO TALK TO
HALLOWEEN PUMPKINS OUT THERE.
DUHHH.
SO, UH, HAROLD.
DON'T YOU GET ON ME!
SO HOW'S IT
GOING?
OH, IT'S GOING GOOD, OH, YEAH.
OH, YEAH, MORON DRIVERS,
IDIOT SALES PEOPLE,
LODGE MEMBERS WITH I.Q.'s
LIKE ROOM TEMPERATURE MAYBE,
ROOM TEMPERATURE CELSIUS.
I LOOK FOR THE LIGHT
IN THEIR EYES,
I DO, I DO LOOK FOR
THE LIGHT IN THEIR EYES.
BULB'S BURNED OUT.
AND IT'S THOSE LITTLE
CHRISTMAS BULBS, TOO, YOU KNOW.
ONE'S GONE;
THE WHOLE ROW IS GONE.
AH, YOU KNOW...
[cheering]
IT'S AWFUL.
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU LIKE THIS.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
ARE YOU STARTING ON ME?
YOU STARTING ON ME -- YOU WANT
A PIECE OF ME?
NO, HAROLD, I'M JUST SAYING
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
CONTROL THAT ANGER A LITTLE BIT.
CONTROL THE TEMPER.
SEE WHAT'S HAPPENED HERE?
WHAT?
YOU SPENT SO MUCH TIME WORKING
ON MY ANGER MANAGEMENT
THAT YOU'VE LET YOUR OWN ANGER
GET OUT OF THE CAGE A BIT.
SEE, LOOK HOW ANGRY
YOU ARE, SEE?
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
WHEN YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
YOU CAN SEE SOMEBODY ABOUT THAT.
WELL, I THINK IT'S THE WAY
EVERYBODY
TREATS ME.
REALLY?
YES.
I THINK IT'S
YOUR LOOKS,
PERSONALITY, YOU
KNOW YOU'RE A GOOF.
WELL, IF YOU WOULDN'T
INSULT ME ALL THE TIME,
I WOULDN'T BE SO ANGRY.
BUT I WOULD,
SO IT'S A...
OH, YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
[squealing]
OH, IT'S MEETING
TIME, UNCLE RED.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
OK, EXCELLENT.
DON'T GET MAD.
FOR WHAT?
GET EVEN.
ALL RIGHT, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I LEARNED TODAY THAT
THE BEST WAY TO CONTROL ANGER
IS TO BE THE BOSS.
BUT OF COURSE, YOU KNEW THAT
ALL ALONG, DIDN'T YOU?
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
YOU KNOW, SIT WHERE
YOUR DESIGNATED SEATS ARE...