IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE MAN
WHO LOOKS BOTH WAYS
AFTER HE CROSSES THE STREET,
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU!
NICE OUTFIT, HAROLD.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THIS IS QUITE A DAY.
OUR CHESTS ARE SO PUFFED OUT
WITH PRIDE, THEY STICK OUT
ALMOST PAST OUR STOMACHS.
YOU'LL NEVER GUESS
WHAT HAPPENED TODAY.
THE POSSUM LODGE
PEEWEE HOCKEY TEAM
WON THE REGIONAL FINALS!
(Cheering and whistling)
HOW ABOUT
THAT, HUH?
I GOTTA TELL YOU,
IT WAS CLASSIC HOCKEY.
HITTING, CROSS-CHECKING,
ELBOWING, LOTS OF BLOOD...
THAT WAS JUST THE PARENTS.
I SURE HOPE
THEY DON'T START A FOOD FIGHT
AT THE HOCKEY BANQUET.
THE PARENTS ARE HAVING
A BANQUET?
EXCELLENT!
OH, NO, NO, WE ARE.
WE SPONSORED THE TEAM AND
THEY'RE GOING TO THE FINALS.
IT'S UP TO US TO HAVE A BANQUET
FOR THEM -- IT'S TRADITION.
WE'LL BE BREAKING
THAT TRADITION.
NO, YOU CAN'T -- IT'S EXPECTED.
THE KIDS EXPECT IT,
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY,
THE PARENTS EXPECT IT.
YOU DON'T WANT TO UPSET THEM.
SURELY THE LODGE CAN THROW
A LITTLE HOCKEY BANQUET.
WELL, LET'S SEE.
THE LODGE HAS
ABOUT 23 BUCKS, HAROLD.
WE CAN'T USE ALL THAT
'CAUSE THE LODGE
HAS TO PICK UP MILK AND BREAD.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MAIN MESSAGE BEING,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL GO AHEAD
WITH THIS BANQUET
'CAUSE THE TEAM WE SPONSORED
WON THE DARN REGIONAL FINALS.
PRICE OF SUCCESS, I GUESS.
THEY GOT THE PARENTS COMING IN.
THEY WANT US TO CLEAN
THE LODGE A BIT.
(Audience laughing)
PROBABLY NEEDED IT ANYWAY.
UNCLE RED!
UNCLE RED, I GOT THE TROPHIES
FOR THE BANQUET.
I GOT 'EM ALL -- THE M.V.P.,
THE M.V.P., THE M.V.P.,
THE M.V.P., M.V.P.,
AND THE M.M.V.V.P.P.
(Audience laughing)
YOU GOT FIVE
MOST VALUABLE PLAYER TROPHIES?
NO, NO, LET'S SEE -- GOT, UM...
THAT'S, UH,
MOST VOLATILE PLAYER...
(Laughing)
MOST VERBAL PROFANITY...
MOST VULGAR PLAYER...
MOVING VIOLATION WITH A PUCK...
(Laughing)
AND WHAT ABOUT
THE M.M.V.V.P.P.?
MAJOR MAIMING OF A VULNERABLE
VICTIM'S PRIVATE PARTS.
(Laughing and applause)
(Cheering)
WOW.
I DIDN'T GET
A MOST VALUABLE PLAYER TROPHY.
WHAT ABOUT
THIS BRASS CUP?
THIS IS THE THUMBSTON CUP.
THAT'S
A BEAUTY.
DONATED BY DR. THUMBSTON,
THE DENTIST.
TEETH IN THERE, HAROLD?
WHATEVER PLAYER LOSES THE MOST
TEETH, THEY GO IN HERE.
HE MAKES THEM INTO AN UPPER
OR LOWER PLATE, YOUR CHOICE.
THAT'S REALLY NEAT.
OH, HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
SPEAKING OF CHEWING, HOW'S
THE PLANNING OF FOOD GOING?
IT'S ALL UNDER CONTROL.
HAVE A LITTLE FAITH.
I HAVE FAITH,
THE TEAM HAS FAITH.
WHAT THEY'RE REALLY GONNA WANT
IS FOOD!
(Audience laughing)
(Red): HERE'S A TEASER
FOR THE ADVENTURE WITH BILL...
HI, BILL.
... THE ADVENTURE WITH BILL,
COMING UP LATER.
BILL AND HAROLD ARE GONNA WORK
ON THIS ONE.
THEY GOT A DO-IT-YOURSELF...
IT'S A DO-IT-YOURSELF
LOG CABIN KIT.
QUITE A BIG UNIT.
AND, UH... MAY NOT GO
THAT WELL,
I'M THINKING AT THIS POINT.
IF YOU GET INJURED
JUST OPENING THE BOX,
THAT'S A SIGN FROM GOD
TO BUY ONE ALREADY BUILT.
KIND OF AN UNUSUAL KIT.
I'LL TELL YOU ONE THING.
THE COMPANY'S INTO PACKAGING
IN A BIG WAY.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
THERE'S YOUR
DO-IT-YOURSELF KIT --
A COUPLE OF AXES... OH, BOY.
A COUPLE OF AXES,
AND A COUPLE OF-- OHHH!
DON'T BE DOING THAT, HAROLD.
IF YOU'RE NOT HAVING KIDS,
MAYBE IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
OHHH! I WOULD THINK
THAT WOULD HURT,
BUT WITH HAROLD,
YOU JUST NEVER KNOW.
OH, I SEE -- ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS IMPORTANT
FOR YOU YOUNGSTERS WATCHING
WHO WANT TO DO THINGS.
YOU REALLY ARE NEVER
ANY SHARPER THAN YOUR TOOLS.
YOU CAN SEE THESE ARE TWO GUYS
IN BIG TROUBLE.
MAYBE THIS ONE'S ALL RIGHT.
NO? OH, YEAH,
THAT ONE'S FINE, THAT'S FINE.
BILL ALWAYS QUESTIONS
EVERYTHING, DON'T YOU?
AHHH!
IT'S A GOOD POLICY.
THERE THEY ARE -- THEY'RE FINE.
THEY'VE GOT THE GRINDER GOING.
OHHHH!
WE'RE DOWN TO ONE AXE, ARE WE?
JUST DOWN TO ONE AXE NOW?
NO, OK, HE BROUGHT 'ER BACK.
HE'S GONNA SHARPEN THAT,
'CAUSE THE OTHER ONE WAS SHARP.
WATCH OUT FOR THE SPARKS...
AND THERE'S SOME SPARKS.
THAT COULD...
THAT'S THE KIND OF SPARKS
THAT COULD IGNITE CLOTHING.
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
OH, BY GOLLY.
ALL RIGHT, GET SOMETHING.
HAROLD, GET SOMETHING.
NEVER MIND, IT'S FINE,
WE'RE FINE.
OHHHH! OHHH!
OH, BOY.
WE'LL COME BACK ONCE WE BUY
SOME MORE INSURANCE.
OHHHH...
PIZZA IN THE KITCHEN
PIZZA IN THE HALL
PIZZA ON THE CARPET
AND HALFWAY UP THE WALL
PIZZA IN THE PARLOUR
PIZZA ON THE FLOOR
IT'S NOT ACTUALLY PIZZA
WE JUST FORGOT TO PUT THE
LID ON THE FOOD PROCESSOR
THIS IS THE BIG ONE!
FOR THE GRAND PRIZE
OF AN ELECTRIC HAMMER AND GLUE,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. DALTON HUMPHREYS
OF HUMPHREYS' EVERYTHING STORE
TO SAY THIS WORD.
CHARITY.
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT,
DALTON.
IN THE BIBLE, IT SAYS
THIS BEGINS AT HOME.
ARGUMENTS.
WHEN YOU GIVE MONEY TO A GOOD
CAUSE, YOU DONATE TO A...
... A MUTUAL
FUND.
YOU'RE NOT EXPECTING
MONEY BACK.
IT'S A...
... SAVINGS ACCOUNT.
OK, UNITED WAY IS A...
... NUISANCE!
WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
FAMILY COMES INTO YOUR STORE.
THEY HAVE NO MONEY, FIVE KIDS.
YOU GOT CRAPPY USED TOYS.
WOMAN COMES AND SAYS,
"IF I BUY FOUR TOYS, CAN I HAVE
THE 5th TOY FOR NOTHING?"
WHAT DO YOU THINK I'M RUNNING?
A CHARITY?
(Laughing and applause)
THAT'S IT?
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
I WANT TO SHOW YOU
HOW YOU CAN DO
A VEHICLE UPGRADE
THAT I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO DO,
BUT COULDN'T AFFORD,
UNTIL HAROLD EXPLAINED
THAT ANYTHING ON THIS SHOW
IS A TAX WRITE-OFF.
HAROLD'S ON THE SHOW
AND HE'S A COMPLETE WRITE-OFF.
HE MUST BE RIGHT.
I DO A LOT OF OFF-TRACK
DRIVING IN THIS VEHICLE,
NOT NECESSARILY ON PURPOSE.
THE STEERING AND BRAKES ARE...
WELL, THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
UP TILL NOW, I'VE BEEN
LIKE THAT BLANCHE DUBOIS.
I'VE RELIED ON THE KINDNESS
OF STRANGERS.
I WON'T HAVE TO DO THAT
ANY MORE.
I'LL PULL MYSELF OUT OF DITCHES
FROM NOW ON.
LOOK WHAT I GOT IN HERE!
HUH? A ONE-TON WINCH.
I JUST GOTTA HOOK THAT UP
TO THE FRONT BUMPER
AND BOB'S YOUR AUNT --
IT'S THE '90's.
(Grunting)
ALL RIGHT, NO SENSE
GETTING MY CONDITION FLARED UP.
I'LL GET A TOOL TO HELP ME.
THE RIGHT TOOL FOR THE JOB.
THAT'S WHAT I SAY
WHEN THINGS GO WRONG.
I SAY THAT A LOT.
TRY THAT UNDER THERE.
(Grunting)
BY GOLLY, SHE'S...
SHE'S A HEAVY UNIT.
I'LL JUST PUSH THAT OUT
WITH MY FEET.
ALWAYS HAD STRONG LEGS.
REAL PROUD OF THAT.
ALL RIGHT, STAND BACK.
(Grunting)
WELL, UM...
I NEED A LEVER
OF SOME KIND TO...
I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
WHY DON'T WE LET THE TOOL
DO THE WORK?
ALL I GOTTA DO...
HOOK THE CHAIN
ONTO THE FRONT BUMPER,
TURN ON THE WINCH
AND LET IT PULL ITSELF.
I'LL GO HOOK 'ER UP.
MAN, DARK DOWN HERE.
IS THAT SHOCK ABSORBER LEAKING?
MAYBE IT'S THE DIFFERENTIAL...
IT'S BOTH!
I KEEP CATCHING THE PANTS
ON EVERYTHING.
GOOD PLACE FOR A PARTY.
THAT RAD'S LEAKING...
SO'S THE TRANSMISSION,
THE ENGINE...
IT'S LIKE IT'S RAINING HERE.
(Grunting)
MAN!
OHHH...
NOT TOO BAD.
WE JUST TAKE THIS,
HOOK 'ER ONTO THE BUMPER,
AND THEN LET THE WINCH
PULL ITSELF.
LET THE TOOL DO THE JOB.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID
WHEN I MADE HAROLD PRODUCER.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT MY CHAIN
AROUND THE GRILLE
AND MAN, SHE IS SOLID.
THE GRILLE ISN'T,
BUT THE CHAIN SURE AS HECK IS.
I'VE GOT CABLES HOOKED UP
TO TAKE ELECTRICITY
FROM THE BATTERY
TO THE WINCH --
SHE'S HOOKED RIGHT--
YEAH! LOTS OF POWER.
WE'RE ALL SET
AND I JUST FLICK 'ER ON
AND JUST FLICK A SWITCH
AND STAND BACK
AND LET THE WINCH DO THE WORK.
MY KIND OF PROJECT.
HOPE I GOT
ENOUGH POWER CABLE ON THERE.
THERE SHE GOES AGAIN.
MUST BE MORE THAN I THOUGHT.
GOLLY, THAT'S NOT
SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
I'LL TURN THAT WINCH OFF.
SHE'S WAY UP THERE NOW.
THIS IS A GOOD THING
'CAUSE I CAN USE
THIS OPPORTUNITY
TO CHECK THE ENTIRE
ELECTRICAL SYSTEM.
THAT LIGHT BULB'S BURNT OUT.
NEVER WOULD HAVE SEEN THAT.
LOOK AT THOSE SPARK PLUGS.
THEY NEED TO BE GAPPED.
YEAH, BY GOLLY,
THAT NEEDS REPAIR.
THE WINCH IS
A FABULOUS THING.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I SHOULD PULL
THE ENGINE OUT, TOO.
OH, HERE IT COMES NOW.
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
WANT TO TALK TO YOU GUYS
ABOUT A DISTURBING FAD.
SELF-HELP BOOKS --
YOU SEEN THESE THINGS?
YEAH, THEY'RE IN THE BOOKSTORE.
ODD TITLES, THINGS LIKE
"DIAPERING YOUR INNER CHILD."
(Laughing)
"WOMEN ARE FROM VENUS,
MEN ARE IN THE BASEMENT."
"THE SEVEN DEVIOUS HABITS
OF SUCCESSFUL PEOPLE."
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT THE LAST THING I WANT
IS AN INNER CHILD FROM VENUS
WHO'S MORE SUCCESSFUL
THAN I AM.
WE SHOULD ALL BACK OFF
ON THE SELF-HELP THING.
WE NEED ANOTHER KIND OF BOOK
TO HELP MEN, WITH TITLES LIKE,
"HEY, MEN ARE PRETTY MUCH
PERFECT THE WAY THEY ARE."
OR "EVERYTHING I NEED TO KNOW
ABOUT LIFE,
"I LEARNED
IN THE HARDWARE STORE."
I KNOW ONE.
"SELF-ESTEEM THROUGH
ABSENT-MINDED SCRATCHING."
THAT WOULD PROBABLY BE A MOVIE.
WE SHOULD EASE OFF
ON THE SELF-HELP
BECAUSE IT COULD BE DANGEROUS.
YOU COULD END UP
BEING OVER-IMPROVED
FOR THE NEIGHBOURHOOD
IN WHICH YOU LIVE,
IF YOU CATCH MY DRIFT.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause)
THE PARENTS AND KIDS
AND EVERYTHING,
THE HOCKEY PLAYERS,
THEY'RE DOWN IN THE BASEMENT,
GETTING READY FOR THE BANQUET.
THINGS ARE CRANKING UP
PRETTY GOOD.
HAROLD'S ENTERTAINING THEM.
HE'S GETTING A SING-SONG GOING.
(Harold): OWWW!
OWWW!
STOP THAT!
STOP IT!
THAT'S NOT FUNNY!
SOMEONE'S GONNA GET HURT
AND THERE'S GONNA BE TROUBLE!
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S SERIOUS!
THAT-- OK, OK, THAT'S IT!
HA-HA!
NO MORE GAMES!
(Shouting)
ALL RIGHT,
SOMETHING'S GONNA BREAK!
(Glass
breaking)
(Laughing)
UNCLE RED! WHERE'S THE FOOD?
THEY'RE GOING CRAZY --
IT'S LIKE A RIOT!
CAN'T THE PARENTS
CONTROL THEM?
THOSE ARE THE PARENTS!
THE KIDS ARE OUTSIDE,
PLAYING BASKETBALL!
WE GOTTA GET FOOD!
THEN THEY'LL PUT DOWN
THEIR WEAPONS.
ALL RIGHT, YOU TELL 'EM
PIZZA'S ON THE WAY.
PIZZA'S
ON THE WAY!
YOU TELL THEM, HAROLD.
I'M GOING
BACK IN!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT!
OHHH! OK!
I SAW YOU! I KNOW WHO THAT IS!
I'M GONNA TELL
YOUR CHILDREN!
COME ON, COME ON...
HELLO, PIZZA SHACK?
THIS IS RED GREEN
AT POSSUM LODGE.
I WANT 20 LARGE PIZZAS,
EVERYTHING ON 'EM.
YEAH, I'LL PAY CASH.
IF THEY'RE NOT HERE
IN 30 MINUTES, THEY'RE FREE?
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, BYE.
JUNIOR, TELL THE GUYS.
PUT NAILS ON THE ROAD,
BURN THE VAN, BLOCK THE BRIDGE,
SHOOT OUT THE PORCH LIGHT,
SWITCH THE STREET SIGNS.
(Applause and cheering)
(Siren)
POSSUM 911, CAN WE HELP YOU?
UH, RED?
YES, SIR!
IS THAT RED?
RIGHT HERE.
THAT'S RED RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S NOT RED.
I'M HAROLD -- THAT'S RED.
WOULD YOU PUT RED ON?
RED'S RIGHT HERE!
I'M HERE!
UH, RED? IS THAT YOU?
YEAH!
TALK TO ME, RED!
IS THAT YOU, REALLY?
HE'S RIGHT HERE,
IF YOU WANT TO TALK!!
WHO'S THAT, NOW?
THAT WAS
HAROLD.
I'M RED -- GO AHEAD.
THAT YOU, RED?
DID YOU SAY "FRED" OR "RED"?
RED'S HERE -- I'M HAROLD --
YOU'RE TALKING TO RED.
COULD YOU GET A MESSAGE TO RED?
I'LL DO MY BEST!
UH... ARE YOU THERE, RED?
TIME TO PUT A DOOR
ON THE MICROWAVE, ALL RIGHT?
I AM THE LEADER
OF POSSUM LODGE!
YOU'RE ACTUALLY TALKING TO ME
BUT IT WON'T LAST FOREVER,
IF YOU GET MY DRIFT!
I AM THE ACTUAL RED GREEN!
RED GREEN?
YEAH.
OH... HONEY, WE GOT
THE WRONG NUMBER.
OHHHH!
(Red): MEANWHILE,
BACK AT THE RANCH...
OHHH...
MUST BE DINNERTIME.
THE BRAIN TRUST OF POSSUM LODGE
IS WORKING ON THE LOG CABIN.
WHAT?
BOY, THAT'S AN ODD THING.
THAT WOULD BE A HAUNTED LOG.
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR LOGS
TO MAKE THEIR LOG CABIN.
THERE'S ONE --
THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD ONE.
BILL WANTS IT A CERTAIN LENGTH
AND TELLS HAROLD
WHERE HE WANTS-- OH, BY GOLLY!
(Laughing)
HEY! YOU KNOW, HERE'S A LESSON.
IT'S A GOOD IDEA
TO BRING A PENCIL.
THIS IS NOT-- OH, BOY!
THIS IS NOT THE WAY TO DO IT.
SO FAR, YOU'RE JUST LUCKY.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE LUCKY--
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
OH, BOY... OH, BOY... OH, BOY.
OHHH! JUST CUT THE WATCH.
(Laughing)
JUST IN THE NICK OF TIME,
WE CALL THAT.
ALL RIGHT... OH, THIS IS GOOD.
HAROLD HOLDS THE LOG.
OK, GOOD, OK.
THAT MAKES PERFECT SENSE TO ME.
UH... KIDS?
DON'T TRY THIS ANYWHERE,
ALL RIGHT?
THERE GOES THE LOG AGAIN.
ROLLIN', ROLLIN',
ROLLIN'
THEY'RE GONNA GO
SOMETHING HEAVIER...
LOOKS LIKE YOU GUYS
ARE A BIT STUMPED, HUH?
THAT'S TOO MUCH JUICE.
THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
OH, BY GOSH.
LET'S SKIP THIS PART.
DON'T BE LOOKIN' AT THAT.
READ A BOOK FOR A SECOND.
WE'LL GET BACK TO YOU.
OK, BILL'S GOT AN IDEA.
THAT SHOULD WORK -- RIGHT.
OH, THIS IS INTERESTING.
WE'RE GOING BACK
TO THE PIONEER DAYS
BEFORE THEY EVEN HAD LIVESTOCK.
AND THEY WOULD RUN ROPES
AROUND THINGS
AND GET THE BIGGER WOMEN
TO PULL ON THAT.
LOOK AT THAT -- LOOK AT THE...
OHHH! OHHH! OHHH!
CAREFUL, GUYS!
OK, THEY'RE GONNA--
OK, THEY FIXED 'ER UP.
GOT A BETTER KNOT AND
GOT 'ER WOUND ROUND MORE TIMES.
WRAP THAT AROUND YOUR NECK.
PULL THE SAME WAY, HAROLD.
THE THING WITH THIS IS,
YOU GOTTA HAVE BOTH GUYS
OF EQUAL STRENGTH.
I THINK MAYBE HAROLD'S
A LITTLE WEAK IN THAT AREA.
ACTUALLY, HAROLD'S WEAK
IN EVERY AREA.
BILL, PULLING
AS HARD AS HE CAN,
DOESN'T REALIZE THAT
HE'S WRAPPED HAROLD
IN AROUND THE...
OH, BOY! OH, BOY!
YOU'VE CUT OFF HIS... YOU KNOW,
THAT THING THAT HE HAS.
YOU CUT THAT OFF --
IT'S COMPLETELY CUT OFF.
BILL, YOU MIGHT WANT TO
GET THAT OUT.
I DON'T THINK HE'S FAKING.
HERE'S THE THING-- OH, BOY!
I WOULDN'T RECOMMEND-- OH, BOY!
I WOULD NOT RECOMMEND THIS
AS A WAY
OF REMOVING...
OH, ALL RIGHT, OK.
IN THIS ONE INSTANCE,
IT WORKED FINE,
BUT DON'T FORGET --
WE CAN EDIT.
ALL RIGHT, THEY'RE ALL SET,
AND, UH, BILL...
(Glass
breaking)
THE VAN WAS CLOSE BY.
BILL HAS ANOTHER IDEA --
TWO SAWS.
HOW ARE YOU GONNA MAKE
A LOG CABIN?
(Sawing)
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES!
EH? THERE'S THE KIT!
(Laughing)
YOU GUYS HAVE NO CHANCE.
OH!
WHAT A WASTE OF TIME.
LOOK AT THIS "CHAIN SAW",
SENT BY A VIEWER.
MY FAVOURITE PART OF THE SHOW,
WHERE WE EXAMINE THE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
(Audience):
"I DON'T KNOW!"
(Laughing)
I LOVE THAT PART.
JOINING MY UNCLE RED
ON THE EXPERT PART
IS MR. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
OF ROTHSCHILD SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD.
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU.
I'M A GOOD GUY TO KNOW WHEN
YOU CAN'T GO WITH THE FLOW.
(Laughing)
CHARMING... ALL RIGHTY.
LETTER GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS, I NEVER HAD
A STRONG FASHION SENSE.
"I DON'T HAVE A GIRLFRIEND
TO SHOP WITH ME
"SO I'M NOT SURE HOW WIDE
A STRIPE TO GET ON A SHIRT
"TO COMPLEMENT MY
GREEN-AND-YELLOW PLAID PANTS."
WAHHH!
BOY! SAYS HE DOESN'T HAVE
A GIRLFRIEND.
GO FIGURE, HUH?
BUT HEY, GUY, I KNOW
WHERE YOU'RE COMIN' FROM.
HOPEFULLY,
SOMEWHERE DARK.
(Red): COME ON,
NOW, HAROLD.
I'M SAYING THAT
A LOT OF MEN HATE
TO GO SHOPPING FOR CLOTHES.
HUH! SPEAK
FOR YOURSELF,
CAPTAIN FLANNEL.
I JUST LOVE
SHOPPING FOR SNAPPY NEW OUTFITS
FOR MYSELF.
SURE, I THINK OF MYSELF
AS THE CALVIN KLEIN OF SEWAGE.
AS A GREAT MAN ONCE SAID,
HE SAID, UH,
"YOU ARE WHAT YOU WEAR."
I THOUGHT IT'S
"YOU ARE WHAT YOU EAT".
I SPILL STUFF ON MY SHIRT
SO THEY'RE ALL COVERED.
WHAT YOU NEED TO DO IS
HOOK IN TO WORLD-FAMOUS
SELF-HELP GURU ANTHONY ANTHONY,
AUTHOR OF THE BOOK
"DON'T HAVE A CRAPPY LIFE".
(Audience laughing)
ANTHONY ANTHONY SAYS THAT
WHAT WE WEAR
SAYS A LOT ABOUT OURSELVES.
SEE, RED, YOUR OUTFIT,
IT BASICALLY SAYS,
"I'M LAID-BACK, SLOPPY,
AND REALLY REALLY MARRIED."
(Laughing)
WHEREAS HAROLD OVER HERE,
THAT JUST SCREAMS
"I'M ENERGETIC, I'M NERVOUS,
AND INEXPERIENCED WITH GIRLS."
(Audience laughing)
TWO VERY OPPOSITE LOOKS, TWO
VERY OPPOSITE PERSONALITIES.
WINSTON, WE ARE WEARING
EXACTLY THE SAME UNIT, HERE.
YOU ARE?
YEAH!
BECAUSE YOU HAVE MORE
OF THE...
NO, NO, NOT REALLY.
BUT HAROLD DOESN'T HAVE
HALF AS MUCH...
NO, NO, IT'S THE SAME, UH...
MAYBE IT'S NOT
SO MUCH WHAT YOU WEAR.
IT'S HOW YOU WEAR IT.
(Laughing)
YOU PUT YOUR FOOT IN IT,
DIDN'T YOU, MR. ROTHSCHILD?
THAT'S WHY HE HAS HIP-WADERS.
(Laughing and applause)
29 MINUTES AND
STILL NO PIZZA DELIVERY!
(Shouting)
WE'RE 60 SECONDS AWAY
FROM A FREE BANQUET.
I HOPE THOSE OBSTACLES
DON'T STOP THE GUY COMPLETELY.
IF THOSE PIZZAS ARE LATE...
THOSE HOCKEY PARENTS
WILL LEVEL THIS PLACE.
30 SECONDS TO GO!
(Car door closing)
PIZZA'S HERE!
WHAT?!
OH, NO!!!
YEAH, WHAT?
YOU WON'T BELIEVE THIS.
AFTER YOU ORDERED, I WENT OUT
TO MAKE SURE
THE PORCH LIGHT WAS ON
SO HE COULD FIND US.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHAT?
IT WAS SHOT OUT!
OHHH, HAROLD!
IT WAS WEIRD, 'CAUSE
WHEN I TURNED IT ON,
I SAW SMOKE COMING
FROM MERCURY CREEK BRIDGE.
KNOW WHAT I SAW?
(Together): A VAN ON FIRE!
YEAH, JUST ON FIRE!
I TOLD THE PIZZA GUY
TO TAKE THE SHORT WAY.
WHAT SHORT WAY?
ACROSS THE LAKE IN A BOAT.
OHHHH,
MY GOSH!
LUCKY I SAW FLAMES --
HE MIGHT HAVE BEEN AN HOUR.
GOSH, THAT
WAS LUCKY!
HERE'S THE BILL.
THERE'S THE BILL
RIGHT THERE -- $315.75.
OH, MY...
I'LL TAKE THESE DOWN,
IF YOU'LL PAY HIM.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
HAROLD, YOU KNOW,
YOU ARE AN M.V.P.
WELL, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
DON'T FORGET TO TIP HIM.
(Audience laughing)
I'M COMING! I'M COMING, YOU...!
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M NOT GONNA BE
COMING HOME FOR A WHILE.
I'M GOING TO THE PIZZA SHACK.
I'LL BE WASHING PANS
FOR A CERTAIN AMOUNT OF TIME.
PROBABLY BE PAINTING THE PLACE
AND TUNING UP
THEIR DELIVERY TRUCKS.
(Crying)
I'M NOT REALLY HUNGRY
ANYWAY, SO...
EVERYBODY ELSE...
SEE YA.
(Laughing and applause)
(Possum squeal)
EVERYBODY WANT PIZZA?
(Shouting)
THERE'S SOME OVER THERE!
THERE'S PEPPERONI HERE!
THE DOUBLE-CHEESE IS--
NO, DOUBLE-CHEESE IS THERE!
NOW, SOMEBODY WANTED
NO-ANCHOVIES!
NO-ANCHOVIES IS...
THIS IS NO-ANCHOVIES.
THAT'S NO-PIZZA, REALLY.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S HIGH FIBRE
IN THE BOX!
DON'T NEGATE THE BOX!