AND YOU NEED
TO LOOK AT THE MAP,
BUT MAYBE IT BLEW
OUT THE SUN ROOF?
OR IT'S STUCK TO
THE FLOOR IN THE AFTERMATH
OF SOME TYPE OF
A BEVERAGE SPILL?
WELL, HERE'S A BETTER IDEA.
DUCT TAPE THE MAP RIGHT
TO THE HOOD OF THE CAR.
THAT WAY YOU ALWAYS KNOW WHERE
IT IS WHEN YOU WANNA FIND IT.
I GUESS ANOTHER SOLUTION
WOULD BE TO STOP AND
ASK FOR DIRECTIONS.
[chuckle]
I DON'T SEE THAT
HAPPENING IN MY LIFETIME.
OKAY, LET'S GIVE HER A TRY.
FIRST THING, YOU HEAD
OUT ON YOUR TRIP.
THEN WHEN YOU WANNA
CHECK YOUR MAP,
YOU JUST PULL
ON THE HOOD RELEASE.
[cheering and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
WELL, I JUST GOT A CLEAN BILL
OF HEALTH FROM THE DOCTOR.
WELL, I DIDN'T ACTUALLY
GO TO THE DOCTOR.
I WAS TESTING MY BLOOD
PRESSURE ON ONE OF
THOSE MACHINES.
I PUSHED THE BUTTON, AND THING
JUST KEPT GETTING TIGHTER
AND TIGHTER AND TIGHTER...
SO FINALLY I JUST YELL OUT,
AND THE PHARMACIST COMES OVER
AND UNPLUGS THE MACHINE,
BUT SHE DOESN'T
LOOSEN IT OFF AT ALL.
SO THEN THEY CALLED 911.
A COUPLE OF PARAMEDICS
COME OVER.
ONE OF THEM HAD
TO CUT THE THING OFF.
I NOTICED THE OTHER PARAMEDIC,
A GUY I HAVEN'T SEEN
FOR 20 YEARS,
HE LOOKED AT ME,
HE SAYS,
YOU KNOW, YOU LOOK
PRETTY GOOD.
SO I FEEL REAL GOOD.
UNCLE RED.
[cheering and applause]
I'M SO EXCITED.
I'M COMPLETELY READY.
I'VE GOT EVERYTHING READY
FOR THE FABULOUS '50s
WEEKEND FESTIVAL.
OH, REFRESH MY MEMORY
ON THAT ONE, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW, IT'S WHEN WE INVITE
ALL THE CITY FOLK UP TO
POSSUM LAKE,
AND THEY CAN RELIVE
THE FABULOUS '50s.
SO DOES EVERYONE FROM TOWN
HAVE TO GET CLOTHES AND
HAIRSTYLES FROM '50s?
NO, THEY'VE PRETTY MUCH
GOT THAT COVERED ALREADY.
I'M HAVING TROUBLE
GETTING ENTERTAINERS.
EVERYONE I'M SEEING IS
REALLY BAD OR REALLY OLD.
MOST OF THEM
ARE BOTH.
WELL, COME ON,
HAROLD.
THERE ARE A LOT OF GREAT
ENTERTAINERS FROM THE '50s
WHO ARE STILL PERFORMING.
YEAH, BUT THEY
WON'T BE HERE.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT THAT
ROMPIN' RONNIE HAWKINS?
HE PLAYED HERE.
MAYBE HE COULD TELL THE
OTHERS ABOUT POSSUM LAKE.
HE DID.
THAT'S WHY THEY
WON'T BE HERE.
DOESN'T MATTER.
INSTEAD WE'RE HAVING AN
ELVIS IMPERSONATION CONTEST!
OH! OH! OH!
YEAH, YOU -- YOU -- YOU
SHOULD SIGN UP AND REPRESENT
MEMBERS OF THE LODGE.
YOU.
I'LL PUT YOU DOWN.
I'M NOT GONNA BE
IN THAT, HAROLD.
WHY? WHY?
YOU'D MAKE A GREAT --
COME ON!
YOU'D MAKE A GREAT ELVIS.
BUST A MOVE FOR US.
COME ON.
BUST A MOVE.
READ MY HIPS,HA.
IT'S NOT GONNA
HAPPEN, OKAY?
BUT IT IS LUNCH TIME,
SO I'M OFF TO
GREASE LAND.
I DUNNO.
I THINK RED GREEN
WOULD MAKE A GREAT ELVIS.
RED GREEN HAS LEFT
THE BUILDING.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheering and applause]
IF YOU LIKE SAUNAS,
YOU'RE LOVE TONIGHT'S PRIZE.
OUR WINNER WILL WALK AWAY
WITH 200 HOURS OF SAUNA FUN
FROM FAT JACK'S
HOUSE OF STEAM.
ALL 200 HOURS MUST
BE USED IN ONE VISIT.
OKAY, COVER
YOUR EARS, ED.
OKAY, RED, YOU'VE GOT
30 SECONDS TO GET ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICER ED FRITH
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, ED, IF YOU SEE
SOMEBODY STRUTTING AROUND
AND BRAGGING, YOU SAY
THE PERSON IS FULL OF...
ALCOHOL.
NO, NO, NO.
OKAY, WHEN THE
COMPANY IS HIRING,
THIS IS THE MAIN THING THEY
LOOK FOR IN THEIR EMPLOYEES.
DESPERATION.
NOW, YOU WORK
WITH ANIMALS, RIGHT?
NOW, WHAT IS IT THAT YOU HAVE
THAT ALLOWS YOU TO DO THAT?
MEDICAL INSURANCE.
NO, THIS IS LIKE A
CHARACTERISTIC,
LIKE A LEADERSHIP QUALITY.
THIS IS WHAT LEADERS HAVE.
OH, CONTEMPT.
NO, THIS IS A GOOD THING.
I MEAN, IF YOU HAD THIS,
YOU'D BE A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT PERSON.
SEX CHANGE?
UH, YOU GUYS ARE
ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
OKAY, ED, REMEMBER WHEN
YOU HAD THAT COUGAR
CORNERED IN
FLINTY McKLINTOCK'S BARN?
I KNOW THERE WAS A BIG FIGHT,
BUT AT THE END YOU GOT THAT
CAT INTO THE CAGE, RIGHT?
THAT TOOK A LOT OF...
BLOOD TRANSFUSIONS.
LET ME TELL YOU,
IF I'D KNOWN THAT
WAS IN THE BARN --
OKAY, OKAY.
OKAY, ED.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT YOU THAT
MAKES YOU A GOOD ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICER?
NOTHING.
I HATE THE JOB.
SCARES ME TO DEATH.
BUT I DON'T HAVE THE
CONFIDENCE TO TRY
ANYTHING ELSE.
[applause]
W.W.F. style announcer:
SUCKING SEWAGE ISN'T ALL
GLAMOUR AND GLITTER.
WINSTON HERE.
HM-MM.
I'M ON MY WAY!
announcer:
AT ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES
WE KNOW THAT EACH
DECISION CAN MEAN THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
LIFE AND DEATH.
[dramatic music]
announcer:
WE'RE SERIOUS ABOUT SEWAGE,
AND WE KNOW SOMETIMES
EVERY SECOND COUNTS.
[quirky upbeat music]
announcer:
EVEN THOUGH WE TAKE IT AWAY,
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE,
WE LIKE TO GIVE
A LITTLE BACK.
ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES,
WE DON'T JUST SUCK.
[applause]
NOW, I DONT REALLY
ENJOY A SALAD.
I HAVE MORE OF
A HUNTER MENTALITY.
I ONLY LIKE TO EAT
THINGS I HAVE TO CHASE.
BUT THERE IS ONE GOOD
THING ABOUT SALADS,
THE CHEESE GRATER.
A LOT OF ENGINEERING
IN THESE BABIES, YOU KNOW.
YOU SLIDE THE MATERIAL
AGAINST THE OUTSIDE
OF A ROTATING DRUM
THAT HAS BLADES CUT IN IT.
THEN THE SHREDDED OUTPUT
IS EXHAUSTED THROUGH
THE CENTRE CORE.
IT'S A GREAT DESIGN.
BUT WHAT IF IT COULD DO MORE
THAN CUT THE CHEESE?
YOU KNOW, NO MATTER HOW LONG
YOU LEAVE YOUR CHRISTMAS
TREE OUT FRONT,
THE GARBAGE MAN IS NOT
GOING TO TAKE IT AWAY.
SO I SAY, LET'S USE THE
TECHNOLOGY OF THE
CHEESE GRATER
TO MAKE OURSELVES A WOOD
CHIPPER OUT OF THIS
CLOTHES DRYER.
FIRST THING YOU WANNA
DO IS REMOVE THE DOOR.
OKAY, THAT'S 9 1/2.
THAT'S MY SHOE SIZE.
ALL RIGHT, NEXT YOU WANNA
CUT SOME SHARP EDGES
INTO THE DRUM
USING A POWER CHISEL.
NOT BECAUSE IT'S THE
RIGHT TOOL FOR THE JOB.
I JUST ALWAYS WANTED
TO USE ONE OF THESE.
[loud drilling sound]
shouting:
THAT WENT WELL!
normal:
THAT WENT WELL.
OKAY, I CUT A WHOLE WHACK OF
JAGGED SLOTS IN THE DRUM.
THAT'LL DO MY SHREDDING.
THEN THE CHIPS WILL JUST
COME OUT THE DOOR HOLE.
I NEED THAT DOOR HOLE
TO BE POINTING DOWN.
OKAY, NOW I JUST NEED TO RAISE
THE UNIT OFF THE GROUND
SO THERE'S ROOM FOR
THE CHIPS TO PILE UP.
OR I COULD JUST LAY IT
DOWN ON TOP OF THE WELL.
NO, I'LL RAISE IT UP.
AND THERE IT IS.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
DID THAT SOUND OKAY,
OR WAS I TOO
CHIPPER?
[chuckles]
ALL RIGHT, NOW ALL I GOTTA
DO IS SET THE CONTROLS
HM, I'D SAY EXTRA DRY.
[applause]
I WANNA SPEAK TO
ALL THE WIVES OUT THERE.
YOU KNOW, AS FAR BACK
AS I CAN REMEMBER
THERE HAVE BEEN
MEN'S MAGAZINES.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT,
"PLAYBOY," "PENTHOUSE,"
THAT KIND OF THING.
NOW, I'M NOT HERE TO PASS
JUDGEMENT ONE WAY
OR THE OTHER.
BUT I BET A LOT OF WIVES DON'T
APPRECIATE THEIR HUSBANDS
LOOKING AT THOSE MAGAZINES.
COMPARISON SHOPPING DOESN'T
BELONG IN THE BEDROOM.
BUT YOU KNOW, LIKE SO MANY
THINGS IN LIFE,
YOU GOTTA PUT IT
INTO PERSPECTIVE.
I WANT EVERY WIFE TO KNOW
THAT THERE IS SOMETHING
MUCH MORE DANGEROUS
THAN YOUR HUSBAND LOOKING
AT MEN'S MAGAZINES.
YOU SEE, A LOT OF GUYS MY AGE
HAVE ABANDONED THE GIRLIE
PUBLICATIONS,
AND THEY'VE REPLACED THEM
WITH THESE MONTHLY MAGAZINES
THAT FEATURE USED
TRUCKS, BOATS, RVs.
THEY'RE ALL FOR SALE,
COMPLETE WITH PICTURES,
AND SOME OF THEM
ARE VERY SUGGESTIVE.
NOW, I FIGURE THAT'S
GOTTA BE A LOT SCARIER
THAN SEEING YOUR HUSBAND
BROWSING THROUGH "PLAYBOY,"
BECAUSE WHEN HE SEES PICTURES
IN A MEN'S MAGAZINE,
THERE'S NO CHANCE HE'S GOING
TO BRING ANY OF THOSE HOME.
REMEMBER I'M
PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
[loon calling]
YOU KNOW, YOU BOYS ARE
THE LUCKIEST GUYS
IN THE WORLD.
WHO'S HE TALKING TO?
THE BAIT.
NO,
YOU GUYS.
YOU'RE BOTH MARRIED.
YOU HAVE WIVES.
GO ON.
NO,
THAT'S IT.
YOU HAVE WOMEN WHO CARE
FOR YOU AND LOOK AFTER YOU.
TAKE CARE OF
YOUR EVERY NEED.
NO, WE DON'T.
WE'RE MARRIED.
YOU KNOW, WINSTON,
MARRIAGE DOESN'T WORK
EXACTLY THE WAY THEY DESCRIBE
IT IN THOSE MAGAZINES YOU BUY.
MAYBE NOT.
I STILL SAY
YOU'RE LUCKY.
YOU KNOW, I'D GIVE UP
EVERYTHING TO FIND A WIFE.
[scoffs]
I DID.
WHY IS MARRIAGE SO
APPEALING FOR YOU,
WINSTON?
I DUNNO.
COMPANIONSHIP,
SHARING YOUR
LIFE WITH SOMEONE,
THAT'S A GOOD THING.
FINDING SOMEONE
WHO'LL STAY OVERNIGHT.
YOU KNOW,
EVERY NIGHT.
NOW, DON'T GET CARRIED
AWAY HERE, WINSTON.
YOU KNOW, WINSTON,
99% OF THE TIME
WHEN YOU'RE SLEEPING
WITH SOMEONE --
YEAH?
YOU'RE SLEEPING
WITH SOMEONE.
THEN THERE'S THE COLD FEET
IN THE MIDDLE OF YOUR BACK.
AND WORSE.
MUSCLE SPASMS IS THE REASON
THEY INVENTED KING SIZED BEDS.
WELL, GUYS, I'M IN
THE SEWAGE BUSINESS.
I'M USED TO MAKING IT
THROUGH TOUGH SITUATIONS.
YEAH, BUT MARRIAGE IS MORE
OF A GIVE AND TAKE, WINSTON.
YOU GOTTA MEET
THE PERSON HALF WAY.
THAT'S THE SAME AS
IN THE SEWAGE BUSINESS.
I MEAN, YOU GOTTA GET
A LITTLE GIVE IN
THE BLOCKAGE;
OTHERWISE, YOU'RE
GONNA BE BACKED UP
FROM HERE
TILL SUNDAY.
YOU KNOW, WINSTON, AS LONG
AS YOU APPROACH MARRIAGE
THE WAY YOU WOULD
A PLUGGED SEPTIC SYSTEM,
I THINK YOU'LL
BE FINE.
JUST DON'T
GET SUCKED IN.
WELL, EVERYBODY'S GETTING
EXCITED ABOUT THIS
BIG '50s WEEKEND THING
THAT HAROLD'S GOT PLANNED.
FUNNY HOW PEOPLE REMEMBER
THINGS AS BEING BETTER
THAN THEY WERE.
SOMEBODY ASKED ME WHATEVER
HAPPENED TO URSEL HICKEY.
AND I SAID I'M SURE
IT'S CLEARED UP BY NOW.
UNCLE RED, PLEASE,
YOU HAVE TO JOIN
THE ELVIS CONTEST.
HAROLD,
I'M NOT GONNA --
BESIDES, I HEARD YOU
GOT A TON OF CONTESTANTS.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, YEAH.
QUANTITY I GOT.
QUANTITY'S NEVER
A PROBLEM UP HERE.
NO, IT'S JUST WHEN YOU
MENTION THE WORD QUALITY
THE ROOM GETS AWFULLY QUIET.
WELL, IT DOESN'T
MATTER, HAROLD.
AS LONG AS YOU
HAVE CONTESTANTS,
YOU HAVE A CONTEST.
IF YOU CAN'T PICK THE BEST,
PICK THE LEAST WORST.
NO, I WANNA TURN THIS
INTO AN ANNUAL EVENT.
IF IT STINKS THIS YEAR,
NO ONE'LL EVER COME BACK.
OH, HAROLD,
IT CAN'T BE THAT BAD.
HA! YEAH!
WHAT?
YOU STAY --
OKAY, OKAY,
OKAY, GUYS,
COME ON IN.
WHAT'S THIS?
[laughter]
[whistling and applause]
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
I SEE WHAT YOU MEAN.
OH, NO!
OH, NO, YOU DON'T.
OH, NO,
NOT YET.
WATCH THIS.
[quirky upbeat music]
OKAY, THANK YOU,
GENTLEMEN!
THANK YOU
VERY MUCH!
THAT'S --
IT'S SCARY, REALLY.
BACK TO THE BUFFET.
[applause]
COME ON, UNCLE RED.
YOU GOTTA BE ELVIS.
OH, NO, I'M SORRY, HAROLD.
I CAN'T HELP YOU OUT THERE.
I'D LIKE TO,
BUT I JUST CAN'T --
WHAT?
$100!
I DON'T CARE IF
YOU WIN OR LOSE.
PLEASE, JUST BE
IN THE CONTEST.
WELL, HAROLD,
I'M A HUNK-A, HUNK-A
BURNIN' LOVE.
[cheering and applause]
Red: WE HAD THE
POSSUM LAKE CAR RALLY.
WE ENTERED AGAIN, AND I HAD
MY PIT CREW WAITING THERE.
AND I HAD ONE LAST
PIT STOP BEFORE --
AND THEY WERE --
NOT AS SHARP AS REALLY
YOU WANT IN A PIT CREW.
I GUESS YOU GET
WHAT YOU PAY FOR.
SO THEY GOTTA ROTATE
ALL FOUR WHEELS THERE.
PUT BRAND NEW TIRES ON IT.
AND MIKE'S JOB WAS TO
CLEAN OFF THE WINDSHIELD.
AND HE WAS ALSO GONNA GET ME
SOME KIND OF A DRINK
AND THEN FUEL HER UP.
UNFORTUNATELY, WHILE MIKE WAS
CLEANING THE WINDSHIELD,
HE DIDN'T NOTICE THAT DALTON
HAD JACKED UP THE WHOLE
FRONT END THERE,
AND -- OH, BOY.
BUT THEY GOT THE THING UP.
YOU KNOW WHEN A FLATBED GETS
AHEAD OF YOU IN A RACE,
YOU KNOW IT'S
NOT GOING WELL.
SO WINSTON HAS
THE POWER WRENCH THERE.
HE JUST GOT THAT OFF
LIKE NOTHING.
HE'S GOT THE NEW TIRE THERE.
HE GOT THE OLD ONE OFF
AND PUT THE NEW ONE ON.
OKAY, THAT'S ONE DONE.
SO WE'RE GETTING THERE.
WE'RE GETTING THERE.
WE'RE UP TO MAYBE
EIGHT SECONDS IN.
AND THEN DALTON GETS THE
BAD TIRE OFF THE FRONT.
AND HE GOES TO GET
THE NEW TIRE TO PUT ON.
NO, THAT'S THE OLD ONE.
UH --
AND THEN MIKE BRINGS ME
SOMETHING TO DRINK,
WHICH IS GREAT.
AND THEN HE GOES AROUND
THE BACK TO GAS HER UP
WITH THE OTHER BOTTLE.
THEN HE NOTICES HE
MADE A LITTLE MISTAKE.
THANK YOU, MIKE.
YEAH, YEAH.
THERE'S PLENTY THERE.
SO DALTON'S NOW DONE.
A GUY ON A BIKE
HAS NOW BEATEN US.
OKAY, WE'RE ALL
SET TO GO.
I GOTTA GO HERE.
GET THAT JACK DOWN
THERE, WINSTON.
GET HER DOWN.
I GOT NO MORE TIME.
OKAY, THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
I'M GOING.
IT'S NOT THAT FAR
TO THE FINISH LINE.
THERE WE GO.
NO PROBLEM.
NO HARM DONE.
AND DEAD LAST AGAIN.
[applause]
IT'S TIME FOR THE EXPERTS'
PORTION OF THE SHOW,
WHERE WE ADDRESS
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
THOSE ARE THE
THREE WORDS.
OKAY.
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"RECENTLY I READ IN
THE PAPER ABOUT SOME GUY
"WHO HAS 12 WIVES.
"HOW DOES THAT WORK?
"SIGNED, JUST THE ONE."
I DON'T KNOW HOW IT WORKS,
BUT I'D LIKE TO FIND OUT.
GEEZ, 12 WIVES.
HATE TO SEE THAT
GUY'S TO DO LIST.
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
THIS GUY AND HIS WIVES,
THEY PROBABLY BELONG TO ONE
OF THOSE RELIGIOUS SECTS,
YOU KNOW, WHERE THEY ALLOW
MULTIPLE MARRIAGES.
WELL, WHICH ONE'S THAT?
OH, GOSH, THERE'S
LOTS OF SECTS.
NO KIDDING!
NO, THIS IS
S-E-C-T.
OH, YEAH.
OH.
SO YOU GUYS,
IF YOU HAD THE CHANCE,
WOULD YOU HAVE
MORE THAN ONE WIFE?
WELL, I WOULDN'T
MIND A FEW MORE.
ANN-MARGRET,
RAQUEL WELCH FOR STARTERS.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'D
NEED THE STARTER, DALTON.
AND THAT GIRL ON
THAT "FRIENDS" SHOW.
OH, WHICH ONE?
IT'S THE SHOW ABOUT
THAT GROUP OF FRIENDS.
NO, WHICH GIRL?
ONE OF THE BLONDE ONES.
THE PRETTY ONE.
HOW CAN YOU MARRY SOMEONE
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW HER NAME?
I'D GO THROUGH HER AGENT.
WHAT ABOUT
YOU, RED?
WOULD YOU, UH, LIKE A
BUNCH OF DIFFERENT WIVES?
AH, NO, WHEN
IT COMES TO WOMEN,
I'M MORE QUALITY
THAN QUANTITY,
ESPECIALLY SINCE
THE SURGERY.
YOU KNOW,
YOU COULD BE RIGHT,
BUT I'D DIE TO HAVE A BUNCH
OF WOMEN LOOKING AFTER ME.
FAT CHANCE, HUH?
AH, NO, IF ANN MARIE
IS WATCHING,
YOU'VE GOT A PRETTY GOOD
CHANCE AT THE DYING PART.
[applause]
WELL, HAROLD'S BIG
ELVIS-OFF IS TONIGHT,
AND I THINK THE KING'S GOING
TO BE ROLLING OVER
IN HIS GRAVE.
YOU KNOW, THESE CONTESTANTS
THEY UNDERESTIMATE HOW
MUCH TALENT YOU NEED
TO BE ELVIS PRESLEY.
YOU KNOW, BEING 100 POUNDS
OVERWEIGHT AND SHOOTING
YOUR TV SET
IS NOT ENOUGH.
UNCLE RED --
[cheering and applause]
[wolf whistles]
SO IT'S COME TO THIS,
HAS IT, HAROLD?
WELL, EVERYONE ELSE
BACKED OUT.
MY JOB'S ON THE LINE HERE.
WELL, YOU KNOW, YOU MAKE
A PRETTY GOOD ELVIS.
YEAH, YOU REALLY
THINK SO?
YEAH, YOU KNOW, IF HE WAS
A LITTLE MORE EFFEMINATE
AND A GEEK.
OKAY, I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO BE ELVIS PRESLEY.
OKAY, WELL, YOU JUST
GOTTA BE KING, HAROLD.
YOU GOTTA THINK, ACT AND
FEEL LIKE YOU'RE THE KING.
YEAH.
AH.
AND YOU GOTTA GET
THE LIP GOIN',
THE BADBOY SNEER.
NO. NO. NO.
THERE!
THAT'S IT!
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
WELL, HE MUST'VE
SMILED SOMETIMES.
YEAH, ELVIS HAD A
GREAT SENSE OF HUMOUR.
HE WOULD SMILE AND
LAUGH A LOT, YEAH.
[ SINGING IN
HIGH-PITCHED VOICE ]
NO, NO, I'M WRONG.
HE DIDN'T LAUGH.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
SPREAD YOUR LEGS
OUT WIDER.
THAT'S IT.
OKAY, NOW YOU GOTTA
MOVE YOUR HIPS AROUND.
OKAY, DO IT LIKE YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR A WOMAN
NOT A BATHROOM.
OH, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, YEAH!
THAT'S IT!
YOU GOT IT!
THAT'S IT.
[cheering and applause]
I THINK SO.
YOU GOOD?
OKAY, GO, GO, GO.
I'M OUTTA HERE.
[possum squealing]
ALL RIGHT, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'M GONNA GO TO THE MEETING.
GOOD LUCK,
HAROLD, EH.
as Elvis:
THANKS, UNCLE RED.
I'M JUST GONNA GO
ROCK'N'ROLL, MAN.
[applause]
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
HAROLD IS DOING AN ELVIS
THING HERE TONIGHT.
I HOPE HE SINGS
"TREAT ME LIKE A FOOL."
HE'S BEEN REHEARSING
FOR IT HIS WHOLE LIFE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND THE KING
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
UNCLE RED! UNCLE RED!
I WON!
I WON THE CONTEST.
I WON THE ELVIS CONTEST.
ALL RIGHT, WAY TO GO, HAROLD.
[applause]
HE WAS THE ONLY
CONTESTANT.
YOU JUST WAIT
TILL NEXT YEAR.
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF HAROLD CAN WIN AN ELVIS
IMPERSONATOR CONTEST,
IT'S TIME TO MOVE ON.
MAYBE NEXT YEAR WE'LL HAVE A
HAROLD IMPERSONATOR CONTEST.
[imitating Harold]