IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW!"
AND NOW HERE HE IS,
A MAN WHO WALKS SOFTLY
BUT CARRIES A BIG CRAMP,
YOUR HOST AND HERO,
MY UNCLE,
RED GR-E-E-E-N!
[applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
IT'S KIND OF A ROUGH WEEK
ON THE PERSONAL SIDE
THERE THIS WEEK.
BERNICE AND I, WE HAVE SOME
FRIENDS THAT HAVE RETIRED
AND MOVED TO FLORIDA,
AND BERNICE IS THINKING
THAT MAYBE WE SHOULD
DO THE SAME THING.
THAT'S A BIT OF
A CHALLENGE, UNCLE RED.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO RETIRE FROM?
THE THANKLESS JOB OF
NOT HURTING YOU, HAROLD.
HOW COME YOU DON'T
WANT TO GO TO FLORIDA?
YOU'D BE DOWN THERE AMONGST
THE WARMTH AND ALL THE OTHER
OLD PEOPLE AND STUFF.
OTHER OLD PEOPLE?
DID I SAY
OLD PEOPLE?
YES.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I MEANT?
WHAT?
I MEANT
"OLDER" PEOPLE
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, I MEAN,
YOU ARE OLDER THAN SOME THINGS;
YOU KNOW, LIKE,
TREES AND --
NO, I DON'T WANT
TO GO DOWN THERE.
I DON'T WANT TO
GO DOWN SOUTH.
IT'S LIKE AN ELEPHANT
BURIAL GROUND DOWN THERE.
IT'S A GATHERING OF PEOPLE
WITH GREAT BIG EARS
AND WRINKLED SKIN,
KIND OF LUMBERING AROUND
THE PARKS, YOU KNOW.
AT LEAST WITH ELEPHANTS
THEY DON'T FORGET EVERYTHING.
AND THEY DON'T CARRY
GOLF CLUBS IN THEIR TRUNKS.
TRUNKS RIGHT?
[imitating elephant]
ELEPHANTS, RIGHT,
BECAUSE THEY HAVE TRUNKS.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD
HAPPEN IF YOU DID GO?
YOU KNOW, YOU MIGHT MAKE
ALL SORTS OF NEW FRIENDS.
OKAY, WELL AUNT BERNICE
MIGHT MAKE FRIENDS.
NO, NO, I DON'T
WANT TO GO.
IN FACT, WHENEVER THERE'S
AN ARTICLE IN THE PAPER
OF A PLANE CRASH,
I CUT IT OUT AND
SHOW IT TO BERNICE,
SO SHE WON'T WANT TO FLY
ANYWHERE, YOU KNOW.
ALL I'VE GOT TO DO IS CONVINCE
HER THAT POSSUM LAKE IS A GREAT
PLACE TO BE IN THE WINTER.
HOW?
WELL, YOU KNOW, IF YOU
WOULD MOVE TO FLORIDA,
THAT WOULD HELP ME.
[applause]
[ QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING ]
Red Green:
HERE'S A FEW SCENES
FROM THIS WEEK'S SHOW.
I'M NOT GOING TO RUIN
THAT BY DESCRIBING IT.
BILL IS GOING TO
TRY THE LUGE THING.
THERE'S A TREE
COMING UP, BILL.
THIS MAY FEEL GOOD.
IT'S GOING TO GET VERY,
VERY COLD UP AT THE LODGE.
OH, MY GOSH.
OKAY, I GOT IT.
I GOT IT.
BERNICE IS GOING TO FORGET
ALL ABOUT MOVING SOUTH.
I GOT A WAY TO MAKE HER WANT TO
STAY AT POSSUM LAKE ALL WINTER.
DID YOU GET
HER A BOYFRIEND?
[laughter]
PRETTY GOOD.
PRETTY NERVY COMING FROM SOMEONE
WHO OBVIOUSLY HAS EXTRA TEETH.
[laughter]
JUST A JOKE.
C'MON, CAN'T YOU
TAKE A JOKE?
IT'S A JOKE.
HAROLD, I WORK
WITH A JOKE.
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE.
THAT WAS GOOD.
YOU WORK.
[laughter and applause]
LIKE I SAY,
I'VE GOT THIS PLAN.
IT'S GOING TO MAKE
BERNICE FORGET ALL
ABOUT GOING DOWN THERE.
SHE'S GOING TO WANT TO BE UP
HERE ALL WINTER LONG.
HAROLD, WHAT DO WINTER
COMMUNITIES DO WHEN THEY
WANT TO ATTRACT TOURISTS?
PUT IN ELECTRICITY?
NO.
THEY GET CABLE TV!
OH, I KNOW
WHAT THEY DO.
THEY INSTALL CO-ED
BATHING SUIT OPTIONAL
HOT TUBS.
NO, NO, NO.
THEY HAVE A
WINTER CARNIVAL.
A WINTER CARNIVAL?
NO, UNCLE RED, YOU'VE GOTTA
HAVE SOME SORT OF NATURAL
ATTRACTION FOR A
WINTER CARNIVAL,
LIKE A BEAUTIFUL MOUNTAIN
OR A GLACIER
OR MAYBE A SKI RESORT THAT HAS
CO-ED BATHING SUIT OPTIONAL.
HOT TUBS!
OH, YOUR HANDS ARE
CONNECTED TO YOUR ARMS
YOUR ARMS ARE CONNECTED
TO YOUR SHOULDERS
YOUR SHOULDERS ARE
CONNECTED TO YOUR BODY
AND YOUR BODY IS
CONNECTED TO YOUR HEAD
WELL, YOUR HEAD
IS CONNECTED TO...
NOTHING
WHICH EXPLAINS A LOT
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
AND HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
A BRAND NEW BASS BOAT
WITH A 150-HORSEPOWER OUTBOARD
MOTOR AND MATCHING TRAILER?
EVERYBODY WOULD LOVE THAT
BECAUSE YOU WOULD LOOK SO COOL
WHEN YOU GO FISHING WITH OUR
NEW GRAND PRIZE OF TONIGHT,
A BAIT BUCKET!
AND TONIGHT'S CONTESTANT IS
Mr. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET Mr. ROTHSCHILD TO
SAY THIS WORD...
DEAD.
OKAY, GO.
OKAY, WINSTON, YOUR BODY HAS
ITS LIFE SUCKED OUT OF IT.
YOU ARE...
STANDING TOO CLOSE
TO THE SEWAGE PUMP.
NO. NO. NO.
YOU'RE SIX FEET UNDER.
YOU'RE...
RUNNING OUT OF HOSE.
WHEN ANIMALS BECOME
ROADKILL, THEY ARE...
BIGGER,
BUT THINNER.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I KNOW, THERE'S
AN EXPRESSION,
"HE'S AS SOMETHING
AS A DOORNAIL?"
SHORT?
NO.
FLAT HEADED?
POINTY AT ONE END?
RUNNING OUT
OF TIME, UNCLE RED.
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON, IF ALL
OF US GO ON TOWN SEWERS...?
OH, GEEZ, I'D BE DEAD.
[frantic bell ringing]
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU LIVE
IN THE COLDER CLIMATES
THERE ARE SOME VEHICLES
THAT ATTRACT A CERTAIN
AMOUNT OF ATTENTION.
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE GOT THE
SNOWPLOW AND THE 4x4,
THE SNOWMOBILE, YOU KNOW,
THAT KIND OF THING.
BUT IF YOU WANT TO REALLY
GRAB ATTENTION,
GET YOURSELF A ZAMBONI.
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO
LIVE DOWN SOUTH,
A ZAMBONI IS NOT
A PASTA DISH.
IT'S  A --
WELL, IT'S A BIG THING,
BIG THING LIKE THAT,
AND IT'S --
YOU KNOW WHAT, IT'S THE
THING THEY USE TO MAKE
ICE ON THE RINKS.
YOU'LL SEE.
YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE PRETTY
DEEP POCKETS TO BUY A ZAMBONI.
SO TODAY ON HANDYMAN'S CORNER,
WE'RE GOING TO BUILD OUR OWN,
USING, ONCE AGAIN, OUR
VEHICLE OF CHOICE, THE K-CAR.
NOW, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO USE A K-CAR.
I SUPPOSE YOU CAN
BUILD AN "OLDSMABONI."
BUT WE LIKE THE K-CAR
BECAUSE OF THE COMBINATION
OF AVAILABILITY, COST,
AND THE SENSE OF REVENGE.
LET'S GET STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, I TOOK THE
WINDSHIELD OUT OF THIS FOR
A COUPLE OF REASONS.
FIRST OF ALL, THE FUN;
AND, SECONDLY, I NEEDED TO HOOK
UP MY ZAMBONI STEERING WHEEL
DOWN TO THE ACTUAL CAR
STEERING WHEEL.
I PUT A PULLEY IN HERE AND A
PIECE OF ROPE, AND HERE'S
HOW THE DEAL WORKS.
WHEN I TURN THE ZAMBONI WHEEL
TO THE RIGHT, IT TURNS THE CAR
STEERING WHEEL TO THE LEFT,
BUT WE'RE GOING BACKWARDS,
SO WE END UP GOING TO THE RIGHT.
SO IT ALL WORKS OUT.
PLUS WE'LL BE DRIVING ON ICE,
SO HOW DANGEROUS CAN THAT BE?
AND HERE'S THE THIRD THING.
BECAUSE OF WHERE I'VE GOT
THE PEDALS MOUNTED ON THERE,
WHEN I STEP ON
THE GAS OR THE BRAKE,
I'VE GOT MY FEET OVER
THE DEFROSTER VENT THERE.
AND I TELL YOU,
IN THE DEAD OF WINTER,
NOTHING BRINGS A SMILE TO YOUR
FACE LIKE A DRAFT WHIPPING
THROUGH YOUR PANTS.
NOW, A LOT OF YOU WILL SAY,
"HEY, YOU KNOW, RIGHT THERE,
THAT'S ENOUGH FUN FOR ME."
WE ARE NOT DONE YET.
OH, NO, SIR.
BECAUSE THE REAL ZAMBONI IS
A FULLY FUNCTIONAL ICE
MAINTENANCE MACHINE.
THAT'S WHERE WE'RE HEADING.
YEAH, THE REAL ZAMBONI, THEY'VE
GOT THE HOT WATER TANKS THERE,
AND THE HOT WATER GOES ON
THE ICE AND MELTS IT
AND SMOOTHS IT OVER.
WELL, WE DON'T HAVE
THE HOT WATER TANKS,
BUT THE BEAUTY OF A K-CAR,
IT'S NOT ALL THAT HARD TO GET
SOME KIND OF HOT FLUID
LEAKING SOMEWHERE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, I JUST NEED
SOMETHING I CAN DRAG BEHIND
THE UNIT TO SCRAPE THE ICE
AND KIND OF SMOOTH
OUT THE WATER.
OH, THIS WILL WORK.
ALL RIGHT, I'VE GOT THE CAR
BUMPER TO KNOCK THE BIG
CHUNKS OFF THE ICE,
AND I'VE GOT CAR FLOOR MATS
TO KIND OF SMOOTH THEM OUT.
ONE MORE STEP
THEN WE'RE ALL DONE.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE GOING
TO BE DRIVING THIS UNIT
AROUND THE ARENA,
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
TURNING A FEW HEADS.
WHY NOT PUT IT
TO GOOD USE?
EVERY ZAMBONI HAS
ADVERTISING ON THE SIDE.
WHY SHOULD YOURS
BE ANY DIFFERENT?
SURE HOPE HE
APPRECIATES THAT.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GIVE HER A GO.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY...
THE PROOF OF THE PUDDING
IS IN THE ZAMBONI.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
YOU CAN ALMOST HEAR THE
ORGAN MUSIC, CAN'T YOU?
OH, BOY.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW,
THE PART OF THE SHOW WHERE WE
EXAMINE THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND OH,
SO HARD TO SAY...
Audience:
I DON'T KNOW.
HA HA HA.
JOINING ME AND UNCLE RED ON THIS
PORTION OF THE SHOW IS HIS
GOOD FRIEND, RANGER GORD.
[applause]
OKAY, THE LETTER
READS AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"I HAVE JUST BEEN
BITTEN BY A SNAKE.
"I'M NOT SURE IF
IT IS A POISONOUS ONE,
"AND I'M HOPING THAT
YOU EXPERTS COULD TELL ME.
"THE SNAKE HAS LONG YELLOW
STRIPES AND IS SHARP
AT ONE END.
"PLEASE HURRY
AS I AM IN --"
IS THAT IT?
WELL, THERE'S MORE,
BUT IT GETS ALL SCRIBBLY.
RED AND HAROLD,
THERE'S NO USE
ANSWERING THAT LETTER.
THE VENOM FROM THAT PARTICULAR
BREED OF SNAKE CAN DROP EVEN
A FULL-GROWN BIRCH.
THE PERSON THAT WROTE IT
PROBABLY USED UP THEIR
LAST OUNCE OF STRENGTH
LICKING THE STAMP.
JUST LIKE A BIRCH,
AS IN TREE?
OH, YEAH,
ABSOLUTELY.
YOU KNOW, SNAKES AND TREES
AREN'T NATURAL ENEMIES.
THEY DON'T NORMALLY FIGHT,
BUT IF THE TREE WERE
TO ATTACK FIRST,
THE SNAKE WILL BITE BACK
AND KILL THE TREE.
EVEN IF THE TREE
STANDS PERFECTLY STILL?
ABSOLUTELY.
ABSOLUTELY, RED.
I'VE SEEN A LOT OF STRANGE
THINGS DURING MY 18 YEARS
UP AT FIRE WATCH TOWER 13.
BUT WHEN YOU FIRST SEE A
TREE AND A SNAKE BATTLE
TO THE DEATH,
YOU THINK YOU'RE
SEEING THINGS.
YOU KNOW, YOU THINK
IT'S A TRICK OF LIGHT,
OR MAYBE ONE OF THOSE STRANGE
MUSHROOMS YOU JUST ATE.
BUT WHEN IT
HAPPENS EVERY DAY,
DAY AFTER DAY --
OR IF A TREE WERE
TO COME AFTER YOU,
YOU BETTER BELIEVE
IT'S REAL, BUDDY.
I JUST WISH I HAD A CAMERA
WHEN IT WAS HAPPENING,
OR EVEN A PENCIL.
OR A GIRLFRIEND.
YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY,
RANGER GORD,
BY THE DESCRIPTION
OF THIS SNAKE,
IT JUST SOUNDS LIKE A
TYPICAL GARTER SNAKE.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
IT'S PROBABLY
JUST A JOKE, YOU KNOW.
AND WHAT ABOUT
THE BIRCH, HAROLD?
WHAT ABOUT THE BIRCH?!
YEAH, HAROLD.
RED, HAROLD, EVERYONE,
THIS IS AN EXCELLENT LESSON.
THINK OF A SNAKE
AS A ROPE,
A ROPE WITHOUT LEGS AND NOT
AVAILABLE IN HARDWARE STORES.
A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE DIED
AT THE END OF A ROPE;
AT THE END OF A SNAKE.
THINK ABOUT IT.
I DID.
FOR FIVE MONTHS ONE WINTER.
OH, YEAH.
REMEMBER, FOLKS, SNAKES
ARE JUST AS AFRAID OF YOU
AS WE ARE OF RANGER GORD.
[cheers and applause]
OKAY, THE WINTER CARNIVAL
IS COMING ALONG REAL GOOD.
BOY, SHE'S A LITTLE
NIPPY OUT THERE, HAROLD.
YEAH, YEAH.
I WAS LISTENING TO MY
WEATHER RADIO LAST NIGHT.
I WAS GOING TO WATCH
"X-FILES", BUT IT WAS A RERUN.
YOU KNOW, IT'S THAT
SLIME SEWER GUY ONE.
I SAW IT BEFORE,
SO I DIDN'T WATCH IT, RIGHT,
AND I FINISHED ALL MY HOMEWORK
BECAUSE I SAT OUT OF GYM CLASS.
I EVEN HAD TIME TO FINISH
ALL THE BULLIES' HOMEWORK.
AND I WAS SITTING THERE,
AND I WAS LISTENING TO
THE WEATHER RADIO,
AND THEY SAID THAT THERE'S
A LOW PRESSURE ZONE OVER
UPPER STATE NEW YORK,
AND IT'S CAUSING, LIKE, THIS
INVERTED THERMAL AIR FLOW,
AND IT'S DRAWING ALL THE WARM
AIR FROM THE SOUTH
AND IT'S PUSHING OUT
OVER THE ATLANTIC OCEAN,
WHICH IS DRAWING DOWN THE
FRIGID AIR FROM THE ARCTIC,
AND THAT'S RIGHT
INTO OUR REGION.
THAT'S COMING
IN OUR REGION.
THAT'S WHY YOU FEEL
SO NIPPY AS YOU DO RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, I KIND OF
WISH YOU'D GONE TO GYM CLASS.
WE'D HAVE BETTER WEATHER,
AND IT WOULD BE YOUR THERMALS
THAT WERE INVERTED.
ANYWAY, WE'RE ALL SET FOR
THE CARNIVAL THERE.
WE'VE GOT THE REFRESHMENT BOOTH,
THE EVENTS ARE ALL SET UP.
I THINK IT'S GOING
TO BE A REAL HOOT.
WHAT KIND OF EVENTS
DO YOU HAVE?
BECAUSE EVENTS MAKE OR BREAK
THESE KIND OF THINGS, YOU KNOW?
'CAUSE REMEMBER LAST
SUMMER'S FAIR?
STINKY PETERSON SET UP THAT
RUNNING SHOE TRADE-IN BOOTH OUT
THERE IN THE HOT SUMMER SUN.
COMPLETELY DESTROYED
FOOD SALES.
NO, NO, WE'VE
GOT GREAT STUFF.
WE'VE GOT SNOWMOBILE RACES,
WE'VE GOT 4x4 RACES,
WE'VE GOT SNOWPLOW RACES,
WE'VE GOT ZAMBONI RACES.
NO, NONE OF THAT STUFF.
AUNT BERNICE
WON'T LIKE THAT.
IT'S TOO LOUD.
YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE NICE,
PEACEFUL SPORTING EVENTS;
LIKE, CROSS-COUNTRY SKIING.
OH, YEAH, NO, I FORGOT
TO MENTION THAT.
WHEN WE DO THE
SNOWMOBILE SLALOM,
WE'RE GOING TO USE
CROSS-COUNTRY SKIERS AS PYLONS.
YEAH, LIKE THAT.
THAT'S WHAT I MEANT, YEAH.
YOU'VE GOTTA HAVE
STUFF FOR KIDS TOO.
KIDS ARE GOING TO BE THERE.
KIDS LIKE STUFF.
THEY LIKE TOBOGGANING
AND HOT CHOCOLATE
AND MAKING SNOWMEN
AND ICE SCULPTURES.
ICE SCULPTURE!
I COULD MAKE
AN ICE SCULPTURE.
LET ME MAKE AN ICE SCULPTURE
FOR AUNT BERNICE.
I COULD DO THAT
FOR THE WINTER CARNIVAL.
ALL RIGHT, BUT NOTHING WUSSY
OR IN POOR TASTE.
I DON'T WANT LIKE A 12-FOOT HIGH
NAKED LADY OR SOMETHING.
NO --
GOOD, 'CAUSE YOU'D
PROBABLY MELT IT.
Red Green:
SUPPOSED TO DO A LITTLE
TOBOGGANING WITH BILL.
WHERE'S YOUR TOBOGGAN, BILL?
WHERE'S YOUR TOBOGGAN?
YOU NEED --
I'VE GOT A BIG TOBOGGAN.
OH, FOR GOSH SAKE.
IT'S A LITTLE --
A LUGE.
KIND OF LUGE.
A LITTLE LUGE SLED,
A LITTLE LUGE.
OKAY, BILL,
GET ON IT.
GET ON IT, BILL.
ISN'T THERE A JUMP AT THAT END?
A JUMP THERE SOMEWHERE?
YEAH, YEAH, THERE'S
A JUMP THERE, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S
TRY IT AGAIN.
"RE-LUGE" I GUESS
YOU CALL THIS.
IT'S THE RE-LUGE MAN.
ALL RIGHT, GET ON THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
AND AWAY WE GO.
AWAY WE GO.
THERE YOU GO.
NOW YOU'RE MOVING.
OH, THERE'S A TREE.
THERE'S A TREE, BILL.
YEAH, THAT'S THE ONE.
OH, GOING BACKWARDS.
ISN'T THAT JUMP THERE STILL?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
LUCKY THE MIRROR
WASN'T THERE, EH, BILL?
WATCH FOR THE VAN THERE.
WATCH FOR THE VAN.
YEAH, YOU GOT IT.
SO HE'S GOT A
GREAT IDEA HERE.
HE'S GOT HER DOWN
IN THE DITCH.
IT'S KIND OF BEVELLED OUT THERE,
SO HE WON'T GET OFF TRACK.
HE'S A LOT SAFER.
A LOT SAFER.
I'LL GET HIM GOING,
SO HE WON'T COME BACK.
LOOKING GOOD.
BASKETS!
UH-OH, DRAINPIPE!
SEWER DRAIN!
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH!
GOLLY, BILL LOOKS GOOD
WITH A PIPE.
HOW ARE YOU, BILL?
HE'S A LITTLE DRAINED.
IS IT EVER
COLD OUT THERE!
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK
IT'S GOING TO RUIN THE
WINTER CARNIVAL.
PEOPLE, WHEN THEY'RE HAVING FUN,
THEY DON'T NOTICE THE COLD.
EVEN LIKE AT AN N.F.L.
GAME OUT AT GREEN BAY,
OR WHAT HAVE YOU THERE,
THE PEOPLE ARE --
THEY'RE FREEZING,
BUT THEY'RE FINE.
HALF OF THEM HAVE
THEIR SHIRTS OFF.
MIND YOU, ALCOHOL
DOESN'T FREEZE.
I THINK PEOPLE AROUND HERE WILL
GET THE SPIRIT AND HAVE FUN.
AND I THINK BERNICE IS ACTUALLY
GOING TO THANK ME
FOR NOT FIRING HER DOWN TO
FLORIDA BECAUSE SHE'D HAVE
TO MISS ALL THE GOOD TIMES HERE.
OH, THANK GOODNESS!
I THOUGHT I WAS
OUTSIDE STILL.
BOY, THAT'S QUITE A SCARF
YOU'VE GOT THERE, HAROLD.
I WAS WAITING FOR A GIRL
TO RETURN MY CALL.
[laughter and applause]
I'M ACTUALLY SURPRISED
IT'S THAT SHORT.
I'VE GOT FOUR OF THEM.
YOU KNOW, I WAS LOOKING
AT YOUR ICE SCULPTURE.
WHAT EXACTLY IS THAT?
WHAT DO YOU
THINK IT IS?
A WASTE OF ICE.
I DUNNO, IT COULD BE
A GOOSE, A BEAR.
I'D SAY A MALE BEAR,
JUDGING BY THAT ONE ICICLE.
NO, NO, IT'S NOT AN
ANIMAL AT ALL.
IT'S SOMETHING YOU SIT ON.
A HEMORRHOID?
IT'S A THRONE.
IT'S THE ICE THRONE OF THE
POSSUM LAKE WINTER CARNIVAL
WHERE THE SNOW QUEEN
WILL SIT AND RULE OVER
HER LOYAL SUBJECTS.
WELL, WHATEVER IT IS, HAROLD,
IT BETTER BE DONE BY TONIGHT
BECAUSE THE WINTER CARNIVAL
STARTS FIRST THING TOMORROW
MORNING AT 9:00 A.M.
BERNICE IS COMING UP
WITH HER GIRLFRIENDS,
AND I WANT EVERYTHING
TO BE PERFECT.
OH, BOY, THAT'S
A TALL ORDER.
WELL, HAROLD, WHEN YOU'VE
BEEN MARRIED AS LONG AS
BERNICE AND I HAVE,
THE CONCEPT OF PERFECT
SLIDES A LITTLE.
OH, PERFECT.
RIGHT, YEAH.
[applause]
THIS IS THE REPAIR PART
OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
"IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
TODAY WE HAVE GOT JOINING
US Mr. MIKE HAMAR.
WHAT BRINGS YOU TO THE
REPAIR SHOP TODAY, MIKE?
ACTUALLY IT'S A
CONDITION OF MY PAROLE.
THE JAIL WAS FULL.
OH, DID YOU BRING
SOMETHING FOR US TO FIX?
MY STETHOSCOPE, Mr. GREEN.
IT'S BROKEN.
HOW DID YOU
BREAK THIS, MIKE?
I DROPPED IT WHEN
I WAS RUNNING AWAY.
I MEAN, WHEN I WAS RUNNING
AROUND THE BLOCK.
I LIKE TO CHECK MY HEARTBEAT
WHEN I'M JOGGING AWAY
FROM THINGS.
I THINK IT'S THE PART THAT
YOU DON'T PUT IN YOUR EAR
THAT'S BROKEN.
THE FLAT PART
THERE IS CRACKED.
OH, YEAH, THE SURFACE
HAS GOT --
YOU GOT ANY LABORATORY-GRADE
MEDICAL LATEX SHEATHING?
I'VE GOT A THING
IN MY WALLET.
I THINK WE'RE GOING TO GO WITH
THE DUCT TAPE ON THAT, MIKE.
IF I CAN PULL THAT TIGHT
ENOUGH ON THERE IT WILL
PICK UP THE VIBRATIONS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH
A STETHOSCOPE, MIKE?
WELL, OH, I THOUGHT I'D LIKE TO
IMPROVE MY LIFE AND GET A JOB.
I THOUGHT MAYBE
I COULD BE A DOCTOR,
LIKE, A NEUROLOGIST
OR SOMETHING, YOU KNOW.
SO I THOUGHT I'D GET A
STETHOSCOPE AND SOME
TONGUE DEPRESSORS
AND MAYBE SOME
PRESCRIPTIONS,
AND SEE HOW I LIKED IT.
I'VE BEEN DOING
SOME READING,
AND I KNOW ALL ABOUT
THE CIRCULAR SYSTEM.
AND HOW THE HEART PUMPS BLOOD
DOWN THROUGH YOUR TINY LITTLE
ARTILLERIES AND --
OH, BONES,
AND OF COURSE, MUSCLES.
DID YOU KNOW YOU'VE GOT MORE
THAN 3,000 BONES IN YOUR HAND?
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
ACTUALLY, I'M MORE
CONCENTRATING ON THE BRAIN.
I'M NOT ALL THAT UP
ON HAND BONES.
MIKE, DID YOU KNOW THAT
A STETHOSCOPE CAN BE USED
TO CRACK THE COMBINATION
OF A SAFE?
REALLY?
WELL, BOY, OH, BOY,
Mr. GREEN,
THAT SURE IS
GOOD TO KNOW.
BUT FOR ME, REALLY, I USE --
I LIKE TO USE THE STETHOSCOPE
TO LISTEN TO THE INSIDE
OF A PERSON.
YEAH, YOU KNOW, HONESTY IS
A BIG PART OF LIFE, MIKE,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE GOING
TO BE A NEUROLOGIST.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S
A GOOD POINT, Mr. GREEN.
ACTUALLY, I MOSTLY USE MY
STETHOSCOPE TO LISTEN
TO MY OWN HEART.
DO YOU REALLY?
YEAH, SEE?
HOW DOES YOUR
HEART SOUND?
IT'S PERFECT.
YOUR HEART IS ON
THE OTHER SIDE, MIKE.
OH, YEAH.
[laughter and applause]
[cheers and applause]
I GOT TO TELL YOU, THAT'S
THE COLDEST EVENT I'VE BEEN AT
SINCE I TOLD BERNICE'S PARENTS
WE WERE GETTING MARRIED.
[laughter]
IT'S MINUS 60 DEGREES
WITH A WIND CHILL FACTOR
OF MINUS 73.
IS THAT CELSIUS
OR FAHRENHEIT?
WHO CARES?
THE WINTER CARNIVAL
WAS A DISASTER.
NONE OF THE SNOWMOBILES
WOULD START,
AND THE HOT CHOCOLATE
ALL FROZE OVER.
PEOPLE'S BREATH WAS SO THICK,
THEY HAD TO STOP TALKING BEFORE
YOU COULD SEE WHO IT WAS.
DID AUNT BERNICE
ENJOY HERSELF?
YEAH, I THINK SHE --
I WAS A LITTLE DISAPPOINTED
SHE DIDN'T GET OUT OF THE CAR.
BUT THEY SEEMED TO BE
HAVING FUN IN THERE.
THEY HAD THE RADIO ON,
AND THEY WERE
PLAYING GIN RUMMY.
THEY HAD THE THERMOS
OF GIN AND RUMMY.
[possum call]
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO
AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
YOU MIGHT THINK
ABOUT GETTING CABLE.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING, BERNICE.
AND I WAS HOPING
MAYBE TONIGHT,
WE'LL GET OUT ALL THOSE
BROCHURES OF THOSE RETIREMENT
PLACES DOWN SOUTH,
AND WE'LL HAVE THE
BIGGEST FIRE YOU EVER SAW.
I'M NOT DEAD HONEY,
I'M JUST COLD.
FOR THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
Harold:
EVERYBODY TAKE YOUR SEAT.
HERE HE COMES.
YOU CAN SMELL
WHEN HE'S CLOSE.
DON'T TELL HIM
I SAID THAT.
ALL RISE.
Everyone:
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red:
SIT DOWN.
Harold:
JUST GOT ONE QUICK
ANNOUNCEMENT...
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE THERE
WILL BE NO ICE FISHING
AT POSSUM LAKE.
DUE TO THE EXTREME COLD,
THE LAKE IS COMPLETELY FROZEN
SOLID FROM TOP TO BOTTOM.
SO DON'T BE TRYING
TO CARVE A HOLE IN THERE
BECAUSE YOU'LL BE WRECKING
ALL THE 4x4s AND SNOWMOBILES AND
APPLIANCES THAT ARE DOWN THERE.