YOU EVER NOTICE HOW MANY BOAT
TRAILERS ARE LEFT AT THE SIDE
OF THE ROAD BECAUSE THESE LITTLE
BABY WHEELS EITHER HAD A FLAT
OR FELL OFF?
I MEAN, THEY'RE LOUSY TIRES
TO BEGIN WITH, AND THEY'RE
SO SMALL THAT AT 100 KLICKS,
THEY'RE SPINNING FASTER THAN...
SOMETHING THAT SPINS
REALLY FAST.
[metal crashing]
AND ONLY A DOOFUS WOULD CARRY
AROUND A SPARE
FOR A TRAILER TIRE.
WHERE WOULD YOU STICK THE JACK
ON ONE OF THESE BABIES ANYWAY?
NO, SIR.
I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
I MOUNTED A FEW OF THESE
HIGH-SPEED FANS ON THE SIDE
OF THE TRAILER.
KIND OF TURNED IT INTO
A HOVERCRAFT.
ONCE THESE THINGS GET GOING,
THE UNIT DOESN'T EVEN TOUCH
THE GROUND.
HOW CAN YOU HAVE A FLAT TIRE
WHEN YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE A TIRE?
MAKES IT A LOT EASIER
FOR BACKING DOWN BOAT RAMPS TOO.
NOW, THE FANS ALL RUN OFF
THE JUICE FROM THE ALTERNATOR,
SO SOON AS I START THE ENGINE,
I'M IN BUSINESS.
[engine turns over]
[fans humming]
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, I APPRECIATE THAT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK.
POSSUM LAKE CITY COUNCIL
HAS FINALLY DECIDED TO START
PROMOTING THE AREA, AND THEY'RE
LOOKING TO HIRE SOMEONE
AS A FULL-TIME P.R. PERSON.
WELL, SOUNDS LIKE PRETTY EASY
MONEY TO ME.
I MEAN, THE POSSUM LAKE AREA
PRETTY MUCH SELLS ITSELF--
USUALLY SHORT.
AND THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
THAT I CAN TELL YOU.
THEY BUDGETED 50,000 BUCKS
A YEAR TO PAY WHOEVER GETS
THE JOB.
NOT EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT, BUT
I'M PRETTY TIGHT WITH THE MAYOR.
ACTUALLY, MOST OF THE TIME,
THE MAYOR'S PRETTY TIGHT
ALL ON HIS OWN,
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
HEY, RED, ARE YOU STILL
PLANNING ON APPLYING FOR THE NEW
PUBLIC RELATIONS JOB, HUH?
WELL, I'M THINKING ABOUT IT,
DALTON, YEAH.
60,000 BUCKS A YEAR.
[laughs]
OH, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
NO, IT'S 50,000.
WELL, THAT'S INCORRECT,
MR. GREEN.
YOU SEE, THE MAYOR IS PLANNING
ON KEEPING $10,000 FOR HIMSELF,
SO HE LEAKED THE WRONG NUMBER
TO A FEW IDIOTS.
SO IF YOU GO UP FOR THIS JOB,
MR. GREEN, YOU HAVE TO PROPOSE
SOMETHING FOR THE AREA
THAT YOU WILL PROMOTE.
OH, NO, YEAH, I KNOW.
I'M ALL OVER THAT.
YEAH. NO.
I'M SUGGESTING THAT THEY DECLARE
POSSUM LAKE THE MOSQUITO CAPITAL
OF THE WORLD.
EVERY SPRING, WE HAVE MOSQUITO
FESTIVAL, YOU KNOW?
MAKE IT A CHARITY THING.
RAISE MONEY FOR THE BLOOD BANK.
SO WE'RE ALL IN IT,
AND WE ALL GET SPONSORS.
YOU SIT IN THE BUSH
IN YOUR UNDERWEAR.
YOU GET A BUCK A BITE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW
WHAT I THINK.
WELL, WE ACTUALLY--
WE CAN'T BE OBJECTIVE,
MR. GREEN, 'CAUSE WE'RE BOTH
CANDIDATES FOR THAT JOB TOO.
WHAT?
YOU GUYS DON'T HAVE ANY IDEAS.
WE GOT NO IDEAS FOR FREE.
WE GOT PLENTY OF IDEAS
FOR MONEY.
YEAH, 60,000 OF THEM.
YEAH, AND APPARENTLY,
THE APPLICANTS
WILL BE PROCESSED IN THE ORDER
IN WHICH THEY ARE SUBMITTED,
SO IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME...
[alarm beeps]
JUST A MINUTE THERE, GUYS.
GUYS?
OUT OF THE WAY.
[alarm beeps]
IT'S A REMOTE LOCK.
[laughs]
[alarm beeps]
OH, COME ON!
[grumbles]
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
TODAY'S WINNER WILL RECEIVE
A FREE STYLE AND SET FROM POSSUM
LAKE'S ONLY HAIRDRESSING SALON
EXCLUSIVELY FOR SENIORS,
HAIRYATRICS.
OKAY, MR. GREEN--
COVER YOUR THINGS.
OKAY, MR. GREEN, YOU GOT 30
SECONDS TO GET WINSTON TO SAY
THIS WORD.
AMBITION!
AMBITION.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
OKAY, AND GO!
OKAY, WINSTON, IF YOU DIDN'T
HAVE THIS, YOU'D BE NOTHING.
A SEWAGE TRUCK.
NO.
OKAY, NO, THIS IS NOT
SOMETHING YOU OWN.
THIS IS A THING INSIDE YOU
THAT HAS MADE YOU SUCCESSFUL.
OH, A POOR SENSE OF SMELL.
OKAY, SAY YOU'RE WATCHING
TELEVISION, YOU SEE SOMEBODY
LIKE DONALD TRUMP,
AND YOU THINK, "BOY, HE MUST
HAVE A LOT OF..."
HAIRSPRAY.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU WERE
IN HIGH SCHOOL?
THE GUIDANCE COUNSELOR WOULD
SAY, "WHAT'S YOUR..."
EXCUSE.
THIS IS NOT THE DREAM.
YOU GOT HAVE A DREAM, AND YOU
GOT TO HAVE SOMETHING TO MAKE
THE DREAM COME TRUE.
HAPPY TALK!
HAPPY TALK
KEEP TALKING HAPPY
MIKE, MIKE.
I WAS IN SOUTH PACIFIC
IN PRISON.
I STILL GOT THE COCONUT BRA.
CAN WE PLEASE GET BACK
TO THE GAME?
OKAY, SORRY.
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
MR. GREEN.
GEE, I WONDER WHY THERE,
BOJANGLES.
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON, HOW COME
YOU'RE THE ONLY SEWAGE SUCKER
IN THE WHOLE TRI-COUNTY AREA?
'CAUSE NOBODY AROUND HERE
HAS ANY AMBITION!
THERE YOU GO!
[bell dinging]
I KNOW MY COMPETITORS
AND WHAT THEY'RE ABOUT.
THEY CHARGE TOO MUCH MONEY.
OF THAT, THERE'S NO DOUBT.
SO IF YOU WANT A FAIR PRICE,
GIVE ROTHSCHILD'S A SHOUT.
DON'T GET SUCKED IN
WHEN YOU GET PUMPED OUT.
LOT OF GOOD THINGS ABOUT
HAVING A DOG.
MAKE A GREAT COMPANION.
THEY'LL PROTECT YOU.
MAKE THE MAILMAN THINK TWICE
ABOUT DELIVERING THOSE BILLS.
PROBLEM IS, WHAT DO YOU DO
WHEN THE DOG GETS DIRTY?
NOBODY ENJOYS BATHING THEIR DOG.
YOU GET SOAKED.
YOU GET SCRATCHED.
THE DOG DOESN'T GET
ALL THAT CLEAN.
I SUPPOSE YOU COULD GET RIGHT
INSIDE THE BATHTUB WITH THE DOG,
BUT THAT'S HOW YOU
END UP ON THE FRONT PAGE
OF THE NATIONAL ENQUIRER.
NOW, I'M THINKING, WHY NOT TAKE
THE TECHNOLOGY OF AN AUTOMATIC
CAR WASH--
MAKE YOURSELF AN AUTOMATIC
DOG WASH?
ALL YOU NEED IS THE STANDARD
LAWN AND GARDEN STUFF THAT
EVERYBODY HAS AROUND THEIR HOUSE
AND OF COURSE A COUPLE
OF DOGHOUSES SO YOU GOT ROOM
TO MOUNT ALL THE GEAR.
NOW, I'M GONNA CUT THESE
DOGHOUSES IN HALF SO I CAN
GET INSIDE TO WORK ON THEM.
I SUPPOSE I COULD JUST CRAWL
RIGHT INSIDE THE DARN THINGS,
BUT AFTER 35 YEARS OF MARRIAGE,
I BEEN IN THERE ENOUGH.
I THOUGHT I'D SHOW YOU
HOW THE WHOLE THING WORKS
BEFORE I PUT THE TWO HALVES
BACK TOGETHER HERE.
OKAY, FIRST OF ALL,
I GOT MY GARDEN HOSE COMING IN.
GOES IN TO ONE OF THESE
T-CONNECTORS HERE.
NOW, ON THE FIRST LEG OF
THE T-CONNECTOR, I'M GOING OUT
INTO ONE OF THESE
OUTDOOR WINDOW WASHER BOTTLES.
YOU KNOW, THE KIND THAT HOOKS
ON TO YOUR HOSE?
COURSE, NOW, I DUMPED THE WINDOW
WASHER FLUID OUT OF THERE.
REPLACED THAT WITH DOG SHAMPOO.
THE DOG ACTUALLY TURNS THE SOAP
ON HIMSELF WITH THIS STRING
I GOT TIED TO THE TRIGGER
OF THE MACHINE, AND ON THE OTHER
END, I GOT A DOG BISCUIT
HANGING THERE.
AND I'LL TELL YOU, BY THE TIME
HE FINISHES CHEWING ON THAT
BABY, HE'LL HAVE WORKED HIMSELF
INTO A LATHER.
NOW, ON THE OTHER SIDE OF MY
T-CONNECTOR, THAT GOES DOWN INTO
THE LAWN SPRINKLER YOU SEE
THERE, AND THAT'LL RINSE
ALL THE SOAP OFF THE DOG PLUS
GIVE HIM A GREAT UNDER-WASH
FOR THOSE HARD-TO-GET-AT PLACES.
THEN HE JUST MOVES ON DOWN
THE LINE TILL HIS HEAD COMES UP
AGAINST THE BLADE OF THIS HOCKEY
STICK, AND THAT TURNS ON MY
LEAF BLOWER DOG DRYER.
[blower hums]
OKAY, LET'S JUST GET
THE PIECES BACK TOGETHER,
AND WE'RE IN BUSINESS.
OKAY, I GOT THE DOG WASH
BLOCKING THE ONLY EXIT
FROM THE YARD.
NOW I JUST NEED TO ENTICE
THE DOG TO COME OUT THROUGH IT.
ACTUALLY, THERE ARE ONLY TWO
THINGS THAT'LL MOTIVATE A DOG,
AND SINCE THIS ISN'T MATING
SEASON, I'M GOING WITH FOOD.
THAT'S ALL YOU NEED, THOUGH
TO MAKE YOUR OWN DOG WASH,
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
[squeaking and barking]
[blower hums]
[cheers and applause]
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
MIDDLE-AGED GUYS WITH GARAGES
OUT THERE.
YOU KNOW, MY WIFE SAYS OUR
GARAGE IS A MESS, BUT I DON'T
AGREE WITH HER.
SURE, I GOT SOME UNFINISHED
PROJECTS IN THERE.
PARKING METER WITH A DENT IN IT
THE SAME COLOR AS MY TRUCK.
CHARRED PISTONS FROM
A FOUR-CYCLE ENGINE THAT TURNED
OUT TO BE A TWO-CYCLE ENGINE.
REPLACEMENT TUBES FROM THAT
GUITAR AMP THAT WAS REPO'D
DURING MY SOLO
AT THE HIGH SCHOOL DANCE.
BUT THAT STUFF IS COMPLETELY OUT
OF SIGHT, OR AT LEAST IT WOULD
BE IF I COULD GET THE GARAGE
DOOR TO CLOSE.
BUT GARAGE CLUTTER
IS NOT A BAD THING.
IF YOU'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF A MESS, YOU'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF HISTORY.
OH, YEAH, IT'S THE STORY
OF EVERYTHING THAT'S HAPPENED
IN THAT GARAGE SINCE THE WORDS
"I'LL GET TO IT LATER"
WERE FIRST SPOKEN.
AND CLUTTER IS BY FAR
THE EASIEST ORGANIZATIONAL
SYSTEM TO LEARN.
WHY, WITH A CLEAN GARAGE, YOU
GOT TO REMEMBER WHICH CUPBOARD
THE TOOLS ARE IN.
WITH A MESSY GARAGE, THEY'RE
RIGHT WHERE YOU CAN SEE THEM,
LYING THERE RUSTING
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE FLOOR.
AND IT'S AMAZING WHAT YOU CAN
CREATE JUST BY LEAVING STUFF
LYING AROUND.
YOU TAKE THAT GUY THAT INVENTED
CHIA PETS.
I FIGURE IT WAS A BUNCH
OF BROKEN LAWN GNOMES LYING
THERE BESIDE SOME SPILLED
GRASS SEED UNDER A LEAKY ROOF.
I BUT THERE'S A BUNCH
OF MILLION DOLLAR PROJECTS
RIGHT IN MY GARAGE.
ALL I GOT TO DO IS SORT
THROUGH THE CLUTTER.
[laughs]
I'LL GET TO IT LATER.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WHEN YOUR BACK LAWN'S AS HIGH
AS AN ELEPHANT'S EYE--
WHEN STARLINGS AND SPARROWS
FALL FROM THE SKY--
IT'S TIME TO GIVE
ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE A TRY.
WE'LL DIVE IN YOUR TANK
AND SUCK HER DRY.
WELL, DIDN'T GET THE JOB,
WHICH IS FINE.
I DON'T MIND NOT GETTING
THE JOB, BUT I THINK
THEY GAVE IT TO MIKE.
AW, COME ON.
I MEAN, MIKE'S A GOOD GUY
AND EVERYTHING, BUT THE MAN
IS A KNOWN THIEF.
WHY WOULD YOU GIVE
A $60,000-A-YEAR JOB
TO A GUY WHO'S GOT
NO EXPERIENCE, NO EDUCATION,
AND NO--
I HAVE EXACTLY THE SAME
QUALIFICATIONS, AND I'M OLDER.
I DIDN'T GET THE JOB EITHER,
MR. GREEN.
OH, MIKE, I'M SORRY
TO HEAR THAT.
I WAS REALLY ROOTING FOR YOU.
THANKS.
YEAH, I GUESS DALTON MUST HAVE
GOT THE JOB.
WHAT A SCAM, EH?
I MEAN, HE'S A GOOD GUY
AND EVERYTHING.
YEAH.
BUT YOU COULDN'T HIRE
A WORSE PERSON.
OH, MAN, THERE'S A WASTE
OF MONEY, MIKE, RIGHT THERE.
DALTON IS NOT THE GUY
FOR THAT JOB!
DALTON'S AN IDIOT.
YEAH.
A GOOD GUY, THOUGH.
GREAT GUY. SUPER GUY.
SUPER GUY. YEAH.
WELL, COUNT ME OUT.
I DIDN'T GET IT.
OH, WHAT A SHAME.
GEE, WE WERE REALLY HOPING
FOR YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, GUYS.
YEAH.
YEAH, THEY WOULDN'T EVEN TELL ME
WHO DID GET IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
I THINK THEY MAYOR GAVE THE JOB
TO HIS OWN WIFE.
AW, NO, SHE'S ALREADY
THE REGIONAL CHAIRPERSON.
THAT'S HOW THE MAYOR
GOT HIS JOB.
[knocking on door]
I'LL GET IT.
WELL, SOUNDS TO ME
LIKE SOMEBODY'S BEEN PAID OFF.
NO, THEY WOULDN'T
TAKE A BRIBE.
I WOULDN'T THINK.
GENTLEMEN, I'M PLEASED
TO PRESENT THE NEWLY-APPOINTED
DIRECTOR OF PUBLIC RELATIONS
FOR THE COUNTY OF POSSUM LAKE.
[cheers and applause]
I GOT A JOB!
WALTER WANTED TO PUT A GARDEN
IN BEHIND THE LODGE, SO HE GOT
ONE OF THE ROTOTILLERS THERE,
'CAUSE APPARENTLY THAT'S CHEAPER
THAN BUYING VEGETABLES.
AND THE PROBLEM WAS, EVERY TIME
HE PUT HER INTO GEAR, SHE WOULD
STALL OUT ON HIM THERE.
SO HE'D GET HER GOING,
HE'D PUT HER INTO GEAR,
AND SHE'D STALL OUT.
SO THEN HE GOT A GOOD IDEA.
HE FIGURED HE NEEDS SOME WAY
TO KEEP HER IN GEAR
ALL THE TIME,
SO HE INSTALLED THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET CLUTCH, BUT NOW HE'S JUST
GOT TO FIRE THAT--
FIRE IT UP, WALTER.
LET HER RIP. LET HER GO.
LET HER GO.
APPARENTLY, THAT'S THE MANUAL
ROTOTILLER TECHNIQUE.
SO HE OPENS UP THE--
AND APPARENTLY HE'S OUT OF--
YEAH, HE'S OUT OF--
NOT A DROP IN THERE, AND SO HE
GOES TO THE SHED WHERE WE KEEP
THE GAS CAN.
YOU NOTICE I SAID "GAS CAN."
NOT GAS, 'CAUSE IT'S--
YES, EMPTY AS WELL,
BUT THERE'S OTHER--
THERE'S ALWAYS A LIQUID
OF SOME KIND, AND MOST OF THEM
ARE FLAMMABLE.
AND THERE'S A CAN WITH
SOMETHING IN IT.
KIND OF A POTLUCK APPROACH
TO INTERNAL COMBUSTION ENGINES
WE USE AT THE LODGE.
PLUS HE'S NOT PUTTING
THAT MUCH IN.
HOW MUCH DAMAGE
COULD HE POSSIBLY--
I'M PRETTY SURE THAT'S--
WHATEVER IT IS,
I'M PRETTY SURE--
I'M PRETTY SURE THAT WOULD BURN.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S FLAMMABLE.
NOW, HE'S PROBABLY TRIPLED
THE HORSEPOWER OF THE UNIT
RIGHT NOW, BUT--
WHICH HE FINDS OUT AT THIS--
SO HE APPARENTLY TAKES OFF ON--
I WAS JUST GETTING A SHOVEL
OUT OF THE VAN AND NOT PAYING
TOO MUCH ATTENTION TO WHAT WAS--
HELLO, WALTER.
AND DALTON WAS PUTTING OUT--
HE LOVES THESE LITTLE
LAWN ORNAMENTS.
HE'S BEEN COLLECTING THESE FOR
YEARS, BUT WALTER HAD THE THEORY
THAT IF YOU BROKE THEM DOWN,
YOU COULD ACTUALLY USE THEM
AS SEEDS.
THAT DIDN'T WORK OUT SO GOOD.
THEN I WAS JUST PUTTING
THE SHOVEL AWAY, AND THEN WALTER
DECIDED TO PUT IN A ROOF GARDEN.
AND HE'S UP THERE HACKING AWAY
AT THE SHINGLES, AND...
THIS IS NOT GONNA WORK OUT
AT ALL, SO I'M GONNA--
THE BEST ADVICE I COULD GIVE HIM
WAS YOU COME ON DOWN, WALTER.
HERE YOU GO.
BUT BY GOLLY, THE UNIT--
YOU KNOW, SHE'S A GOOD ONE.
SHE KEPT RUNNING, AND HE WASN'T
HEADING OUT TOWARDS THE HIGHWAY,
SO I WASN'T TOO WORRIED.
THEN I GOT THIS IDEA: IF WE PUT
A RAMP UP AGAINST THE BACK
OF THE POSSUM VAN THERE, AND IF
WE COULD STEER HIM IN THAT WAY,
HE'S JUST GONNA GO RIGHT UP,
AND THEN THAT'LL BE
KIND OF A HOLDING.
AND THE FIRST YOU GOT TO DO--
YOU GOT TO LET GO, WALTER.
YOU GOT TO LET GO OF THE UNIT.
TAKE YOUR HAND--
LET HER GO. LET HER GO.
LET HER GO, WALTER.
THERE YOU GO.
OH! OKAY, VERY GOOD.
AND...
NOW, THE ONLY PROBLEM WAS,
THE UNIT DIDN'T ACTUALLY
STOP RUNNING.
SHE'S CHEWING UP THE SEATS
IN THERE.
TURNING AROUND, WHICH WE DIDN'T
NOTICE, AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
SHE STARTS COMING BACK DOWN
THE RAMP TOWARDS US, BUT,
YOU KNOW, AS LUCK WOULD HAVE IT,
SHE RAN OUT OF GAS,
AND SO DID DALTON.
[cheers and applause]
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW WE CALL
"IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
JOINING ME TODAY IS LOCAL MARINA
OWNER AND HAMMOCK ENTHUSIAST
DWIGHT CARDIFF.
SO TELL ME, DWIGHT, HOW ARE
THINGS AT THE MARINA THESE DAYS?
OH, BEEN BETTER, RED.
WE LOST PART OF THE FLEET
OVER THE WEEKEND.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
THE BOATS SANK?
NO, THEY JUST KIND OF
FLOATED AWAY.
WELL, YOU KNOW, DWIGHT,
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO TIE THEM UP
TO THE DOCK, EH?
I'M NOT BIG ON BENDING.
WELL, YOU GOT A BAD BACK?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, WHAT DID YOU
BRING US HERE TODAY?
GARBURATOR.
SHE'S JAMMED.
WELL, YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO
BRING THE WHOLE SINK
IN HERE, DWIGHT.
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN ACTUALLY
JUST TAKE THE GARBURATOR
OFF THE BOTTOM.
WELL, HOW WOULD I DO THAT?
WELL, YOU OPEN THE CUPBOARD
DOORS UNDER THE SINK,
AND THEN YOU BEND--OKAY.
YEP.
WELL...
GOT A PAIR OF NEEDLE-NOSE
PLIERS HERE.
SEE IF I CAN FIGURE OUT WHAT'S
JAMMING HER.
YOU KNOW, I THINK I GOT
A PAIR OF THOSE IN THE SHOP
AT THE MARINA.
I'M NOT SURE.
I DON'T GO IN THERE VERY MUCH.
THERE WE GO.
HUH?
THERE'S YOUR TYPICAL GARBURATOR
JAM RIGHT THERE.
IT'S A TAB OFF A POP CAN.
SEE THAT?
BOY, THOSE POP CANS JUST ARE
TOO MUCH WORK, AREN'T THEY?
ACTUALLY, THE WHOLE CAN IS
IN THERE, DWIGHT.
I KNOW WHAT CAUSED THAT, RED:
GRAVITY.
I THINK THE--
I THINK THE MARINA'S
A GRAVITY HOTSPOT.
SOME DAYS, I CAN BARELY GET OUT
OF MY CHAIR.
THAT WOULD BE A MILK CARTON,
DWIGHT.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO SAY, RED?
YOU THINK I'M SHOVING ALL--
STUFFING ALL MY GARBAGE
DOWN THE GARBURATOR?
I THINK YOU'RE STUFFING--
YES.
EXACTLY RIGHT.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING THIS
BACK, DWIGHT.
I'M CONFISCATING
THE GARBURATOR, OKAY?
YOU'RE NOT GETTING IT.
FROM NOW ON, YOU PUT YOUR
GARBAGE OUT ON GARBAGE DAY
LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE.
HAVE YOU SEEN THE LENGTH
OF MY DRIVEWAY?
I DON'T CARE, DWIGHT.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING
THE GARBURATOR BACK,
AND THAT IS FINAL.
FINE, FINE.
ON A COMPLETELY UNRELATED
SUBJECT, DO YOU KNOW HOW
TO BUILD A CATAPULT?
GET OUT.
[explosion]
DOES IT BOTHER YOU WHEN YOUR
WIFE STARTS LOOKING AT PICTURES
OF FANCY MANSIONS IN MAGAZINES,
THEN SHE LOOKS AT YOUR HOUSE,
THEN SHE LOOKS AT YOU?
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
IF YOU COULD IMPRESS PEOPLE
WITH YOUR HOUSE?
NOW, I DON'T MEAN FRIENDS
AND NEIGHBORS.
I'M TALKING ABOUT STRANGERS
WHO LIVE FAR, FAR AWAY.
YOU HAVE ZERO CHANCE
OF IMPRESSING ANYBODY
WHO ACTUALLY KNOWS YOU.
THEY SAY A PICTURE SAYS
1,000 WORDS.
WELL, HOW ABOUT A PICTURE
THAT TELLS 1,000 LIES?
FIND YOURSELF A SHOT OF ONE
OF THOSE FANCY MANSIONS IN
THE MAGAZINE, THEN TAKE A KNIFE
AND CUT OUT WHERE THE FRONT
DOOR IS ON THAT UNIT.
JUST LIKE THAT.
OH, LOOK, I'M HOME.
THEN WHAT YOU DO IS FIND
SOMEBODY WHO CAN TAKE A PICTURE
FOR YOU AND GET THEM TO LINE
THAT MANSION UP JUST RIGHT.
WHAT YOU'LL GET IS A PICTURE
OF YOU AT YOUR FRONT DOOR
THAT YOU CAN PROUDLY SEND
TO RELATIVES OVERSEAS AS LONG
AS YOU'RE POSITIVE THEY'LL
NEVER COME AND VISIT YOU.
[camera shutter clicks]
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, UNCLE RED?
WELL, HAROLD, IT'S A LOT
FOR ME TO TAKE IN.
IT'S A LOT FOR ME TO PUT OUT.
WHY ARE YOU HERE, HAROLD?
I MEAN, AND WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR LIFE,
YOUR JOB IN THE CITY?
[squeaks]
I QUIT THAT JOB.
WELL, THAT WAS
A GOOD JOB, HAROLD.
IT'S GONNA BE HARD
TO GET ANOTHER JOB.
I HAVE ANOTHER JOB.
YEAH, BUT YOU MIGHT NOT HAVE
GOTTEN IT, HAROLD.
I APPLIED FOR THAT JOB,
YOU KNOW?
YEAH, YOU ALL APPLIED
FOR THAT JOB.
THAT REALLY HELPED.
THANKS.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
NO, I SUPPOSE IF THEY WERE
LOOKING TO HIRE SOMEBODY LIKE
YOU, THEY'RE NOT GONNA HIRE
SOMEBODY LIKE ME.
OH, WELL, YOU KNOW, THAT'S
EXACTLY RIGHT.
THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
YEAH.
'CAUSE THEY WERE LOOKING
FOR SOMEONE YOUNG AND DYNAMIC
AND WITH A COLLEGE DEGREE WHO'S
COMPUTER-LITERATE AND HAS SOME
EXPERIENCE IN A RELATED FIELD.
YEAH, WELL, NO.
NO, THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
BUT YOU KNOW, WHEREAS IF THEY
WERE LOOKING FOR SOMEONE
MIDDLE-AGED, OPINIONATED,
UNEMPLOYED, BUT VERY GOOD
WITH A CHAINSAW--
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
THAT'S ENOUGH, OKAY?
WE UNDERSTAND.
WE GET IT.
OKAY, I'M JUST--
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE--
YEAH.
I'M VERY HAPPY TO BE BACK.
OKAY, GREAT, GREAT.
I'M VERY EXCITED ABOUT
THE NEW JOB AND EVERYTHING,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHAT?
TRUTH BE TOLD,
I--I-I MISSED--
[whimpers]
I-I MISSED, YOU KNOW, EVERYBODY.
OH, WELL, DID YOU--
DID YOU MISS ME, HAROLD?
DID YOU MISS ME?
I WASN'T EVEN SHOOTING
AT YOU.
[laughs]
YEAH, I DID.
I MISSED YOU.
YEAH?
YEAH.
WELL, I MISSED
YOU TOO, HAROLD.
[laughs]
OH, NO, NO, NO.
NO.
I THINK I'M GONNA CRY.
SEE, NO, I DIDN'T MISS THAT,
ALL RIGHT?
YOU KNOW WHAT THE BEST
PART IS?
WE GET TO WORK TOGETHER AGAIN.
HOW DO YOU FIGURE THAT?
OH, YEAH, THAT'S MY PROPOSAL.
I'M GONNA MAKE MY JOB TO BE
THE PROMOTION AND MARKETING
OF POSSUM LODGE.
[squeaks]
AND WE GOT A LOT OF WORK TO DO!
WOW, HAROLD.
YEAH.
YOU MEAN YOU THINK
POSSUM LODGE IS GOOD ENOUGH
TO ATTRACT VISITORS?
WE GOT A LOT OF WORK TO DO!
[pig squealing]
YOU STILL HAVEN'T GOT THAT
FIXED, HUH?
THAT'S THE MEETING CALL,
HAROLD.
YEAH.
WELL,
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I DID NOT GET THE BIG $60,000
JOB, BUT HAROLD DID,
WHICH IS CLOSE ENOUGH,
'CAUSE I FIGURE, IN THE NEXT
TWO WEEKS, SOMEBODY IS BOUND
TO KILL HIM.
WE'LL GET THE MONEY SOONER
OR LATER.
FOR THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[pig squealing]
SIT DOWN.
YEAH, GET DOWN OVER THERE.
COME ON, GUYS.
COME TO ORDER.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
all: QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
all: I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, AS YOU CAN
SEE, HAROLD IS HERE WITH US NOW,
AND HE'S GONNA BE HANGING AROUND
THE LODGE A FAIR BIT BECAUSE
OF HIS NEW JOB AND EVERYTHING,
AND I WANT YOU EACH TO GIVE HIM
YOUR FULL COOPERATION.
AND I'D LIKE TO PROPOSE THAT
WE ALL WELCOME HAROLD BACK
WITH A BIG ROUND OF APPLAUSE.
[one man claps slowly]
OH, OKAY, GUYS.
NOW, HE WENT AWAY,
AND HE DID FINE,
AND I THINK IT'S ONLY RIGHT
THAT WE WELCOME HIM BACK.
[two men clap slowly]
OKAY, UM, FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO
DON'T KNOW THIS, HAROLD IS
MAKING $60,000 A YEAR.
[cheers and applause]