I LIKE HAVING
A LARGE VEHICLE.
IT MAKES ME FEEL SAFER.
I LIKE SITTING UP
NICE AND HIGH
SO I CAN SEE
THE COPS SOONER.
THE PROBLEM WITH ANY OF THESE
VANS OR S.U.V.s OR WHATEVER
IS WHEN YOU GO AROUND
A CORNER THEY ROLL OVER.
I FIND THAT INCONVENIENT.
THAT'S BECAUSE
THEY'RE TOP HEAVY --
BUT THEN, SO AM I.
SO I ATTACHED
THIS LANDING GEAR,
FROM THIS OLD AIRPLANE
I FOUND SOMEWHERE --
IT'S NOT IMPORTANT REALLY.
AND NOW, WHENEVER I TAKE
A CORNER TOO FAST,
THE LANDING GEAR IS GOING
TO STOP ME FROM BECOMING
AIRBORNE, SEE?
BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT THEY SAY,
ACTIONS SPEAK
LOUDER THAN WORDS.
AND I KNOW A LOT OF YOU
DON'T HEAR TOO WELL.
[cheers and applause]
THANKS VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
IT'S BEEN A STRANGE WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
LLOYD CARSON PASSED AWAY.
YEAH, THAT'S PRETTY MUCH
THE SAME WAY WE FEEL.
LLOYD WAS A WEIRD GUY.
HE WAS ONE OF
THOSE MILITARY NUTS,
ALWAYS DRESSED FOR
COMBAT, YOU KNOW.
HE WAS MARRIED FOUR TIMES.
MAYBE THAT EXPLAINS IT.
I ALWAYS GOT ALONG
OKAY WITH LLOYD,
AS LONG AS HE'D
TAKEN HIS MEDICATION.
THIS ACTUALLY
WAS LLOYD'S MUSKET,
BUT IT'S OURS NOW.
SEE, BECAUSE THE BANK HAS
SEIZED HIS PROPERTY
BECAUSE OF DEBTS
BEING OWED THERE,
BUT THEY SAID ANY LODGE
MEMBER CAN GO OVER
AND TAKE ANY PIECE
OF JUNK THEY WANT, EH --
AS LONG AS THEY GET
IT OFF THE PROPERTY.
IT'S FANTASTIC.
UNCLE RED!
OH -- DID YOU
STEAL THAT MUSKET
FROM A DEAD GUY?
SHAME ON YOU.
HAROLD, IT'S NOT STEALING
WHEN THE BANK DOES IT.
IT'S CALLED MEETING YOUR
FIDUCIARY RESPONSIBILITIES.
OH-HO!
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW THE
MEANING OF THAT WORD.
NO, RESPONSIBILITY.
FIDUCIARY?
AND FIDUCIARY.
HAROLD,
ALL I KNOW IS
THE BANK JUST WANTS THE
HOUSE AND THE LAND,
AND THEY TOLD US WE CAN
HAVE ANYTHING ELSE WE FIND,
AS LONG AS WE REMOVE IT
FROM THE PROPERTY.
I STILL THINK
IT'S WRONG.
LLOYD WAS
A WEIRD GUY.
YOU COULD FIND ALL
SORTS OF DANGEROUS
STUFF OVER THERE.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE YOU
SHOULD COME OVER,
KIND OF PICK AROUND.
YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO
FIND YOURSELF A LIFE.
RED! WE GOT BIG TROUBLE
OVER AT THE CARSON PLACE.
WHAT?
WELL, THE WATER TASTED FUNNY,
SO WE SHONE A LIGHT
DOWN THE WELL,
AND YOU'LL NEVER GUESS WHAT
WE SAW WHEN WE LOOKED
DOWN THERE.
STINKY PETERSON?
NO. A MISSILE.
A MISSILE, RED,
WHAT?
POINTING STRAIGHT
UP AT US.
OH, NO!
WE'RE ALL GOING TO DIE
AND I'VE NEVER BEEN
WITH A WOMAN!
GO AHEAD.
THERE'S NOTHING TO
WORRY ABOUT, HAROLD.
THERE'S NOTHING
DANGEROUS GOING ON.
THE MISSILE'S NOT
ANY PROBLEM AT ALL.
WE'LL JUST HOIST HER
OUT OF THERE, NO SWEAT.
RED, IT'S A MISSILE.
WELL, SO WHAT?
THOSE DON'T JUST GO OFF.
AND NOW IT'S TIME TO PLAY
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
[cheers and applause]
TODAY'S WINNER WILL
RECEIVE A COUPON
FOR THREE TANNING SESSIONS
AT THE PORT ASBESTOS
LEATHER FACTORY.
OKAY, COVER YOUR EARS.
RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET RANGER GORD
TO SAY THIS WORD...
ALL RIGHT, ED.
AND... GO.
OKAY, GORD.
THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT'S VERY HOT.
CONNIE STEVENS.
OKAY, OKAY, THERE'S
AN EXPRESSION,
WHERE THERE'S SMOKE
THERE'S...
CHEECH AND CHONG.
NO. OKAY, OKAY, WHEN
YOU WERE IN YOUR TOWER
AND LIGHTNING HIT YOUR
FOREST, WHAT DID YOU GET?
CRISPY NOSE HAIRS?
OKAY. NO.
THIS IS THE ONE THING
THAT'S DESTROYING ALL
OF OUR FORESTS.
YEAH. TOO MUCH URINE.
ALMOST OUT OF TIME, RED.
YEAH. OKAY.
OKAY, GORD, REMEMBER
HOW THAT FOREST
BURNT TO THE GROUND
OUTSIDE ROCK CREEK POINT?
WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
YEAH, RIGHT, THE FOREST
RANGER FELL ASLEEP...
FOR A MONTH.
YOU KNOW,
FOR A WHILE THERE,
I THOUGHT THEY WERE
GOING TO FIRE HIM.
HEY! THERE WE GO!
[quirky upbeat music]
Winston:
I'M A LITTLE HUNGRY.
Red:
WELL, THERE'S SOME SANDWICHES
IN THE COOLER THERE, WINSTON.
Winston:
UH, THIS SMELLS
A LITTLE WEIRD.
HOW OLD IS THIS?
Red:
I'M NOT SURE.
WHEN'S THE LAST
TIME WE WENT FISHING?
Mike:
HEY, WHAT'S THE WORST
FOOD YOU GUYS EVER ATE?
Red:
VEGETABLES.
Winston:
NO OFFENCE, MIKE,
BUT FOR ME IT HAD TO BE
YOUR MACARONI SURPRISE.
Mike: REALLY?
I THOUGHT YOU LIKED IT.
Red:
SURPRISE.
Mike:
THAT'S NOTHING.
YOU GUYS EVER
HAD PRISON FOOD?
Red and Winston:
NO. UH-HUNH.
Mike:
WELL, IT IS DISGUSTING.
AND SUCH TINY PORTIONS.
Red:
WHAT'S THE WORST THING
YOU EVER ATE, MIKE?
Mike:
EVIDENCE.
Winston:
I ATE GRUBS ONCE.
Mike:
WHY WOULD ANYONE EAT GRUBS?
Red: MAYBE THEY
WERE OUT OF CRICKETS.
Winston:
HEY, LOOK, WHEN YOU'RE
LOST IN THE WOODS FOR DAYS
AND YOU HAVEN'T EATEN,
GRUBS START TO LOOK
PRETTY DARN GOOD.
Mike:
OH, OKAY, WELL,
THAT'S JUST HUMAN NATURE.
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE CAPABLE OF
UNTIL YOU'RE IN A
DESPERATE SITUATION.
LIKE MANY TIMES
I WAS FORCED TO STEAL
SIMPLY BECAUSE PEOPLE
WOULDN'T GIVE ME THEIR STUFF.
Winston:
WE ALL MAKE CHOICES, YOU KNOW?
Red:
YUP, THAT WE DO.
Winston: ANTHONY ANTHONY SAYS
THE QUALITY OF YOUR CHOICES
IS BASED ON THE CALIBRE
OF YOUR ALTERNATIVES.
Red:
WELL, YEAH, THAT'S WHY
THE SELL A LOT MORE LADAs
IN RUSSIA
THAN THEY DO HERE.
Mike: IT'S SUPPLY
AND DEMAND, REALLY.
LIKE, WHEN YOU'RE
IN PRISON,
THE WOMEN START
LOOKING BETTER.
Red:
SO DO THE MEN, I HEAR.
Winston:
BERNICE MARRIED YOU.
I MEAN, SHE MUST HAVE HAD
SOME PRETTY SLIM PICKINGS.
Red:
YEAH, IT WAS EITHER
ME OR ONE OF YOU GUYS.
DID YOU KNOW IT TOOK
ISAAC NEWTON OVER 20 YEARS
TO DISCOVER GRAVITY?
THAT'S BECAUSE HE
JUST SAT AROUND THINKING.
IF HE WAS AN
ACTIVE HANDYMAN,
HE WOULD HAVE HIT ON
GRAVITY A LOT SOONER,
ESPECIALLY IF HE HAD ONE OF
THESE EXTENSION LADDERS.
I TELL YOU, AN EXTENSION
LADDER IS A DANGEROUS THING.
IT'S LIKE A FAT GUY
WITH TINY FEET.
IT CAN TIP OVER ABOUT
A MILLION DIFFERENT WAYS.
SO THIS TIME ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
WE'RE GOING TO BUILD SOMETHING
A LOT SAFER THAN A LADDER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
AN ESCALATOR.
OKAY, FOR STARTERS YOU
WANNA TAKE DOWN YOUR
CLOTHESLINE,
BECAUSE THAT'S
GOING TO BECOME
PART OF THE DRIVE
MECHANISM FOR THE UNIT.
BUT YOU'RE ALSO GOING
TO NEED A MOTOR.
SO TO SAVE MONEY THERE,
I SUGGEST YOU TAKE THE MOTOR
OF AN EXISTING APPLIANCE,
LIKE, SAY,
MAYBE A WASHING MACHINE.
I MEAN, YOU ALREADY TOOK
DOWN YOUR CLOTHESLINE.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE
DOING ANY LAUNDRY.
OKAY, I GOT MY DRIVE
UNIT ALL IN PLACE THERE.
AND WIRED HER UP WITH A
COUPLE OF 3-WAY SWITCHES
SO I CAN TURN IT ON AND OFF
FROM TWO DIFFERENT PLACES.
YOU KNOW, LIKE THOSE SWITCHES
YOU HAVE IN YOUR HOUSE
FOR WHEN YOUR WIFE
FORGETS YOU'RE STILL HOME
AND TURNS OFF THE BASEMENT
LIGHT WHILE YOU'RE DOWN THERE
TRYING TO GET A SLIVER
OUT OF YOUR UPPER THIGH.
SO I CAN TURN
MY ESCALATOR ON
BY PUSHING THE
SWITCH DOWN HERE
AND THEN TURN IT OFF
FROM THE TOP OF THE LADDER.
I'LL TELL YOU WHY
THAT'S IMPORTANT LATER.
OKAY, NOW WE GET
TO THE TRICKY PART...
THE COLLAPSIBLE STEPS.
I'M GOING TO USE
FOLDING CHAIRS ON THAT.
BUT HERE, AGAIN, YOU DON'T
WANT TO GO OVER BUDGET.
SO GO TO THE MOST UNPOPULAR
CLUB IN YOUR TOWN --
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING LIKE
CITIZENS AGAINST BEER.
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE WAY
MORE FOLDING CHAIRS
THAN THEY NEED,
AND YOU CAN HELP THEM
OUT WITH THAT PROBLEM.
OKAY, BUT ALL
I NEED IS THE BACK
AND THE FOLDING SEAT THERE,
SO I'M JUST GOING TO
TAKE A COUPLE OF MINUTES
AND HACK THE
LEGS OFF THERE.
OKAY, I'VE GOT
MY LEGLESS CHAIRS
ATTACHED TO THE
CLOTHESLINE LIFT SYSTEM,
AND WHAT I WANTED TO SHOW YOU
I ENDED USING THOSE SKIS
THAT YOU SAW EARLIER.
I TURNED THEM UPSIDE DOWN
SO THE CHAIRS DON'T
CATCH ON THE RUNGS,
BECAUSE DOING A
HANDYMAN PROJECT IS
LIKE MAKING WIENERS...
YOU END UP
USING EVERYTHING.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GIVE
HER A DRY RUN.
OKAY, WE'RE ALMOST DONE,
BUT I BETTER PICK UP
THE PACE A LITTLE BIT
BECAUSE I WANT
TO FINISH THIS PROJECT
BEFORE MY MEDICAL
INSURANCE RUNS OUT.
OKAY, JUST HAD TO ADD
THE HANDRAIL ON THERE,
AND WE'RE READY TO GO.
AGAIN I SAVED MYSELF
A FEW DOLLARS HERE.
THIS IS JUST A
GARDEN HOSE THAT I SPLIT
AND THEN FIT IT OVER THE
EDGE OF THE PLYWOOD.
THE HOSE DIDN'T
COST ME ANYTHING
BECAUSE MY
NEIGHBOURS ARE AWAY.
ACTUALLY, EVEN THE PLYWOOD
WASN'T THAT HARD TO COME BY.
OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH TALK.
TIME FOR A LITTLE
UPWARD MOBILITY.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD, AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[quirky upbeat music]
YOU KNOW, WHEN A MAN
GETS TO A CERTAIN AGE,
HE'S LEARNED A
THING OR TWO.
I DON'T MEAN THAT
FIGURATIVELY EITHER.
I'M SAYING MAYBE
ONE, TWO THINGS TOPS.
NOW, SOME OF
YOU GUYS MAY THINK
YOU KNOW MORE THAN I'M
GIVING YOU CREDIT FOR,
BUT YOU'RE JUST MISTAKING
USELESS TRIVIA
FOR ACTUAL KNOWLEDGE.
OH, SURE, I'M SURE YOU SIT
THERE IN YOUR LIVING ROOM
YELLING OUT THE ANSWERS TO
YOUR FAVOURITE TV GAME SHOW.
YOU MIGHT EVEN GET
SOME OF THEM RIGHT.
BUT I'M TALKING ABOUT APPLIED
WISDOM FOR YOUR GOLDEN YEARS
IN THE OFF CHANCE THAT YOU
ACTUALLY HAVE GOLDEN YEARS.
SEE, THE MIDDLE-AGED MIND IS
KIND OF LIKE A COMPUTER --
AN OLD COMPUTER,
LIKE MAYBE A COMMODORE 64.
AND YOU GOT PEANUT BUTTER
ON THE KEYS
AND SNEEZE MARKS ALL
OVER THE SCREEN.
NOW, IF YOU DON'T WANT THAT
COMPUTER TO BE DECLARED
OBSOLETE,
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT
YOU GOT TO DO.
YOU GOT TO CLEAR
OFF SOME SPACE ON THE
OLD HARD DRIVE THERE.
THINGS LIKE
YOUR WIFE'S BIRTHDAY,
HEY, THAT'S A KEEPER.
BUT KNOWING WHO WROTE THE
THEME SONG TO
McHALE'S NAVY,
WELL, THAT ONE CAN GO.
LIKEWISE, I'M SURE
THERE WAS A TIME
WHEN IT WAS IMPORTANT
TO KNOW WHO SCORED
THE WINNING TOUCHDOWN
IN THE 1976 SUPERBOWL,
HOW MANY YARDS HE RAN,
THAT FACT THAT HE
SLIPPED IN THE ENDZONE
BECAUSE IT WAS
RAINING THAT DAY.
BUT IF THAT STOPS YOU
FROM REMEMBERING
WHICH WIRES GO WHERE WHEN
YOU'RE JUMP STARTING A CAR,
OR THAT FLAMMABLE AND
INFLAMMABLE ACTUALLY
MEAN THE SAME THING,
WELL, YOU'RE PROBABLY NOT
GOING TO ENJOY ANY MORE
SUPERBOWLS.
SO WHAT I'M SAYING
IS LOSE THE TRIVIA,
KEEP THE KNOWLEDGE.
YOU MAY NEVER
BE ON
JEOPARDY,
BUT YOU'LL
ALSO NEVER BE IN IT.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
WHEN THERE'S NO FOG IN TOWN
EXCEPT FOR YOUR PATCH,
WHEN IT GIVES
YOU AN ITCH WHERE
YOU'D RATHER NOT SCRATCH,
CALL ROTHSCHILD'S NOW,
AND I'LL BE DISPATCHED.
LIGHT UP THAT SWITCHBOARD,
JUST DON'T LIGHT A MATCH.
BRING THAT MANHOLE COVER,
WILL YOU, HAROLD?
OKAY, I THINK WE GOT THAT
MISSILE PROBLEM ALL
FIGURED OUT.
I THINK WE SHOULD CONTACT
THE U.S. AIR FORCE.
YOU KNOW,
FROM THE COLD WAR.
THIS COULD BE ONE
OF THEIR MISSILES.
WELL, I'M NOT GOING
TO BE CALLING THE
U.S. AIR FORCE.
WHAT DO I SAY?
WE'VE GOT A MISSILE?
THEY TAKE
THAT AS A THREAT,
WE'RE IN REAL TROUBLE.
WELL, THEN CONTACT
THE CANADIAN AIR FORCE.
HAROLD, IT'S AFTER SIX.
HE'S GONE HOME.
[applause]
YOU HAVE
TO CALL SOMEBODY.
CALL THE BOMB SQUAD.
JUST CALL
SOMEBODY, PLEASE.
JUST RELAX.
ARE YOU AFRAID THAT
WE DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT MISSILES?
I'M AFRAID YOU DON'T
KNOW MUCH ABOUT ANYTHING.
JUST BE REASONABLE.
WHAT'S THE WORSE THING
THAT COULD HAPPEN?
HMM.
OH, LET'S SEE.
OH! THE MISSILE GOES OFF
AND KILLS EVERYTHING
IN A 50-MILE RADIUS!
YOU DON'T THINK?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, THE DANGER IS THE
MISSILE GOING OFF
UNEXPECTEDLY.
SO THE SOLUTION IS
WE GOT TO SET THE
MISSILE OFF ON PURPOSE.
YES.
I FEEL SO MUCH BETTER.
WELL, AND YOU
SHOULD, SEE?
I FIGURE WE'RE GOING
TO SCREW THE MANHOLE COVER
DOWN ON TOP
OF THE WELL, OKAY.
THEN WE DETONATE THAT
PUPPY RIGHT DOWN
INSIDE THERE.
WE PUT THE FISH NET TO LAY
DOWN RIGHT ON TOP OF THAT
MANHOLE COVER THERE.
I FIGURE THE COVER'S
GOING TO ABSORB,
I'M GUESSING,
95% OF THE ENERGY.
SO THEN THE MISSILE
WILL GET ALL TANGLED
UP IN THE FISH NET
AND JUST FLOP DOWN
BESIDE THE WELL.
YEAH.
YUP. YUP.
AND YOU'RE SERIOUS?
DEAD SERIOUS.
LET'S HOPE NOT.
Red:
WALTER HAD ASKED ME TO
JOIN HIM IN BEHIND THE LODGE
TO DO A LITTLE
BIT OF WORK ON HIS CAR.
AND ONE OF THE
FIRST THINGS I DO WHEN
WORKING ON A VEHICLE
IS KIND OF CHECK THE OIL.
AND HE HADN'T CHANGED
HIS OIL IN A WHILE.
SO WE HAD A CASE OF OIL.
I THOUGHT THIS MIGHT
BE A GOOD WAY TO START.
SO I GIVE HIM THE WRENCH
AND THE PAN THERE
AND SAID GO DOWN UNDERNEATH.
PUT A PIECE OF PLYWOOD DOWN
THERE AND SO HE KEEPS HIS
CLOTHES A LITTLE CLEANER.
ALL HE'S GOT TO DO IS TAKE
THE DRAIN PLUG OFF THE PAN
AND GET THE OLD OIL OUT,
AND WE'LL PUT THE NEW OIL IN.
I'M SURE IT'S THE FIRST TIME
WALTER HAD EVER DONE THIS.
IT'S KIND OF RUSTED ON THERE.
BUT HE FINALLY GOT THE --
GET THE PAN.
THE PAN, WALTER, THE PAN.
THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT.
SO WE GOT HER ALL FILLED UP
AND HE WRINGS THAT OUT.
AND HE DIDN'T SPILL
TOO MUCH OF IT REALLY.
NOT TOO BAD.
SO HE GETS UP AND --
WHEN YOU'RE DOING
YOUR OWN OIL CHANGES,
HERE'S AN IMPORTANT --
LOOK FOR THE DRAIN PLUG.
A LOT OF TIMES
IT'LL DROP RIGHT INTO THE.
THERE IS IS THERE.
SEE, IT'S IMPORTANT.
YOU GO PUT THAT
BACK ON, WALTER.
THAT GOES BACK ON.
AWAY YOU GO.
AND WE HAVE A BIG CAN
WE KEEP FOR RECYCLED
OIL DOWN THERE.
SO I JUST GO DOWN AND
DUMP THE PAN IN THERE,
AND, WELL, SHE GOT AWAY
FROM ME A LITTLE BIT.
SO, OKAY.
GOOD ENOUGH.
NOW I'M STARTING
TO PUT THE OIL --
I PUT A FEW QUARTS
IN AT THIS POINT.
I FIGURE IT WAS --
YOU KNOW,
FOR A SMALL ENGINE,
IT WAS REALLY
HOLDING A LOT OF OIL.
SO I THOUGHT MAYBE I'D JUST
CHECK TO SEE HOW WE'RE DOING.
AND, UH, REAL SURPRISE.
I PULL IT OUT,
AND IT'S JUST BONE DRY.
AND, UH, I CAN
HEAR OIL RUNNING.
IT'S RUNNING
DOWN THE WOOD
AND RIGHT DOWN THE HILL.
SO, YOU KNOW,
I'M SAYING TO WALTER,
LIKE WHAT HAPPENED
TO THAT DRAIN PLUG?
AND HE SAYS, NO PROBLEM.
I GOT IT RIGHT HERE.
I SAID, YOU GOTTA GO
PUT THAT IN WALTER.
IT'S GOT TO GO
INTO THE PAN.
BUT NOW EVERYTHING
IS SO DARN SLIPPERY,
THE GRASS, EVERYTHING,
THAT IT JUST VIRTUALLY TAKES
OFF ON HIM AND AWAY HE GOES.
AND I TRY TO --
I DID MY BEST TO SAVE HIM.
OH, BOY.
SO HE'S OKAY, BUT --
NOW, I'M LOOKING
AT THE BOARD,
AND SUDDENLY I
GOT A GREAT IDEA.
HMM... YEAH...
SO WHAT I DID WAS
I MOUNTED THE BOARD ON KIND
OF A DISPLAY / EASEL THING
'CAUSE TO ME,
THIS IS AN OIL PAINTING.
AND WE HAD A BIG
LOCAL COLLECTOR.
HE'S ABOUT 6'5",
AND HE CAME OVER AND LOOKED.
HE WAS INTERESTED IN IT,
AND WE WERE HAVING KIND OF
A SPECIAL FEATURE TODAY.
YOU COULD
MEET THE ARTIST.
AND I THINK WE WERE DOING
FINE UNTIL WALTER TRIED
TO SHAKE HIS HAND.
WAY TO GO, WALTER.
KILLED ANOTHER ART SALE.
[quirky upbeat music]
OKAY, NOW,
THIS MAY LOOK LIKE A
ROMANTIC CANDLELIGHT DINNER,
BUT IT'S NOT.
FOR STARTERS,
I'M ALONE,
SO THERE'S NO CHANGE FOR
ROMANCE OR JUST FRIENDS.
SO WHY THE CANDLES?
WELL, THAT COULD BE
BECAUSE THE POWER IS OUT.
MY WIFE'S OVER
AT HER MOTHER'S,
AND I'M EATING LEFTOVER CHILI
THAT I WARMED UP OVER THE
EXHAUST MANIFOLD OF
THE POSSUM VAN.
BUT THE BIG PROBLEM IS I'VE
GOT TO GET UP EARLY IN
THE MORNING,
AND ALL I'VE GOT IS THIS
ELECTRIC ALARM CLOCK.
OKAY, HERE'S WHERE
I GET REALLY SMART.
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING A WHILE
FOR THIS, HAVEN'T YOU?
THIS IS A BATTERY POWERED
SMOKE DETECTOR.
AND THIS LEVER CLOSES
THE FIREPLACE DAMPER.
G'NIGHT.
[snoring]
[fire alarm buzzing]
[hacking cough]
COME ON UP
HERE, HAROLD.
OKAY.
YOU SHOULD WEAR THESE
WELDING GOGGLES
FOR SAFETY AND
THAT KIND OF THING.
NO THANKS,
HAROLD.
WHAT'S WITH ALL THE
JUMPER CABLES?
WELL, LLOYD NEVER PAID
HIS ELECTRICAL BILL,
SO HE'S GOT NO
POWER OVER THERE.
SO WE'RE ACTUALLY GOING
TO IGNITE THE MISSILE
FROM POSSUM LODGE
MISSION CONTROL.
RIGHT HERE.
OKAY, RED. IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S ALL SYSTEMS GO.
OKAY.
GREAT. GREAT.
HAROLD, YOU TAKE
THIS JUMPER CABLE.
I WANT TO YOU TO
GO THAT TERMINAL AT
THE FAR END THERE,
BECAUSE I CAN'T REACH
BOTH TERMINALS.
SO IT TAKES TWO GUYS
TO LIGHT THIS CANDLE, BABY.
WOW! IT'S LIKE
THE REAL DEAL,
LIKE WHEN THOSE TWO GUYS
HAVE TO TURN THE KEYS
AT EXACTLY
THE SAME TIME.
WELL, WE LIKE TO DO
EVERYTHING BY THE BOOK.
YOU KNOW THAT, HAROLD.
THIS IS SO COOL.
I'M NOT DOING IT,
BUT IT'S SO COOL.
WELL, FINE.
ED, HERE.
YOU DO THE
HONOURS.
HAROLD, YOU DO
THE COUNTDOWN, OKAY?
OKAY, OKAY.
WATCH THAT.
Red: GO!
Harold: ALL RIGHT.
INITIATING FINAL COUNTDOWN
SEQUENCE TO LAUNCH.
10 MINUTES AND COUNTING.
9 MINUTES
AND 59 SECONDS.
JUST START AT 10 SECONDS,
WOULD YOU, PLEASE!
INITIATING FINAL REVISED
COUNTDOWN TO LAUNCH.
TEN SECONDS.
HAROLD, FORGET IT.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1,
BLAST OFF!
WE HAVE LIFT-OFF!
OH, BABY!
UNCLE RED!
I DON'T THINK THE MANHOLE
COVER ABSORBED 95%
OF THE FORCE.
THE MANHOLE
DID NOTHING.
THE FISH NET IS GOING
TO DO NOTHING AT ALL,
UNCLE RED.
OH, YEAH, HAROLD?
THE FISH NET CAUGHT
IN THE RAFTERS,
JUST LIKE I PLANNED.
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
AND IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
KIND OF HOPING WE CAN PUT AN
END TO OUR OWN PERSONAL
COLD WAR.
I'M CERTAINLY READY
TO LAY DOWN MY ARMS.
AND TO REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheers and applause]
EVERYBODY TAKE A SEAT.
WE'LL BEGIN THE MEETING
AS SOON AS HE ARRIVES.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, GUYS,
WELL, WE GOT THE MISSILE
OFF OF LLOYD'S PROPERTY,
BUT WE GOT A LITTLE BIT OF
REPAIR WORK TO DO ON THE ROOF.
[explosion]
AND THE LODGE ITSELF,
APPARENTLY.