(Cement truck backing up)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE MAN WHO KNOWS THE
MEANING OF "SELF-SUFFICIENT",
IF NOT THE SPELLING...
MY UNCLE, YOUR HOST, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
(Whistling)
(Applause)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WE WERE GOING THROUGH
THE "LARGE VEHICLES
"WITH OVERSIZED ENGINES" TRADER
AND YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
WE DECIDED THAT WE NEED
TO BROADEN OUR INTERESTS
A LITTLE BIT.
OH, EXCELLENT!
I WAS THINKING OF STARTING
A CHESS CLUB.
YOU GO RIGHT AHEAD, HAROLD.
SO THE BUNCH OF US
ARE GONNA MAKE AN INVESTMENT.
WE'RE GETTING OURSELVES
A SUBMARINE.
G-G-GONNA GET YOURSELVES
YES, WE ARE, HAROLD.
WE'VE ORDERED THE CONCRETE
FOR THE SUBMARINE PEN.
WE'LL CHARGE PEOPLE MONEY
TO TAKE 'EM ON SUBMARINE RIDES,
MAYBE FIND BURIED TREASURE,
AND GENERALLY
GET STINKIN' RICH.
YOU'RE HALFWAY THERE.
ALL YOU NEED
IS THE "RICH" PART.
(Audience laughing)
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): WE GOT
A JAM-PACKED SHOW.
I'M GONNA BUILD A HOVERCRAFT.
RANGER GORD IS GONNA CRY OUT
FOR LAND WHALES.
GARTH HARBLE'S GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW TO CONTROL YOUR SKUNK,
AND HAROLD'S GONNA GET
UNDER THE COVERS.
WE'RE ALL GETTING EXCITED
ABOUT THIS SUBMARINE THING.
WE'VE ORDERED LUMBER
AND A TON OF CONCRETE
TO MAKE THE SUBMARINE PEN.
WE'RE PUTTING MONEY BACK
INTO THE COMMUNITY.
PROVIDING YOU PAY YOUR BILLS.
WE WILL WHEN
WE START MAKING MONEY.
WE'LL CHARGE PEOPLE FOR RIDES
LIKE THEY DO AT DISNEYWORLD.
TAKE 'EM DOWN
TO "UNDERSEA WORLD".
WE'LL HAVE SCENES
OF SUNKEN SHIPS
AND MERMAIDS AND SHARKS
AND FORMER MEMBERS
OF THE TEAMSTERS UNION.
(Audience laughing)
YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO SPEND ANY MONEY.
MOST OF YOUR BOATS
ARE ALREADY SUBMARINES.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I'M KEEPING THE BUDGET IN MIND.
IF WE CAN'T AFFORD A SUB
FROM RUSSIA,
WE'LL GET A STEEL CORN BIN
FROM IOWA.
YOU GUYS SCARE ME
WHEN YOU START BUYING STUFF.
REMEMBER THAT TIME YOU BOUGHT
THAT ROCKET-POWERED R.V.
OUT OF THAT MAGAZINE?
REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN YOU STARTED IT UP?
SO WHAT?
IT WAS FIRECRACKER DAY ANYWAY.
NOBODY HEARD ANY COMPLAINTS.
WE WERE ALL DEAF FOR A WEEK!
HEY, THAT SAVED MY MARRIAGE.
(Applause)
(Red): OH, BOY.
HAROLD AND BILL
HAVE A PROJECT GOING.
THEY WANTED ME TO HELP.
THEY HAD LUMBER
AND HAROLD'S GONNA SIT--
NO, HAROLD, WATCH OUT.
OH, BOY, OH, BOY, OH, BOY.
I WASN'T PAYING ATTENTION.
DIDN'T NOTICE THE BOARD.
THEY DIDN'T NOTICE
THE BOARD WAS MISSING.
OK, NOW, THIS IS THE BIG ONE!
FOR A FREE HAIRSTYLE AND MOUSSE
FROM ED'S TAXIDERMY--
THAT ISN'T RIGHT, IS IT?
OH!
IT'S FOR A FREE
ANY-STYLE
HARE
OR
FROM ED'S TAXIDERMY.
THAT'S COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. FRANKLIN
TO SAY THIS WORD.
THIRTY SECONDS, AND GO!
ALL RIGHT, UH,
HOUSEHOLD APPLIANCE.
WIDE-SCREEN T.V.
WITH A BUILT-IN V.C.R.
NO, FOR CLEANING.
CLEANING.
YEAH, CLEANING.
UH... NO.
CLEANING, DOUG.
CLEANING.
IT'S FOR CLEANING.
GIVE ME ANOTHER CLUE.
FOR CLEANING THE FLOOR.
UH, OLD UNDERWEAR.
(Audience laughing)
A WOMAN USES THIS
TO CLEAN THE HOUSE.
AIR FRESHENER.
THIS THING SUCKS STUFF UP
OFF THE FLOOR.
OH, A DOG.
NO, THIS SUCKS EVERYTHING UP --
DIRT, LINT, DUST, EVERYTHING.
A BABY?
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YOUR MONSTER TRUCK SUCKS MONEY
OUT OF YOUR WALLET LIKE A...
A VACUUM.
THERE WE GO.
(Applause)
(Strums acoustic guitar)
OH, LATELY
THE HEALTH-CONSCIOUS
FANATICS HAVE TRIED
TO STOP US FROM EATING
ANYTHING FRIED
FRENCH FRIES AND ONION RINGS
AND BACON AND MORE BACON
LOTS OF BACON.
A LOT OF BACON IN THERE.
THEY TELL US THE GREASE
WILL GET OUR HEART ACHIN'
BUT I DO BELIEVE
THEY'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG
WITHOUT ANY LUBRICANT,
NOTHIN' RUNS VERY LONG
IF YOU WORK ON AN ENGINE,
YOU'LL SOON UNDERSTAND
THAT THE WHOLE THING
SEIZES UP
IF YOU'VE GOT NO OIL
IN YOUR PAN
OH!
HE SLIPPED.
RANGER GORD?
HI, RED.
GEE!
SHHH!
I'M LISTENING
TO THE SOUNDS OF NATURE.
YOU HEAR THAT?
THAT'S A LAND WHALE.
A LAND WHALE?
RIGHT, AND THAT'S
THE EERIE SONG
OF THE BEAUTIFUL LAND WHALE.
(Buzzing)
SOUNDS LIKE A CICADA.
RIGHT, CICADA, CICADA.
I'VE BEEN UP HERE SO LONG,
I FORGOT THE WORD.
CICADA, CICADA.
THAT'S IT.
OH, LISTEN --
I KNOW THAT VOICE.
THAT'S LARRY THE LAND WHALE...
OR -- YOUR FANCY WORD --
CICADA.
HE SAID, "HEY,
IS ANYONE... THERE?"
BEGINNING TO WONDER
THE SAME THING MYSELF, GORD.
OH, LISTEN.
THAT'S GERTA.
SHE SAYS, "YES,
AND DOES ANYONE KNOW
"IF ASHLEY HAS LEFT BRETT YET?"
ASHLEY HAS LEFT BRETT?
WHAT IS THAT, GORD?
THEY'RE NOT PARTICULARLY
BRIGHT ANIMALS.
THEY WATCH A LOT OF SOAPS.
OH, OH.
(Buzzing)
OH, EXCUSE ME.
HAVE TO TELL THEM SOMETHING.
(Imitating cicada)
(Buzzing stops)
WHAT HAPPENED THERE, GORD?
I TOLD THEM IT WAS 12:30.
WHY DID THAT MAKE THEM SHUT UP?
"THE YOUNG AND THE RESTLESS"
STARTS AT 12:30.
OH!
YOU KNOW, I HAVE TO
TELL THEM THAT EVERY DAY.
I HAVE TO REMIND THEM
EVERY DAY.
THEY'RE A LITTLE...
YEAH, YEAH.
WONDER WHAT MAKES THEM GO
LIKE THAT.
LIVING UP HERE,
I WOULD SAY, GORD.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, FOR SURE.
YOU KNOW, THE FIRST
CONSIDERATION
FOR THIS SUBMARINE RIDE
WE'RE BUILDING
WOULD HAVE TO BE "FUN".
THEN COMES POPULARITY;
NEXT COMES COST,
BUT EVENTUALLY
WE'LL GET AROUND TO SAFETY.
I'LL TAKE THIS WEEK'S
"HANDYMAN CORNER"
TO SHOW YOU HOW TO BUILD
YOUR OWN RESCUE BOAT.
THE PROBLEM WITH THE BOATS
UP HERE, THOUGH,
IS THAT THEY'RE ALWAYS SINKING
OR RUNNING OUT OF POWER
OR EXPLODING.
WE HAVE TO TAKE BETTER CARE
OF OUR BOATS,
OR BUILD A HOVERCRAFT.
YOU CAN GUESS WHICH WAY
I'M LEANING.
THIS OLD UNIT HERE
IS GONNA BECOME THE BASIS
OF MY HOVERCRAFT.
IF YOU GET YOURSELF
A STORE-BOUGHT HOVERCRAFT,
THEY COME WITH A RUBBER SKIRT
TO KEEP THE AIR
FROM BLOWING AWAY.
IF YOU HAVE
YOUR OWN RUBBER SKIRT,
WELL, THAT'S YOUR BUSINESS.
I'M NOT ONE TO JUDGE.
FOR ME, I'LL HAVE TO USE
WHATEVER I CAN FIND
THAT'S RUBBER AND BIG.
HAROLD?
I GOT MY RUBBER STUFF
DUCT-TAPED
TO THE GUNNELS
ALL THE WAY AROUND.
I SUPPOSE SOME OF THOSE ITEMS
ARE NOT TECHNICALLY RUBBER
BUT I'M NOT TECHNICALLY
A BOAT-BUILDER SO THAT'S A FIT.
ALLS YOU HAVE TO DO IS
GET YOUR CAPTAIN'S CHAIR
MOUNTED ON THERE
AND SOME SOURCE
OF A COMPRESSED GAS
AND YOU CAN START HOVERING.
PEOPLE ARE GONNA SIT UP
AND TAKE NOTICE
WHEN YOU COME DOWN THE LAKE
IN THIS UNIT...
ESPECIALLY IF YOU GET SIDEWAYS
GOING INTO THE RAPIDS.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
PULL THE TRIGGER
ON THE FIRE EXTINGUISHER.
THE CO2 GAS GOES THROUGH
THE HOLE IN THE HULL,
BUILDS UP PRESSURE, LIFTS ME
OFF THE GROUND, AND AWAY WE GO.
THEN I CONTROL THE STEERING
BY LEANING,
LETTING THE GAS VENT THIS WAY
OR THAT WAY.
WE'VE ALL SEEN THAT
DONE BEFORE.
LET'S GIVE 'ER A TRY.
SEEMS LIKE WE GOT
A FEW TOO MANY HOLES.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO PATCH THEM
WITH DUCT TAPE,
BUT THE TWO-INCH STUFF
ISN'T WIDE ENOUGH.
I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
(Grunting)
ALL RIGHT, I'VE TURNED MY BOAT
INTO AN ALUMINUM HULL.
I GOT MY RESCUE EQUIPMENT
ON BOARD.
GOT THE FLASHLIGHT...
AND I GOT MY WALKIE-TALKIE
SAFETY RESCUE UNIT...
AND MY LIFE-SAVING RING.
I'M ALL SET TO GO.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
TIME TO CAST OFF!
(Farting noise)
THIS IS
THE RESCUE BOAT -- HELP!
OH, WHAT A TANGLED WEB WE WEAVE
WHEN FIRST WE PRACTICE
TO DECEIVE.
WANT TO TALK ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT CONCERNS FOLKS OUR AGE.
OH, YEAH -- MEMORY LOSS.
WE'VE ALL BEEN THERE,
FROWNING IN THE MIDDLE
OF A PARKING LOT,
TRYING TO REMEMBER
WHERE WE PARKED THE CAR,
OR WHICH CAR DID WE BRING?
WAS IT THE SEDAN OR THE WAGON?
DO WE STILL HAVE THE SEDAN?
DIDN'T WE BUY A VAN?
(Audience laughing)
A LOT OF US ARE WORRIED
ABOUT LOSING OUR MEMORY
BECAUSE WE THINK WE REMEMBER
HAVING ONE.
THE TRUTH IS, WE NEVER DID
REMEMBER STUFF REAL WELL.
YOU REMEMBER YOURSELF
BEING FUNNY
OR SMART OR GOOD-LOOKIN'?
NOT ONLY HAVE YOU LOST
YOUR
MEMORY,
YOU'VE PICKED UP
SOMEBODY ELSE'S.
BUT THAT'S A GOOD THING.
IT'S BETTER TO REMEMBER THINGS
AS BEING BETTER
THAN WHAT HAPPENED.
NATURE DOES THAT ON PURPOSE.
OTHERWISE, NOBODY WOULD HAVE
MORE THAN ONE KID
OR GET REMARRIED
OR KEEP CHEERING FOR
THE TORONTO MAPLE LEAFS.
(Audience): OHHHH!
SO...
IF YOU'VE FORGOTTEN
YOU'RE FORGETFUL, FORGET IT.
IF YOU REMEMBER ONE THING,
REMEMBER THIS:
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause)
OH, CHEER UP, HAROLD.
I DIDN'T KNOW A SUBMARINE
WOULD BE THAT EXPENSIVE,
NOT EVEN A RUSSIAN ONE.
WAY OUT OF OUR PRICE RANGE.
FINANCIAL CONSTRAINTS
HAVE FORCED ME, UNFORTUNATELY,
TO CANCEL THE ENTIRE
SUBMARINE PROJECT.
JUNIOR'S WIFE HAD ALREADY MADE
A FAKE SHARK.
SHE'LL TURN THAT INTO
A BEAN-BAG LOVE SEAT WITH FINS.
(Audience laughing)
OLD MAN SEDGWICK HAS SENT BACK
THE MERMAID COSTUMES...
EXCEPT ONE.
(Audience laughing)
WE'VE CANCELLED ALL THE LUMBER
AND I GOT HAROLD TO CANCEL
THE 15 TRUCKLOADS OF CEMENT.
I'M GONNA DO
A BOAT THING--
UNCLE RED, UH...
YOU DIDN'T SAY "CANCEL
THE 15 TRUCKLOADS OF CEMENT."
YES, I DID, HAROLD.
NO, NO, NO,
WHAT YOU SAID WAS...
(Crying)
OH, I GOTTA CANCEL
THOSE TRUCKLOADS OF CEMENT.
ONCE THEY GET HERE...
(Trucks
backing up)
OHHHH...
(Signals
beeping)
THEY'RE HERE.
THERE'S 15 TRUCKLOADS
OF CEMENT--
I SAID HAVE A CHESS CLUB!
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL,
WITH ANOTHER FEATURE
ON CONTROLLING YOUR ANIMALS.
AND SPEAKING OF ANIMALS,
COME ON IN HERE, RED.
(Laughing)
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR EAR?
OH, NOTHING SERIOUS.
THEY SAY CHICKENS CAN'T FLY,
BUT THEY SURE CAN JUMP.
WOW.
EVER BEEN PECKED IN THE EAR?
NOT BY A CHICKEN.
OOH.
YOU KNOW, RED, 19 YEARS,
11 MONTHS, AND 2 DAYS,
AND I'M RETIRED.
WOW!
I'M GONNA FAX A PICTURE
OF MY BUTT TO MY BOSS
AND HE CAN KISS IT.
TODAY, WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT CONTROLLING SKUNKS.
I JUST SAID THAT.
ALL RIGHT, GO ON.
NEVER TRY TO CATCH A SKUNK
WITH YOUR BARE HANDS.
THEY'VE GOT SHARP TEETH
AND THEY'LL CLAMP DOWN
ON YOUR ACHILLES TENDON
AND YOU'RE THERE FOR THE DAY.
YOU GOTTA USE A TRAP.
MAKE SURE IT'S A PROPER TRAP.
DON'T LASSO THEM OR SCOOP THEM
INTO A GREEN GARBAGE BAG
OR STARTLE THEM INTO HAVING
A HEART ATTACK.
BOO!
BECAUSE THEY'LL JUST...
THAT'S RIGHT,
AND TRUST ME -- I KNOW.
THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE
TO AVOID GETTING SQUIRTED.
(Squirting)
SEE?
SO MAKE SURE
THAT IT'S A PROPER TRAP.
A PROPER TRAP
WILL PUT THE TAIL DOWN.
THAT PRETTY MUCH
PUTS THEM OUT OF BUSINESS.
RIGHT, I SEE.
THEN YOU JUST
TAKE 'EM SOMEPLACE,
SAY, LIKE YOUR BOSS'S HOUSE,
AND LET 'EM GO.
OK, WHY DON'T YOU TELL
OUR VIEWERS
HOW CAN THEY TELL IF THEY HAVE
A SKUNK AROUND THEIR PLACE?
REALLY, RED?
YEAH, JUST... YEAH.
SAY YOUR NOSE FALLS OFF, RED.
I SEE, YEAH.
LOOK FOR HOLES
AROUND THE FOUNDATION.
OH, LIKE THAT THERE?
LIKE THAT HOLE YOU GOT THERE
BY YOUR HOUSE, THERE.
(Skunk
panting)
PRETTY MUCH EXACTLY LIKE THAT.
OH!
(Skunk
panting)
OH, BOY.
ANOTHER SUPER DAY.
(Squirting)
HI, RANGER GORD AGAIN.
PEOPLE ASK ME,
"DOES LIVING ALONE IN A FOREST
FOR 16 YEARS DRIVE YOU CRAZY?"
NO, NOT IF YOU FIND WAYS
TO KEEP YOURSELF BUSY.
(Laughing)
FOOLED YA!
WELCOME TO
HAROLD'S HANDICRAFTS,
WHERE CRAFTY HANDS
MAKE "HANDI-CRAFTS"!
OK, TODAY,
LET'S WEAVE A WOOL BLANKET.
WAHHH!
NOW, IF YOU CAN TIE A KNOT,
YOU CAN WEAVE A WOOL BLANKET.
IF YOU CAN'T TIE A KNOT,
YOU PROBABLY MAJORED IN FILM
OR SOMETHING.
OK, SO, UH, FIRST, AS ALWAYS,
STEP ONE.
WAH-HA-HA!
YOU GOTTA FIND A STICK
AND THEN...
(Laughing nervously)
ALL RIGHT.
YES, AND THEN STEP TWO...
YOU TAKE THE WOOL
AND WRAP IT AROUND THE STICK.
AS I SAID, YOU JUST
TIE YOURSELF A KNOT AND...
YOU TIE A KNOT!
THAT'S THE BEGINNING OF
THE ORIGIN OF THE WOOL BLANKET.
THEN YOU CAN MAKE ONE OF THESE.
WHAT YOU DO FROM THIS POINT IS
YOU HAVE TO TIE
ALL THE THREADS TOGETHER
IN A WEAVE-LIKE PATTERN.
AND THEN IT'S, UH...
YOU JUST...
GIDDYUP!
YOU TAKE THEM
AND YOU, UH, TIE THEM TOGETHER
BACK AND FORTH,
BACK AND FORTH...
(Laughing)
AND YOU'RE CREATED
YOUR VERY OWN WOOL BLANKET.
(Applause)
(Cheering)
JUST REMOVE THE STICK
AND YOU'VE CREATED
A PIONEER-LIKE BLANKET,
FROM THE AUTHENTIC WOOL
DOWN TO THE AUTHENTIC LABEL.
OH, BOY.
(Audience laughing)
THAT'S JUST A TOUCH
I LIKE TO ADD MYSELF.
THE BEST PART IS,
YOU CREATED IT YOURSELF.
QUITE AN ACCOMPLISHMENT, IF
YOU JUST TIE WOOL INTO A KNOT.
HOW ABOUT PULLING WOOL
OVER PEOPLE'S EYES, HAROLD?
(Audience laughing)
LOOK, UNCLE RED TRIED
AND HE COULDN'T DO IT!
OH, YOU!
(Laughing)
(Applause)
WELL, SURE ENOUGH, THERE'S
15 CEMENT TRUCKS OUT THERE
AND THEY'RE NOT FULL
OF CONCRETE.
THEY'RE FULL
OF QUICK-DRYING CONCRETE.
IN TWO HOURS,
IT'S GONNA BE HARDER
THAN MOOSE THOMPSON'S FOREHEAD.
I WENT TO THE DRIVERS.
I SAID, "WE MADE A MISTAKE.
"YOU GUYS CAN TAKE IT BACK.
"WOULD THAT BE ALL RIGHT?"
I THOUGHT THEY'D BE UPSET,
BUT THEY LAUGHED.
OH, THEY LAUGHED!
THEY LAUGHED LIKE THAT,
SO THEN
WE
LAUGHED.
WE LAUGHED, WE LAUGHED.
BUT THEN WE STOPPED LAUGHING.
BUT NOT THEM.
THEY KEPT ON LAUGHING
AND LAUGHING...
I FIGURED OUT WHY.
IF WE DON'T TAKE THE CONCRETE
AND IT HARDENS IN THOSE TRUCKS,
WE HAVE TO PAY FOR THE CONCRETE
AND
NEW TRUCKS.
A LOT OF MEN, WHEN THEY SEE
A PROBLEM LIKE THIS,
TRY TO FIND A SOLUTION.
I PREFER TO FIGURE OUT
WHOSE FAULT IT IS
AND THEN LET THEM
TAKE CARE OF IT.
(Audience laughing)
HEY, HANDYMAN,
THIS HERE IS COPPER PIPE.
YOU CONNECT THAT BY PUTTING
SOLDER ON THERE WITH A TORCH.
DOESN'T WORK SO WELL
WITH THE PLASTIC PIPE.
(Red): WITH ALL THAT CEMENT
LYING AROUND,
WE'RE GONNA USE THIS WEEK'S
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL"
TO DO SOMETHING
WITH SOME CONCRETE.
BILL'S MAKING
A CONCRETE COFFEE TABLE.
FIRST, HE HAS TO MAKE
THE FORM FOR IT.
THIS IS OUR VERSION
OF PETER, PAUL AND MARY... OH!
"IF I HAD A HEADACHE"...
OH, YOU'RE FINE, HAROLD.
ANYWAY, HE WANTS TO CUT THAT--
HE'S GOT THE ELECTRIC CHAINSAW.
I'M A LITTLE BIT CAUTIOUS
ABOUT--
YOU SAFETY-CONSCIOUS PEOPLE,
HERE'S SOMETHING NOT TO DO.
DON'T GET ON TOP OF THE WOOD
UNLESS YOU'RE SURE
IT CAN SUPPORT YOU.
THE BLADE'S DIGGING IN.
HAROLD'S WRAPPED
AROUND THE CORD.
AWAY THEY--
I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
HOW THIS WAS HELPING US.
THEN I'M THINKING MAYBE
THEY'VE CHANGED THEIR MIND.
THEY'RE GONNA BUILD
A THEME PARK
AND THIS IS THE MAIN RIDE.
I SAY, "HEY, BOYS,
RIDE'S OVER."
I BET YOU 10 BUCKS
HAROLD WANTS TO GO AGAIN.
I'LL BE UP TO MY ELBOWS
IN YOU-KNOW-WHAT.
(Red): WE GOT THE FORM DONE.
WAITING FOR BILL TO COME BACK.
WOW! WELL, I'M IMPRESSED.
THAT CREDIT CARD IS WORKING
AT THE RENTAL STORE, OBVIOUSLY.
WE GOT THE SHOVELS
AND CEMENT'S GONNA COME DOWN.
OH, I SEE -- OK, OK.
WE'RE GONNA GET IT
WITH THE SHOVELS.
I'M NOT SURE BILL'S AWARE
OF HOW THE EQUIPMENT WORKS.
THERE WE GO, THERE WE GO.
SOMETHING'S STARTING TO HAPPEN.
WE'RE GONNA CARRY IT BY SHOVEL.
I THOUGHT A WHEELBARROW...
WELL, THAT'S JUST ME.
THAT'S FINE, THAT'S FINE.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
IT'S AMAZING
HOW HEAVY THAT STUFF IS.
THERE'S A LOT OF WATER IN THAT,
AND STONE AND SAND AND...
OH, BOY, YOU MAY WANT
TO SLOW THAT...
JUST BACK THAT OFF.
OK, THAT'S FINE.
ALL RIGHT, WE GOT IT.
WE'LL GET THAT OFF.
WE'RE FINE -- GET THAT, HAROLD.
MAYBE A BIGGER SHOVEL
MIGHT HAVE BEEN A PLAN.
OH, BOY, CAN YOU NOT--
IS THERE A DIMMER?
THERE'S A DIMMER RIGHT THERE.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE FINE.
THERE WE GO -- BIGGER SHOVEL.
BIGGER SHOVEL -- THERE WE GO.
BOY, THAT IS HEAVY.
AND THEN WE GOT THE IDEA,
KIND OF A BUCKET BRIGADE THING.
IT'S SEEN IN SOME
OF THE EARLIER
"SWISS FAMILY ROBINSON"
SPECIALS.
OH, BOY, HAROLD,
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE--
I DON'T THINK HAROLD
TOTALLY UNDERSTANDS THE POINT
OF CO-OPERATION.
THAT'S OBVIOUS EVERY EPISODE.
WHAT'S BILL DOING?
SORRY, BILL.
WE HADN'T NOTICED THAT.
WE WERE KIND OF TIED UP.
WE WERE DUMPING THE CEMENT
RIGHT ON...
APPARENTLY RIGHT ON BILL.
YOU CAN ONLY WATCH
SO MANY "I LOVE LUCY"'s,
IT STARTS TO RUB OFF.
GOT OUR TABLE DONE.
WE HEARD SOMETHING
COMING FROM-- WE REALIZED...
OH, BY GOLLY!
BILL'S STUCK INSIDE--
WE HAVE CEMENTED BILL IN--
WE CEMENTED-- OH, BOY!
OH, GOOD, THAT WAS GOOD.
YEAH, HE'S FINE.
THAT'S GREAT.
WELL, THERE WE GO.
BILL AS A TABLE -- I LIKE IT.
HOWDY, THIS IS RANGER GORD,
REMINDING YOU
WHERE THERE'S SMOKE,
THERE'S FIRE,
AND WHERE THERE'S FIRE,
THERE'S RANGER GORD,
AND WHERE THERE'S RANGER GORD,
THERE'S...
... NOTHING.
THERE'S NOBODY.
NOTHING!
OH, NO!
(Can falling over)
OH, MY TOILET!
WELL, WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
YOU'D HAVE FUN WITH CONCRETE?
CONCRETE BEACH,
CONCRETE HEDGE,
CONCRETE PETS...
(Audience laughing)
HAVE YOU FINISHED
THAT WOODEN FORM
TO POUR YOUR CHESSBOARD?
FINISHED HAMMERING
THE LAST NAIL
NOT FIVE MINUTES AGO.
ALL I GOTTA DO
IS POUR THE CONCRETE.
WE SAVED YOU
THE LAST TRUCKLOAD.
ONE TRUCKLOAD'S LEFT?
I NEED SIX FOR THE CHESSBOARD
AND THREE FOR THE PLAYERS.
I GUESS WE'LL HAVE TO ORDER
ANOTHER 15 TRUCKLOADS
FOR TOMORROW.
I GOT DIBS ON THE FIRST FIVE.
HOW DID THAT CONCRETE
SKATEBOARD RAMP TURN OUT?
NOT GOOD, NO.
IT'S HARD TO GET CEMENT
TO FLOW UPHILL.
YEAH, YEAH.
OH...
(Grunting)
AHHH...
WHAT I LEARNED IS I SHOULD POUR
FROM THE TOP NEXT TIME.
YEAH.
(Possum squeal)
IT'S MEETING TIME.
WELL, YOU GO,
HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN
IN 20 MINUTES.
I OUGHT TO BE THERE ABOUT THEN.
WOW.
I'M ON MY WAY.
ALL RIGHT,
THEN, GO.
AWAY YOU GO.
OFF YOU GO,
THEN.
BANG!
OFF YOU GO.
BEN JOHNSON
ON A SENIORS' TOUR.
(Laughing and applause)
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M GONNA BE BRINGING
TWO GAS CANS OF CEMENT.
GONNA HAVE MATCHING HEADSTONES.
I'LL BE NO-LEAD,
YOU'LL BE PREMIUM.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND...
(Possum squeal)
... FLASH...
UNTIL WE MEET AGAIN,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): OK, ALL RISE.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS, MORITATI