[breezy folk music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> AND NOW IT'S TIME AGAIN
FOR THE SHOW THAT ASKS THE
QUESTION: THERE MUST BE MORE
THAN ONE WAY TO SKIN A CAT,
BUT THEY'RE ALL AGAINST
HIS WILL.
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO HAVE SEEN
THE SHOW BEFORE, LET'S JUST
SAY FORGIVE AND FORGET, OKAY?
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW,
STARRING THAT OSCAR-WINNING
RABBIT,
YOUR FRIEND AND MY UNCLE--
AND BELIEVE ME,
THERE'S A BIG DIFFERENCE--
MR. RED GREEN!
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW,
AND THANK YOU TO HAROLD
FOR THAT WARM AND HEARTFELT
INTRODUCTION.
>> LOVE YOU, BABE.
LET'S DO LUNCH.
[laughs]
>> NO, LET'S DO SHOW, HAROLD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> HAD A LITTLE BIT OF A TO-DO
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
MOOSE THOMPSON HAS BEEN
LOOKIN' FOR WORK EVER SINCE
THE PAINT FACTORY BLEW UP,
EVEN THOUGH HE DID APOLOGIZE.
HE SEES AN AD IN THE
NEWSPAPER FOR A MALE DANCER.
NOW, MOOSE IS NOT MUCH OF A
DANCER, BUT HE MORE THAN MAKES
UP FOR IT IN THE MALE
DEPARTMENT.
>> EXCUSE ME, UNCLE RED?
>> OH, I FORGOT ABOUT YOU.
THIS HERE IS MY PRODUCER AND
MY DIRECTOR,
AND BY A CRUEL STROKE OF FATE,
MY NEPHEW.
EVERY TIME I START A STORY
AND HE THINKS IT'S BORING,
HE JUST GETS OUT OF IT BY
FLIPPING SOME THINGS ON HIS
FLIM-FLAMMER THERE.
>> IT'S A SWITCHER CONTROL VOX.
IT ALLOWS ME TO GO FROM ONE
SEGMENT OF THE SHOW INTO THE
NEXT, YOU KNOW,
IN CASE I FIND IT, UH--UH,
BORING OR OFFENSIVE OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
IT ALSO ALLOWS ME TO DO THIS...
PRETTY NEAT THING, HUH?
>> WELL, I WANT TO JUST
CONTINUE MY STORY ON THE MALE
DANCER THING.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> NOTHING OFFENSIVE OR TO BE
ASHAMED ABOUT NAKED BODIES
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> OH, NO. NO, NOT AT ALL.
I GOT NOTHING AGAINST NAKED
BODIES.
UNLESS, OF COURSE IT'S, LIKE,
DURING DINNER.
JEEPERS CREEPERS, I--
NAKED BODIES ARE OKAY.
I'M AS LIBERAL AS THE NEXT GUY.
YOU KNOW, WELL, UNLESS, OF
COURSE, YOU'RE THE NEXT GUY.
THEN I'M WAY MORE LIBERAL,
'CAUSE I ENJOY A NAKED MAN
AS MUCH AS THE NEXT PERSON.
NO, I DIDN'T MEAN THAT!
I DIDN'T--OH!
I SAID THAT?
THAT WAS SO WRONG.
UH...
[laughter]
[strumming acoustic guitar]
>> THERE ONCE WAS A STORY
A LONG TIME AGO
A LEGEND THAT ONLY
THE POSSUMS KNOW
POSSUMS ARE SMART
AND FUN TO THROW
AS LONG AS YOU YELL
"LOOK OUT BELOW"
WITH A WHIFF AND ALL
WHIFF AND ALL
WHIFF AND ALL WOMBAT
WHIFF AND ALL, WHIFFING
DID YOU CATCH A WHIFF
OF THAT?
>> [laughs]
>> both: WITH A WHIFF
AND ALL
WHIFF AND ALL
>> WHIFF ALL WOM--
WOMBAT.
>> NO, YOU DON'T SAY WOMBAT
THAT TIME.
>> OH.
>> THIS WEEK ON
"HANDYMAN CORNER,"
WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU HOW TO
TAKE SOMETHING AND IMPROVE
ON IT.
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO IS, GONNA
SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE A PORTABLE
PHONE FOR UNDER $40.
SOUNDS CRAZY, DOESN'T IT?
HERE'S WHAT YOU'RE GONNA NEED:
A WALL-MOUNTED PHONE,
AN OLD BACKPACK,
A GARDEN HOSE SPOOL,
AND A BUNCH OF TELEPHONE CABLE.
NOW, IF YOU WANT TO GO GET THAT
STUFF, I'LL JUST WAIT.
[laughter]
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, THE FIRST STEP IS TO REMOVE
THE CANVAS FROM THE BACKPACK.
[saw buzzing]
IF YOU'RE CAREFUL HOW YOU DO
THIS, YOU CAN END UP WITH
ENOUGH CANVAS TO MAKE YOURSELF
A DANDY LIL' SUN HAT.
[saw buzzing]
ALL RIGHT, AS YOU CAN SEE,
I'M JUST PUTTING THE FINISHING
TOUCHES ON ATTACHING THE GARDEN
HOSE REEL TO THE BACKPACK
USING THE HANDYMAN SECRET
WEAPON: DUCT TAPE.
NOW WHAT WE DO IS TAKE OUR
TELEPHONE WIRE AND BEGIN
WINDING IT ONTO THE HOSE REEL.
NOW, THE AMOUNT OF WIRE YOU PUT
ON HERE, THAT WILL BE
DETERMINED BY HOW PORTABLE YOU
WANT THE PHONE TO BE.
IF IT'S JUST FOR AROUND THE
HOUSE, 50 FEET WILL PROBABLY DO.
20 FEET IF YOU LIVE IN A NEW
SUBDIVISION,
OR IF YOU WANT THE RUN OF THE
WHOLE NEIGHBORHOOD, I SUGGEST
YOU PUT ON A COUPLE HUNDRED
FEET.
AS YOU CAN SEE, I'M JUST
FINISHING ATTACHING THE PHONE
TO MY BODY WITH THE DUCT TAPE,
AND WE'RE DONE.
NO MORE RUNNING TO THE PHONE,
BECAUSE WITH THIS RIG ON,
BELIEVE ME, YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
RUNNING.
[phone rings]
I'LL GET IT.
HELLO?
COULD YOU JUST HANG ON A
MINUTE, PLEASE?
YEAH.
THIS SOUNDS LIKE AN IMPORTANT
CALL, SO UNTIL NEXT TIME,
REMEMBER,
IF WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
YEAH?
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
THAT WAS ME.
I ORDERED THE EIGHT-SLICER
WITH THE DOUBLE PEPPERONI.
YEAH.
I'M ON MY WAY OVER TO GET IT
RIGHT NOW.
HOW'S MY VOICE SOUND?
I MADE THIS PHONE.
YEAH.
MADE IT MYSELF.
NO, I'M NOT KIDDIN'.
WHOA!
[clattering]
HELLO, UH, 911?
COULD YA--COULD YA SEND AN
AMBULANCE?
JUST FOLLOW THE WIRE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE
WILDLIFE ADVENTURES AMONGST THE
FURRY BEASTS OF THE WOODS.
>> I THINK HE'S BACK TO THE
STORY ABOUT MOOSE THOMPSON
BEING A NUDE DANCER.
[laughter]
>> I WAS GOIN' THROUGH THE
SCRAPBOOK LAST NIGHT,
AND I THOUGHT I SAW SOME
PICTURES OF SOME OLD
CELEBRITIES, YOU KNOW, GUYS THAT
I'VE KNOWN AND WORKED WITH.
>> OH, THEY'D HAVE TO BE OLD.
>> WELL, THEY WERE NOT OLD IN
THE SENSE OF OLD, BUT JUST--
>> OH, OKAY.
>> I MEAN, THEY'VE BEEN
CELEBRITIES A LONG TIME.
>> RIGHT. EXACTLY. YEAH.
>> SLIM WHITMAN.
>> KING.
>> WHAT CAN YOU SAY?
>> [howls]
I CAN SAY THAT, 'CAUSE HE DOES
THAT WHEN HE SINGS.
>> HE DOES THAT?
>> HE YODELS.
>> OH, AND YOU SHOULD SEE THE
ACROBATICS HE DOES WITH HIS
GUITAR AND EVERYTHING,
AND HE GETS THE HOLE RIGHT
IN THE CENTER AND JUST DOES--
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
>> GETTIN' BETWEEN THE STRINGS
IS THE TOUGH PART.
>> WELL, IT'S NOT EASY.
>> NO. NO.
>> THAT'S WHY THEY CALL
HIM SLIM.
>> THAT'S RIGHT. YEAH.
>> AND THAT GUY MITCHELL--
OR, GUY MADISON.
>> OH.
>> YOU KNOW, GUY MITCHELL--
NO, GUY MADISON
AND WILD BILL HICKOK.
>> YEAH.
>> REMEMBER HIM?
>> WELL, I KNEW THE STORIES.
YOU KNEW HIM, WILD BILL HICKOK?
>> WELL, YEAH. WELL, NO.
I--I--NO.
I KNEW GUY MADISON.
>> MADISON WHO PLAYED WILD--
>> YEAH. WELL, YEAH.
HIS GUN'S BACKWARDS.
HE'D SAY, "SHOOT STRAIGHT
AND KEEP YOUR GUNS BACKWARDS."
>> THAT'S SO HE CAN, LIKE,
SHOOT PEOPLE SNEAKIN' UP
ON HIM.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
HE HAD A TERRIBLE ACCIDENT
THOUGH.
HE'S--THE DARN THINGS WENT OFF.
HE BLEW HIS BUNS OFF AT THE
WRAP PARTY.
>> HMM.
>> WE'VE ALL DONE THAT, EH?
>> YEAH.
>> "IT IS WINTER.
THE WINDOWS ARE FROSTED OVER.
NOTHING CAN BE SEEN THROUGH
THIS WHITE PATCHWORK OF ICE
CRYSTALS.
THE ENTIRE WINTER WORLD IS
BLOCKED FROM VIEW,
BUT DON'T WORRY.
YOU KNOW THIS ROAD LIKE THE
BACK OF YOUR HAND."
SO ANYWAY,
MOOSE GOES DOWN AND APPLIES
FOR THIS JOB AS A MALE DANCER.
IT WAS AT THE BAMBOO BAM-BAM
CLUB.
HE FIGURED HE'D BE TEACHIN'
WIDOWS HOW TO FOXTROT.
SO THEY TOLD HIM TO GO HOME
AND COME BACK AT 8:00 DRESSED
UP IN A COSTUME, LIKE AN INDIAN
OR A POLICEMAN OR ONE OF THE
VILLAGE PEOPLE.
SO MOOSE FIGURES, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE HE'LL SEE SOME KIND OF--
LIKE A COSTUME BALL OR
SOMETHING.
SO HE'S LOOKIN' AROUND THE
LODGE, AND HE FINDS AN OLD
MOOSE DECOY THAT WE USED ONE
TIME TO DRAW A MOOSE OUT DURING
MATING SEASON.
THAT'S ANOTHER STORY.
SO ANYWAY, HE GETS THE FRONT
HALF OF THE MOOSE COSTUME ON,
BUT HE NEEDS SOMEBODY TO BE
THE OTHER HALF OF THE MOOSE,
SO THAT'S MOOSE WITH A SMALL
"M," NOT A BIG "M,"
AND BUSTER HADFIELD SAYS THAT
HE'D BE THE BACK END OF THE
MOOSE.
BOY, TALK ABOUT TYPE-CASTING.
>> UNCLE RED.
I JUST WANT TO REMIND YOU THAT,
YOU KNOW, SOME OF OUR VIEWERS
HAVE CHILDREN AND TASTE,
AND MAYBE THEY WON'T APPRECIATE
THIS RIVALED ADVENTURE.
>> WELL, I CAN'T HELP THAT,
HAROLD.
>> I CAN.
>> JACK!
JACK, COME ON UP HERE!
I KNOW YOU'RE DOWN THERE, JACK!
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> WELL, NOTHING.
I JUST THOUGHT WE'D DROP BY,
SEE HOW IT'S GOIN', YOU KNOW?
>> OH. OH!
UH, LET ME GUESS.
>> YEAH?
>> WESTERN CIVILIZATION HAS
FINALLY COLLAPSED AND NOW
ALL THE SMUG KNOW-IT-ALLS
WHO LAUGHED AT ME FOR COMIN'
UP HERE TO LIVE WANT ME TO TAKE
THEM IN AND GIVE THEM SHELTER
AND SEE THEM THROUGH THE COMING
DARK AGES.
>> WELL, UH, NO.
WE WERE JUST ON OUR WAY TO THE
GO-KARTS ON 89,
AND WE THOUGHT WE'D JUST
DROP BY.
THAT'S ALL.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> DO YOU NEED ANYTHING, JACK?
>> I HAVE EVERYTHING I NEED,
RED.
I'M A SURVIVOR.
>> OKAY.
>> AND I DIDN'T JUST RUSH INTO
THIS IN A BLIND PANIC.
>> OKAY.
>> I'LL TELL YOU THAT MUCH.
YOU KNOW, I SPENT FOUR WEEKENDS
PLANNING THIS.
I EVEN DREW MAPS AND BROUGHT
HEAVY SHOES.
>> ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
BUT HAVE YOU GOT ENOUGH FOOD?
>> I HAVE EVERYTHING I NEED.
OKAY?
OH, I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE SAYIN'.
>> YEAH?
>> FORGET IT.
FORGET IT.
I HAVE NOTHING YOU WOULD LIKE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYIN'?
I GROW EVERYTHING I NEED TO
SURVIVE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> EXCEPT MILK.
>> OH, YEAH.
YEAH, BUT WHAT DO YOU GROW?
>> WELL, MUSHROOMS MOSTLY,
YOU KNOW, BUT I'VE ORDERED SOME
SEEDS, AND THEY SHOULD BE HERE
SOON.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, THEY SAID ALLOW SIX TO
EIGHT WEEKS FOR DELIVERY,
BUT I'M HOPIN' THE WORLD
DOESN'T END, YOU KNOW,
BEFORE THEN, 'CAUSE I'VE
ORDERED ENOUGH SEEDS TO SUSTAIN
A SMALL COLONY THROUGH THE
COMING DARK AGES.
>> YOU'VE ORDERED A LOT OF
SEEDS THEN.
>> OH, BELIEVE IT.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, I WON A BICYCLE AND A
SLOT CAR RACING SET.
SURE, AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHEN YOUR CURRENCY SYSTEM
COLLAPSES, YOU SEE,
I'M GONNA TAKE THOSE SLOT CARS,
TRADE 'EM FOR A COW,
AND THEN I'LL HAVE FRESH MEAT
AND MILK.
>> WELL, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, OKAY, JACK.
IF THERE'S NOTHING THAT YOU
NEED, YOU KNOW--
>> NOTHING.
I DON'T NEED ANYTHING.
>> ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
>> OH, WELL, AN EXTENSION CORD.
>> AN EXTENSION CORD?
I THINK WE HAVE ONE IN THE
TRUCK.
UH, WHAT'S IT FOR?
>> NOTHING.
SOMETHING, BUT--SURVIVAL.
I CAN'T TELL YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
FINE, FINE, FINE.
JUST TELL ME THIS, WILL YOU?
WILL YOU BE ABLE TO GIVE IT
BACK TO US, YOU KNOW,
AFTER THE CURRENCY THING
COLLAPSES?
>> SURE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I MEAN, NO!
OH, DARN.
>> JACK?
[strumming acoustic guitar]
>> STOP THE WHALE HUNT NOW
PUT YOUR HARPOONS AWAY
OR ELSE
STOP HUNTING WHALES
THAT'S WHAT YOU SHOULD DO
AND AS SOON AS HAROLD AND I
CATCH ONE
WE'LL QUIT TOO
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, UNCLE RED,
THIS IS SO EXCITING.
THIS IS GREAT!
WE GOT SOMETHING REALLY
DIFFERENT ON THE MAIL CALL
SEGMENT TODAY.
THERE'S A LITTLE BIT OF A SPIN
ON IT.
SOMETHING JUST A TAD DIFFERENT.
WE GOT A LETTER FROM A KID!
THIS COULD BE HUGE!
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
WOULDN'T THAT BE GREAT?
THIS IS--OH, THIS IS VERY
EXCITING.
>> JUST READ THE LETTER, HAROLD.
>> OH, YEAH.
YEAH, OKAY.
THAT'S WHAT I MEANT.
I MEAN, I WASN'T GONNA CHANGE
A LOT OF THINGS.
JUST--IT'S HUGE.
WHY DON'T I READ THE LETTER
ALREADY?
"DEAR MR. GREEN,
I LIKE YOU.
YOU DO FUNNY THINGS.
I LIKE YOU WHEN YOU HURT
YOURSELF AND WHEN BILL SMITH
HURTS HIMSELF,
AND WHEN YOUR NEPHEW, HAROLD,
HURTS HIMSELF."
[laughs]
THIS IS CUTE.
LOOK AT THAT.
HE SPELLS NEPHEW WITH AN "F."
>> JUST ONE.
THAT IS CUTE.
>> "I WANT TO BE JUST LIKE YOU
WHEN I GROW UP.
CAN I HAVE YOUR AUTOGRAPH?"
>> NO, I'M SORRY, HAROLD.
I'M USING IT.
EH, YOU WANT TO BE LIKE ME,
EH?
WELL, YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT THAT
EASY HOSTING YOUR OWN
TELEVISION SHOW.
IF IT WAS, HAROLD HERE WOULD
BE DOING IT.
>> OH, BOY.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
>> AND YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
EVEN IF YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
STUFF,
AS YOU KNOW, YOU GOTTA GET
YOUR EDUCATION.
I MEAN, I USE ALL THOSE SUBJECTS
EVERY DAY:
ADDING, SUBTRACTING, SOCIAL
STUDIES, METAL SHOP,
GYM, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE YOU NEED THE LETTERS,
SEE, OR YOU CAN'T READ THE
CUE CARDS,
AND THEN YOU HAVE TO RELY ON
YOUR MEMORY.
I GUESS THAT'S ABOUT IT.
WHERE WAS I, DO YOU KNOW?
>> YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT
EDUCATION.
IT WAS VERY EXCITING TO SEE
YOU TAKE A STAND ON THAT,
UNCLE RED.
WE SHOULD ALSO MENTION TO OUR
VIEWERS ABOUT COLLEGE AND
UNIVERSITY.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THAT, HAROLD.
I THINK COLLEGE EDUCATION IS
A DRAWBACK FOR BEING A TV STAR.
MAKES YOU THINK ABOUT THINGS.
AS FOR UNIVERSITY, WELL, THAT'S
JUST A BUNCH OF EGGHEADS
WALKIN' AROUND BETWEEN THE
TREES SAYIN' THINGS LIKE,
"HENCE" AND "THEREFORE."
>> OH, NO, UNCLE RED.
IF I MIGHT JUST STEP BACK A
STEP OR TWO,
IN MY OPINION,
EDUCATION IS VERY IMPORTANT.
WE SHOULD BE STRESSING TO OUR
VIEWERS TO GO ON TO COLLEGE.
LEARN AS MUCH AS YOU CAN.
THAT'S MY OPINION.
>> WELL, HOW CAN WE DO THAT,
HAROLD?
I DIDN'T GO TO COLLEGE AND
YOU DIDN'T GO COLLEGE,
AND LOOK AT US.
>> WE'RE SELF-MADE MEN.
>> OH, SURE, BLAME ME.
THIS WEEK ON "ADVENTURES WITH
BILL," WE'RE GONNA DEAL WITH
A PROBLEM THAT A LOT OF PEOPLE
HAVE IN THE WOODS,
AND THAT IS MOSQUITOES.
THEY DON'T BOTHER ME.
MIND YOU, I HAVE FLIES IN MY
PANTS...[chuckles]
AS YOU SEE, BILL HAS A REAL
PROBLEM WITH THEM.
THEY SEEM TO JUST--THERE ARE
PEOPLE LIKE THIS.
THEY JUST SEEM TO GO FOR 'EM.
QUITE A FEW OF THEM GOING FOR
BILL IN THIS PARTICULAR...
[laughter]
SO WHAT WE'RE TRYING TO DO
IS SHOW YOU SOME OF THE VARIOUS
WAYS THAT YOU CAN PROTECT
YOURSELF FROM THE MOSQUITOS
OR BLACK FLIES OR GNATS OR
PTERODACTYLS OR WHATEVER IT IS
THAT COMES AFTER YOU.
THIS IS TAKING SOME VINYL
SCREENING AND JUST WRAPPING
YOURSELF UP IN THE SCREEN,
LIKE MAKE YOURSELF INTO A
PORCH, REALLY.
THIS IS BILL'S OWN IDEA,
AND, YOU KNOW, YOU WANT TO GIVE
THAT A REAL GOOD TUG.
YOU COULD PROBABLY START HIM
UP LIKE A LAWN MOWER,
YOU KNOW?
[laughs]
I DON'T THINK THIS ONE IS
VERY EFFECTIVE.
THIS IS ANOTHER.
THIS IS A CONCOCTION MADE UP
OF LEMON JUICE AND HONEY,
I BELIEVE IT IS,
AND ACCORDING TO BILL'S
GRANDMOTHER,
I THINK SHE SAID,
THIS WORKS REAL WELL.
COME ON, SHE WAS COVERED WITH
BEE STINGS.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT WE DISCOVERED,
UNFORTUNATELY, WAS THAT THIS
ACTUALLY ATTRACTED THE
MOSQUITOS.
WELL, IT COULD HAVE BEEN WORSE.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN ON ME.
AND NOW THIS IS MORE OF THE
UNUSUAL APPROACH.
HE'S MADE HIMSELF COMPLETELY
AIRTIGHT WITH SOME TAPE AND
A BUG JACKET,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY, THERE'S
A MOSQUITO IN THERE WITH HIM.
NOW IT'S UP IN THE ARM.
UP IN THE ARM.
YOU CAN'T SEE IT, OF COURSE,
'CAUSE IT'S INSIDE.
IT'S OVER HERE NOW.
IT'S IN THE--IT'S IN THE JACKET,
SO I'LL--I THOUGHT I SAW IT
GO BY HIS FACE.
OH!
I GOT IT.
NOW, THIS IS THE CONVENTIONAL
METHOD.
THESE ARE THE AEROSOL CANS
WITH THE C.F.F--
C.F.F.--C.F.F'S IN THEM
THAT THEY'RE PUNCHIN' A HOLE
OVER THE ANTARCTIC.
WHO CARES, YOU KNOW?
ANYWAY, I'M GONNA BE USING
THE DOUBLE DOSE HERE ON BILL--
>> [yells]
>> YOU KNOW, THEY SAY THERE--
IT'S A NERVE GAS OR SOMETHING
THAT IT CAN ACTUALLY COMPLETELY
DESTROY THE HUMAN MIND,
WHICH I DIDN'T REALIZE BILL
WAS EQUIPPED WITH,
SO I WAS--THAT WAS A LITTLE
CRUEL, I THINK, ON MY PART,
BUT FUN.
SO BILL SHOWED US SOME OF THE
OTHERS.
THESE ARE VARIOUS HAND LOTIONS.
I THINK AVON HAS ONE AND SO ON.
THEY WORK REAL WELL IN THE
WOODS.
APPARENTLY THEY WORK AS WELL
AS ANY BUG REPELLANT.
AND WHAT YOU DO IS YOU JUST--YOU
HOLD OUT YOUR HAND THERE AND
JUST PUT IT ON THERE,
AND...
[makes squirting noise]
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THAT HAPPENED,
BUT I GUESS HE HAD IT SET FOR
SPRINKLE OR--ANYWAY, I MANAGED
TO CLEAN THE MOST OF IT OFF
MYSELF.
"IT IS WINTER.
MY SKIES SWOOSH UNDER ME.
MY FEET THROWN LEFT AND RIGHT.
I STRUGGLE TO STAY UPRIGHT.
I'M OUT OF CONTROL,
GOING TOO FAST.
FALLING, SLIPPING ON THE
EDGE OF DISASTER.
I HATE THESE T-BARS."
ALL RIGHT, AT THIS POINT
IN THE SHOW WE LIKE TO HAVE
A FEATURE WHERE YOU CAN KIND OF
GET TO KNOW HAROLD AND THE
YOUNG PEOPLE OF TODAY AND THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THE TWO.
>> PROGRESS.
FRIEND OR FOE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
SHOULD THINGS BE EXPECTED TO
GET BIGGER EVERY YEAR?
THINK ABOUT YOUR AUNT.
OH.
[laughs]
MAYBE THINGS ARE OKAY.
MAYBE THINGS SHOULD JUST STAY
THE SAME OR GET A LITTLE WORSE.
HEAR ME OUT, OKAY?
HEAR ME OUT.
OKAY, OKAY.
IMPLYING THAT THINGS SHOULD
GET BETTER EVERY YEAR SAYS THAT
MAYBE SOMETHING WAS BAD.
WELL, MAYBE IT WASN'T BAD.
MAYBE IT WAS GOOD.
MAYBE IT WAS SO GOOD THAT IT
COULD ONLY GET BAD.
THAT COULD HAPPEN, RIGHT?
THAT COULD HAPPEN, SURE.
AND I'VE LEARNED TO ACCEPT THAT.
I DON'T--I DON'T THINK THAT THE
OLDER GENERATION HAS, THOUGH.
NO, I DON'T THINK THAT AT ALL.
AND IF YOU AGREE WITH ME
THAT THAT COULD HAPPEN,
THAT THAT COULD HAPPEN IN
THIS LIFETIME,
WOULD YOU PLEASE PHONE MY
PARENTS AND TELL THEM THAT
"D" MINUS IS NOT TECHNICALLY
FAILING A COURSE?
PLEASE?
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE
FEATURES, MORE GUESTS,
AND THE SPIN-TINGLING
CONCLUSION OF THE STORY OF
MOOSE THOMPSON, DANCING BUFF.
>> THAT'S SHORT FOR "BUFFOON."
>> IF ANY OF YOU HAVE A
TEENAGER IN YOUR HOUSE,
I'D LIKE TO HAVE A WORD WITH
YOU,
UNLESS YOU'RE JERRY LEE LEWIS.
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
THAT YOU NEED TO REMEMBER
WITH A TEENAGER,
AND THAT IS THAT EVERY ONE OF
'EM NEEDS A SHOWER.
SOME OF 'EM ACTUALLY NEED
A COLD SHOWER.
SOME OF 'EM SHOULD BE DIPPED
IN ICE.
YOU WANT TO KEEP YOUR KID CLEAN,
AND YOU WANT TO KEEP 'EM
AT HOME.
YOU WANT TO KEEP YOUR KID OUT
OF TROUBLE WITH THE POLICE,
THE DERMATOLOGIST, AND THE
OBSTETRICIAN,
KEEP 'EM IN THE SHOWER AS
MUCH AS YOU CAN, AND MAKE
SURE THEY'RE ALONE.
WE'RE OUT HERE ON LOCATION WITH
MY GOOD BUDDY DOUGIE FRANKLIN
AND WHAT HAS TO BE MORE TRUCK
THAN I EVER THOUGHT POSSIBLE.
>> WELL, RED, YOU GOTTA HAVE
YOURSELF A BIG TRUCK
IF YOU'RE GONNA BE CRUSHIN'
CARS, AND, YOU KNOW,
CRUSHIN' CARS, IT'S FULFILLING.
IT'S A FULFILLING JOB,
BUT YOU GOTTA TAKE IT IN
PERSPECTIVE.
IT'S ONLY ONE SMALL FACET
OF THE TRULY--THE TRULY
BALANCED EXISTENCE,
AND IT SHOULD BE TREATED AS
SUCH.
>> WELL, NOW, THIS IS AN
EXCELLENT MESSAGE TO THE YOUNG
PEOPLE OF TODAY, DOUGIE.
DRIVING A MONSTER TRUCK IS
JUST NOT THE BE-ALL AND END-ALL.
>> NO.
OH, YOU CAN SAY THAT AGAIN,
RED.
I MEAN, THERE'S POLISHING HER.
POLISHING HER UP.
THERE'S ADDING STUFF TO HER,
LIKE THEM LIGHTS UP THERE.
THEY DIDN'T COME STOCK.
I PUT THOSE ON MYSELF.
>> AH. ALL RIGHT.
>> THEN, YOU KNOW--
THEN THERE'S PAYING FOR IT TOO.
THAT'S A CHALLENGE,
AND THE YOUNG FOLKS,
THEY NEED A CHALLENGE TODAY,
RED.
>> YEAH. YEAH, THEY DO.
YOU JUST KNOW SO DARN MUCH
ABOUT TRUCKS.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU TAKE HER APART SO MANY
TIMES AND PUT HER BACK TOGETHER,
AND IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE YOU FIGURE WHAT THEM
EXTRA PARTS IS YOU GOT
LEFT OVER,
AND, OR COURSE, YOU GOT TO TAKE
HER ALL APART AGAIN,
AND AFTER A WHILE, YOU KNOW
ALL ABOUT IT.
THAT DOES MAKES SENSE.
IT DOES MAKE SENSE.
>> ARE YOU GONNA START HER
UP FOR US?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA SAY
THAT.
>> I WAS GONNA SAY IT.
>> I LOVE THAT YOU'RE GONNA DO
THAT.
>> YOU KNOW, THERE'S A VIBRATION
GOING ON HERE TODAY.
ISN'T THERE?
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE PICKIN' UP
ON THE BEACH.
>> LOVE YOU, BIG GUY.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO, RED.
NOW, LOOK.
I'M GONNA START HER UP,
AND I'LL JUST TELL YOU AS
I START HER AND GO THROUGH
THE OPERATION OF HER.
OKAY?
>> WELL, THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FORWARD
TO THIS.
DOUGIE'S GONNA START THE--
START HER UP FOR US.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
>> GREAT.
>> WE GOT IGNITION.
>> ALL RIGHT. GO AHEAD.
[engine turns over]
>> ALL RIGHT NOW, RED.
YOU SEE HERE...
[engine rumbling loudly]
[laughter]
[voice drowned out by engine]
WELL, THAT'S ABOUT HER IN A
NUTSHELL, RED.
[laughter]
YOU'RE REALLY PRETTY WELL.
I DON'T THINK YOU NEED TO KNOW
ANY MORE TO TAKE THIS BABY OUT.
>> NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
IT'S DOUGIE FRANKLIN,
A MAN OF FEW WORDS.
>> I THINK MAYBE I SHOULD--
I HEARD--WHEN SHE WAS GOING
THERE, I SHUT HER DOWN.
I WAS HEARING A BIT OF A TICK.
I THINK I'LL JUST START HER UP
ONE MORE TIME.
>> START HER UP AGAIN?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
I MEAN, WE'VE HEARD--
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO--
>> WELL, IT'S FOR MY OWN
EDIFICATION.
YOU CAN CARRY ON WITH WHAT
YOU'RE DOING.
[engine grinding]
THE BATTERY'S GOING ON ME.
>> AH, THAT'S TOO BAD.
THERE IS A GOD.
SO ANYWAY,
I JUST WANTED TO FINISH OFF
ABOUT MOOSE AND BUSTER DOWN
AT THE BAM-BAM CLUB IN THE
MOOSE COSTUME.
THEY'RE DOWN THERE,
AND THEY COME OUT ON STAGE
IN THE FRONT OF ABOUT 400
REVVED-UP WOMEN WHO'VE PAID
20 BUCKS EACH,
AND IT ISN'T TO SEE COSTUMES.
THE STEREOS PUMPIN' AWAY THERE,
AND THE TWO OF THEM ARE
STAGGERING AROUND ON THE STAGE,
AND SUDDENLY MOOSE'S FOOT
CATCHES THE COSTUME AND RIPS
A BIG HOLE IN IT.
WELL, THE WOMEN GO WILD,
AND THEY'RE TRYING TO SEE WHY
THEY CALL HIM MOOSE WITH A BIG
"M," AND GOLLY,
THEY'RE GOING NUTS IN THERE,
AND THEY'RE HOLDIN' UP
$10 BILLS AND YELLING,
"TAKE IT OFF,"
AND SUDDENLY BUSTER AND MOOSE
REALIZE WHAT'S GOING ON,
BECAUSE THEY WERE SITTIN' IN
THOSE SAME SEATS A WEEK EARLIER
HOLDIN' UP $5 BILLS WHEN IT
WAS LADIES NIGHT.
IT SUDDENLY STRUCK THEM THAT
THIS FORM OF ENTERTAINMENT
WAS TAWDRY AND EXPLOITIVE
AND DARN PROFITABLE.
WELL, GOLLY.
THE TWO OF THEM COME HOME
FROM THERE AND THEY HAD
THEIR UNDERWEAR FULL OF MONEY,
WHICH NO BANK WILL TOUCH.
BUT ANYWAY IT WAS A GREAT TIME,
AND IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME,
AND THERE IS NOTHING IN MY
UNDERWEAR THAT WASN'T THERE
WHEN I LEFT THIS MORNING.
SO ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND--
>> HAROLD.
>> THAT SAYS IT ALL FOR ME,
AND THE REST OF US UP HERE AT
THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.