YOU KNOW HOW FRUSTRATING IT IS
WHEN YOU'RE WORKING ON A PROJECT
AND YOU GET THIRSTY,
BUT YOU'VE JUST FINISHED
OFF YOUR FAVOURITE BEVERAGE,
AND YOU REALLY DON'T WANT TO
BREAK YOUR CONCENTRATION
AND GO BACK INTO THE HOUSE TO
GET YOURSELF ANOTHER ONE?
WELL, HERE'S A SIMPLE SOLUTION.
ALL YOU NEED IS AN
ASSISTANT IN THE KITCHEN,
STANDING BY THE FRIDGE
AND A PRETTY GOOD LENGTH
OF EAVESTROUGH
AND A BELT SANDER.
PERFECT.
NOW ALL YOU DO IS PUT YOUR
SANDER BACK ON THERE,
FACING THE OTHER WAY,
AND YOU CAN SEND YOUR EMPTIES
BACK IN FOR RECYCLING.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
[ INAUDIBLE ]
OH, OH, OH.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
GOT A BIT OF AN EMERGENCY IN THE
AREA.
THERE'S A TOXIC CLOUD AROUND THE
WHOLE REGION.
THEY'VE IDENTIFIED THE SOURCE.
UH, STINKY PETERSON SET HIS
MATTRESS ON FIRE.
BUT UNTIL SHE DISSIPATES NOW,
WE'VE ALL GOTTA STAY PUT WITH
OUR DOORS AND WINDOWS LOCKED.
SO I'VE EVACUATED
THE WHOLE LODGE,
AND I HAD TO CANCEL
TONIGHT'S MEETING.
I'M KIND OF TRAPPED
HERE FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
CAN'T GO HOME.
NOBODY CAN COME HERE.
NOBODY TO TALK TO.
NOBODY TO LISTEN TO.
CABLE'S ALL PAID UP.
SHE'S GONNA BE ROUGH,
I'LL TELL YA.
I THOUGHT I HEARD SOMEONE.
OH, NO.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE, DALTON?
WELL, THE SAME
THING YOU ARE.
I CAN'T GO HOME.
I CAN'T GO TO WORK.
IT'S HELL.
[ LAUGHING ]
YOU KNOW, I WAS LOOKING FORWARD
TO HAVING THE WHOLE LODGE
TO MYSELF.
YEAH, WELL,
YOU KNOW, SO WAS I.
WELL, YOU SCREWED
THAT UP, DIDN'T YOU?
WELL, SO DID YOU!
ALL RIGHT, WE CAN
WORK THIS OUT.
TELL YOU WHAT,
YOU GET HALF THE LODGE,
I GET THE OTHER HALF.
SEE THAT TRUNK THERE?
YOU GET THE PART
THERE ON THAT SIDE.
I GET THE PART OVER
HERE ON THIS SIDE.
THAT TRUNK'S NOT
IN THE MIDDLE!
HOLY MACKEREL.
[ GRUNTING ]
Hey!
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY, RANGER GORD
WILL BE PLAYING FOR A YO-YO.
HOW IRONIC IS THAT?
OKAY, GORD, CLOSE --
UH, COVER YOUR EARS THERE.
OKAY, RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET RANGER GORD TO
SAY THIS WORD...
AND GO!
OKAY, GORD, THIS IS
SOMETHING YOU SIT ON,
BUT IT'S NOT A CHAIR.
A MUSKRAT.
NO, NO, UM --
OKAY, IT'S LIKE A CHAIR,
BUT IT HAS THREE LEGS
INSTEAD OF FOUR.
A REALLY TIPPY CHAIR.
OKAY, OKAY.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT A LOT OF
PEOPLE SIT ON IN BARS.
SAILORS?
OKAY, OKAY, SAY YOU'VE
GOT A GUY WHO'S
IN THE MAFIA,
AND HE'S BEEN ASKED TO TESTIFY
AGAINST THE GODFATHER.
HE'S A BLANK PIGEON.
YEAH, A CARRIER PIGEON.
CARRIER PIGEON?
EXTINCT.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
OKAY, GORD, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT A SPECIMEN IS?
YES, I A BELIEVE A SPECIMEN
IS AN ITALIAN ASTRONAUT.
(play on 'spaceman')
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU'RE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME, RED.
I'VE GOT NOTHING.
MY WITS ARE NO MATCH
FOR HIS STUPIDITY.
COME ON, RED.
IT'S A POOR WORKMAN
THAT BLAMES THE STOOLS.
I HEARD IT IN
THERE SOMEWHERE.
I HEARD IT!
COME ON, MIKE,
DINNER'S COMING.
STOP FOOLING AROUND.
I'M NOT FOOLING
AROUND, Mr GREEN.
I'M VIDEO TAPING
OUR EXPERIENCE.
THESE REALITY SHOWS ARE
VERY POPULAR, YOU KNOW.
WELL, UNLESS DALTON STARTS
RUNNING AROUND NAKED,
THE FIRST GUY I VOTE OFF THE
ISLAND IS THE CAMERAMAN.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE
REALLY LOVE THIS STUFF.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE PEEKING IN
YOUR NEIGHBOUR'S WINDOW.
THE LAST TIME I TRIED
THAT, I GOT SIX MONTHS
IN THE SLAMMER.
WELL, I HOPE YOU
LEARNED YOUR LESSON, MIKE.
YEAH, IF I'D HAVE
DONE IT WITH A CAMERA,
I'D HAVE HAD A HIT SERIES.
WELL, I HOPE
YOU'RE HUNGRY.
I'D HAVE TO BE.
WHAT WAS THIS ORIGINALLY?
DON'T YOU START WITH ME.
NO, NO, I NEED TO
KNOW WHAT I'M EATING.
I'M SURE THEY'LL
ASK AT THE HOSPITAL.
YOU THINK THIS
IS EASY, HUH?
TRYING TO DECIDE WHAT TO MAKE,
PREPARING IT ALL AND THEN
GETTING IT TOGETHER AT
THE SAME TIME?
NO, I THINK YOU'VE
DONE REAL WELL.
SHE'S PRETTY MUCH
EQUALLY BURNED.
ALL RIGHT, FINE, FINE!
YOU DON'T WANNA EAT IT,
THAT'S FINE WITH ME!
I MEAN, WHY SHOULD I CARE?
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
I'LL EAT AS MUCH AS YOU DO.
I'M NOT EVEN HUNGRY.
WELL, YOU'RE LUCKY.
MEN!
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, A LOT OF
YOUNG PEOPLE
ARE ASKING ME ABOUT THE
ENTREPRENEURIAL SPIRIT.
THEY WANT TO KNOW WHAT IT IS.
WELL, IT'S NOT THE KIND OF
SPIRIT YOU FIND IN A BOTTLE.
ALTHOUGH, BELIEVE ME,
MANY OF US HAVE LOOKED.
NO, THE ENTREPRENEURIAL SPIRIT
IS ABOUT TAKING A PROBLEM
AND TURNING IT
INTO AN OPPORTUNITY.
NOW, YOU MAY HAVE NOTICED
THAT I'VE GOT A COUPLE OF
FLAT TIRES ON MY 4X4.
ACTUALLY, THERE'S TWO MORE JUST
LIKE THESE ON THE OTHER SIDE.
I'M GONNA TAKE THIS PROBLEM
AND TURN IT INTO AN OPPORTUNITY.
OH, YEAH, I'M GONNA
USE THIS VEHICLE
TO GENERATE ENOUGH MONEY TO BUY
ME A WHOLE NEW SET OF TIRES.
SOUND IMPOSSIBLE?
HEY, IT'S ON TV;
IT MUST BE TRUE.
AND NOW, THROUGH THE MAGIC
OF INNOVATION AND LACK
OF ALTERNATIVES,
I'VE TURNED
MY ALL-WHEEL-DRIVE VEHICLE
INTO A FOUR-STATION WOOD SHOP.
OH, YEAH, NOW I CAN MAKE
PRODUCTS OUT OF WOOD
THAT I CAN SELL TO PEOPLE
AND MAKE ENOUGH MONEY
TO MAKE MYSELF A HALF-DECENT
SET OF RETREADS.
AND THEN IF I WANT, I CAN
CONTINUE ON AS A MANUFACTURER,
MAYBE GO PUBLIC WITH
AN I.P.O.,
MAKE MILLIONS
OF DOLLARS IN PROFITS
AND MOVE ON TO MY NEXT
INVESTMENT.
BUT I'LL PROBABLY
JUST GET THE TIRES.
[ ENGINE STARTING ]
NOW WE COME TO THE NEXT
MOST IMPORTANT STEP OF THE
ENTREPRENEURIAL PROCESS...
DECIDING WHAT TO MAKE.
SO I RESEARCHED AROUND,
FOUND OUT WHAT LOCAL PEOPLE
WANTED AND WHAT THEY
COULD AFFORD.
I'VE DECIDED
TO MAKE DUCK CALLS,
MAINLY BECAUSE I KNOW WHAT
A DUCK CALL LOOKS LIKE.
PLUS, I'D BE SELLING
MOSTLY TO MEN,
WHICH I THINK IS EASIER.
AS LONG AS SOMETHING WORKS,
MEN WILL BUY IT.
THEY DON'T CARE WHAT IT COSTS
OR WHAT COLOUR IT IS.
HECK, EVEN IF IT DOESN'T WORK,
MEN WILL BUY IT.
TAKE A LOOK IN YOUR DRIVEWAY.
OKAY, FIRST OF ALL
I GO TO MY CUTTING STATION.
I'M GONNA CUT THIS TO ROUGHLY
THE LENGTH THAT I WANT.
ALL RIGHT, NOW WHAT WE DO
IS WE TAKE HER DOWN TO
OUR LATHE AREA THERE.
WE'RE GONNA ROUND OFF THE
CORNERS A BIT.
NOW, I'VE ALREADY MOUNTED
A PIECE TO KIND OF SPEED
UP THIS DEMONSTRATION.
OKAY, ONCE I GET
THE LATHING DONE,
I'VE GOT MY BASIC DUCK CALL.
BUT YOU KNOW, THIS IS
A LITTLE ROUGH FOR TODAY'S
DISCERNING CUSTOMER,
SO NOW I'VE GOT TO GO
TO MY SANDING STATION.
IT'S JUST REALLY A PIECE
OF FINE GRAIN SANDPAPER
MOUNTED ONTO A RECORD
ALBUM AS A BACKING.
ACTUALLY, I USED
NAT KING COLE ON THAT
BECAUSE HE'S EXTRA SMOOTH.
AND THEN JUST DO
YOUR LITTLE SANDING.
PERFECT.
NOW TO TURN IT
INTO A REAL DUCK CALL,
I'VE GOT TO DRILL A HOLE
INTO THE DARN THING,
AND FOR THAT I'M GONNA USE
MY DRILLING STATION HERE.
JUST SLOWLY --
YOU KNOW, YOU MAY WANT TO
WEAR SAFETY GOGGLES ON THIS,
MAYBE EVEN SOME
CAST IRON GLOVES.
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
SO YOU ENTREPRENEURS REMEMBER
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[ HONKING NOISE ]
I SHOULD ALSO MENTION THAT
99% OF NEW BUSINESSES FAIL
IN THEIR FIRST YEAR.
[ HONKING NOISE ]
[ GEESE HONKING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW SOMETHING HAPPENS
TO GUYS' MAJOR SENSES
WHEN THEY APPROACH
MIDDLE AGE?
THEY LOSE 'EM.
BUT THEY LOSE 'EM
IN KIND OF AN ODD WAY.
THE OTHER DAY, BERNICE
WAS TALKING STRAIGHT
TO MY FACE THERE,
AND ALL I COULD HEAR WAS THE
RADIO IN THE NEXT ROOM
BECAUSE IT WAS RUNNING
THAT AD FOR THE BOAT SHOW.
SHE WAS PROBABLY GIVING ME THE
DETAILS OF SOME IMPORTANT PLAN,
BUT THAT'S THE KIND
OF INFORMATION
THAT'S BETTER IN THE HANDS
OF SOMEBODY COMPETENT,
SOMEBODY WHO HAS ALL
THEIR FACULTIES.
I'M LOSING MINE LIKE POCKET
CHANGE IN A LAZ-E-BOY.
BUT, LIKE I SAY,
YOU LOSE 'EM KINDA WEIRD;
LIKE, MY EYES AREN'T GOOD
ENOUGH TO READ THE
STREET SIGNS,
BUT I CAN TELL IF THE BEER STORE
IS OPEN SIX BLOCKS AWAY.
I CAN'T WATCH TWO KIDS FOR HALF
AN HOUR WITHOUT A DISASTER,
BUT I CAN WATCH FOUR BALL
GAMES AND AN INDY RACE
SIMULTANEOUSLY.
SO, GUYS, LOOK,
DON'T FIGHT IT.
IT'S NATURAL.
JUST KIND OF
KEEP A LOW PROFILE.
SMILE A LOT, DON'T TALK MUCH,
AND IF YOU FEEL A DRAFT,
CHECK YOUR FLY.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
AND WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING?
WELL,
I'M GOING TO BED.
NOT AFTER THE WAY YOU
SPOKE TO ME AT DINNER,
YOU'RE NOT.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, DALTON?
THIS IS MY BED.
YOU GET THE HECK
OUTTA HERE.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE
BECAUSE THERE IS NO BED
ON MY SIDE OF THE LODGE.
WELL, GO SLEEP
IN THE CABIN.
YOU CAN HOLD YOUR
BREATH THAT LONG.
ISN'T THAT
A GREAT IDEA?
WHY DON'T YOU TRY IT?!
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
DALTON?
YES?
WHAT IS THAT?
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHAT IS WHAT?
THERE'S SOMETHING
COLD IN THE BED.
OH, THAT'S
MY TIRE IRON.
YOU EXPECTING A FLAT?
IT'S FOR PROTECTION.
I DON'T FIND YOU THAT
ATTRACTIVE, DALTON.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
IT'S PROTECTION AGAINST
BURGLARS AND ARSONISTS.
WELL, THERE WON'T BE ANY
ARSON GOING ON HERE.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
MM-HMM, YEAH.
MM-HMM.
GIRL, YOU KNOW BOYS
ARE LIKE THAT IN THEIR
FIRST YEAR OF COLLEGE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
OH, MY GOD, FOR REAL?
I KNOW.
LISTEN, I GOTTA GET GOING.
NO, NO, NOTHING IMPORTANT.
I'M JUST AT WORK.
OKAY?
BYE.
HI, Mr GREEN.
THANK YOU FOR
COMING IN.
DIDN'T REALISE I HAD
A CHOICE, ACTUALLY.
YOU KNOW, I THINK IT IS SO
CUTE HOW YOU WEAR YOUR, UM,
COSTUMES TO EVERY
ONE OF OUR MEETINGS.
BUT REALLY,
IT'S NOT NECESSARY.
COSTUME?
OH, NO, NO, THESE
ARE MY LODGE CLOTHES.
RIGHT. RIGHT.
AND YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST
GREAT TO WEAR THEM IN PUBLIC.
IT'S WACKY,
AND A FANTASTIC WAY TO DRAW
ATTENTION TO YOURSELF.
BUT WHAT WE NEED
IS FOR YOU TO DRAW ATTENTION
TO YOURSELF WHILE YOU'RE
ON TELEVISION.
THE NETWORK IS LOOKING FOR A
LITTLE MORE SHOCK VALUE.
WELL, I GUESS I COULD DO A
LITTLE MORE ELECTRICAL WORK.
[ GIGGLING ]
NO, THAT DOESN'T COUNT.
YOU NEED A
YOUNGER DEMOGRAPHIC,
YOU KNOW, MAYBE SOME MORE
SWEARING, MORE VIOLENCE.
MORE...
WELL, JUST MORE SWEARING
AND VIOLENCE FOR NOW.
I'VE WRITTEN UP SOME
WORDS HERE
THAT ARE PERFECTLY FINE
FOR YOU TO USE DURING
YOUR TIME SLOT.
I THINK YOU SHOULD GIVE
SOME OF THEM A TRY.
WELL, I SAY THIS WORD QUITE A
BIT DURING THE HANDYMAN CORNER,
BUT WE ALWAYS EDIT IT OUT.
WELL, DON'T.
THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT WE NEED.
YOU KNOW, WE MIGHT EVEN MOVE
YOUR SHOW TO A LATER TIME SLOT
SO YOU COULD SAY WORDS LIKE,
[ BLEEP ] OR [ BLEEP ]
OR [ BLEEP ]
WOW, WERE YOU EVER A
MERCHANT MARINE?
OKAY, I UNDERSTAND IF
SWEARING IS NOT YOUR THING.
OKAY, MAYBE
YOU COULD JUST, UM,
PUNCH ONE OF THE LODGE
MEMBERS IN THE FACE
ONCE IN A WHILE.
WELL, I DON'T THINK THE
LODGE MEMBERS WOULD GO
FOR THAT ONE TOO MUCH.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU JUST FAKE IT.
YOU DON'T REALLY PUNCH THEM.
IT'S FINE TO
FAKE THINGS, YOU KNOW?
REALLY?
IT'S PERFECTLY FINE.
JUST SAY WHATEVER
AND DO WHATEVER,
AND PEOPLE WILL BELIEVE
ANYTHING YOU TELL THEM.
OKAY, WELL, THEN I'M TELLING
YOU THAT WE ARE GOING TO MAKE
ALL THESE CHANGES
FOR THE VERY NEXT SHOW.
PERFECT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red: WELL, WE HAD A
BIG DAY SET OUT.
WE HAD FOUR OIL DRUMS.
EACH GUY PUT HIS NAME ON ONE.
OF COURSE, YOU KNOW
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO...
ROLL 'EM DOWN A HILL
WITH US INSIDE, YOU KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
HAVE SOCIALIZED MEDICINE.
BUT WE HAVE TO HAVE
A TEST PILOT, SOMEONE
TO RUN HER FIRST.
WALTER SEEMED LIKE
THE PRIME SUSPECT.
HE'LL HEAL FASTER;
HE'S YOUNGER.
HE'S IN THERE.
WE JUST HAVE TO CAP THAT UP.
GET THAT ON THERE
GOOD AND FIRM.
IT'S OKAY NOW.
AND LET'S JUST GIVE HIM
A LITTLE PUSH AND
GET HIM GOING.
OKAY --
OH, MY GOSH!
UH-OH!
OH, BOY!
OKAY, NOW WE --
OKAY --
MIKE BRING ME A
STICK OR SOMETHING.
WE GOTTA JUST POP
THE LID ON THAT.
ANYTHING ON THE
JUNK PILE THERE?
YEAH, THERE YOU GO.
GET ONE OF THOSE LONG ROLLER
EXTENSION HANDLE THINGS.
NO, NO, NOT THE STICK.
ALL RIGHT, JUST POP
THAT LID OFF.
ALL RIGHT, HERE HE COMES.
ALL RIGHT, HE'S GOOD.
WALTER HAD NOTICED THAT
HE COULDN'T SEE WHERE
HE WAS GOING.
IF WE CUT A WINDOW IN HER,
THEN YOU COULD --
BY LEANING YOU COULD
STEER IT AND EVERYTHING.
SO I GOT THE TORCH.
AND I'M CUTTING
A LITTLE WINDOW.
YOU BETTER GET
OUTTA THERE, WALTER.
AND WE PUT THE
RUBBER AROUND EACH ONE.
I DIDN'T GO FOR THE WINDOW.
I'D RATHER NOT
SEE WHAT'S COMING.
NOW WE JUST GET 'EM ROCKING,
AND, UH, ALL RIGHT,
HERE WE GO.
THERE WE GO.
OH, MAN.
OH, BOY.
[ SCREAMING ]
WAHOO!
OH, BOY.
THERE'S MIKE.
OKAY, HE'S GOOD.
THERE'S WINSTON, I THINK.
MIKE, WINSTON'S COMING IN.
THERE WE GO.
AND HERE COMES WALTER.
OH!
AND HERE'S OUR TRIBUTE
TO THE ABORIGINAL PEOPLES.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
[ BARKING ]
PLAYING FETCH IS A GREAT
WAY TO EXERCISE YOUR DOG
AND DISLOCATE YOUR SHOULDER.
THAT POPPING SOUND
IS CALLED FETCH-ITIS.
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
IF THERE WAS A BETTER WAY?
WELL, THERE IS.
[ GRUNTING ]
ALL YOU NEED IS A BUCKET SEAT,
A SOUP LADLE AND A LITTLE
BIT OF THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON.
YOU'LL FIND THIS
A LITTLE BIT EASIER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
JUST WAITING ON LOCAL ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICER, ED FRID.
I GUESS HE'S RUNNING A BIT
BEHIND SCHEDULE TODAY.
SORRY I'M LATE, RED.
OH, MAN.
YOU OKAY, ED?
NOT REALLY.
DID YOU BRING THE KITTEN
LIKE YOU PROMISED?
HAD A LITTLE
TROUBLE WITH THE KITTEN.
YEAH, BUT YOU SAID YOU
WERE GONNA BRING --
THINGS GOT A LITTLE
OUTTA HAND, OKAY!
ARE YOU TELLING ME A
KITTEN DID ALL OF THIS?
OH, NO, NO, NO.
THERE WERE TWO OF 'EM.
ONE DISTRACTED ME;
THE OTHER JUMPED
ME FROM BEHIND.
GOT MY EAR.
IT'S BEEN A PRETTY ROUGH WEEK.
BEEN TO THE HOSPITAL
A FEW TIMES, HAVE YOU, ED?
WELL, THEY GAVE ME MY OWN
PARKING SPOT, YEAH.
MONDAY MORNING --
YEAH.
MOUNTAIN LION.
OKAY.
OR IT MIGHT HAVE
BEEN A SNAKE BITE.
IT'S A LITTLE BLURRY.
THAT USUALLY
MEANS SNAKE BITE.
OKAY, PROBABLY.
YEP.
THEN ON TUESDAY
AFTERNOON,
I BANGED MY KNEE ON STINKY
PETERSON'S PORCH.
HE'S GOT A BUNCH OF
SKUNKS UNDER THERE,
AND THEY'RE CREATING
QUITE A PROBLEM.
YEAH, PROBABLY THE
SMELL IS BOTHERING THEM.
[ LAUGHING ]
NO KIDDING.
BUT THE HOLE WAS TOO SMALL
FOR ME TO GET A TRAP
UNDER THERE.
SO I TRIED TO LURE THEM OUT
AND INTO THE WOODS
BY SMEARING BACON FAT
ALL OVER MY BODY.
THAT'S WHEN THE
BEAR GOT ME.
HE MAULED YOU, ED?
NO, BUT HE GAVE ME
A PRETTY GOOD LICKING.
YOU KNOW, I GOT
THINGS TO DO, ED.
I CAN'T --
NO, WAIT.
I NEED YOU TO
DO ME A FAVOUR HERE.
YEAH, TAKE A
LOOK AT THIS.
I SAT ON A PORCUPINE.
YEAH, I CAN SEE THAT, ED.
WELL, HOW DO YOU
THINK IT LOOKS?
I DON'T REALLY HAVE
A REFERENCE POINT HERE.
DO YOU HAVE A BEFORE
PICTURE OR ANYTHING?
YOU SEE, I'M WORRIED
ABOUT AN INFECTION, EH.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT PEOPLE
WHO JUST TUNED IN.
OH!
[ APPLAUSE AND LAUGHTER ]
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU.
YEP.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
SORRY WE COULDN'T LET
YOU IN HERE EARLIER,
BUT THE AIR'S FINALLY CLEAR,
AND WE'RE FREE TO MOVE
ABOUT THE COMMUNITY,
WHICH MEANS THAT DALTON
AND MIKE CAN GO HOME
SO THE DANGER IS OVER.
Mr GREEN,
I THINK YOU HAVE SOMETHING
THAT BELONGS TO ME.
I DO?
MY VIDEOTAPE OF OUR
LAST TWO DAYS HERE.
AND NIGHTS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
SPECIFICALLY, MIKE?
MY VIDEOTAPE OF YOUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH DALTON,
INCLUDING THE SLEEPOVERS.
I'M GONNA SHOW IT
AT THE MEETING TONIGHT
AND USE ALL THE LODGE MEMBERS
AS A FOCUS GROUP FOR
MY TV PILOT.
WELL, I THINK THAT'S
A GREAT IDEA.
HERE YOU GO, MIKE.
OH.
WHAT'S THIS ON THE
SIDE HERE?
WELL,
THAT'S A MAGNET.
THAT'S A HORSESHOE
MAGNET FOR GOOD LUCK.
I PUT THAT ON
THE SIDE FOR YOU.
OH, GEE,
THANK YOU.
YEAH, IT'S ALWAYS GOOD
TO HAVE SOMETHING ON
THE SIDE, MIKE.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH,
IT'S MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
THESE LAST COUPLE OF DAYS
HAVE BEEN A REAL LEARNING
EXPERIENCE FOR ME;
THE MAIN THING BEING THAT
AFTER 34 YEARS OF MARRIAGE,
I'D RATHER BE WITH
YOU ON YOUR WORST DAY
THAN ANYBODY ELSE
ON THEIR BEST DAY.
AND AROUND HERE THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THOSE TWO
IS EXTREMELY MARGINAL.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
COME ON, GUYS.
TO ORDER. TO ORDER.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
SIT DOWN.
THERE WE GO.
OKAY, ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
Dalton: OH, SURE,
YOU SAY YOU WILL,
BUT YOU NEVER DO.
Red: ALL RIGHT, MEN AND DALTON,
WE HAVE A SPECIAL
TREAT FOR YOU.
I KNOW IT'S BEEN KIND OF A
CRISIS THIS WEEK,
BUT, UH, MIKE HERE HAS
FILMED THE WHOLE THING,
AND HE WANTS TO SHOW YOU A
LITTLE TV PILOT RIGHT NOW.
Mike: ACTUALLY, Mr GREEN, I
LOOKED AT THE TAPE,
AND THERE WAS NOTHING ON IT.
NO CONTENT.
Red: SOUNDS LIKE A HIT!