♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: RED GREEN HERE,
ON THIS WEEK'S SHOW
BILL GOES BACKPACKING
AND HAROLD FORMS
THE POSSUM LODGE CADETS
AND I'M GOING TO TURN
A BARBEQUE INTO SCUBA GEAR.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(SHATTERING OF GLASS)
♪ ♪ ♪
>>HAROLD: AND NOW HERE'S
MY PERSONAL HERO,
A MAN WHO JUST OUT WINDMILLS,
A REAL DON COYOTE
OF THE MAN OF
THE MUNCHIES,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
MR. RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
THANK YOU, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH AND THANK YOU ALL
FOR TUNING US IN.
I WOULD LIKE TO SAY THAT
THAT INTRO YOU JUST HEARD
HAD ABSOLUTELY NOTHING TO DO
WITH ME, UNFORTUNATELY
THE GUY WHO SAID IT DOES,
MY NEPHEW HAROLD.
I DIDN'T ASK YOU COME
OVER HERE HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: IT'S OKAY.
>>RED: I GUESS YOU CAN SEE
WHY I'D LIKE TO KEEP
A SHOVEL HANDY.
ANYHOW, BOY THINGS HAVE REALLY
BEEN HUMMING UP AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK AND IT'S NOT JUST
FROM THE WAY WE REWIRED
THE WATER HEATER.
THE LOCAL RADIO STATION HAS MADE
AN ANNOUNCEMENT THAT SOMEWHERE
IN THE AREA SURROUNDING
POSSUM LAKE THERE'S THE LARGEST
DEPOSIT OF GOLD EVER RECORDED.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH?
WHERE DID YOU HEAR THAT?
>>RED: WELL I JUST SAID
HAROLD ON THE RADIO.
>>HAROLD: WELL I DON'T THINK
YOU COULD BELIEVE EVERYTHING
YOU HEAR FROM THAT STATION,
I MEAN THE ENTIRE STAFF'S
AN ALCOHOLIC.
>>RED: NO HAROLD THIS IS JUST
NOT BERNIE HALLUCINATING OKAY?
>>HAROLD: NO?
>>RED: THIS IS A SCIENTIFIC
STUDY DONE BY THE GOVERNMENT
AND I DON'T THINK THE WHOLE
GOVERNMENT WOULD ALL BE
HALLUCINATING AT THE
SAME TIME AGAIN.
SO YEAH, ANYHOW A BUNCH
OF US HAVE DECIDED TO DIG
OURSELVES A GOLD MINE
AND I EVEN ASKED OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK TO PITCH IN
BECAUSE I FIGURED YOU KNOW
HE WAS PROBABLY IN THE
ORIGINAL GOLD RUSH YOU KNOW,
HE'S PROBABLY GOING TO
KNOW WHERE TO DIG.
>>HAROLD: THAT WAS 1849.
>>RED: THE SHOVEL?
NO IT'S $5 BUCKS.
ANYWAY WE'RE GOING TO GET
OUT THERE AND GET AT IT AS
SOON AS WE CAN BUT IT'S NOT
GOING TO GET IN THE WAY OF
THE SHOW, I'LL KEEP YOU POSTED
ON THE GOLD MINE THING
AND I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
EVEN IF WE STRIKE GOLD
WE'RE STILL GOING TO
FINISH THE SHOW,
IT WILL JUST HAVE A LOT MORE
OF HAROLD IN THE SECOND HALF.
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ OH HOW SMART CAN YOU BE ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER KNOW ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU TRY ♪
(HAROLD SINGING)
♪ YOU'LL NEVER KNOW ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU TRY ♪
♪ HOW FAR CAN YOU GO ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER KNOW ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU TRY ♪
(HAROLD SINGS)
♪ YOU'LL NEVER KNOW ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU TRY ♪
♪ ARE YOU SLOW ♪
♪ OR ARE YOU QUICK ♪
♪ YOU'LL NEVER KNOW ♪
♪ UNTIL YOU POKE ♪
♪ A MOUNTAIN LION ♪
♪ WITH A STICK ♪
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' I'M GOING
TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING
YOU CAN DO WITH AN OLD,
BROKEN DOWN BARBEQUE.
NOW I'VE BEEN SAVING THIS BEAUTY
HOPING THAT IT WOULD EVENTUALLY
HAVE VALUE AS AN ANTIQUE
BUT APPARENTLY THE MARKET FOR
RUSTY, METAL APPLIANCES
COVERED WITH BITS OF BURNT MEAT
HAS GONE A LITTLE SOFT ON US.
AND NOW I SUPPOSE A BUNCH OF
YOU ARE SAYING HEY RED,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST THROW
THE DARN THING IN THE LAKE?
OR WHO CARES?
OR WHAT ELSE IS ON?
THAT'LL BE YOUR WIFE
TALKING PROBABLY.
WELL THE TRUTH IS IF YOU DO
THROW ONE OF THESE IN THE LAKE,
WITHIN A COUPLE OF DAYS YOU GET
ALL THAT GREASE AND FAT COMING
UP ON SHORE THERE AND THEN
THE PROPANE TANK WILL CUT LOOSE
AND SHOOT RIGHT UP THROUGH
THE BOTTOM OF THAT OLD
LATH STRAIGHT CANOE
THAT'S BEEN UP HERE AT
THE LODGE SINCE BEFORE
I STARTED COMING.
WELL I SHOULD SAY THAT'S
WHAT COULD HAPPEN,
THE FUNNY THING IS WE WERE
ACTUALLY GOING TO THROW THIS
BARBEQUE INTO THE LAKE BUT
WITH OURSELVES ATTACHED TO IT,
BECAUSE WE'RE GOING TO TURN
THIS PROPANE BARBEQUE INTO
A FULL SET OF SCUBA GEAR.
ALL RIGHT STEP ONE,
DISASSEMBLE THE UNIT
INTO ITS INDIVIDUAL COMPONENTS.
YUP, OXIDATION IS
A WONDERFUL THING ISN'T IT?
ALL RIGHT STEP 2,
DISCONNECT THE PROPANE TANK.
NOW THE CONNECTOR ON THESE
UNITS IS LEFT HAND THREAD,
SO TO LOOSEN THEM YOU GOT
TO TURN THEM TO THE RIGHT,
YOU CAN LOOSEN THEM BY TURNING
THEM TO THE LEFT IF YOU'RE
THE SIZE OF MOOSE THOMPSON
BUT IT WON'T EVER GO BACK
TOGETHER AGAIN.
NOW ONCE YOU GOT THE HOSE
OUT OF THERE YOU MIGHT
JUST WANT TO ABANDON THE
PROJECT AND TRY SOMETHING ELSE,
MAYBE TURN THE PROPANE TANK
INTO SAY A PARTY SIZE
CIGARETTE LIGHTER OR A
PROPANE POWERED LAWN ROLLER.
OH I KNOW WHAT WOULD
BE KIND OF FUN, YOU JUST
THROW THE WHOLE TANK INTO
A SMOLDERING CAMPFIRE FOR
AN EXCITING GAME OF
LET'S SURPRISE THE BOY SCOUTS.
BUT FOR OUR PURPOSES WE'RE
GOING TO DRAIN THE GAS OUT
OF THERE AND SO WE CAN
USE IT FOR SCUBA GEAR.
(GAS HISSING OUT)
PHEW! WELL I'LL JUST, PHEW!
MOVE THIS ASIDE UNTIL WE GET
ALL OF THE GAS OUT OF HER,
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE 20,000
MAJOR LEAGUES UNDER THE SEA
AND SUCK IN A LUNGFUL OF PROPANE
INSTANT HEADACHE THERE
I'LL TELL YOU.
NOW YOU WANT TO SAVE THESE
GRILLS, YOU CAN MAKE YOURSELF
A DANDY LITTLE SHARK CAGE,
NOT BIG ENOUGH FOR YOUR WHOLE
BODY BUT CERTAINLY BIG ENOUGH
TO PROTECT WHATEVER IT
IS YOU CARE ABOUT.
THE BURNER YOU DON'T
REALLY NEED, CHUCK THAT.
BUT YOU WANT TO SAVE THE HOSE
AND YOU WANT TO SAVE THE HEAT
CONTROLS BECAUSE THESE BECOME
YOUR AIR REGULATORS,
ONE FOR YOU, ONE FOR YOUR BUDDY.
AND YOU GOT THAT FAT JAR THAT
HANGS DOWN UNDERNEATH THE
BARBEQUE, HANG ONTO THAT,
THAT'S GOING TO BECOME
YOUR DIVING MASK.
BOY YOU CAN GET A LOT OF FAT OUT
OF 4 STRIPS OF BACON CAN'T YOU
IF YOU SQUEEZE THEM RIGHT.
ANYWAY I THINK THAT'S PRETTY
WELL EVERYTHING WE NEED
AND WE SURE AS HECK DON'T
NEED THE SPARK IGNITER,
NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO
START A FIRE UNDERWATER.
(LOUD EXPLOSION)
(SHATTERING OF GLASS)
>>RED: (COUGHING) NOW I GUESS
THAT TANK WILL BE EMPTY NOW.
WELL WE GOT LUCKY THERE SINCE
THE PROPANE TANK LANDED IN TOWN
WHICH IS WHERE I HAD TO GO
ANYWAY TO GET HER FILLED UP
WITH AIR AT THE GAS STATION.
NOW BREATHING THIS AIR MIGHT
MAKE YOU A LITTLE SLEEPY
BECAUSE IT'S TIRE AIR,
ALWAYS TIME FOR HUMOUR
AT THE LODGE...
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
SOMETHING TO PUT ON YOUR FEET
TO HELP YOU MOVE ALONG IN
THE WATER, HOW ABOUT THIS?
THEY'RE FLIPPERS AREN'T THEY?
IT'S TIRE AIR...
OKAY SO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO
IS YOU GOT TO PUT THE TANK
ON YOUR BACK, THE FLIPPERS
ON YOUR FEET AND THE JAR ON
YOUR FAT FACE OR THE FAT
JAR ON YOUR FACE,
AND THEN YOU'VE GOT TO DO
ALL THESE JOBS USING THE
HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
NOW THIS IS PROBABLY GOING
TO TAKE ME AWHILE SO WHY DON'T
WE GET ON WITH THE SHOW AND
WE CAN COME BACK WHEN
I GOT HER ALL BUILT.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S MY
FAVOURITE PART OF THE SHOW,
THE PART WHERE YOU EXPOSE THOSE
3 LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW.'
AND NOW HERE TO PROVE THAT
ONCE AGAIN IS MY UNCLE RED AND
HIS BEST FRIEND IN THE WHOLE,
WIDE WORLD, OH OKAY,
MR. GLEN BRAXTON.
ALL RIGHTY, IT SAYS HERE WE GOT
'DEAR EXPERTS, I AM ORGANIZING
A COOKOUT FOR ALL THE GANG
AT WORK AND I AM WONDERING
WHAT TYPE OF FOOD TO PREPARE
AND SERVE, WOULD YOU HAVE
ANY HINTS YOU WOULD
LIKE TO PASS ON?'
>>RED: WELL I ALWAYS FIND
BUDGET IS THE MAIN CONSIDERATION
YOU KNOW LET'S SAY WE'D HAVE
SOMETHING LIKE FISH FRY UP
AT THE LODGE AND THEN OF
COURSE NOBODY CATCHES ANYTHING
AND SO WE HAVE TO AUGMENT
THE MENU AND IT ALWAYS FORCES
US OVER BUDGET AND THEN YOU
GET ALL THE WHINERS WHO WANT
TO KNOW HOW DO HOTDOGS AND
MACARONI QUALIFY AS FISH FRY.
I JUST TELL THE GUYS,
HEY THROW SOME WORMS IN.
>>HAROLD: WELL YOU SOUNDED
SERIOUS AT THE TIME.
>>RED: OH HAROLD.
>>GLEN: WELL THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING IS TO FIND THE RIGHT
MAN FOR THE JOB,
FOR YOUR CHEF YOU NEED
TO GET A WELDER.
>>RED: A WELDER?
>>GLEN: OH YEAH AND
ACETYLENE TORCH WILL COOK
A 12 POUND ROAST IN UNDER
4 MINUTES AND IF YOU'VE GOT
ELECTRICITY YOU CAN ARC WELD
A WHOLE PIG IN LESS THAN
A MINUTE.
MY BROTHER FOUND THAT OUT,
HE WAS UPPING THE VOLTAGE
AROUND THE PIGPEN AT THE FARM
AND ELECTRICITY ADDS TO
THE PRESENTATION OF THE MEAL,
YEAH SURE BECAUSE THE LITTLE
PIGS THAT TAIL STRAIGHTENS
RIGHT OUT AND ALL THE HAIR,
ALL THE HAIR ALL OVER HIM
STANDS STRAIGHT UP.
BUT YOU GOT TO MAKE SURE
ALL YOUR GUESTS ARE GROUNDED
BECAUSE IF THEY STICK
A FORK INTO IT.
>>RED: IT IS WINTER,
TIME TO GET YOUR SLED OUT
AND SWISH DOWN GIANT HILLS
TO LEARN TO HANG ON TIGHT
AND HAVE THOSE HIGH
SPEED THRILLS,
THE GOOD, OLD SLED
WILL SHOW YOU HOW TO FLY
AND SOAR AND WHIZ,
AND TEACH YOU JUST
HOW HARD A FROZEN
ELM TREE REALLY IS.
>>RED: WELL THERE YOU
HAVE IT, YOUR VERY OWN SCUBA.
THE BOTTOM OF THE LAKE
HERE I COME...
THIS FAT JAR SMELLS LIKE EVERY
GRADE OF MEAT I'VE EVER
EATEN AND THEN SOME.
WELL REMEMBER IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
WHOA! IS THIS JUST HEAVY
OR AM I GETTING THE BENDS?
(BOB GRUNTING WITH EACH SWING)
>>RED: BOB?
>>BOB: OH RED, I DIDN'T
SEE YOU STANDING THERE,
I WAS JUST DOING AN
AIR DIRECTION TEST FOR
THE DEPARTMENT.
I GOT TO WRITE THAT
DOWN ON MY SCORECARD,
I MEAN MY NOTEBOOK.
>>RED: WELL YOU GOVERNMENT
GUYS ARE PRETTY SOPHISTICATED.
>>BOB: OH YEAH.
>>RED: SEE I WOULD OF THOUGHT
THIS WAS AN ORDINARY GOLF
BALL HERE.
>>BOB: NO THAT'S A
DIMPLED ERGONOMINATOR.
>>RED: WOW AND THIS
IS JUST NOT A PUTTER?
>>BOB: NO THAT'S THE PARAMETERS
FOR THE WIND SPEED INDICATOR,
IT'S A RECALIBRATION WRENCH.
>>RED: NO KIDDING?
AND YOU DON'T JUST
CALL THAT A PUTT?
>>BOB: NO I'D CALL
THAT A BIRDIE.
>>RED: BOB WORKS FOR THE
DEPARTMENT OF NATURAL RESOURCES
SO YOU ALWAYS KNOW WHERE TO
FIND HIM DURING WORKING HOURS.
I THOUGHT I'D GO AND ASK HIM
ABOUT THE GOLD THING BECAUSE
WITH HIM BEING WITH THE
GOVERNMENT AND EVERYTHING I
FIGURED HE'D KNOW ALL ABOUT IT.
OF COURSE ALL HE WANTED WAS FOR
ME TO PLAY GOLF WITH HIM.
WELL NO THANKS BOB,
I JUST WANTED TO COME BY AND
ASK YOU ABOUT THIS GOLD THING.
>>BOB: WHAT GOLD THING?
YOU MEAN LIKE A GOLF TROPHY?
>>RED: NO, NO, NO, NO,
DIDN'T YOU HEAR ABOUT THIS
ON THE RADIO, THEY SAY THAT
THERE'S THE LARGEST DEPOSIT
OF GOLD EVER RIGHT ABOUT
POSSUM LAKE, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU GUYS AT NATURAL RESOURCES
DON'T KNOW SOMETHING ABOUT
NATURAL RESOURCES,
I MEAN WHAT ELSE IS
THERE TO THE JOB BOB?
>>BOB: RED I THINK YOUR
INFORMATION IS A LITTLE OFF,
THE REPORT STATED THAT
POSSUM LAKE HAS THE LARGEST,
THE LARGEST DEPOSIT OF
MOLD EVER RECORDED.
>>RED: MOLD?
>>BOB: MMM HMM.
>>RED: WELL WHAT THE HECK
ARE WE GOING TO DO WITH MOLD?
>>BOB: WELL I DON'T KNOW,
YOU COULD TURN POSSUM LODGE
INTO A YOGURT RANCH.
LISTEN RED, WHY DON'T YOU
JOIN ME FOR A GAME OF GOLF,
IT'LL TAKE YOUR MIND OFF
YOUR DISAPPOINTMENT.
>>RED: WELL I THOUGHT YOU WERE
JUST TESTING THE WIND HERE BOB?
>>BOB: WHATEVER...
(SPLASH OF CLUB HITTING WATER)
>>RED: BOY IT MUST BE REAL
WINDY OVER THERE WHERE YOU ARE.
>>RED: WELL THIS GOLD/MOLD
THING HAS BEEN A BIT
OF A SETBACK,
WE'VE NEVER HEARD OF ANYONE
GETTING RICH DURING A MOLD RUSH.
>>HAROLD: WELL YOU KNOW
UNCLE RED THAT MOLD HAS ITS
VALUE TOO YOU KNOW, BECAUSE
THEY USE IT LIKE TO MAKE BREAD
OR PENICILLIN, SO MOLD IS
NOT A BAD THING.
>>RED: WOULD YOU PAY $400 BUCKS
AN OUNCE FOR IT HAROLD?
IF NOT THEN IT'S A BAD THING
BECAUSE THAT'S HOW MUCH WE SPENT
DIGGING THE GOLD MINE ALL RIGHT.
>>HAROLD: $400?
HOW DID YOU MANAGE TO SPEND
$400 ON LIKE 12 VOLUNTEERS
DIGGING A HOLE IN
THE GROUND?
>>RED: MAINLY REFRESHMENTS.
WELL YOU CAN BUILD UP A THIRST
INHALING THAT MOLD I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT WE FOUND IS THAT BREWER'S
YEAST IS THE BEST FOR HANDLING
MOLD OF THAT TYPE.
ANYWAY WE'VE DECIDED TO CONVERT
THE MINE INTO AN UNDERGROUND
PARKING LOT AND WE FIGURE
WE CAN GET 15 CARS SINGLE FILE
IN THERE AND THE ONLY TRICK IS
YOU HAVE TO PARK IN THE REVERSE
ORDER THAT YOU'D BE LEAVING.
>>HAROLD: EXCUSE ME UNCLE RED,
HAVE YOU THOUGHT THIS
PLAN THROUGH?,
BECAUSE YOU KNOW I DON'T WANT
TO MAKE JUDGMENTS HERE
YOU KNOW BUT I WAS JUST THINKING
THAT I THINK YOUR PLAN IS FLAWED
BADLY FLAWED, LIKE RESCUE 911
FLAWED YOU KNOW.
>>RED: WELL NOW HAROLD IF
WE'RE GOING TO GET INTO
COMPARING THINGS WITH FLAWS
IN THEM, I THINK YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO HAVE A VERY NICE DAY.
>>HAROLD: WELL I JUST MEAN
LIKE SAY JUST EVEN ONE CAR
GETS STUCK IN THE MINE,
THEN YOU KNOW EVERYBODY
GETS SHAFTED.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
WELL WE GOT THAT COVERED HAROLD,
YOU SEE YOU'RE GOING TO BACK
THE FIRST CAR IN, YOU'RE GOING
TO DRIVE THE NEXT ONE,
BACK THE NEXT ONE
AND DRIVE THE NEXT ONE,
SO THEY'RE ALL BUMPER TO BUMPER
AND WE GIVE EVERYBODY JUMPER
CABLES, PLUS WE'RE GOING TO
CHARGE THEM ALL $3 BUCKS A HEAD.
>>HAROLD: WELL THAT'S GREAT,
SO THEN YOU'LL GET LIKE
YOUR $400 BACK IN NO TIME.
>>RED: WELL IT'S 800 NOW,
WE HAD TO BUY THE JUMPER CABLES
AND OF COURSE WE ALL WANTED
YOU KNOW SNAZZY VESTS AND THEN
EVERYBODY WANTED A FLASHLIGHT,
WE BOUGHT 100 FLASHLIGHTS.
>>HAROLD: WELL THAT'S OKAY TOO
BECAUSE YOU KNOW YOU FINALLY
LEARNED THAT IN ORDER TO MAKE
IT BIG YOU GOT TO SPEND BIG.
>>RED: WELL I'M REAL GLAD
TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT HAROLD
BECAUSE WE TOOK IT RIGHT
OUT OF YOUR SALARY.
♪ THE FISH SWAM IN LIKE HORSES ♪
♪ AND JUMPED UP ON THE BEACH ♪
♪ THEY CLIMB THE ♪
♪ SPILT LEAF MAPLE ♪
♪ AND EAT ONE GAVE A SPEECH ♪
♪ THEY SANG A BUNCH ♪
♪ OF SHOW TUNES AND ♪
♪ JUMPED BACK INTO THE LAKE ♪
♪ IT'S AMAZING WHAT YOU SEE ♪
♪ UP HERE AFTER YOU ♪
♪ BANG YOUR HEAD ♪
♪ REALLY, REALLY HARD ♪
♪ ON THE DOCK ♪
>>RED: ATTENTION EVERYBODY,
CLEAR THE AREA, IT'S TIME
FOR ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
BILL HAD ASKED ME TO DROP
OVER SO I DID, AND HE WANTED
TO DO SOME BACKPACKING TODAY,
SO HE'S GOT THESE,
THESE ARE AMAZING,
DO YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE NEVER HAD THESE IN THE ARMY,
OF COURSE I WASN'T IN THE ARMY
BUT I'M SURE WE DIDN'T,
WOULDN'T OF HAD.
OH HIS HAS GOT A LITTLE BIT
OF BEND IN HER THERE SO,
BILL, VERY RESOURCEFUL JUST BEND
IT OVER HIS KNEE AND JUST,
OH, OH, WELL IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
A BIT OF A, IT'S NOT GOOD
ENOUGH FOR BILL NOW
HOWEVER APPARENTLY IT'S
GOOD ENOUGH FOR ME.
NOW BILL THERE'S A COUPLE
OF STRAPS, YOUR ARM GOES IN,
THAT'S IT, GET YOUR ARM IN THE
OTHER ONE, THE OTHER, NO BILL,
BILL, BILL YOU'RE GOING TO GET
DIZZY THERE, LET ME HELP YOU.
IT'S GOOD TO GO BACKPACKING
WITH SOMEONE ELSE, THEY CAN
HELP YOU GET THE ARMHOLE
THROUGH THERE AND THEN YOU GET
IT CENTERED ON THERE AND THEN,
WELL, WELL, NO, NO, NO BILL,
BILL, BILL, BILL,
WELL WE WORKED THAT OUT.
SO NOW AND THERE IS,
I GUESS THAT LOOKS LIKE
THE AREA IN THE DAILY LOG
THAT YOU KEEP IN THE WOODS,
ANYWAY BILL WANTED ME TO LOAD
HIM UP THERE, THIS IS A BEAUTY,
THESE THINGS ARE SO LIGHT AND
THEY'RE PERFECTLY BALANCED,
AND IT'S AMAZING HOW MUCH
STUFF YOU KNOW IF YOU GOT
THE LITTLE ATTACHMENTS
AND SO ON, HOW MUCH STUFF
YOU CAN GET ONTO YOUR BACKPACK
AND THEN YOU'RE JUST FREE TO
GO THROUGH THE WOODS AT YOUR
LEISURE BECAUSE YOU MISS SO
MUCH WHEN YOU SAY GOING OVER
THE WOODS IN A CONCORD OR
SOMETHING OF THAT NATURE,
THIS WAY YOU CAN SEE ALL
THE TREES AND YOU CAN SEE
THE GROUND AND WELL
ALMOST ALL THE BRANCHES.
THERE WE GO, NOW A LITTLE BIT
OF LIMBO THERE GIVES YOU
APPRECIATION FOR THE CARIBBEAN
AND ALL THAT THEY STAND FOR.
THERE WE GO AND THE BEAUTY IS
IF YOU DO GET TIRED YOU
CAN SIT DOWN AND RELAX,
YOU ARE IN FACT ONE
WITH NATURE, OH, OH, OH,
OH WELL...
AND YOU GOT BASICALLY
ALL YOUR BELONGINGS,
YOU'RE SELF SUFFICIENT
AT THIS POINT WITH THIS TYPE
OF A RIG AND THEN YOU GET
COMFORTABLE YOU TAKE THE THING
OFF AND, OH, OH, OH, OH,
OH BOY!
BUT YOU KNOW RESOURCEFULNESS
IS THE MARK OF A GOOD BACKPACKER
AND BILL IS RESOURCEFUL.
>>RED: THIS NEXT PART OF
THE SHOW IS FOR ALL YOU
YOUNG PEOPLE OUT THERE,
YOU DESERVE THIS.
>>HAROLD: HI AND WELCOME
ADVENTURE SEEKERS TO THE
FIRST EDITION EVER OF.
♪ TRUMPET BLOWING ♪
>>HAROLD: POSSUM LODGE CADETS!
OKAY, WELL POSSUM LODGE CADETS
ARE FOR THOSE OF US WHO AREN'T
YOU KNOW OFFICIAL MEMBERS OF
THE REAL, ACTUAL POSSUM LODGE.
BUT THAT'S ONLY BECAUSE WE
DON'T BELIEVE IN THEIR RULES,
THEIR ATTITUDES AND WELL, OKAY,
THEY WON'T LET US JOIN.
BUT I'LL BET YOU BEING A POSSUM
LODGE CADET IS EVEN WAY MORE
BETTER, I BET YOU IT IS, OKAY.
SO YOU WANT TO MAKE
A UNIFORM RIGHT?
NO PROBLEMO, COOL HUH?
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, SO ALL YOU
NEED FOR A UNIFORM IS LIKE
CLOTHES YOU KNOW AND SOME
SCISSORS, AN OFFICIAL POSSUM
LODGE HAT YOU KNOW AND A FEW
INCIDENTALS AND THEN OF COURSE
YOU'RE GOING TO WANT TO HAVE
A MEETING, SO YOU HAVE TO HAVE
AT LEAST ONE OTHER PERSON TO
JOIN THE POSSUM LODGE CADETS
WHICH AT THIS POINT I AM FINDING
TO BE YOU KNOW TO BE THE
HARDEST PART, BUT WHAT I DO.
>>RED: HAROLD I NEED ANOTHER
BUNGEE CORD, I PUTTING SOME
LUMBER ON THE ROOF RACK THERE.
>>HAROLD: NO UNCLE RED, NO, NO,
THIS IS LIKE AN OFFICIAL
CADET TIE NOW.
>>RED: WELL FINE YOU CAN
LEAVE IT ON IF YOU LIKE.
>>HAROLD: CADETS ENJOY
ACTION FILLED DANGER,
MOMENT TO MOMENT EXCITEMENT.
>>RED: I KNOW YOU TEENAGERS
WATCH A WHOLE LOT OF TELEVISION
AND YOU GET KIND OF A MIXED UP
IDEA OF WHAT THE WORLD'S
REALLY LIKE.
THE WORST THING IS TV MAKES
CRIME LOOK GOOD WHERE ACTUALLY
CRIME IS BAD, FIRST OF ALL
THERE IS NO SUCH THING AS
A CRIMINAL MASTERMIND OKAY,
THE PRISON POPULATION IS
NOT A BRAIN TRUST.
IF YOU EVER SKIM THROUGH
THE MUG SHOTS DOWN AT
THE POLICE STATION THERE,
YOU KNOW YOU'RE NOT LOOKING
AT THE M.I.T. GRADUATING CLASS.
AND IF YOU'RE A CRIMINAL,
ONE OF THESE GUYS ARE GOING
TO BE YOUR ROOMMATE FOR
THE NEXT 20 YEARS.
ALSO IF YOU GET INTO THE
CRIMINAL LINE OF WORK YOU
GOT TO WORK A LOT OF NIGHTS.
THERE IS ZERO BENEFITS AND
NOBODY IS GOING TO COME TO
YOUR PATIO PARTY BECAUSE
THEY'RE AFRAID THERE'S GOING
TO BE A DRIVE-BY SHOOTING.
DESPITE WHAT YOU SEE
ON TELEVISION, MOST CRIMINALS
EITHER GET CAUGHT OR KILLED
OR THEY HAVE TO CHANGE THEIR
IDENTITY AND MOVE TO A COUNTRY
WHERE THERE'S NOTHING
WORTH STEALING.
SO I'M ASKING YOU TO JUST
SAY NO TO ASSAULT,
BREAK AND ENTER, ARSON,
MURDER, THEFT, DRUG TRAFFICKING
AND OH YEAH, REAL ESTATE SALES.
>>RED: JOSHUA TWO FEATHERS
IS A REAL ESTATE DEVELOPER
ON THE RESERVE NEXT DOOR
TO THE LODGE AND I THOUGHT
HE MIGHT HAVE SOME ADVICE
ABOUT THE UNDERGROUND
PARKING LOT.
>>JOSHUA: THIS WAS HANDED
DOWN TO ME BY MY FATHER.
>>RED: WOW IT'S LIKE AN
INDIAN LEGEND OR SOMETHING.
>>JOSHUA: THIS IS A GEOLOGICAL
SURVEY OF THE WATER TABLE
DRAINAGE PATTERNS.
NOW YOU SEE HERE HOW THE
WATER COMES CLOSE TO
GROUND LEVEL?
>>RED: YEAH.
>>JOSHUA: YOU COULDN'T DIG
A BASEMENT FOR A TOWNHOUSE
WITHOUT HITTING WATER,
FORGET THE UNDERGROUND
PARKING LOT RED UNLESS YOU
CAN CONVERT IT TO A CARWASH.
>>RED: WELL ARE YOU SURE
THE CHART IS ACCURATE JOSHUA?
I MEAN I'D HATE TO CHANGE ALL
OUR PLANS JUST BECAUSE OF SOME
OLD PIECE OF PAPER AND WHAT
IT HAS TO SAY.
>>JOSHUA: CAREFUL WHAT YOU
SAY RED, I WON'T LET YOU
DISHONOUR MY FATHER,
HE HAD A P.H.D. IN
URBAN PLANNING.
>>RED: WELL JUST LIKE
I TOLD THEM, THE DARN PARKING
LOT ALL FLOODED THERE
AND 14 CARS UP TO THEIR
DOOR HANDLES IN WELL WATER
AND I'LL TELL YOU BY THE TIME
THOSE SEATS GET SATURATED
THERE'LL BE MORE MOLD
AROUND HERE THAN IN
A BACHELOR'S FRIDGE.
>>HAROLD: EXCUSE ME UNCLE RED,
WHAT ABOUT THE POSSUM VAN?
YOU WEREN'T CRAZY ENOUGH LIKE
TO PARK THE POSSUM VAN
IN THERE WERE YOU?
>>RED: OH NO, NO, NO HAROLD,
TRIED TO BUT SHE'S JUST
A LITTLE TAD HIGH THERE AND
SHE KIND OF WEDGED INTO
THE ENTRANCE YOU KNOW,
SO THAT WAS A LIFESAVER
BUT UNFORTUNATELY THIS OF
COURSE PREVENTED THE OTHERS
FROM GETTING IN AND GETTING
THEIR CARS AND I NEVER WOULD
HAVE GUESSED THE SHORT TEMPER
ON SOME OF THESE LODGE MEMBERS.
BUT IT'LL WORK OUT OKAY,
THEN WE GOT THE IDEA THAT
YOU KNOW IF WE COULD RAISE
THE WATER PRESSURE,
MAYBE WE COULD JUST POP
THE VAN OUT OF THERE.
SO WE STARTED THINKING ABOUT
THE WATER TABLE AND SO ON
AND WE FIGURED WE'D GET
MOOSE THOMPSON TO CANNONBALL
DOWN THE WELL AND I THINK
IT WOULD OF WORKED HAROLD,
BUT WELL WE FORGET TO TAKE
THE BUCKET OUT FIRST AND
I THINK WE SHOULD OF GREASED
THE SIDES BECAUSE HE SEIZED
UP ABOUT 30 FEET DOWN.
WE'LL GET HIM OUT,
WE'LL JUST POUR SOME BACON
FAT DOWN THE WALLS OVER THERE
AND WINCH HIM UP ON THE ROPE,
BUT HE'S GOT TO TAKE THOSE
SPLINTERS OUT ON HIS OWN.
>>HAROLD: OKAY WHOA!
MAYBE YOU KNOW WE GOT THAT
PARKING PROBLEM STORY,
YOU MIGHT JUST WANT TO
YOU KNOW STICK TO THAT.
>>RED: YEAH I THINK WE'LL
BE ALL RIGHT, I MEAN IF WORSE
COMES TO WORSE WE'LL JUST WAIT
FOR THE WINTER BECAUSE
THE VAN WILL BE COLD,
SHE'LL SHRINK A BIT AND THE
ENTRANCE WILL FREEZE UP
AND I THINK SHE'LL JUST POP
RIGHT OUT OF THERE.
>>HAROLD: OKAY BUT, WELL
CONSIDER THIS, MAYBE THE OTHER
CARS WILL LIKE FREEZE WHERE
THEY ARE, THEY'LL GET
STUCK IN THERE.
>>RED: WELL IF THAT HAPPENS
WE'LL GIVE THEM THEIR
$3 BUCKS BACK.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH THAT'S THE
SQUEAL OF THE POSSUM,
THAT'S MEETING TIME UNCLE RED
WE BETTER GET GOING.
>>RED: YEAH, OKAY.
YOU GO AHEAD HAROLD,
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
>>HAROLD: WELL OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING AND I'M SORRY
I DIDN'T STRIKE GOLD THIS WEEK,
BUT I DIDN'T STRIKE HAROLD
EITHER SO YOU GOT TO BE
PROUD OF ME AND TO ALL
OF THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca