SOMEBODY SAID THAT EVERY
PERSON
GETS FIFTEEN
MINUTES OF FAME
A GUY NAMED ANDY WARHOL,
WHOEVER HE IS.
A LOT OF MEN SECRETLY
DREAM OF BEING FAMOUS,
OF BEING NOTICED,
OF STANDING OUT
IN THE CROWD.
YOU CAN TELL THAT BY
THE FACES THEY MAKE
IN THE SECURITY CAMERA
AT THE 7/11.
IT'S NOT THAT WE'RE
STARVED FOR ATTENTION,
IT'S JUST THAT WE HAVE
SUCH A HUGE APPETITE
FOR IT.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT MAKES
US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red Green: ON TODAY'S SHOW,
BUZZ SHERWOOD'S GOING
TO DO SOME
RENOVATIONS TO
HIS BUSH PLANE,
I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU SOME SAFETY TIPS
USING A POWER DRILL,
BILL IS GOING TO
SHOW YOU HOW TO HAVE
YOUR KAYAK AND BEAT IT, TOO
AND EDGAR K.B. MONTROSE
IS GOING TO BLOW OFF
A LITTLE STEAM.
AND NOW HERE HE IS,
THE BIGGEST STAR IN
THE GREAT OUTDOORS
SINCE GODZILLA,
MY UNCLE RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH AND
WELCOME TO POSSUM LODGE
WHERE MEN ARE MEN
AND HAROLD IS MY NEPHEW.
HELLO WORLD.
BYE EARTH.
REAL EXCITING
STUFF THIS WEEK.
APPARENTLY POSSUM LAKE
IS THE SITE OF A
UFO INVASION
WITH SPACE CREATURES
LANDING RIGHT HERE.
NO, THAT'S JUST OLD
MAN SEDGWICK IN HIS
UNDERWEAR.
NO, HAROLD.
STINKY RENTED
SOME BOATS TO A
COUPLE OF AMERICANS THERE
AND HE FIGURES THEY'RE
HERE TO TRACK THE UFO
SPACE ALIEN CREATURES
COMING INTO TOWN.
THEY SAID THEY WERE
JUST FISHING BUT HEY
THEY DIDN'T HAVE ANY
FISHING EQUIPMENT.
WELL THAT'S OKAY, POSSUM
LAKE DOESN'T HAVE
ANY FISH.
UNCLE RED, OKAY, MAYBE
THEY'RE NOT HERE TO FISH
BUT WHAT WOULD LEAD YOU
TO SUSPECT THE FACT
THAT THEY'RE
CHASING ALIENS?
YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN
WATCHING TOO MANY
EPISODES
OF THE X FILES.
NO, HAROLD, THEY HAD
STRANGE BLACK LUGGAGE
AND CASES WITH STRANGE
METAL PARTS IN IT.
STINKY SAID HE'S NEVER
SEEN ANYTHING LIKE IT,
SO HE FIGURES IT MUST
BE AN ALIEN LIFE
FORM DETECTOR.
WHY WOULD IT HAVE
TO BE THAT?
BECAUSE STINKY'S
NEVER SEEN AN ALIEN
LIFE FORM DETECTOR EITHER,
SO IT KIND OF MAKES SENSE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER
CAN'T YOU UNDERSTAND
SIMPLE LOGIC, HAROLD?
NOT THAT SIMPLE.
UNCLE RED, IT COULD
BE ANY NUMBER OF THINGS
STINKY HASN'T SEEN BEFORE,
LIKE A BOOK, AN OPERA,
A BAR OF SOAP.
[ MAKING BUZZING SOUND ]
HOW'S IT GOING?
OH, THEY'RE WEIGHING THE
FISH AT THE FISH WEIGH IN
DOWN AT
MERCURY CREEK
FIRST PRIZE IS A BOAT
AND THOUSAND BUCKS
FOR THE BIGGEST
FISH OF THE WEEK
I CAUGHT ME A NICE
LITTLE SUNFISH
IT'S GOING TO MAKE
ME A WINNER
NOT FROM THE WEIGHT
OF THE FISH ITSELF
BUT FROM THE BALL BEARINGS
I FED IT FOR DINNER
ALL RIGHT, LAST NIGHT
YOU WENT TO A PARTY
WITH YOUR WIFE OR YOUR
GIRLFRIEND OR YOUR
FEMALE COMPANION.
WELL, YEAH, YOUR
SIGNIFICANT MOTHER, EH?
AND TODAY YOU'RE
FINDING OUT THAT
YOU DID NOT
HAVE QUITE AS
GOOD A TIME AS
YOU THOUGHT YOU DID.
THIS IS BECAUSE YOUR
PARTNER DID NOT
APPRECIATE
YOU IGNORING HER
TOTALLY, EH,
OR FLIRTING
WITH OTHER WOMEN
OR DOING THAT
OLD PARTY TRICK,
YOU KNOW THAT
ONE YOU USED TO
DO WHERE YOU'D PLAY
"GOD SAVE THE QUEEN"
BY MAKING THEM LOUD
WET SOUNDS
WITH VARIOUS PARTS
OF YOUR BODY?
AMAZING HOW MANY PEOPLE
DON'T APPRECIATE LIVE
ENTERTAINMENT.
ANYWAY, YOU GOT
YOURSELF INTO A
BIT OF A JAM
AND YOU NEED
OUR HELP TO GET
OUT OF THE SITUATION.
WHENEVER YOU CAN
BLAME THE BOOZE, EH?
ABSOLUTELY.
OH, YEAH.
JUST SAY TO YOUR WIFE
OR YOUR SIGNIFICANT
MOTHER THERE
THAT YOU
WERE OVERSERVED.
YOU KNOW, AND YOU JUST
WEREN'T ACTING YOURSELF.
OF COURSE NOW
IF YOU DON'T DRINK,
THAT'S UNFORTUNATE,
BECAUSE IT FORCES
YOU TO LIE.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO SAY, WELL,
I'M SORRY
I WAS UPSET ABOUT,
I DON'T KNOW,
THE DEATH OF A CLOSE
FRIEND OR SOMETHING.
OKAY, BUT NOW YOU
KNOW SHE'S GOING
TO SAY WHO DIED
AND YOU'RE GOING
TO BE EXPECTED TO
COME UP WITH A NAME.
JUST SAYING OLD
WHAT'S HIS NAME
IS PROBABLY NOT
GOING TO CUT IT.
NO.
WHAT I LIKE TO DO
IS I LIKE TO NAME A
FRIEND FROM THE PAST
THAT I REALLY DON'T
CARE IF I EVER
SEE AGAIN.
YEAH.
THAT'S GOOD.
OR YOU COULD TAKE
THE TOUGH ROUTE
AND JUST SAY,
HEY, THAT'S THE WAY
I AM AT PARTIES
AND THAT WILL
BE THE END OF THAT.
YEAH, BUT THAT WILL
ALSO BE THE END
OF YOU EVER GOING
TO PARTIES WITH HER
OR ANYWHERE
WITH HER AGAIN
WITH ANYBODY.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
SO I GUESS THE
BEST THING IS JUST
TO SEE HER SIDE OF IT
AND STOP ACTING
LIKE A WIENER.
UNLESS OF COURSE
YOU'RE A HEAVY DRINKER,
WHICH, AS WE SAY, GETS
YOU OFF SCOTCH FREE, EH?
WELL, WITH ALL THIS
TALK OF ALIENS SPYING ON US,
I THOUGHT I WOULD TAKE THIS
WEEK'S HANDYMAN CORNER,
SHOW YOU HOW YOU CAN
BUILD YOUR VERY
OWN TELESCOPE.
MAYBE YOU CAN DO SOME
SPYING ON THE ALIENS
OR SCAN THE CORE OF
THE CENTRE OF THE GALAXY
OR CHECK OUT THE WINDOWS
IN THE HOUSES
IN YOUR AREA.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, FOR
STARTERS YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED A CEMENT MIXER,
WHICH ACTUALLY YOU
CAN GET FOR FREE
IF YOU HAVE AFTER-HOURS
ACCESS TO YOUR LOCAL
CONSTRUCTION SITE.
FIRST THING YOU WANT
TO DO IS TO MAKE
THE INSIDE OF THE CEMENT
MIXER A REFLECTIVE
SURFACE.
YOU CAN DO THAT BY
PUTTING THE CHROME
PLATE IN THERE
OR MAYBE LINING HER
WITH TINFOIL,
BUT I
RECOMMEND THE HANDYMAN
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
JUST GET IN THERE.
GET RIGHT IN AND STICK
HER ON THE SIDES
AND UP INTO THE BACK
AND GET ALL THE CORNERS
AND ANYTHING WHERE
THE LIGHT IS GOING
TO POSSIBLY HIT BACK.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU JUST BASICALLY LINE
THE WHOLE INSIDE
OF HER THERE.
NOW WE COME TO THE
REALLY HARD PART
OF THE PROJECT,
YOU HAVE TO
EAT SOME SALAD.
NOT BECAUSE IT'S
GOOD FOR YOU
BUT BECAUSE WE NEED
TO USE THE BOWL
AS OUR PRIMARY LENS
FOR THE TELESCOPE.
NOW THE SALAD BOWL LENS
THERE WILL CATCH
ALL THE LIGHT,
FIRE IT DOWN
INSIDE THE MIXER
WHERE IT BOUNCES
AROUND ON THE DUCT TAPE
AND THEN IT WILL COME
OUT THE HOLE THAT
I'VE DRILLED.
I'M GLAD THAT
WASN'T MY DRILL BIT.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW TO FOCUS
THE LIGHT EVEN MORE,
YOU GET ONE OF THESE
DRAIN TRAPS OUT OF
YOUR KITCHEN SINK
AND YOU TAKE
THE ELBOWS APART.
AND YOU WANT
TO PUT A LITTLE
MIRROR IN EACH ELBOW.
NOW YOU'RE SAYING
TO YOURSELF,
WHERE AM I GOING
TO FIND A MIRROR
THAT SMALL?
HOW ABOUT RIGHT
IN FRONT OF YOUR EYES?
STICK THAT IN,
ONE AT EACH ELBOW
AT A 45-DEGREE ANGLE
FACING EACH OTHER
AND THEN YOU MOUNT
THE WHOLE RIG BACK
INTO THE HOLE THAT WE MADE.
I WOULD WAIT UNTIL
SHE COOLED DOWN FIRST.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE ALL SET TO BE
THE PEEPING TOM OF
THE UNIVERSE.
AND THE BEAUTY OF
THE CEMENT MIXER RIG
IS WITH ALL THE
GEARS AND LEVERS AND
THE WAY SHE'S MOUNTED HERE,
YOU CAN PRETTY MUCH
AIM IT AT WHATEVER IT
IS YOU WANT TO LOOK AT.
YOU CAN TUNE IN
MARS OR SATURN
OR EVEN LOOK
UP YOUR URANUS.
WOW, THE MILKY WAY
IS ALL GREEN
AND LEAFY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
OH FOR GOSH SAKES.
THERE'S A PIECE OF
DRIED SALAD ON THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TRY THAT AGAIN.
WHOA.
THE SUN IS BRIGHT.
MAN.
I'LL TELL YOU, THOUGH,
THE TELESCOPE WORKS GREAT,
I CAN SEE A BLACK
HOLE, EVERYWHERE.
SO REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
THIS IS MORE THAN
A TELESCOPE,
IT'S ALSO A
GREAT FIRE STARTER.
Red Green: STAY TUNED,
BILL AND I ARE GOING
TO HAVE A RUN IN
OUT ON POSSUM LAKE
AND HAROLD IS
EITHER EXCITED ABOUT
GETTING INTO THE MOVIES
OR INTO
THE WASHROOM.
I WANT TO TALK TO ANY
OF YOU GUYS WHO HAVE BEEN
MARRIED TO THE SAME
WOMAN FOR 20 YEARS OR MORE.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GOING THROUGH.
BERNICE AND I
ARE IN OUR 28TH
YEAR OF CONTROLLED BLISS.
I KNOW IT TAKES A
LITTLE EXTRA TO KEEP
'ER GOING THAT LONG.
IT SEEMS THAT AFTER
ABOUT 20 YEARS
OF MARRIAGE,
THE MARRIAGE TURNS
INTO KIND OF LIKE
A ROUTINE.
SORT OF LIKE
BEING ON A DIET,
LOSING A WHOLE
BUNCH OF WEIGHT
AND THEN THEY
PUT YOU ON WHAT THEY
CALL A MAINTENANCE DIET.
YEAH, A LOT OF
MARRIAGES TURN INTO A
MAINTENANCE DIET, YOU KNOW.
YOU GOT TO HAVE
A LITTLE NIBBLE
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE
BUT THERE'S A GENERAL
EMBARGO ON PIGGING OUT.
WELL, IT SEEMS TO ME
THAT THIS IS ALL
BACKWARDS,
NOW 'CAUSE WHEN
YOU'RE YOUNG
AND AS GOOD LOOKING
AS YOU'RE GOING TO GET,
YOU DON'T NEED ANYBODY
MAKING A FUSS OVER
YOU AT THAT TIME
BECAUSE YOU GOT
LOTS OF ALTERNATIVES,
YOU CAN GET
ANYBODY YOU WANT.
BUT WHEN YOU'VE
GROWN A LITTLE OLDER,
MAYBE PUT ON A COUPLE
HUNDRED POUNDS OR SO,
AND YOUR FACE LOOKS
LIKE NOLAN RYAN'S GLOVE
AND YOU ARE PRETTY
MUCH OUT OF ALTERNATIVES.
SO I SAY THE LONGER
YOU'VE BEEN MARRIED,
THE MORE AFFECTIONATE
YOU SHOULD BE WITH
EACH OTHER.
GET OFF THE MAINTENANCE
DIET AND GO NUTS.
BUT NOT ON THE
DINING ROOM TABLE.
AT LEAST NOT UNTIL
THE KIDS MOVE OUT,
ALL RIGHT?
I'M PULLING FOR
YOU 'CAUSE WE'RE
ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, BUSTER AND STINKY
HAVE BEEN SPYING
ON THESE AMERICANS
POSING AS FISHERMEN
AND THEY ARE DEFINITELY
TRACKING UFO SPACE ALIENS.
AND HOW DO
YOU KNOW THIS?
DID YOU TALK
TO THEM, UNCLE RED?
OH, HAROLD, YOU
DON'T TALK TO THEM.
THEY'LL JUST
DENY EVERYTHING
AND THEN FORCE
YOU TO SWALLOW
THE CYANIDE CAPSULE.
I FIGURE THESE GUYS
ARE MAYBE WITH THE CIA
OR PERHAPS A SPECIAL
BRANCH OF THE POST OFFICE.
EVERYTHING IS VERY,
VERY HUSH-HUSH, HAROLD.
WELL THEN WHY DON'T
ALL YOU GUYS JUST
SHUT UP ABOUT IT?
NOTHING.
I DIDN'T -- WHAT?
I GOT PROOF
HERE, HAROLD.
LOOK AT THIS PICTURE
BUSTER TOOK.
YOU TELL ME, IS THAT
NOT AN ALIEN SPACE PAD
LANDING SUPPORT
RIGHT THERE?
IT'S A TRIPOD FOR
A CAMERA, UNCLE RED.
NO, NO, LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S AN ALIEN LIFE
FORM DETECTOR IF I
EVER SAW ONE.
NO, THAT'S
A MOVIE CAMERA.
WELL HOW ABOUT
THIS UFO RADAR UNIT?
WHAT'S THAT THEN?
MOVIE LIGHT.
OH, I SEE.
ALL RIGHT.
THEY'RE SHOOTING FILM
FOOTAGE OF THE
SPACE ALIENS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU GUYS.
YOU LET YOUR
IMAGINATIONS RUN WILD
AND YOU
EXTRAPOLATE NOTHING
INTO SOMETHING RIDICULOUS.
TWO GUYS SHOW UP
WITH A MOVIE CAMERA
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
THERE'S LIKE ALIENS
AND YOU'RE SPREADING
RUMOURS ABOUT UFOS.
MAYBE THEY'RE JUST
UP HERE, YOU KNOW,
SHOOTING A NATURE FILM,
YOU KNOW, OR SHOOTING
SHOTS FOR A TV COMMERCIAL
OR SCOUTING LOCATIONS FOR
SOME MAJOR HOLLYWOOD
PRODUCTION,
SOME BIG BUDGET FILM THAT'S
GOING TO BE SHOOTING HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE
IN A COUPLE OF
MONTHS, YOU KNOW?
SOME $50 MILLION SPECIAL
EFFECTS EXTRAVAGANZA
BASED ON A NUMBER
ONE BESTSELLER,
IT HAS TOM CRUISE
AND HARRISON FORD
AND JAMIE LEE CURTIS
AS MY LOVE INTEREST
AND SPECIAL SIDEKICK.
WE'RE GOING TO
BE MOVIE STARS!
YOU GUYS!
HERE'S ONE.
HOW MANY FOREST RANGERS
DOES IT TAKE TO CHANGE
A LIGHTBULB?
JUST ONE.
IF HE HAD A
LIGHTBULB OF COURSE.
DO THEY STILL
HAVE LIGHTBULBS?
THROUGHOUT THE WORLD
YOU WILL NOT FIND
A SMALL PLANE BEING
AS BIG A PART
OF HISTORY
AS IT IS IN THE
CANADIAN NORTH.
AND SO IN A CERTAIN
WAY BUZZ SHERWOOD HERE,
IS PART OF A LONG
AVIATION TRADITION.
ON A WING AND A PRAYER,
THAT'S ME, RED.
ESPECIALLY IF THERE'S
SUPPOSED TO BE
TWO WINGS.
YEAH, YOU GOT
TO HAVE A --
YOU GOT TO
HAVE A LOVE,
YOU GOT TO FEEL THE
ROMANCE OF FLYING, RED.
I MEAN,
WOMEN LOVE IT.
THAT'S WHAT
THEY TELL ME.
AND, YOU KNOW, YOU
GOT TO BE A RISK
TAKER, RIGHT,
BECAUSE YOU KNOW
YOU GET OLD AND
COMFORTABLE LIKE YOU,
NO, THIS IS A GAME
FOR THE YOUNG KIDS
BECAUSE US YOUNG KIDS
WE TAKE ALL THE RISK.
WE KNOW HOW TO BE
SELF-RELIANT WITH
WHAT'S AT HAND, YOU KNOW?
LIKE THIS.
LOOK AT THIS
HANDY WORK, HUH?
WHAT IS THIS THING,
A WIND VANE OF SOME KIND?
NO, IT'S A NEW
PROPELLER FOR MY PLANE.
SEE I FIGURE FOUR
PADDLES WILL GIVE
ME MORE LIFT
'CAUSE I GOT A LOT
OF DELIVERIES TO
MAKE, YOU KNOW.
I GOT TO GET ALL THIS
STUFF UP TO A COUPLE
OF GUYS FISHING
AND THERE'S TWO MORE
MINERS UP THERE,
THEY'RE WAITING
FOR THAT BOX.
AND THEN WHAT ELSE
HAVE WE GOT HERE?
LOOK AT THIS STUFF.
THERE'S A MINING COMPANY
WANTS THAT FIRST AID KIT.
I GOT SOME SMOKE
JUMPERS, NATURAL
RESOURCES,
A BOY SCOUT CREW
AND TWO PEOPLE
UP IN TUCAHA INLET.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE
TUCAHA INLET IS?
JUST THIS SIDE OF
THE INLET, I BELIEVE.
OH, WELL,
THERE YOU GO.
AND THEN THOSE TWO
GUYS UP HERE FILMING,
THEY WANT SOME STUFF.
AND I'M GOING TO
NEED EIGHT PADDLES
TO GET THIS STUFF UP.
THE TWO GUYS FILMING
NOW, WHEN YOU WERE
FLYING THEM
DID THEY SAY EXACTLY
WHAT IT IS THEY'RE
FILMING?
NO, NO.
THEY JUST SPENT
THE WHOLE TIME
TALKING INTO THE
AIR SICKNESS BAG,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
YEAH, 'CAUSE HAROLD,
HERE THINKS THEY'RE
FROM HOLLYWOOD.
HOLLYWOOD?
REALLY HAROLD?
FAR OUT.
YEAH.
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
THEY MIGHT NEED LIKE
SOME STUNT FLYING SHOTS
AND THOSE GUYS MAKE
A TON OF DOUGH WHEN
YOU DO STUNT FLYING.
WOAH, I'M OUT OF HERE.
SEE YOU LATER RED.
YOU SEE HOW IT
WORKS KIDS,
IF YOU WANT TO BE
A BUSH PILOT
ALL IT TAKES IS A
LITTLE SELF-RELIANCE,
THE LOVE OF ROMANCE.
A PILOT'S LICENSE
MIGHT BE A NICE TOUCH.
BUZZ, WHAT ABOUT ALL
THE STUFF ON THE SIDES?
WANTED, THINGY YOU PUT
ON THE END OF A DO-HICKY,
ONE OF THE OLD ONES
THEY DON'T MAKE ANYMORE
THAT HAS THAT WHAT'S-IT
ON THE MAIN PART,
CONTACT OCCUPANT.
I MAY HAVE ONE OF THOSE.
Red Green: KIND OF A
HISTORICAL THING THIS
WEEK WITH THE KAYAKING.
OH, THERE'S BILL.
THERE'S BILL
AND HIS KAYAK,
SO I THOUGHT I WOULD
JUST DO THE RIGHT THING
AND HELP HIM
INTO THE WATER.
HE'S ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW THE THING
WITH A KAYAK IS
IT'S A VERY
HISTORICAL VESSEL.
LONG BEFORE
THE WHITE MAN,
YOU KNOW, THERE
WAS THE INUIT AND
THE ESKIMOS, WHATEVER IT IS,
THEY HAD THE KAYAKS.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, BILL?
OH I THINK HE'S GOT
HIMSELF A LITTLE
WEDGED IN THERE.
IT'S HARD TO GET
INTO THE KAYAK.
I GUESS THE INUIT WERE
A LITTLE SLIMMER THAN
THE BILLUIT.
HERE WE GO.
AND WE GOT HIM IN THERE.
YOU GOT TO PUT THE
FEET IN THERE FIRST,
THAT'S IT, LEAVE
THE BUTT 'TIL LATER.
AND DO YOU
GOT THE HELMET?
DO YOU WANT THE
HELMET ON THERE, BILL?
BILL?
BILL NEEDS TWO HELMETS,
ONE TO BE
WEARING WHILE HE'S
GETTING THE OTHER HELMET.
AND NOW HE'S --
YOU SEE THE PADDLE
THAT'S GOT THE DOUBLE END,
THAT'S A VERY
UNIQUE DESIGN.
IT WORKS WELL TO
CLEAR THINGS OUT
OF THE WAY.
AND OUT HE GOES
OUT INTO THE WATER.
NOW, THE THING
WITH A KAYAK IS THEY'RE
VERY, VERY MANEUVERABLE.
LOOK AT THIS, IT'S
LIKE A HELICOPTER
ON WATER.
HE CAN BACK UP THERE
AND HE CAN JUST TURN
ON A DIME.
AND YOU KNOW THE
THING TO DO,
THEY DO WHAT THEY CALL
THE ESKIMO ROLL
WHERE THEY --
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S HALF
AN ESKIMO ROLL.
BUT LOOK AT THE
MANEUVERABILITY.
LOOK HOW HE CAN EVEN
STEER IT AND PADDLE IT.
LOOK AT HIM.
LOOK AT THAT.
AND BILL LOOKED
LIKE HE WOULD BE
GOOD AT THINGS, YOU KNOW.
WAIT.
NOW THIS DOESN'T --
THIS DOESN'T LOOK -- NO.
IT'S STARTING TO DAWN
ON ME THAT BILL
MAY BE HAVING A
LITTLE DIFFICULTY,
SO I FIRE UP
THE BIG INBOARD,
BOY SHE'S SOUNDING ROUGH,
AND OUT WE GO
TO GET HIM.
YOU KNOW WITH THE KAYAKS,
THEY GOT THE LOW
PROFILE THERE
AND THE BOAT SITS
UP HIGH IN THE WATER,
YOU CAN'T ALWAYS
SEE THEM UNFORTUNATELY.
OH, OH, OH, SORRY,
SORRY, SORRY!
BILL?
OH, HE'S ALL RIGHT.
TURNED HIS
KAYAK INTO FOUR-WHEEL
DRIVE, VERY IMPRESSIVE.
Red Green: STAY TUNED
AS HAROLD REENACTS
THE GUN FIGHT
AT HOKIE CORRAL
AND RANGER GORD
SHOWS US A QUICK WAY
TO GET DOWN
FROM THE TOWER.
[ GUNSHOTS ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
BAD NEWS,
HAROLD, THEY'RE NOT
SHOOTING LONESOME DORK.
WELL, OKAY.
WELL, PERSONALLY,
YOU KNOW, I'M HOPING
THEY'RE DOING A COMEDY,
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE
I'D LOVE TO BE IN
A TEENAGE SEX FARCE.
HAROLD, YOU ARE A
TEENAGE SEX FARCE.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S
HOPING IT'S GOING
TO BE A SCI-FI
SO HE'S RUNNING AROUND
TELLING EVERYBODY THAT
HE'S AN OKI FROM KENOKI.
UNCLE RED, I THINK HE
MEANS OBI WAN KENOBI.
YEAH, HE KEEPS SAYING,
LUKE FEEL THE FORK.
[ LAUGHTER ]
AND HE TRIES TO
GET YOU TO FIGHT HIM
WITH A ROLL OF LIFESAVERS.
THAT'S LIGHTSABER.
IN THE MOVIE STAR WARS
THEY USE LIGHTSABERS.
WHAT IS WITH EVERYBODY?
WE ALREADY HAVE A
TELEVISION SHOW,
WHY WOULD WE WANT
TO BE IN THE MOVIES?
OH, UNCLE RED, MOVIES
ARE WAY MORE BETTER
THAN TELEVISION.
LOOK AT ALL THE CLASSIC FILMS
THAT HAVE JUST BEEN RELEASED
LATELY, OKAY,
LIKE BEVERLY HILLBILLIES,
ADAM'S FAMILY,
FLINTSTONES, STAR TREK.
HAROLD, THOSE ARE
TELEVISION SHOWS.
OKAY.
RIGHT.
YES.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW
THEY'RE GOING TO DO
A FEATURE FILM
OUT OF WHEEL
OF FORTUNE,
IT WILL BE PAT SAJAK
AND CISSY SPACEK
IN "A VOWEL RUNS
THROUGH IT."
Red Green: HERE WE ARE UP
AT FIRE TOWER 13,
50 MILES FROM
THE NEAREST PERSON,
100 MILES FROM TOWN,
COMPLETELY ISOLATED
AND CUT OFF FROM
EVERYTHING,
MR. ISOLATION
HIMSELF, RANGER GORD.
HI FOLKS.
THAT'S HIM, CUT OFF
AND ISOLATED,
ARE YOU NOT UP HERE
RANGER GORD?
OH ABSOLUTELY
NO WAY TO GET
WORD IN OR OUT.
BY THE THE WAY, I HEAR
THERE'S A MOVIE CREW
OVER AT POSSUM LODGE.
I HOPE THEY'RE DOING
A COMEDY 'CAUSE I
LOVE SLAPSTICK.
WELL, HOW DID
HEAR ABOUT THAT WHEN
YOU'RE CUT OFF AND ISOLATED?
OH, WELL, HAROLD TOLD
ME WHEN WE WERE WAITING
FOR MR. HUFF AND PUFF
TO CLIMB THE STAIRS.
RIGHT HAROLD?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, TELL OUR
VIEWERS, RANGER GORD,
WHAT DO YOU DO UP
HERE WHEN YOU NEED
A MEDICAL PROFESSIONAL
OF SOME KIND?
WELL, USUALLY I JUST
GO TALK TO A SPECIAL
BIG ROCK I KNOW.
BEST PSYCHIATRIST
I EVER HAD.
STRICTLY JUNGIAN
BY THE WAY.
NO, NO, NO, I'M
TALKING ABOUT A
MEDICAL EMERGENCY,
YOU KNOW,
LIKE INJURIES.
LIKE WHERE DO YOU
KEEP YOUR FIRST
AID KIT?
OH, IT'S AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE STAIRS.
WHAT IF YOU HAVE AN
ACCIDENT UP HERE
IN THIS AREA?
OH, I NEVER DO, RED.
ONLY ONE KIND OF
MEDICAL EMERGENCY
HAPPENS AT MY TOWER
AND I HAVE EVERYTHING
I NEED RIGHT THERE.
LET ME SHOW YOU.
NO, NO, WAIT,
WAIT, WHAT IS THE
ONE KIND OF EMERGENCY?
OH, WELL, SOMETIMES
I DON'T LOOK WHERE
I'M GOING
AND I'LL TRIP
AND I'LL FALL.
[ FALLING DOWN STAIRS ]
OW! OW! OW!
HE'S ALL RIGHT.
[ CONTINUES FALLING ]
OW!!!
NO, MAYBE NOT.
OH BOY.
OH FOR GOSH SAKES.
YEAH, SEE, RED, I --
I HAVE EVERYTHING I
NEED RIGHT OVER THERE,
SPLINTS AND ICE
PACKS AND STUFF
LIKE THAT, YOU KNOW?
Red:
YOU OKAY, GORD?
OH YEAH.
I LOVE SLAPSTICK.
OKAY, THIS WEEK
ON THE EXPERT'S
PORTION OF THE SHOW,
JOINING MY UNCLE RED
IS MR. EDGAR K.B. MONTROSE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, HERE GOES
THE LETTER AND IT'S
FROM HELEN OF HELENA, MONTANA.
HELEN OF HELENA,
ISN'T THAT --
THAT'S COOL, EH,
BECAUSE --
ALRIGHTY,
I'LL JUST READ.
DEAR EXPERTS, I'M
DRIVING A SIX
YEAR OLD CAR
WHICH IS NEEDING MORE
AND MORE REPAIRS
BUT I'M SURE ALL THE LOCAL
MECHANICS ARE CHEATING ME
BECAUSE I'M A WOMAN.
HOW CAN I GET
FAIR SERVICE?
OKAY.
JUST GET YOUR HUSBAND
TO TAKE IT INTO
THE SHOP,
THAT WILL FIX IT UP.
WELL, NOW, IF THIS
HELEN IS FROM HELENA
AND IT SOUNDS
LIKE SHE IS.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S
NOT SOLVING HER
PROBLEM, RED.
WHAT I RECOMMEND IS
SOMETHING I CALL
FOUR ON THE FLOOR
AND ONE
IN THE TANK.
ONE WHAT IN THE TANK?
STICK OF DYNAMITE.
YOU PUT FOUR STICKS
OF DYNAMITE ON
THE FLOOR
AND ONE STICK OF
DYNAMITE IN THE TANK
AND KABOOM!
NO MORE EXPENSIVE
CAR REPAIRS.
EXCUSE ME, BUT I
THINK BLOWING UP CARS
IS KIND OF
MISSING THE POINT.
THIS WOMAN JUST WANTS
TO BE TREATED FAIRLY.
ALL RIGHT.
JUST GO ON
INTO THE SHOP THERE
AND TELL THEM THAT
YOUR HUSBAND IS THE
GOVERNMENT INSPECTOR
THAT GIVES THE AUTO
MECHANIC'S LICENSE
AND THE SERVICE STATION
INSPECTIONS AND ALL
THAT KIND OF STUFF
AND TELL THEM THAT
HE'S THE ONE THAT
WANTS THE CAR FIXED.
YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE
THE SERVICE I GET
IN RESTAURANTS
WHEN I PRETEND I'M
A HEALTH INSPECTOR.
WELL, NO, YOU JUST
DON'T GET IT, RED.
WHAT THE WOMAN WANTS IS
TO BE ABLE TO WALK INTO
ANY GAS STATION,
LOOK THE MECHANIC RIGHT
SQUARE IN THE EYE,
EXPLAIN THE PROBLEM
AND GET TREATED FAIRLY.
EXACTLY.
YOU ARE SO
SENSITIVE, MR. MONTROSE.
OKAY.
NOW, I'VE GOT
ANOTHER PLAN,
WHAT I CALL FOUR
IN YOUR POCKETS AND
ONE TAPED TO YOUR HEAD.
NOW, BELIEVE ME, NOBODY
GETS BETTER SERVICE
OR MORE RESPECT
THAN A HUMAN BOMB.
WELL, WE GOT THE
MYSTERY ABOUT THE MOVIE
AND IT'S NOT
A MOVIE MYSTERY.
WE GOT IT ALL
STRAIGHTENED OUT.
[ CHEERING ]
HELLO, TIFFANY.
DON'T EVEN LAUGH.
I JUST HEARD THAT THE
FILM CREW IS HERE,
THEY'RE GOING TO
FILM A REMAKE OF
"SOME LIKE IT HOT."
THAT'S THE
COMEDY WHERE THE
TWO GUYS GET DRESSED UP
AND THEN ONE OF
THEM THEY GET TO
SLEEP WITH MARILYN MONROE.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
PLAYED BY DEMI MOORE
AND I HEARD THIS RUMOUR
COMES STRAIGHT FROM
THE TOP.
YEAH, IT DOES HAROLD,
I STARTED IT.
NO, NO, NO, BECAUSE IT'S
CALLED "SOME LIKE IT HOT."
YEAH, IT'S CALLED
"SOME LIKE IT HOT."
NO,IT'S A DOCUMENTARYT'S
CALLON GLOBAL WARMING.OT."
THIS IS TOTALLY
EMBARRASSING THEN.
YOU SHOULD SEE OLD
MAN SEDGWICK IN THAT
PINK CHIFFON NUMBER,
HE LOOKS LIKE
A COCKTAIL PRUNE.
IT TURNS OUT THE GUYS
LOOKING AT THE ALIENS
ARE ACTUALLY DOING AN
ENVIRONMENTAL PICTURE
ON A TOTAL ENVIRONMENTAL
COLLAPSE UP HERE.
THAT MEANS THEY'RE
GOING TO SHUT DOWN
POSSUM LODGE.
NO, IT'S OKAY, I BLAMED
ALL THE POLLUTION ON
BIG BUSINESS,
THEY LOVE THAT.
THAT REALLY
IS YOUR COLOUR,
YOU KNOW, HAROLD.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
THERE'S THE POSSUM CALL.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET
TO THE MEETING AND SEE
THE REST OF THE ROCKETTES.
I'M GOING
TO CHANGE FIRST.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING
AND I WON'T BE WEARING
WOMEN'S CLOTHING
SO PLEASE DON'T CONFUSE
ME WITH YOUR SISTER.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH
FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
WHATEVER WE CALL THAT,
AND THE WHOLE REST OF
THE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI
OKAY GUYS,
C'MON OUT NOW.