[fishing line whirring]
[man yawning]
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S A MAN
WHO'S A LITTLE BIT COUNTRY,
A LITTLE BIT CITY,
AND A GREAT DEAL OF BOG...
MY UNCLE, YOUR HOST, RED GREEN!
WAHOO!!
[applause]
[cheering and whistling]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU, UH...
HAD A BIT OF A CLOSE CALL
BUT WE'RE OKEY-DOKEY NOW.
STINKY PETERSON AND I
WERE JUST OUT FISHING, THERE,
WHERE THE POSSUM LODGE
SEWER OUTLET COMES DOWN.
BOTH OF US LOOKED AWAY
AT EXACTLY THE SAME MOMENT
AND EIGHT MILLION GALLONS
OF WHATEVER COME DOWN THERE
AND KNOCKED US OUT OF THE BOAT
INTO THE LAKE.
WE'RE OK NOW.
WOW! WERE YOU KILLED?
[audience laughing]
DO I LOOK LIKE I WAS KILLED?
YEAH.
I BET YOU WERE SCARED.
YOU MUST HAVE SCREAMED, LIKE...
AHHHHHH! AHHHHH!
DID YOU SCREAM LIKE "OHHHH"?
THEN YOU GET WATER
AND YOU GO "AHHHH!"
DID YOUR LIFE FLASH
BEFORE YOUR EYES?
IT IS NOW!
[audience laughing]
[horns honking]
[geese honking]
[quacking]
(Red): I'M GONNA MAKE
A LIFEJACKET OUT OF JELLY.
AND RANGER GORD GETS
SOME SPECIAL BADGES.
DALTON LOOKS FOR THE MISSING
WORD AROUND HERE: "JOB".
AND HAROLD TRIES...
WELL, I GUESS THAT'S RAP.
THERE, THAT'S BETTER.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN SCARED
WHEN YOU SAW THAT WATER
COMING AT YOU.
I SCREAMED TO STINKY.
I SAID, "IF GOD GETS US
OUT OF THIS ONE,
"I'LL NEVER MISS CHURCH AGAIN."
THIS HAND LIFTED ME UP
AND I SAW A TUNNEL
WITH A LIGHT AT THE END.
I WAS MOVING TOWARDS THE LIGHT.
WOW! UNCLE RED, YOU HAD
AN OUTER-BODY
NEAR-DEATH EXPERIENCE!
YES! OH, YES, YES!
I HEARD ABOUT THESE ON JOJO'S
PSYCHIC ALLIANCE HOTLINE.
YEAH! OH!
YOU FELT THE HAND OF GOD.
YOU SAW THE GATEWAY
TO THE AFTERLIFE.
I FELT MOOSE THOMPSON'S HAND.
I SAW POSSUM LODGE'S SEWER.
I WALKED OUT --
I'M FINE, HAROLD.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU
AT CHURCH.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU SAID IF GOD SAVED YOU,
YOU'D GO TO CHURCH.
GOD DIDN'T SAVE ME --
MOOSE DID.
COME ON,
UNCLE RED.
MOOSE WAS MERELY
GOD'S TOOL.
MOOSE IS EVERYBODY'S TOOL,
HAROLD.
NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO.
YOU GOTTA GO
TO CHURCH.
IF YOU DON'T,
YOU'LL TURN
INTO A PILLAR
OF SALT OR SOMETHING.
HAROLD, YOU DO GO TO CHURCH.
LOOK WHAT YOU TURNED INTO.
I'LL TAKE MY CHANCES.
[applause]
(Red): GOT A TREAT FOR YOU.
AWAY YOU GO, BILL, UP AND OVER.
OHHHHH... MAN!
OW! OW!
LATER, WE'LL HAVE
MARTIAL ARTS FROM BILL,
BUT FIRST,
THERE'S A LITTLE TEASER,
A LITTLE DEMONSTRATION.
HE'S GONNA DO
A LITTLE FOREHEAD "FU", HERE,
I BELIEVE THIS IS CALLED.
IT'S KIND OF
LUMBER AGAINST LUMBER.
UNFORTUNATELY, BILL'S GOT
THE SOFT WOOD.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION.
THIS WEEK, WE HAVE TWO EXPERTS,
ONE BEING UNCLE RED
AND HIS FRIEND,
MR. DALTON HUMPHREY.
[applause]
THIS WEEK'S LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS:
"DEAR EXPERTS" -- WAHHH! --
"MY WIFE AND I ARE GOING
THROUGH A DIVORCE...
"FROM EACH OTHER.
"HOW CAN WE DIVIDE STUFF
"WHEN WE ONLY HAVE
ONE GOOD PIECE OF FURNITURE?"
WELL, THE PHRASE "CHAINSAW"
COMES TO MIND.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S
A TOUGH PROBLEM.
I KNOW, 'CAUSE
ABOUT THREE WEEKS AGO,
MY WIFE AND I DECIDED
TO DIVORCE.
WHAT?! YOU AND ANNE-MARIE
ARE GETTING DIVORCED, ARE YOU?
SHE WANTED TO WAIT
TILL OUR DAUGHTER WAS 20,
AND THAT HAPPENED LAST MONTH,
SO AFTER, UH...
AFTER 14 YEARS OF MARRIAGE,
SHE MOVED OUT.
[audience laughing]
WALKED RIGHT OUT.
SORRY TO HEAR THAT,
MR. HUMPHREY.
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
THAT IS HER LOSS.
YOU'LL FIND OUT THAT YOU'RE
GONNA BE THE LUCKY ONE NOW.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING.
MOST FOLKS AROUND HERE
NEVER LIKED HER.
[audience laughing]
YOU'D HEAR 'EM SAYING,
"BOY, HOW DID HE END UP
WITH THAT ONE?"
"HE'D BE BETTER OFF
WITHOUT HER.
"SHE'S HOLDING HIM BACK."
SO DON'T YOU WORRY.
I HAD NO IDEA
THAT FOLKS FELT THAT WAY.
THEY JUST COULDN'T STAND
THE SIGHT OF HER.
WHEN THEY FIND OUT
THIS THING HAS GONE KAPUT,
THERE'S GONNA BE
A BIG CELEBRATION.
I WONDER HOW THEY'LL FEEL
WHEN THEY FIND OUT
THAT SHE'S COME BACK
AFTER A WEEK
AND WE RECONCILED,
DECIDED WE LOVED EACH OTHER.
[audience laughing]
[applause]
WELL...
[clearing throat]
JUST OFF THE TOP
OF MY HEAD, I...
I WOULD IMAGINE
THEY'D BE SOMEWHAT EMBARRASSED
ABOUT SOME OF THE THINGS
THEY'D SAID
AND I WOULD-- I WOULD--
I WOULD EXPECT
THAT THEY WOULD OWE YOU
A FAIRLY GOOD-SIZED APOLOGY.
WHO WAS IT
WAS SAYING THAT STUFF?
UH, WELL, TO BE HONEST
WITH YOU,
IT WAS MAINLY HAROLD.
[laughing and applause]
OH, PLANTS SHRIVEL UP
WHEN YOU WALK IN THE ROOM
PEOPLE PULL BACK
WHEN YOU'RE NEAR
ANIMALS REEL,
FALL DOWN AND GO BOOM
AND THE REASON
IS PERFECTLY CLEAR
YOU GOT HALITOSIS
IT'S NOT OSMOSIS
IT AIN'T NO BED OF ROSES
IT'S HALITOSIS
EYES WILL WATER,
FRIENDS WILL FALL
HALITOSIS IS WORSE THAN
HAVING NO BREATH AT ALL
WHEN THAT WATER KNOCKED ME
OUT OF THE BOAT, I REALIZED
THAT "LIFE PRESERVER"
IS JUST A NAME,
RATHER THAN A DESCRIPTION
OF WHAT SOMETHING DOES,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU LEAVE THESE
IN THE WEATHER FOR 20 YEARS,
OR USE 'EM AS BOAT FENDERS.
[glass
breaking]
I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW TO MAKE YOURSELF UNSINKABLE
BECAUSE BOYS WILL BE BOYS
BUT THAT DOESN'T MAKE THEM
BUOY-- BUOY--
BOY, THE THINGS THAT...
THAT WAS SO SMART
WHEN I THOUGHT OF IT.
WHAT I GOT HERE IS
A BOWL OF JELLY
AND A PAIL OF WATER.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO WITH THESE?
REMEMBER, THIS IS
A FAMILY SHOW.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA TAKE
THE JELLY, OK?
THOUGHT THERE WAS
A SPOON AROUND HERE.
OH, WELL, NEVER MIND.
OH, BOY,
THAT BRINGS BACK MEMORIES.
THAT WAS THE WORST SUMMER JOB
I EVER HAD.
I'LL DROP THIS INTO THE WATER.
WATCH WHAT HAPPENS.
THE JELLY FLOATS,
LIKE THE WAY FAT PEOPLE FLOAT.
MOOSE THOMPSON FLOATS SO HIGH,
HE COULD GET REGISTERED
AS A CRUISE SHIP.
THE POINT IS, IF YOU PACK
YOURSELF FULL OF ENOUGH JELLY,
YOU'LL BE A FLOATER.
FIRST, GET INTO
ONE OF THESE DRYSUITS.
THESE THINGS KEEP OUT
ALL WATER AND MOISTURE.
THEY ALSO KEEP IT IN,
SO DROP IN AT THE JOHN
BEFORE YOU HOP INTO THIS UNIT.
[rubber squeaking]
[panting]
WASN'T TOO BAD.
ALL RIGHT, ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS
PUT THE MAN-SIZED WETSUIT
OVER TOP.
[gasping]
OH, GOOD.
[grunting]
[glass
breaking]
ALL RIGHT, FORGET THE WETSUIT.
I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
A RAINSUIT IS WATER-TIGHT.
ALL YOU DO IS SEAL
THE SEAMS WITH DUCT TAPE,
THE CUFFS AND SO ON,
AND YOU'RE AS GOOD
AS MAKING IT HAPPEN.
NOW COMES THE FUN PART.
YOU WANT TO GET YOURSELF
A WHOLE WHACK OF JELLY POWDER.
FIGURE ON ONE CUP OF POWDER FOR
EVERY 10 POUNDS OF BODY WEIGHT.
YOU WANT TO PULL THE RAINSUIT
AWAY FROM THE DRYSUIT
AND THEN POUR THE POWDER
IN BETWEEN.
TRY TO PICK A FLAVOUR OF JELLY
THAT MATCHES YOUR SKIN COLOUR,
'CAUSE THERE MAY BE
SOME LEAKAGE HERE.
[coughing]
MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE PUT THAT
IN THERE
WITH AN INSULATION BLOWER,
BUT WE'RE ON A BUDGET.
ALL'S YOU DO IS ADD THE WATER.
THIS IS PRETTY
SELF-EXPLANATORY,
ALTHOUGH IT'S HARD TO EXPLAIN
TO PEOPLE PASSING BY.
ALL RIGHT, ALL'S YOU GOTTA DO
IS MIX THE WATER
WITH THE JELLY POWDER.
[water gurgling]
[rubber squeaking]
THERE YOU GO.
YOU'RE SET --
YOU'RE UNSINKABLE.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
THEY'LL FIND ME FISHING.
[jelly squeaking]
[laughing]
DO I LOOK SOBER?
YOU CAN TELL A LOT ABOUT PEOPLE
FROM HOW THEY REACT TO WORMS.
WE'RE SET TO GO FISHING SUNDAY.
I GOT
GREAT NEWS--
NO, NO TIME FOR THAT.
STICK YOUR HAND OUT --
THOSE ARE FOR YOU.
YOU SAVE MONEY
WHEN YOU BUY WORMS IN BULK.
[screaming]
[shrieking]
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
SUIT YOURSELF --
I'LL TAKE 'EM.
YOU CAN'T GO FISHING SUNDAY --
YOU'LL BE IN CHURCH.
SORRY, HAROLD, BUT COME SUNDAY,
YOU'LL FIND ME OUT ON THE LAKE.
THAT'S PART
OF MY EXCITING NEWS.
WE'RE GONNA MEET,
TIE THE BOATS TOGETHER,
AND HAVE A SERVICE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE LAKE.
I WOULDN'T MIND SITTING
IN A PEW
IF IT HAD A 200-HORSEPOWER
OUTBOARD ON THE BACK.
SO I WILL SEE YOU
IN CHURCH ON SUNDAY.
I WON'T NEED THESE, THEN.
OH, NO!
DON'T GIVE-- AHHH! AHHH!
FOR THOSE OF YOU LOOKING
FOR SOMEBODY
ON THE CUTTING EDGE OF SAFETY,
LOOK NO FURTHER
THAN BUZZ SHERWOOD.
HEY, CHUBBY RED GUY.
AND HAROLD!
ALL RIGHT, LET'S TALK SAFETY.
LET'S TALK TO THE GUYS
THAT THINK THEY'RE WIMPING OUT
WHEN THEY'RE SAYING
THEY'RE HURT.
IT'S OK TO SAY UNCLE.
MY AUNT TAUGHT ME THAT.
IT TAKES A BIG MAN
TO ADMIT HE NEEDS HELP.
TAKE ME, FOR EXAMPLE.
WE'RE OUT ON THE WATER,
HORSING AROUND.
I'VE HURT MYSELF --
I NEED TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
I'M NOT TOO PROUD TO ADMIT IT.
MY GOSH! WHAT WERE YOU DOING?
WE WERE TRYING
THIS NEW THING OUT.
WE CALL IT WHITE-WATER
PARA-AIR-SKIING.
WOW! SOUNDS DANGEROUS, BUZZ.
WE'RE STARTING
TO THINK SO, TOO.
YOU STRAP ON A PAIR OF SKIS
BEHIND THE PLANE.
TOWS YOU OUT ON THE LAKE
AND UP 5,000 FEET.
YOU PULL THIS RELEASE
AND YOU DROP,
BUT NOT BEFORE YOU PULL
YOUR PARA-SAIL OUT,
AND YOU GLIDE AROUND THE LAKE
FOR A WHILE
AND THEN YOU RELEASE THAT
AT 100 FEET
AND YOU FALL
INTO MERCURY CREEK RAPIDS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE A PERSON
COULD GET HURT DOING THAT.
OH, GO FIGURE, HUH?
I THINK IT'S WHEN I BANKED
OFF THE BEAVER DAM.
THAT MIGHT HAVE DONE IT.
STARTING TO BLACK OUT.
I NEED SOME X-RAYS,
SO SAFETY FIRST.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
THAT MIGHT BE PART
OF YOUR PROBLEM.
OH!
OH, YEAH!
YOU ALL RIGHT?
RED, I'M CURED!
HEY, BILL,
I'M GONNA GO AGAIN!
SAFETY FIRST!
YAHOO!
OK, THIS IS THE BIG ONE,
FOR THE GRAND CASH PRIZE OF...
... ABOUT 45 CENTS OR SO.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO MAKE MR. HUMPHREY SAY
THIS WORD.
GO!
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT YOUR DAUGHTER
DOES NOT HAVE.
A CLUE?
SOMETHING SHE DOESN'T HAVE.
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
A LIFE?
MONEY
OF HER OWN?
AMBITION?
DECENT FRIENDS,
A CAR?
I'M NOT GONNA BUY A CAR
FOR HER!
HOW ABOUT SOME SELF-ESTEEM?
HOW ABOUT THE DESIRE
TO GET OFF THAT COUCH?
HOW ABOUT A DECENT HUSBAND
INSTEAD OF THAT NEANDERTHAL
SHE'S DATING?
HOW ABOUT ONE CLUE
ABOUT WHAT TO DO
WITH THE REST OF HER LIFE?
HOW ABOUT A JOB?
THERE YOU GO! CONGRATULATIONS!
[applause and cheering]
HERE'S THE MONEY.
[applause]
[audience laughing]
THERE ARE SO MANY USES
FOR THE HAMMER,
YOU HAVE TO LIST THEM
ALPHABETICALLY.
"A" FOR ABBA...
"B" FOR BEE GEES...
"C" FOR CAPTAIN AND TENILLE...
THIS FLOATING CHURCH SERVICE
GOT EVERYBODY ALL EXCITED.
STINKY PETERSON WANTS
TO STICK A CANOE UP
SO WE GOT A STEEPLE THING
POINTING OUT OF THE LAKE.
JUNIOR SINGLETON SAID
IF WE POUR GASOLINE OVER ALL
THE THING, YOU GET THE COLOURS
LIKE A STAINED GLASS...
LAKE, REALLY.
WHO'S THE MINISTER
AT THIS WIs1DING,
HAROLD?
THE REVEREND GARTH --
VERY, VERY PROGRESSIVE.
THE GUY WITH THREE EX-WIVES
AND THE LIVE-IN GIRLFRIEND?
HE'S KEEPING UP WITH THE TIMES.
HE INTRODUCED ALL THE NEW TYPES
OF MUSIC INTO THE HYMN SINGS.
YEAH, THERE'S FOLK MUSIC HE DID
AND HEAVY METAL.
REMEMBER THE RAP VERSION
OF "AMAZING GRACE"?
[making boombox sounds]
AMAZING GRACE,
HOW SWEET THOU ART
THAT S-S-S-SAVED
A WRETCH LIKE ME
YO, MAMA!
[applause]
[cheering and whistling]
YOU LIKE RAP, HAROLD?
OH, YEAH.
STICK YOUR KNUCKLES OUT.
HEY!
OH, HEY, MAN, SAFETY FIRST!
I'M BUZZ SHERWOOD,
AND IF YOU FLY YOUR PLANE,
DON'T GO CHASING BIRDS, OK?
YOU MIGHT THINK IT'S FUN,
BUT IT'S DANGEROUS!
BESIDES, IF YOU HIT ONE,
THERE'S ONLY ENOUGH
FOR, LIKE, ONE SERVING.
(Red): BACK AT THE MARTIAL ARTS
DEMONSTRATION,
BILL'S GONNA TRY
A RUNNING ATTACK
ON THE.. THAT'S THE ROPE.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE FINE.
THE RUNNING ATTACK
ON THE BOARD.
KIND OF DID THE UP-AND-OVER
THING AND-- OH, BOY!
OH, MY GOSH! HEY! HEY!
WELL, HE SPLIT THE BOARD.
HE SPLIT THE BOARD,
WHICH WAS REAL CONVENIENT
FOR WHAT WE HAD PLANNED NEXT.
REST IN PEACE, BILL.
OF COURSE, HE'S FINE.
OK, WE GOT A KARATE THING
GOING ON HERE, HAROLD?
KARATE -- THAT'S... OH...
WHAT? OH, MY GOSH.
OH, MY.
OHHH!
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS, UH...
MY APOLOGIES
TO SUMO WRESTLERS EVERYWHERE.
HOLY MACKEREL.
OH, MAN! IS THAT
A TRACTOR TIRE?
WHEN I STARTED DOING
THIS PROGRAMME, I REALLY...
WHAT I HAD IN MIND WAS
AN OUTDOORSY KIND OF...
SOMETHING YOU COULD BE PROUD OF
WHEN YOU WANT
TO GIVE PEOPLE...
OH, MAN.
GIVE PEOPLE HINTS AND TIPS
ON HOW TO DO THINGS
AND HOW TO BE SMARTER
WITH THEIR FELLOW MAN,
AND THEN SOMETIMES YOU...
YOU SEE THE RESULTS
AND YOU JUST-- OH!
THIS IS NOT WHAT I HAD IN MIND
WHEN I WAS... YEAH, FINE.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA SEE THAT
ON THE EDUCATIONAL CHANNEL --
WHAT DO YOU--
OH, OH, OH, OH!
ALL RIGHT, BILL, I GUESS...
I GUESS WE'VE SEEN
THE LAST OF BILL, AND...
OK, HAROLD, HAROLD, HAROLD,
YOU WIN.
[ringing
bell]
SAVED BY THE BELL, THERE, BILL.
IT DOESN'T GET ANY BETTER.
RANGER GORD GETS
A BUNCH OF MEDALS.
OUR CHURCH SERVICE IS TURNING
INTO A BIG ATTRACTION.
GUESS WHO'S COMING.
WHO HAS MADE MORE NORTH
AMERICAN MEN TURN TO RELIGION
THAN ANYBODY ELSE?
LORENA BOBBITT?
[audience laughing]
HAROLD, FOR GOSH SAKES!
THE GUY AT THE SPORTING EVENTS!
THE GUY THAT HOLDS UP
THE SIGN, SAYS "JOHN 11:13".
THE SIGN GUY'S COMING?
WILL HE HAVE
A STRIPED WIG AND EVERYTHING?
THIS IS GONNA BE
THE BIGGEST THING
THAT EVER HIT POSSUM LAKE --
WAIT TILL THE FIREWORKS.
NOAH'S ARK, ALL DONE
IN PINWHEELS.
WHOA, WHOA,
UNCLE RED.
YOU GUYS ARE
MISSING THE POINT.
RELIGION'S NOT ABOUT
PUTTING ON A SHOW.
THAT'S WHY THEY GET
THE LOUSY TURN-OUT, HAROLD.
YOU ADD A COUPLE OF MIRACLES
AND A LITTLE PIZZAZZ,
YOU CAN TURN A MONEY-LOSING
VENTURE INTO A CASH COW
WITH INTERNATIONAL
FRANCHISE POTENTIAL!
IS THIS YOU SPEAKING
IN TONGUES, UNCLE RED?
I GOT RELIGION, HAROLD.
OH, HEAVEN, HELP US.
RED GREEN!
[laughing]
AND HAROLD!
GUESS WHAT.
I GOT A BIG PROMOTION.
PROMOTION, GORD?
YES, SIR.
AFTER 16 YEARS OF BEING
A FOREST RANGER GRADE 3,
I'M NOW BEING PROMOTED
TO FOREST RANGER GRADE 2.
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS
TO YOU, GORD!
THANKS VERY MUCH.
YOU SURE PAID YOUR DUES.
SIXTEEN YEARS UP HERE,
ALL ALONE.
WHERE WILL YOU BE WORKING NOW?
HERE.
OH, BUT I GUESS YOU'RE GETTING
A BIG RAISE IN PAY.
I HAVEN'T HAD A PAYCHEQUE
IN OVER 10 YEARS.
ANYWAY, THE THING IS,
I GET TO DECORATE MY UNIFORM
WITH THESE MEDALS.
THE FORESTRY DEPARTMENT
MUST HAVE DROPPED THEM OFF.
I FOUND THEM
IN A PILE OVER THERE.
UH, THOSE ARE
BEER BOTTLE CAPS, GORD.
[laughing]
RED, EVERYBODY KNOWS
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO DRINK BEER IN THE FOREST.
OH, YEAH, WHAT WAS I THINKING?
I DON'T KNOW.
NOW, THIS ONE SAYS "BUD".
THAT'S FOR
"BUDDY OF THE FOREST".
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES.
THIS ONE SAYS "50".
THAT'S FOR "50 YEARS--"
OH... OH...
"50 MONTHS OF SERVICE".
OK, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I GET FOUR OF THESE.
ALL RIGHT!
TWO, THREE, FOUR.
THIS ONE SAYS "LAGER".
YEAH.
THAT'S FOR MY WORK PROTECTING
THE FOREST AGAINST LOGGERS.
THAT WILL BE IT.
THOUGHT "LOGGER" WAS SPELLED
WITH AN "O".
DOESN'T MATTER.
CAN YOU STICK AROUND
FOR THE PRESENTATION CEREMONY?
WE WOULDN'T MISS IT
FOR THE WORLD!
OKEY-DOKEY.
RANGER...
QUK MARCH!
[mimicking drum sounds]
RANGER... SMALL JUMP!
FORWARD... MARCH!
[mimicking drum sounds]
RANGER...
BIG JUMP!
QUICK... MARCH!
[mimicking drum sounds]
RANGER GORD, FOR SERVICE ABOVE
AND BEYOND THE CALL OF DUTY...
AND NATURE...
AND CERTAINLY SANITY...
CONGRATULATIONS TO YOU, SIR.
[whispering]: THANK YOU.
LEFT... TURN!
QUICK... MARCH!
[mimicking drum sounds]
I THINK I DESERVE A MEDAL
FOR KEEPING A STRAIGHT FACE.
IT'S "MALE CALL"!
OH, HAROLD.
[applause]
OW.
HERE'S OUR LETTER THIS WEEK,
FROM LARRY IN MICHIGAN,
AND LARRY WRITES:
"DEAR RED, DOES EVERYONE
IN CANADA SPEAK FRENCH?"
WELL, UH, YEAH, A LITTLE,
YOU KNOW,
OR AS THE FRENCH WOULD SAY,
UN "POO".
[audience laughing]
WE ALL TRY TO SPEAK
A LITTLE FRENCH.
TRY TO KEEP
THE COUNTRY TOGETHER.
SO FAR, IT'S NOT GOING
ALL THAT WELL.
[audience laughing]
I WONDER WHY.
[speaking French badly]:
OUI, CE EST UN GROS DOMMAGE,
UN ET UN MYSTERIO
POUR "MOO-AH".
N'EST-CE PAS-QUE?
YEAH.
[audience laughing]
WE HAD A LITTLE REHEARSAL
FOR OUR CHURCH SERVICE.
DIDN'T GO JUST EXACTLY
AS PLANNED, YOU KNOW.
IT WAS
A JUDGMENT!
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT, HAROLD.
A LIGHTNING BOLT
ON A CLEAR DAY?
I TAKE THAT AS A WARNING.
IT WASN'T A LIGHTNING BOLT.
IT WAS TOO MANY BOATS
TOO CLOSE TOGETHER
WITH TOO FEW BILGE PUMPS
AND TOO MANY LEAKY GAS LINES.
BUT THE CANDLES --
THAT WAS STUPID.
WE DID HAVE A MIRACLE.
NOBODY WAS KILLED.
AND THE EXPLOSION
PARTED POSSUM LAKE...
JUST FOR A SECOND.
I CAUGHT A GLIMPSE
OF YOUR SNOWMOBILE.
[possum squeal]
MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
IT'S OVER THERE, HAROLD.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'VE GAINED A NEW RESPECT
FOR RELIGION.
I WAS HOPING YOU COULD JOIN ME.
WE'D GO TO CHURCH
AND RENEW OUR VOWS,
AND GO TO THE MOTEL,
RENEW OUR HONEYMOON,
PROVIDING I CAN RENEW
MY MEDICAL INSURANCE.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND THE REVEREND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
[cheering and whistling]
[possum squeal]
(Harold): ALL RISE, ALL RISE!
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
STINKY PETERSON
WILL BE HAVING
A FAMILY REUNION
AGAIN.
[audience
groaning]
HE SAID, "DON'T WORRY,
YOU'LL KNOW WHERE."