MEN HAVE MADE SOME PRETTY
IMPORTANT STATEMENTS...
GIVE ME LIBERTY OR
GIVE ME DEATH.
I REGRET THAT I HAVE ONE
LIFE TO GIVE FOR MY COUNTRY.
AND THE MOST FAMOUS,
NOBODY TOUCHES MY STUFF.
SEE, MEN ARE
TERRITORIAL BY NATURE,
AND OF ALL THE THINGS
IN THE NATURAL WORLD
THAT A MAN WILL
FIGHT TO HOLD ONTO,
NOTHING IS MORE SACRED
THAN THE T.V. REMOTE.
WE'RE WATCHING T.V.,
WE HOLD ON TO THIS THING LIKE
A FAT KID WITH A CORN DOG.
EVERY NOW AND THEN YOU NEED
TO HAVE BOTH HANDS FREE.
LIKE WHEN YOU WANT
TO PICK UP YOUR BEVERAGE
AND THE SNACK BOWL
AT THE SAME TIME.
AND IN THAT SPLIT SECOND,
YOUR WIFE STEALS THE REMOTE
AND THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE WATCHING DR. PHIL.
THIS IS A GOOD
TIME TO REMEMBER
THE SECOND LAW OF
MARITAL DYNAMICS...
SHE WON'T STEAL WHAT
SHE CAN'T USE.
SEE, THIS REMOTE DOESN'T
HAVE ANY BATTERIES
IN IT AT ALL.
THEY'RE DUCT TAPED
TO MY WRIST HERE,
AND YOU SEE THESE WIRES.
THEY'RE CONNECTED TO THE RINGS
THAT I HAVE ON MY FINGERS,
WHICH JUST HAPPEN TO LINE UP
ON THE CONTACTS ON THE BACK
OF THE REMOTE.
HAPPY FLIPPING.
OH, NEVER COULD
REMEMBER WHICH FINGER
THE WEDDING RING GOES ON.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU. APPRECIATE IT.
SORRY I'M A LITTLE BIT LATE.
WE WERE TRYING
TO LAUNCH MY NEW BOAT.
BOY, SHE'S A BEAUTY.
CLASSIC, WOODEN HULL.
GOT A LITTLE
BIT OF ROT IN HER,
BUT IT WAS ONLY 30 BUCKS
INCLUDING THE AIR FRESHENERS.
THE PROBLEM IS THE
DARN BOAT RAMP.
WE'VE GOT SO MANY
SUNKEN BOATS,
TOW VEHICLES AND
SNOWMOBILES IN THERE
YOU HAVE TO ACTUALLY PRY YOUR
TRAILER THROUGH THE SHIPWRECKS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THIS IS NOT FUNNY.
HAROLD, I TOLD YOU
TO STAY IN THE BOAT.
IT SANK TO THE BOTTOM!
YOU SAID THAT WOULDN'T
HAPPEN AGAIN.
IT'S THE DARN
BOAT RAMP, HAROLD.
THERE'S SO MUCH
SUNKEN CRAP IN THERE.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
WELL, CALL THE PEOPLE
THAT LEFT ALL THEIR
STUFF IN THERE
TO GET THEM TO
HAUL IT OUT.
PEOPLE CAN'T BE
BOTHERED DOING THAT.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE IT'S MY
STUFF AND I CAN'T
BE BOTHERED DOING THAT.
SEE, ALL WE GOT TO DO IS
BUILD A NEW BOAT RAMP
OVER THE
OLD BOAT RAMP.
OH, WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT
BUILDING BOAT RAMPS?
OH HAROLD, IT'S
PRETTY DARN SIMPLE.
IT'S LIKE GRAVITY,
LIKE BEING A PLUMBER.
ALL YOU GOT TO REMEMBER
IS THAT WATER GOES
DOWNHILL
AND PAYDAY'S FRIDAY.
NO, IT'S NOT
LIKE PLUMBING.
IT'S ENGINEERING.
PLEASE, DO ME A FAVOUR.
PLEASE!
JUST BUILD A SCALE MODEL
OF THE BOAT RAMP FIRST.
OH, HAROLD.
YEAH, BECAUSE IF
IT WORKS IN MINIATURE,
IT WILL WORK IN
NORMAL SIZE.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
BUT I WANT YOU TO THINK
ABOUT THE PLAN THAT
I COME UP WITH
AND SEE IF IT MAKES
SENSE IN YOUR MIND.
I WILL BE HAPPY
TO DO THAT.
GOOD, BECAUSE IF
IT WORKS IN MINIATURE,
IT'LL WORK IN NORMAL SIZE.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YES, SIR, AND TODAY'S
PRIZE IS A COUPON
TO HAVE YOUR PICTURE
TAKEN WITH BOBO,
THE WORLD'S LARGEST RABBIT.
HE STANDS FOUR FOOT TALL
AT THE SHOULDER
AND EACH EAR
WEIGHS 50 POUNDS.
OH, WARNING, DO NOT
SHOUT AROUND BOBO
OR DRESS UP AS A CARROT.
OKAY, RED --
COVER YOUR EARS.
YOU GOT 30 SECONDS TO GET
WINSTON TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, OKAY,
ALL RIGHT.
AND... GO!
AH, OKAY, WINSTON,
IF YOU KNOW SOMEBODY
AND YOU CAN REVEAL YOUR
PERSONAL SECRETS TO THEM
AND THEY WON'T
TELL ANYBODY,
WHAT KIND OF
FRIEND IS THAT?
AN IMAGINARY ONE.
OKAY. NO. NO. NO.
THIS IS SOMETHING PEOPLE
DO BEHIND CLOSED DOORS.
HIDE?
REMEMBER WHEN HAROLD GOT
MAD BECAUSE WE ALL
READ HIS DIARY?
THAT'S BECAUSE THE THINGS
THAT WERE WRITTEN IN
THERE WERE...
HILARIOUS.
TIME'S ALMOST UP, RED.
OKAY, WINSTON,
YOU KNOW I NEVER TALK ABOUT
BERNICE AND I
AND THE THINGS THAT
WE DO, YOU KNOW,
LIKE LATER ON IN THE
EVENING AT NIGHT, OKAY,
BECAUSE IT'S...
BORING.
NO, WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
WHAT BERNICE AND I DO
IN THE BEDROOM.
OH, RIGHT.
RENOVATIONS.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT GOES ON
IN THE BEDROOM, WINSTON?
WELL, I DOUBT THERE'S
MUCH GOING ON BETWEEN
YOU AND BERNICE
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
TRYING TO INTIMATE.
YEAH. THAT'S IT.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THIS IS THE PART OF THE
PROGRAM WHERE WE EXAMINE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS THAT
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
THAT'S 'CAUSE IT'S TRUE.
OKAY, HERE'S
TODAY'S LETTER,
GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS" --
LA LA LA.
"I'VE BEEN HAPPILY
MARRIED FOR 23 YEARS,
"BUT LATELY AN ATTRACTIVE
WOMAN AT MY OFFICE
"HAS BEEN MAKING
PASSES AT ME.
"HOW CAN I TELL HER
THAT I'M NOT INTERESTED
"WITHOUT HURTING
HER FEELINGS?
"HAS THIS EVER
HAPPENED TO YOU?"
UM --
DALTON?
I'M STILL STUCK ON
THE HAPPILY MARRIED PART.
OH, BROTHER.
YOU GUYS.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE HAVEN'T
HAD BEAUTIFUL YOUNG WOMEN
PURSUING US, HAROLD.
YEAH, YEAH,
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE JUST TRYING TO
REMEMBER WHAT WE DID
IN EACH INDIVIDUAL
CIRCUMSTANCE.
MAYBE YOU WOKE UP?
ANY CHANCE YOU'LL EVER
WAKE UP, HAROLD?
YOU KNOW,
I REMEMBER NOW.
ONCE I WAS WITH PAM STUBBS
IN PORT ASBESTOS, YOU KNOW.
AND THERE WE WERE ALL
ALONE IN HER OFFICE.
SHE REACHES OVER
AND SHE CLOSES THE DOOR.
SHE STARTS ASKING
ME A WHOLE BUNCH OF
PERSONAL QUESTIONS.
SHE REACHES OVER,
SHE STARTS
TOUCHING MY KNEE.
SHE'S AN ARTHRITIS
SPECIALIST, DALTON.
OKAY. WELL, OKAY.
I SUPPOSE ALL SORTS OF WOMEN
ARE INTERESTED IN YOU.
WELL, AS A MATTER
OF FACT I DO.
YES, I DO.
IN FACT I DO.
AND THE OTHER DAY, I HEARD
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S DAUGHTER
TELL HAROLD THAT SHE REALLY
LIKES MY FURRY BEARD.
SHE DIDN'T SAY SHE
LIKES YOUR FURRY BEARD.
NO, SHE SAID SHE THOUGHT
YOU WERE VERY WEIRD.
WELL, I CAN SEE WE NEED
SOMEONE HERE WITH SOME
PERSONAL EXPERIENCE,
WHICH IS ME,
LA LA LA.
THIS SHOULD BE GOOD.
WELL, MY ADVICE
TO THIS VIEWER
IS THAT YOU SIMPLY TAKE
THIS PERSON ASIDE,
IN PRIVATE,
AND SAY, ALTHOUGH SOMEONE AS
WONDERFUL AS THEM IS
VERY TEMPTING,
IT SIMPLY CANNOT BE.
ACTUALLY,
THAT'S NOT BAD.
YEAH, BUT WHAT
IF IT DOESN'T WORK?
OH, THEN YOU GOT
TO BE FIRMER.
YEAH, YOU JUST SAY,
OKAY, I'M NOT INTERESTED
AND I NEVER COULD BE.
YOU KNOW, AND YOU GOT TO
STOP HANGING OUT IN
FRONT OF MY HOUSE,
AND YOU GOT TO STOP TELLING
YOUR FRIENDS THAT YOU'RE
GOING OUT WITH ME,
AND IF YOU DON'T I'M GOING
TO CALL THE POLICE ON YOU,
HAROLD GREEN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, YOU TRY YOUR
BEST TO SAVE THE ENVIRONMENT.
SWITCH TO AN
ELECTRIC LAWN MOWER,
WHERE DOES IT GET YOU?
BACK TO THE HARDWARE STORE
FOR ANOTHER 100 FEET OF
EXTENSION CORD.
DON'T WORRY, AS USUAL,
I'VE GOT A BETTER IDEA.
FIRST THING WE HAVE TO
DO IS TAKE DOWN THIS
CHAIN LINK FENCE.
I'M SURE SOME OF YOU
HAVE SEEN STREETCARS,
AND IF YOU'RE NOT
FAMILIAR WITH STREETCARS,
I'M SURE YOU'RE
DRIVEN BUMPER CARS,
AND IF YOU'RE NOT
FAMILIAR WITH BUMPER CARS,
YOU'RE PROBABLY NOT
WATCHING THIS SHOW.
WE'RE GOING TO USE
THAT SAME TECHNOLOGY
TO MAKE OUR MODIFIED
ELECTRIC LAWN MOWER HERE.
SEE, YOU'VE GOT TWO WIRES
COMING OFF THE ELECTRIC MOTOR.
I ATTACH ONE OF THEM TO
THE FRAME OF THE MOWER,
AND THE OTHER ONE I ATTACH TO
THIS FENCE POST HERE.
SOME OF YOU MAY HAVE
ALREADY NOTICED
THAT I'VE REPLACED THE STANDARD
ISSUE RUBBER LAWN MOWER TIRES
WITH THESE
CLOTHESLINE PULLEYS
BECAUSE THEY'RE METAL AND
THEY CONDUCT ELECTRICITY.
NOT THAT YOU NEED TO BE METAL
TO CONDUCT ELECTRICITY,
AS OLD MAN
SEDGWICK FOUND OUT
WHEN HE RELIEVED HIMSELF
ONTO A POWER TRANSFORMER.
OKAY, THE ONLY OTHER
MODIFICATION WE NEED HERE
IS TO MAKE A SOFTER CONTACT
POINT FOR MY FENCE POST.
DONE.
OKAY, SO INSTEAD OF
HOOKING THE LAWN MOWER UP
DIRECT WITH AN EXTENSION CORD,
WHICH I'VE RUN OVER FOR
THE THIRD TIME THIS MONTH,
ONLY TO FIND OUT THAT
THE WARRANTY COVERS
THEIR MISTAKES,
NOT MINE,
I'VE GOT A DIFFERENT WAY
TO HOOK UP THE ELECTRICITY.
TOOK ONE WIRE,
ATTACHED IT TO THIS SPIKE
I'VE GOT IN THE GROUND, SEE,
AND THAT CONNECTS TO THE METAL
WHEELS ON THE LAWN MOWER.
AND THEN THE OTHER WIRE
I ATTACHED TO THIS
ELECTRIC GRID
THAT I'VE MADE OUT OF
THE CHAIN LINK FENCE.
ONCE THE LEAF RAKE CONNECTS
TO THAT, YOU SEE,
THAT CLOSES THE CIRCUIT,
MAKES THE LAWN MOWER GO.
ISN'T THAT A LOT SAFER
THAN LUGGING AROUND A
DANGEROUS EXTENSION CORD?
SO REMEMBER, IF THE
WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
AND NOW,
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I'VE GOT TO SAVE
THE ENVIRONMENT.
I WANT TO TALK
TO YOU OLDER GUYS
ABOUT YOUR GOOD LOOKS --
OR MORE SPECIFICALLY,
WHERE THEY WENT.
NOW, YOU MAY THINK THAT YOUR
HANDSOME, YOUTHFUL BODY
IS BEHIND YOU,
BUT THE PEOPLE STANDING BACK
THERE MAY NOT NECESSARILY
AGREE WITH YOU.
YOU LOOK BAD,
BUT HERE'S THE GOOD NEWS...
YOU LOOK WAY BETTER
THAN YOU'RE GOING TO LOOK.
UNLESS, OF COURSE, YOU START
EATING RIGHT AND EXERCISING.
YEAH!
OKAY, SURE, I'M SUPPOSE
YOU COULD START WEARING
MAKEUP AND A GIRDLE AND HAVE
SOME COSMETIC SURGERY,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S FOR GUYS WHO BAKE PIES
AND MAKE THEIR OWN CURTAINS.
I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
AS YOUR LOOKS
START SLIPPING,
SO SHOULD YOUR STANDARDS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO LOOK GOOD.
YOU JUST HAVE
TO LOOK GOOD ENOUGH.
DON'T GET A FACELIFT.
JUST SIT NEAR A BASSET HOUND.
YOU'LL LOOK FINE.
DON'T MAKE
ANY EFFORT AT ALL.
SEE, APATHY IS THE KEY TO
A YOUTHFUL APPEARANCE.
I MEAN, TEENAGERS DON'T
CARE ABOUT ANYTHING.
SEE HOW YOUNG THEY LOOK?
AND DON'T WORRY ABOUT PEOPLE
SAYING YOU LET YOURSELF GO.
THEY'VE ALREADY BEEN SAYING
THAT ABOUT YOU FOR 10 YEARS.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
I GUESS I'M JUST LUCKY.
WELL, SOME PEOPLE GO THROUGH
THEIR ENTIRE LIVES
WITHOUT EVER REALLY KNOWING
THEIR TRUE PURPOSE.
BUT FOR ME EVER SINCE
I WAS A YOUNG BOY,
I'VE KNOWN THAT I WAS PUT ON
THIS EARTH TO SUCK SEWAGE.
OH, SURE, YEAH, THE KIDS
USED TO TEASE ME A BIT.
THEY'D SAY, WINSTON
LIKES TO SUCK SEWAGE
OR, THERE GOES WINSTON
THE SEWAGE SUCKER.
OR I ALSO REMEMBER
THEM SAYING,
HEY, WINSTON, WHY DON'T
YOU GO SUCK SOME SEWAGE?
YOU KNOW,
THAT TYPE OF THING.
BUT WHERE ARE
THOSE KIDS NOW?
OKAY, WELL, ACTUALLY,
A LOT OF THEM HAVE DONE
PRETTY WELL FOR THEMSELVES,
BUT THAT'S NOT
THE POINT, RIGHT?
YEAH, YEAH.
I THINK WHEN FOLKS CALL ME
THEY KNOW THEY'RE
GETTING A REAL PERSON.
YEAH, SURE, YOU COULD CALL
ONE OF THOSE BIG,
FACELESS MULTINATIONAL
SEWAGE SUCKING COMPANIES,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
IT'S NOT ALWAYS ABOUT
WHO HAS THE
BIGGEST TRUCK, RIGHT?
IT'S ABOUT --
IT'S ABOUT PEOPLE,
PEOPLE WITH, UH,
SEPTIC TANKS.
IF YOU'RE HAVING A PROBLEM,
CALL ME.
WE'LL TALK.
I'M HERE TO
LIGHTEN YOUR LOAD.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS
ABOUT A MIDDLE-AGED GUY
AND THE SOUND
OF RUNNING WATER.
IF I WAS DEAF,
I WOULD'VE HAD
THIS DONE AN HOUR AGO.
UNCLE RED, HERE'S THE
BOARD THAT YOU WANTED.
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S NOT A BOARD.
THAT'S MY MODEL
BOAT RAMP.
SEE, I'M DOING WHAT
YOU SAID, HAROLD.
I'M BUILDING THE WHOLE
THING IN MINIATURE,
SEE, 'CAUSE ARGUING IS
JUST A WASTE OF TIME
AND ENERGY.
NOW, THAT SOUNDS
LIKE A MATURE MAN.
NO, IT SOUNDS LIKE A
MARRIED MAN, HAROLD.
NOW YOU SEE
THIS TUB HERE?
THAT REPRESENTS
POSSUM LAKE.
WELL, THAT CAN'T BE.
THIS IS WATER.
AND YOU SEE ALL
THIS SCRAP HERE?
THAT REPRESENTS THE VARIOUS
BOATS AND TOWING VEHICLES
THAT HAVE COME TO
AN UNTIMELY DEMISE
DURING THE
LAUNCHING PROCESS.
NOW, IS THIS TO SCALE?
IT'S A LITTLE LOW,
BUT I RAN OUT OF
BROKEN TOYS.
AND NOW, OF COURSE,
WHAT WE HAVE HERE
IS THE TOW VEHICLE,
AND WE GOT THE BOAT
THAT WE'RE ACTUALLY
TRYING TO LAUNCH.
THAT IS SO CUTE!
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT!
I'LL BE SURE TO TELL
KEN AND BARBIE THAT
YOU LIKED IT.
NOW, WE JUST --
SEE, WE JUST PUT OUR BOAT
RAMP INTO PLACE JUST
LIKE THAT, SEE?
AH!
YEAH. YEAH.
HOW DO YOU
GET ON TO IT?
OH, NO, OKAY, YOU SEE,
YOU DRAG HER BACK
JUST PAST THE HALFWAY POINT
AND SHE SLIPS DOWN THIS WAY.
THEN YOU TAKE YOUR UNIT
AND AS YOU DO IT,
SIMPLE AS THIS,
YOU BACK HER UP,
BACK HER UP, BACK HER UP,
THEN ONCE YOU GET PAST
THE HALFWAY POINT, SEE --
Red: WE HAD A PROBLEM.
WE HAD KIND OF
A FLASH FLOOD,
AND WE KNEW THAT THE WATER
WAS GOING TO COME UP
IN POSSUM LAKE
BECAUSE MOOSE THOMPSON HAD
DONE A CANNONBALL UP NEAR
PORT ASBESTOS.
AND IT WAS
COMING UP OVER,
AND WE KNEW WE HAD TO DO
SOMETHING AND DO IT QUICK.
AND WE HAD THIS
BOAT OUT THE BACK,
AND SHE WASN'T
IN THE BEST SHAPE,
AND WE THOUGHT IF WE COULD
GET HER OUT OF THE WAY,
MOVE HER OUT,
BECAUSE SHE DOESN'T FLOAT.
AND UNFORTUNATELY, SHE'S
PRETTY HEAVY AND KIND OF
ROTTED INTO THE GROUND,
SO WE THOUGHT, YOU KNOW,
RATHER THAN TRYING TO
MOVE THE BOAT
WHAT WE CAN DO IS TO
BUILD KIND OF A DYKE,
A WALL AROUND IT.
JUST NEEDED A
COUPLE OF SHOVELS.
OKAY, THIS IS THE DOWN SIDE
OF NEVER CLEANING
OUT YOUR VAN.
I'M NOT SAYING YOU HAVE
TO CLEAN OUT YOUR VAN.
JUST THAT IF YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO CLEAN OUT YOUR VAN
AND YOU'RE TRYING TO GET
A SHOVEL OUT OF HER,
YOU GOT TO BE
PRETTY CREATIVE.
SO NOW THE IDEA IS WE'RE
GOING TO DIG UP SOME SAND
AND WE'RE GONNA
MAKE SOME SANDBAGS.
SO I'M TELLING
DALTON AND WALTER
TO GO TO GET US SOME BAGS.
ANY KIND OF
BAGS YOU CAN GET.
SO DALTON SEES
A GARBAGE CAN THERE
AND FIGURES HE'LL JUST
USE THOSE GARBAGE BAGS.
SO WE GOT A FAIR
AMOUNT OF SAND THERE,
AND THEN WALTER SHOWS UP,
AND I WAS IMPRESSED
THAT HE HAD EMPTIED
THE GARBAGE BAGS FIRST.
AND I ASKED HIM, WHERE DID
YOU EMPTY THEM EXACTLY?
AND THEN.
I DEFINITELY GOT
TO CLEAN OUT THAT VAN
ONE DAY SOON.
SO WE STARTED MAKING
THE SANDBAGS
AND DID KIND OF LIKE
A BUCKET BRIGADE UNIT THERE.
I MEAN, THEY'RE HEAVY.
THEY ARE HEAVY.
AND YOU JUST SORT OF
MOVE ONE GUY DOWN TO
THE NEXT AND SO ON.
THE WATER WAS STARTING TO COME
UP BUT WE'RE GETTING THERE.
YOU JUST START SLOW
AND WATCH OUT FOR
THE SHOVEL THERE, DALTON.
OH, BOY. OH, BOY.
OH, BOY...
NO, WE'RE GOOD.
SO GET THAT OUT OF THERE.
I DIDN'T REALIZE IT HAD
ACTUALLY CUT THE BAG,
AND THIS ONE WASN'T QUITE AS
HEAVY AS THE OTHER ONE.
AND I DON'T KNOW QUITE WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO DO WITH
THAT ONE, DALTON.
ANYWAY, TIME WENT BY
AND WE EVENTUALLY
GOT ALL THE BAGS MADE UP.
AND DALTON'S WONDERING
HOW HIGH THE WATER IS
AT THIS POINT.
SHE WAS COMING UP
PRETTY GOOD.
SO WALTER, GET
A BOOST UP THERE,
REACH OVER THE SIDE,
AND SEE HOW HIGH THE WATER IS.
YOU CAN ACTUALLY FEEL IT.
WATER'S PRETTY CLOSE --
OH, MY GOSH.
LOOK OUT. LOOK OUT. LOOK OUT.
OH, OH!
IT'S YOUR WAKE-UP CALL.
AND PUT THAT BACK
WHERE IT BELONGS.
THERE YOU GO.
LOOK AT THE WATER,
IT'S RIGHT UP THERE.
SUDDENLY, I REMEMBER,
THE POSSUM VAN.
OH, MY GOSH.
IT'S CAUGHT OUT THERE.
SO WALTER SAYS
HE'LL GO AND GET IT.
HE'S GONNA PUT THE
LIFE THING ON,
AND HE'S GONNA USE THE
ROPE FROM THE BOAT TO
ANCHOR HIMSELF
SO HE CAN CONTROL
THE FLOOD AND SO ON,
BECAUSE WE'RE PRETTY MUCH
AT THE HEIGHT OVER THERE.
SHE'S STARTIN'
TO COME DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
WHAT HE DIDN'T REALIZE IS
THAT THERE'S A FAIR BIT
OF CURRENT GOING THERE
AND IT'S STARTING
TO PULL ON HIM REAL HARD
AND HE ACTUALLY ENDED UP
PULLING THE BOAT
UP AND OVER
THE WALL OF DYKE.
AND BY THEN, OF COURSE,
THE WATER HAD RUN AWAY
AND THERE'S WALTER.
OKAY, EVERYTHING'S GOOD.
WELL, LOOK AT THIS.
I DID GET THE
POSSUM VAN CLEANED OUT.
YOU KNOW, ONE OF THE
IMPORTANT DIFFERENCES
BETWEEN CANADA AND THE
STATES IS THAT UP HERE
WE GET A $2.40 REFUND FOR
A CASE OF EMPTY BEER BOTTLES.
OH, SURE, UP HERE,
A CASE OF BEER COSTS $20 MORE,
BUT THAT ONLY
MATTERS IF YOU'RE BUYING.
SEE, BUT THE PROBLEM IS
OUR AMERICAN FRIENDS
END UP WITH ALL THESE
EMPTY CASES OF BEER,
AND THEY'RE LOOKING FOR
SUGGESTIONS ON WHAT
TO DO WITH THEM.
WELL, HERE'S A NATURAL...
AN OUTDOOR URINAL.
KINDA COMPLETES
THE CIRCLE, DOESN'T IT?
AND IN KEEPING WITH
THE BEER CASE MOTIF,
I CUT UP A REFRIGERATOR BOX
AND MADE FLAPS FOR
THE TOP OF THE UNIT
SO THAT IT CLOSES UP,
JUST LIKE THE REAL THING.
AND THE BEAUTY
OF THIS DESIGN,
IN THE GOOD WEATHER,
YOU CAN JUST PUSH UP ON THE
ROOF, MAKE YOURSELF A SKYLIGHT.
MIND YOU, YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT
ALL THAT DARK IN HERE
'CAUSE I ADDED A FEW
BEER BOTTLE WINDOWS.
THEY LET THE LIGHT IN,
BUT THEY STILL
MAINTAIN YOUR PRIVACY.
AND IT'S YOUR
CHOICE ON THOSE.
YOU CAN GO WITH THE
STANDARD BROWN LONGNECKS,
OR, FOR A LITTLE
TASTE OF MEXICO,
TRY THE CLEAR BOTTLES,
AND IF YOU REALLY WANT TO
IMPRESS THE NEIGHBOURS,
GO WITH THE GREEN IMPORTS.
NOW, THE TOILET ITSELF
IS AN EMPTY KEG.
JUST CRACK THE LID UP,
AND YOU'RE IN BUSINESS.
OH, SURE, IT'S A
LITTLE CRAMPED,
BUT AS I SAY,
THIS IS A MEN'S URINAL...
STANDING ROOM ONLY.
MY MOTHER ALWAYS SAID
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR YOUR
HEALTH TO SIT IN A DRAFT.
IT WAS A GOOD IDEA
TO BUILD A MODEL.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD WAS RIGHT.
BOY, THAT'S HARD TO SAY.
BUT WE GOT HER
ALL FIGURED OUT.
WE ACTUALLY GOT THE REAL THING
OUT FOR A TRIAL RUN THERE.
MIKE'S ACTUALLY GOING
TO BE OUR TEST PILOT.
OKAY, MR. GREEN, I'M ALL
SET TO DRIVE THE POSSUM VAN.
HAVE YOU GOT
THE KEYS?
NO, I THINK
THEY'RE IN IT.
NOT A PROBLEM.
BUT MIKE, WHAT IF
THEY'RE NOT IN IT?
NOT A PROBLEM.
HEY, UNCLE RED.
HAROLD, WE'VE HAD A BIT
OF A BREAKTHROUGH HERE.
WE DON'T ACTUALLY HAVE
TO GET THE POSSUM VAN
OVER THE SCRAP,
WE JUST GOT TO GET THE
BOAT TO GO OVER THE SCRAP.
REALLY?
YEAH. YEAH.
SO WHAT WE DID WAS WE
MOVED THE MARINA
OUTHOUSE --
'CAUSE NOBODY
USES IT ANYWAY,
UNLESS THERE ARE
WOMEN THERE,
AND THEN THAT BECOMES
THE FULCRUM FOR
OUR BOAT RAMP.
RIGHT.
BUT WHERE WE WERE
GOING WRONG IS THAT
THE TEETER-TOTTER THING
DIDN'T HAVE ENOUGH
OOMPH TO HER.
SO I DUCT-TAPED A COUPLE OF
HOCKEY STICKS TOGETHER
TO HOLD THE RAMP UP.
THEN I FIRMED UP THE HITCH
ON THE POSSUM VAN,
SO NOW WHEN THE
POSSUM VAN COMES UP,
IT HITS THE
HOCKEY STICKS AND...
[ APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
LET'S SEE HOW IT WORKS
IN THE NORMAL WORLD, HUH?
YEAH, BUT YOU DON'T LIVE
IN THE NORMAL WORLD.
OKAY, MIKE,
LET HER GO.
[ ENGINE STARTS ]
KEEP YOUR EYE ON THE LAKE,
WATCH FOR THE SPLASH.
[ CRASH ]
OH, NO!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
FOLLOWED BY
QUESTION PERIOD.
OKAY,
YOU GO AHEAD,
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN,
HAROLD.
OKAY, UH,
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AND AS HUGH HEFNER ONCE SAID,
YOU EVENTUALLY GET TOO OLD
TO BE FOOLING AROUND
WITH MODELS.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF, HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
I NEED A SHOW OF HANDS,
ANYBODY WHO'S WILLING
TO HELP CLEAN UP THE
CRAP OUT OF THE BOAT RAMP.
OKAY, OKAY, I'LL
SWEETEN THE DEAL.
YOU GET TO KEEP WHATEVER
YOU HAUL OUT OF THERE.