♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: HI, THIS IS RED GREEN,
ON TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD IS
GOING TO REVIEW SOME MOVIES,
BILL'S GOING TO MAKE
SOME CAMP ALARMS,
AND I'M GOING TO TURN A
TOASTER INTO A C.D. PLAYER.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(SHATTERING OF GLASS)
>>HAROLD: AND NOW HERE'S
THE MAN WITH THE BIG IDEAS
BUT THE SMALL BUDGET,
THE HIGH EXPECTATIONS
BUT THE LOW STANDARDS,
THE RISING PROFILE BUT
THE FALLEN ARCHES,
MY UNCLE, YOUR HOST,
RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
AND THANK YOU HAROLD,
WHAT AN INTERESTING INTRODUCTION
FILLED WITH OXYMORON WHICH
SURPRISED ME,
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU DO
THE OXY PART BEFORE.
>>HAROLD: WELL YOU'D BE
SURPRISED WHAT I CAN DO.
>>RED: NOT PLEASANTLY SURPRISED.
BIG, BIG WEEK AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK, JUNIOR SINGLETON
TOOK ALL HIS MONEY OUT
OF THE BANK AND BOUGHT
HIMSELF A USED HELICOPTER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY WOULD
SELL SOMEBODY A USED HELICOPTER.
>>HAROLD: YEAH ESPECIALLY
JUNIOR, HE DOESN'T EVEN
HAVE A PILOT'S LICENCE.
>>RED: NO BUT HE HAS A BANK
BALANCE HAROLD AND I BELIEVE
THE INSURANCE ON A HELICOPTER
IS A LOT CHEAPER IF YOU
NEVER FLY IT.
JUNIOR'S REAL SMART WITH
MONEY LIKE THAT YEAH.
>>HAROLD: BOY IT'D BE GREAT IF
WE COULD GET SOME AERIAL SHOTS
OF THE LODGE FOR THE SHOW.
>>RED: WELL I THINK YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO GET THOSE FROM
THE AERIAL BECAUSE A COUPLE OF
DAYS AGO JUNIOR WENT DOWN FOR
HIS HELICOPTER LICENSE TEST
AND IT WASN'T GOOD HAROLD,
HE FLUNKED THE ORAL TEST
HE FLUNKED THE WRITTEN TEST
HE FLUNKED THE EYE TEST
HE WENT TO THE WRONG WASHROOM
FOR THE OTHER TEST.
>>HAROLD: WELL YOU KNOW WHAT,
I'D LOOK GOOD IN A
HELICOPTER HUH?
WOULDN'T I LOOK GOOD
AS A CHOPPER PILOT?
>>RED: I SEE YOU MORE
AS CHOPPED LIVER HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: YOU BETTER WATCH
WHAT YOU SAY TO ME UNCLE RED,
YOU MAY NEED ME SOME DAY TO COME
IN MY HELICOPTER AND RESCUE
YOU FROM A MOUNTAINTOP,
YOU KNOW IF WE WERE TO GET
A MOUNTAIN AROUND HERE SOME DAY.
>>RED: HAROLD IF I GO
TO A MOUNTAINTOP
IT'LL BE TO JUMP OFF.
>>HAROLD: YOU WON'T JUMP.
>>RED: WELL MAYBE NOT
IF YOU WENT FIRST.
♪ GO DOWN TO THE MEADOW ♪
♪ A LITTLE AFTER DARK ♪
♪ LISTEN TO THE SOUND ♪
♪ OF THE GOLDEN THROATED ♪
♪ RUBY CRESTED LARK ♪
♪ STAND BY THE WATER WITH ♪
♪ YOUR HANDCUFFS ON YOUR EAR ♪
♪ LISTEN VERY CLOSELY AND ♪
♪ THIS IS WHAT YOU'LL HEAR ♪
>>HAROLD: IT'S EXTINCT.
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE GOT
SOMETHING FOR YOU AUDIOPHILES
WHO COLLECT THE PHONOGRAPHIC
LITERATURE WHICH IS NOT
WHAT THE REST OF YOU ARE
THINKING SO SAVE YOUR MONEY.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE US A
C.D. PLAYER FOR THIS, THE C.D.
NOW HAROLD TELLS ME THAT
THESE C.D.'S HAVE HALF
THE HISS OF AN L.P. OR A 45
OR EVEN AN 8-TRACK WHICH
I FIND HARD TO BELIEVE.
UNFORTUNATELY THE C.D.'S
COST ABOUT 9 TIMES AS MUCH.
IN FACT BY THE TIME YOU BUY
A COUPLE OF THEM C.D.'S
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY LEFT
TO BE ABLE TO AFFORD THE
C.D. PLAYER, SO WE'RE GOING
TO SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE
ONE USING YOUR COMMON
HOUSEHOLD TOASTER.
NOW THE FIRST THING YOU HAVE
TO DO IS GUT THE TOASTER,
JUST LIKE GUTTING A FISH
AND WITH THIS TOASTER,
IT'S PRETTY WELL MUNGED UP
WITH OLD MELTED CHEESE,
IT'S GOING TO SMELL ABOUT
THE SAME TOO.
NO THAT'S NOT GOING TO,
THIS MIGHT LOOSEN HER
OFF A LITTLE, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT ONCE YOU GET
THE HEATING UNIT OUT OF THERE,
JUST PUT IT SOMEWHERE SAFE
FOR LATER BECAUSE IN
A COUPLE OF WEEKS WE'RE
GOING TO TURN A WEED WACKER
INTO A COMBINATION HAIR
DRYER AND SIDEBURN TRIMMER.
ALL RIGHT GET BACK TO
OUR C.D. PLAYER.
THE INSIDE OF A C.D. PLAYER
AS I UNDERSTAND IT IS BASICALLY
A LASER CONTROLLED BY
COMPUTER CHIPS SOLDERED
TO A CIRCUIT BOARD,
SO WHAT I'VE DONE IS I JUST
CRAZY GLUED A BUNCH OF DIGITAL
CLOCKS TO A PIE PLATE,
AND OF COURSE YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED SOME KIND OF A SMALL
ELECTRIC MOTOR TO WORK AS
A DRIVE TO MAKE THE C.D. SPIN.
NO PROBLEM WE GOT THAT COVERED.
AND WHEN IT COMES TO THE ACTUAL
LASER ITSELF, NOW THESE ARE
A USUALLY A GALLIUM ARSENIDE
SOLID STATE LASER BUT IF BY
CHANCE YOU DON'T HAVE ONE OF
THOSE IN YOUR TACKLE BOX,
I THINK YOU CAN JUST GO WITH
A POCKET PENLIGHT BECAUSE
BASICALLY IT'S THE SAME
PROCEDURE AND I THINK
IMAGINATION BEATS INTIMIDATION
ANY DAY OF THE WEEK.
SO ONCE YOU'VE GOT ALL
THAT STUFF, THE IMPORTANT THING
HERE IS TO GET THIS IN HERE,
GET IT LINED UP ABSOLUTELY
PERFECT, GET HER BALANCED
IN THERE ABSOLUTELY PERFECT,
AND THEN TO MAKE SURE THAT
NOTHING EVER MOVES YOU
WANT TO MOUNT IT USING
THE HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT THERE WE GO,
AS YOU CAN SEE I PAINTED
HER UP A LITTLE BIT,
GIVE HER THE FLAT BLACK
KIND OF A SPORTY LOOK,
AND I'VE ADDED SOME CONTROL
KNOBS HERE TO GIVE ME THE
CONTROL OVER THE VOLUME AND
THE TREBLE AND THE BALANCE
AND THE MELTED CHEESE,
WHAT I CALL
COLBY NOISE REDUCTION.
AND SPEAKING OF THINGS THAT ARE
OLD AND KIND OF SMELL FUNNY,
I HAVE HOOKED HER UP TO
MY OWN NORDMENDE THERE AS
AN AMPLIFIER, OF COURSE THIS
HAS GOT THE TUBES IN IT AND I
WAS CONCERNED ABOUT THE TUBES,
BUT I TOOK THEM DOWN TO THE
VARIETY STORE HERE BECAUSE
THEY'VE GOT A TUBE TESTER
IN THERE AND I WAS TRYING
TO TEST THE DARN TUBES,
HAVING A HECK OF A TIME WITH
IT AND FINALLY I WENT TO
THE GUY, I SAID HOW COME THE
TUBE TESTER DOESN'T WORK?
AND HE SAYS BECAUSE IT'S
A BANKING MACHINE,
NOW THAT'S PROGRESS FOR YOU.
SO THEN I NEEDED SOME SPEAKERS,
WELL I DECIDED TO GO WITH
THE HOMEMADE STYLE AND I GOT
THE WIRELESS HOOKUP ON THOSE,
I FIGURE IF I TURN HER UP
LOUD ENOUGH THE SOUND WOULD
GET INTO THE SPEAKERS,
AND ACTUALLY I STARTED WITH
PRICING THEM OUT DOWN AT
THE STEREO STORE, ONE OF THOSE
PLACES WHERE THEY GOT THE
CARPETING ACROSS THE FLOOR
AND UP THE WALL AND ACROSS
THE WINDOW AND OVER THE
GUY'S FOREHEAD AND SO FORTH,
AND BOY THEY GOT SPEAKERS
IN THERE, THEY HAD ONE SPEAKER,
IT HAD TO BE 6 FEET HIGH,
IT LOOKED LIKE A COFFIN
AND IT WOULD OF BEEN ONCE
MY CHEQUE BOUNCED.
SO I JUST GO WITH
THE HOMEMADE STYLE
WE GOT HER ALL HOOKED UP,
I THINK EVERYTHING IS LOOKING
GOOD WHY DON'T WE JUST POP
THE C.D. IN THERE AND
SEE HOW SHE GOES.
(LOUD EXPLOSION) HMM
(WHIRLING OF C.D.)
OH YEAH, WELL THAT'S SIDE 'A'
DONE, IF YOU REALLY LIKE MUSIC
YOU CAN DO THE SAME THING WITH
A 4-SLICER AND YOUR SONGS
WILL PLAY RIGHT UP UNTIL
WHEN THE FIRE TRUCKS ARRIVE.
NEXT WEEK WE'RE GOING TO
SHOW YOU HOW TO TURN A
WAFFLE IRON INTO A CLOSE
AND PLAY RECORD PLAYER.
SO UNTIL THEN REMEMBER
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I WONDER WHAT RAISIN
BREAD SOUNDS LIKE?
YOU KNOW IF IT'S CALIFORNIA
RAISONS THEY MIGHT EVEN SING.
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S THAT
TIME OF THE SHOW WHERE WE
EXPOSE THE 3 WORDS THAT MEN
FIND MOST DIFFICULT TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND NOW HERE TO PROVE THAT
POINT IS MY UNCLE RED AND
HIS BEST GOOD FRIEND IN
THE WHOLE WIDE WORLD,
MR. DOUGIE FRANKLIN.
LETTER NUMBER ONE,
'DEAR EXPERTS, FOR THE PAST
10 YEARS I SPENT EVENINGS
AND WEEKENDS RESTORING A
68 CAMARO TO MINT CONDITION,
I INVESTED THOUSANDS OF HOURS
AND MANY DOLLARS GETTING
IT PERFECT.
>>RED: WOW THAT'S
A BEAUTIFUL CAR.
>>DOUGIE: THAT FELLOW OUGHT
TO BE MIGHTY PROUD YOU
KNOW THAT IS A DANDY.
>>HAROLD: WHEN I WAS FINISHED
I WAS OVERWHELMED WITH
A GREAT FEELING OF EMPTINESS.
SUDDENLY I REALIZED THAT
I HAD WASTED AN ENTIRE DECADE
OF MY LIFE ON A STUPID CAR,
10 PRECIOUS YEARS GONE,
MY FAMILY WERE GONE.
WHAT A SELFISH, BLIND FOOL
I HAD BEEN.
HOW CAN I FIND MEANING IN
LIFE AGAIN?' SIGNED DESPONDENT.
>>DOUGIE: DOES HE SAY IF
HE WANTS TO SELL THE CAR?
>>HAROLD: WELL I DON'T KNOW.
>>RED: I THINK WHAT WE'RE
HAVING HERE WITH OUR VIEWER
IS WHAT WE CALL MID CAR CRISIS,
THIS FELLOW NEEDS A LITTLE
GUIDANCE AND ONE GREAT PLACE
TO FIND SOME WORDS OF COMFORT
AND ADVICE IS IN YOUR
FORTUNE COOKIES.
I WOULD SUGGEST YOU GET
DOWN TO THE BULK FOOD STORE
THERE WITH SAY A 10 GALLON PAIL
AND JUST LOAD HER RIGHT UP
AND SIT DOWN IN FRONT OF ONE OF
YOUR FAVOURITE SOAPS AND JUST
PIG OUT AND GET ALL KINDS
OF WORDS OF WISDOM ALL
AT THE SAME TIME.
>>DOUGIE: YOU KNOW RED THERE'S
ANOTHER SOURCE OF WISDOM
AND ONE I MIGHT ADD THAT HAS
A LITTLE BIT LESS M.S.G.
YOU WANT TO KNOW HOW
TO LIVE YOUR LIFE,
LIVE BY THE 10 COMMANDMENTS,
I DO.
>>RED: YEAH I GUESS
I DO TOO DOUGIE, YEAH.
>>HAROLD: WELL SO DO I,
I DO TOO, THOU SHALT NOT KILL,
I NEVER, EVER KILL.
>>RED: NO AND OF COURSE
THERE'S THOU SHALT NOT
COMMIT ADULTERY.
>>DOUGIE: WELL THAT OF
COURSE IS FOR YOU
MARRIED TYPES.
THEN AGAIN THERE'S
THOU SHALT NOT STEAL,
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
>>HAROLD: YEAH.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>>DOUGIE: THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
>>RED: AND THERE'S THE OTHERS,
HOW MANY DID WE GET?
>>HAROLD: 3, THERE WAS KILLING,
ADULTERY AND STEALING
AND THEN THERE IS?
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH.
>>DOUGIE: ISN'T THERE
ONE ABOUT THE SABBATH?
>>RED: THERE IS.
>>HAROLD: OH, HONOUR THY
MOTHER AND FATHER THAT'S ONE,
HONOUR THY MOTHER AND FATHER.
>>RED: GOOD, GOOD, UNLESS
THEY'RE ANYTHING LIKE MY FATHER.
>>DOUGIE: DO UNTO OTHERS
AS YOU HAVE THEM TO DO UNTO YOU.
>>HAROLD: YEAH.
>>DOUGIE: AND I THINK THAT'S
NUMBER 4, AND NUMBER 10
IS HAVE A NICE DAY.
>>HAROLD: YEAH,
THAT'S A CHEERFUL ONE,
THAT'S YOU KNOW NICE.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH AND I BELIEVE,
I BELIEVE NUMBER 9 IS IF YOU
LOVE SOMETHING SET IT FREE,
IF IT COMES BACK TO YOU
GO FOR IT.
AND NUMBER 3 IS
FINDER'S KEEPERS I BELIEVE.
>>DOUGIE: OH WORDS TO LIVE BY.
>>RED: OH YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>>DOUGIE: WORDS TO LIVE BY,
HOW MANY ARE WE UP TO NOW?
>>HAROLD: 9,
THERE'S JUST LIKE ONE MORE.
>>RED: YEAH.
>>DOUGIE: 9.
>>RED: IT'S NUMBER 2,
WHAT IS THAT? WHAT IS THAT?
>>DOUGIE: GOT IT, GOT IT,
IT AIN'T OVER UNTIL
THE FAT LADY SINGS.
>>RED: OKAY WELL I HOPE
OUR VIEWER CAN GET SOME HELP
OUT OF THESE GREAT WORDS
OF WISDOM.
>>DOUGIE: YEAH AND IF YOU'RE
GOING TO SELL THAT CAMARO
GIVE US A BUZZ WILL YOU?
>>RED: IT IS SUMMER,
YOU HAVE LOST YOUR SON
AT THE AMUSEMENT PARK
HE'S WEARING NEON ORANGE,
LIME GREEN AND BRIGHT PURPLE
ALLOWING HIM TO DISAPPEAR
INTO THE CROWD.
>>REG: THIS IS BEAUTIFUL
THIS IS FIRST CLASS.
>>RED: A NEW TOY THERE REG?
(RIFLE SHOT FIRES)
>>REG: OH BOY, I'M SORRY RED,
THIS NEW TELESCOPIC LENS IS
SO POWERFUL I COULDN'T EVEN
SEE YOU, OH HERE TAKE A LOOK,
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
>>RED: A GREAT BIG EYEBALL
OH NO, THAT'S A CHIPMUNK.
YOU KNOW REG THIS MIGHT
BE A LITTLE BIT TOO STRONG
FOR IT TO BE OF ANY REAL
USE TO YOU, YOU KNOW.
>>REG: WELL I BOUGHT IT TO
HUNT FOR JUNIOR'S HELICOPTER,
YOU CAN'T IGNORE TECHNOLOGY RED
NO SIR, NOW WATCH THIS,
YOU SEE THAT ACORN ON THE
1, 2, 3, 4, 5TH BRANCH
ON THE TOP OF THAT OAK TREE
OVER THERE, WATCH THIS.
(RIFLE SHOT FIRING)
>>REG: DID I GET IT?
PROBABLY EH?
I BET I DID, I BET I DID,
OKAY, NOW SEE THAT ROCK?
>>RED: WELL THE GUYS HAVE
BEEN HAVING A LOT OF FUN WITH
JUNIOR'S USED HELICOPTER BUT
THEY COULDN'T FIND A BIG ENOUGH
LANDING SPACE BETWEEN ANY OF
THE TREES AROUND THE LODGE,
SO THEY GOT OUT THE BIG CHAINSAW
LOPPED ABOUT 6 FEET OFF EACH
END OF THE HELICOPTER'S
ROTOR BLADE.
>>HAROLD: I THINK THAT WOULD
DRAMATICALLY ALTER THE FLYING
CHARACTERISTICS WOULD
IT UNCLE RED?
I MEAN YOU KNOW ACCORDING TO
MY LITTLE BOBBY-HOBBY BOOK
ON HOW TO BE AN ASTRONAUT,
I'M JUST SAYING THAT YOU KNOW
SUCH A MODIFICATION YOU KNOW,
IT WOULD SIGNIFICANTLY
DECREASE THE LIFT.
>>RED: WAS THAT JUST A LUCKY
GUESS OR DID YOU HEAR THE CRASH?
>>HAROLD: IT LANDED RIGHT
BESIDE MY WINDOW,
I ALMOST GOT CIRCUMVENTED
BY THE TAIL ROTOR.
>>RED: THAT WOULD BE NO DAMAGE
AT ALL I DON'T THINK.
THEN ALL THE GUYS HAD TO FIGURE
OUT WHETHER THEY SHOULD DECREASE
THE WEIGHT OF THE UNIT OR
INCREASE THE SPEED OF THE BLADE
AND REGAIN THE ORIGINAL PUSH.
>>HAROLD: THAT'S LIFT,
THAT'S VERTICAL LIFT.
>>RED: NO, NO, NO, NOT IN
THIS CASE, THIS IS MORE OF
A HORIZONTAL PUSH HAROLD,
THEY FIRED HER UP AND THE BLADE
WAS GOING FASTER THAN EVER
BUT THE WHOLE HELICOPTER WAS
DOING ACTUALLY MORE OF
A SIDEWAYS THAN AN UP,
SO NOW THE WHOLE FOREST ON
THE EAST SIDE OF THE LODGE
IS EXACTLY 6 FEET TALL.
>>HAROLD: WELL I GUESS WE GOT
A LOT MORE FIREWOOD THEN HUH?
>>RED: YUP AND A VIEW.
THE QUESTION IS WHO WANTS
A LAWNMOWER THAT CUTS YOUR
GRASS TO 6 FEET AND RUNS
ON AVIATION FUEL?
AND THAT'S A DANGEROUS UNIT,
I MEAN IT CAME RIGHT
THROUGH THE BUNCH OF US,
LUCKILY NONE OF THE GUYS
IS OVER 6 FEET TALL,
AT LEAST NOT ANY MORE.
>>HAROLD: YEAH I THOUGHT
I NOTICED MOOSE THOMPSON
HAD LOST A LITTLE HAIR.
>>RED: AND A LITTLE FOREHEAD,
BUT THEN A LONG FOREHEAD
ON MOOSE IS JUST FALSE
ADVERTISING ANYWAY.
SO NOW THE GUYS ARE GOING
TO MAYBE CONVERT THE THING,
THEY'RE THINKING IT OVER,
MAYBE MAKE A HOVERCRAFT OUT
OF HER OR A FAN BOAT OR
PERHAPS A 4-MAN QUESENART.
>>HAROLD: YOU GUYS ARE SCARY
WHEN YOU GET TOGETHER.
>>RED: WELL HAROLD
YOU'RE SCARY ALL BY YOURSELF.
♪ I'VE HAD TOO MUCH COFFEE ♪
♪ TOO MUCH COFFEE ♪
♪ WAY TOO MUCH COFFEE ♪
♪ AND THAT'S WHY ♪
♪ I'M WATCHING TV IN ♪
♪ THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT ♪
♪ IN THE BATHROOM ♪
♪ IF IT'S ANY OF YOUR BUSINESS ♪
>>RED: WELL BIG TROUBLE OUT
AT THE CAMPSITE THIS WEEK FOR
OUR 'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'.
BILL BROUGHT ME UP TO SHOW
ME WHAT WAS GOING ON.
HE HELD UP THE OLD PADDLE THERE
AND YOU CAN SEE THE BIG TEETH,
LOOK AT THE BIG BITE MARKS
OUT OF THAT FROM A BEAR
OR WHAT HAVE YOU,
ONE OF THOSE ITALIAN LOAVES HAVE
BEEN BADLY TREATED BY SOMETHING
VERY HUNGRY AND HE HAD A CAN OF,
SOME KIND OF CAN OF SOMETHING
THAT HAD BEEN BITTEN.
THEN HE GOT AN IDEA,
HMM, YEAH IT WASN'T AS MUCH
OF AN IDEA AS IT LOOKED
RIGHT THERE,
THAT'S ACTUALLY A LITTLE
PORTABLE LAMP THAT HE BRINGS
TO ALL HIS CAMPSITES
IN CASE THERE IS HYDRO.
ANYWAY HE'S GOT SOME WASHERS
THERE, NOW WHAT'S GOING ON
HERE NOW, SO YOU DROP THE
WASHERS INTO SOME TIN CANS,
I THINK WHAT HE'S TRYING TO
DO IS MAKE SOME KIND OF
A NOISEMAKER TYPE OF DEAL.
HMM, THAT'S KIND OF ODD.
(SPLAT OF BIRD DROPPINGS)
OH THAT'S WHY THAT HAPPENED,
ALL RIGHT NOW HE STRINGS
ALL THE CANS WITH THE WASHERS
ON THEM YOU SEE AND YOU STRING
IT ACROSS LIKE A...
I GUESS IT'S LIKE A TRIPWIRE,
AND HE GETS AROUND THE TREE
TO THAT AND PULLED HER TIGHT,
I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD USE
A JERKING MOTION WITH THOSE,
I THINK YOU SHOULD JUST TIGHTEN
THAT GRADUALLY BILL,
DON'T, DON'T, BILL, BILL, BILL,
OH! OH! OH NOW THE WASHERS ARE
KIND OF LIKE A, ALMOST LIKE
A BULLET AT THIS POINT.
YEAH HE'S FINE, YEAH, YEAH,
NO, OH, OH, OH, OH THE
END OF ANOTHER GOOD IDEA.
ANYWAY WE PUT THE WASHERS
BACK IN, SEE HOW THAT WORKS,
ANY KIND OF AN ANIMAL WILL HEAR
THAT AND THEN HE HAD ANOTHER
RIG THERE WITH A LITTLE BUNCH
OF CURVE FEELERS OFF THE OLD,
(BELLS RINGING)
OH NO THIS IS THE JINGLE BELL
ONE FIRST, YEAH, I LOVE THAT,
IT'S LIKE, IT SOUNDS LIKE
SANTA'S COMING TO TOWN HUH?
THESE ARE THE CURB FEELERS
OFF THE OLD STUDEBAKER,
ISN'T THAT NICE?
OR MAYBE THOSE ARE THE
SPARKLER THINGS, I'M NOT SURE.
ANYWAY THE SAME IDEA,
THE ANIMAL TRIPS OVER THAT AND
SO NOW BILL CAN JUST GET BACK
INTO THE TENT AND LIE DOWN
AND HE'S JUST GOING TO READ,
YOU KNOW HE'S GOING TO
TAKE HIS PADDLE,
HE LIKES TO CUDDLE UP WITH
A PADDLE EVER SINCE THAT
CANOEING ACCIDENT AND HE
JUST PRETENDS HE'S ASLEEP,
(LOUD SNORING)
JUST PRETENDS HE'S ASLEEP!
BILL, HE'S A GOOD ACTOR,
WELL IF HE CAN PRETEND
HE'S ASLEEP, I'LL PRETEND
I'M AN ANIMAL.
TIME TO RING YOUR
BELLS THERE BILL.
(BELLS JINGLING)
UP, GET UP,
STEP ONE GET OUT OF THE TENT,
OUT OF THE TENT,
GET OUT OF THERE BILL!
GET OUT, GET OUT OF THERE,
GET OUT OF THERE,
NOW GO AND GET THAT VARMINT,
THAT'S IT, WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
COME BACK THE OTHER WAY
AND OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
(BILL SCREAMING) OW!
>>RED: OH, OH, NOW SEE IN
THE OLD DAYS HE WOULDN'T KNOWN
THERE WAS AN ANIMAL AND THEN
IT'D BE EATING ALL HIS FOOD,
THAT'S PROGRESS EH BILL?
>>RED: AND NOW WITH MY APOLOGIES
TO YOUNG PEOPLE EVERYWHERE,
HERE'S HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: IT'S TIME NOW FOR
TEENS TO TUNE INTO THAT
TECHNO POP, HIP HOP TALK
PART OF THE OTHER SHOW,
OKAY TODAY I'M GOING TO BE
REVIEWING THAT CLASSIC FILM,
'GONE WITH THE WIND'
PEE-EU!
YOU SEE IT WAS LIKE 4 HOURS LONG
THAT'S LIKE YOU KNOW
2 VIDEO CASSETTES,
OKAY ENOUGH IS ENOUGH EVEN
'GONE WITH THE WIND'
IT SHOULD OF BEEN CALLED
LIKE 'GONE FOR LUNCH' OR
LIKE 'GONE FISHING FOR A PLOT'
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
4 HOURS, YOU KNOW I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE AUDIENCES HAD MORE TIME
ON THEIR HANDS WHEN THIS MOVIE
WAS MADE BACK IN THE 1800'S
OR SOMETHING, I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I'M TELLING YOU
TODAY'S AUDIENCES.
>>RED: HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: WHAT?
>>RED: I REALLY LIKED
'GONE WITH THE WIND' OKAY
4 HOURS OF FIRES, WAR HORSES
AND AT THE END CLARK GABLE
SWORE A LITTLE.
>>HAROLD: YOU KNOW I'D LOOK
A LITTLE BIT LIKE CLARK GABLE
IF I HAD A MUSTACHE.
>>RED: HAROLD IF YOU HAD
A MUSTACHE YOU'D LOOK
LIKE YOUR MOTHER.
>>HAROLD: WELL THANK YOU.
>>RED: BEA'S NOT GOING
TO BE HAPPY TO HEAR.
>>RED: I KNOW A LOT OF YOU
TEENAGERS GO TO THE MOVIES
BECAUSE I'M THE GUY THAT SITS
BEHIND YOU AND TELLS YOU TO
SHUT UP AND REMINDS YOU THAT
THAT GIRL YOU'RE WITH IS THE
DAUGHTER OF A FRIEND OF MINE.
SO I KNOW THAT YOU'RE GETTING
EXPOSED TO A LOT OF VIOLENCE
ESPECIALLY IF YOU KEEP RATTLING
THAT CELLOPHANE BAG OF JUJUBES.
BUT THE MOVIES TODAY,
OH MY GOD, IT SEEMS LIKE
SOMEBODY'S ALWAYS GETTING THEIR
HEAD BLOWN OFF OR YOU GET
THE SLICE AND DICE,
OR YOU GOT RAMBO TURNING
EVERYBODY INTO SPAMBO.
I WOULDN'T DO TO FISH WHAT
THE PEOPLE DO TO EACH OTHER
IN SOME OF THESE MOVIES.
AND I'M CONCERNED THAT THE
YOUNGSTERS START ACCEPTING
THAT LEVEL OF VIOLENCE
AS PART OF THEIR NORMAL
DAILY LIVES, THIS COULD BE
BAD NEWS FOR CROSSING GUARDS.
SO I'M ASKING YOU, YOU TEENAGERS
PARTICULARLY TO JUST PUT THE
VIOLENCE ON THE BACK BURNER,
START CONCENTRATING ON SEX
THAT'S WHERE YOU SHOULD
TURN YOUR MIND BECAUSE THE
LIBIDO WILL ONLY LAST A CERTAIN
LENGTH OF TIME WHEREAS THE URGE
TO SMACK SOMEBODY IN THE
MELON GOES RIGHT TO
THE GRAVE AND BEYOND.
>>RED: I HEARD THAT
JUNIOR SINGLETON WAS FOOLING
AROUND WITH HIS HELICOPTER
DOWN BY THE DOCK, SO I WENT
DOWN TO SEE HAP SHAUGHNESSY
AND SEE IF HE'D SEEN HIM
AND HAD ANY IDEA WHAT
WAS GOING ON?
HAVE YOU SEEN JUNIOR SINGLETON?
I HEARD HE WAS DOWN AT
THE DOCK HERE.
>>HAP: HE'S PROBABLY DOWN AT
THE BOAT HOUSE DOCK RED,
CLIMB ON, I'LL GIVE
YOU A RIDE OVER.
>>RED: WELL I DON'T WANT
TO CAUSE ANY INCONVENIENCE.
>>HAP: NO INCONVENIENCE
TO ME RED.
>>RED: YEAH I KNOW.
>>HAP: WHAT'S JUNIOR SINGLETON
DOING DOWN AT THE BOAT
HOUSE DOCK?
>>RED: I DON'T REALLY KNOW
BUT IT INVOLVES WHATEVER IS
LEFT OF HIS HELICOPTER.
>>HAP: HE WAS ASKING FOR
TROUBLE FLYING WITHOUT A LICENCE
WHY DIDN'T HE ASK ME,
I NEVER CRASHED ONCE IN VIETNAM
OR KOREA OR OPERATION DESERT
SONG, THE FALKLANDS OR TOLEDO,
I WAS A HELICOPTER
TRAFFIC REPORTER.
>>RED: IN TOLEDO?
>>HAP: NO, VIETNAM.
IN TOLEDO I WAS LONI ANDERSON'S
PRIVATE PILOT BUT I NEVER,
EVER CRASHED A HELICOPTER.
>>RED: NO ME EITHER.
>>HAP: YOU DON'T
FLY HELICOPTERS.
>>RED: YEAH ME EITHER.
>>HAP: NOW HANG ON,
I KNOW EVERYTHING THERE IS
TO KNOW ABOUT HELICOPTERS.
THE LAST TIME I WAS IN THE ANDES
THIS PLANE CRASHED INTO
A MOUNTAIN PASS,
THE ONLY WAY TO RESCUE THE
SURVIVORS WAS BY HELICOPTER
BUT THE BIG CHOPPERS COULDN'T
HOVER IN THE THIN MOUNTAIN AIR.
SO I ELIMINATED EVERYTHING BUT
THE ENGINE AND THE THROTTLE,
AND GRIPPING TIGHTLY ONTO
THE EXHAUST I FLEW UP THERE
AND I GOT THOSE PEOPLE,
WELL THEY MADE A BOOK
AND A MOVIE ABOUT IT.
>>RED: OH YEAH,
THE GREAT IMPOSTER.
>>HAP: NO THIS WAS CALLED A LIE,
HARRISON FORD PLAYED MY PART
BUT HE WAS CUT OUT
OF THE FINAL VERSION.
IT'S TOO BAD TOO,
HE GAVE A VERY CONVINCING AND
A VERY BELIEVABLE PERFORMANCE.
>>RED: OH, SO HE CHANGED
THE CHARACTER COMPLETELY.
>>RED: WELL THIS USED
HELICOPTER HAS TURNED
INTO A REAL CHALLENGE,
I SUGGESTED JUNIOR RETURN IT
AND AT LEAST GET SOME OF
HIS MONEY BACK, BUT HE SAID
THAT HIS WIFE ALREADY FOUND OUT
THAT HE BOUGHT IT SO THERE'S
REALLY NO SAFE WAY OUT
OF THIS AT THIS POINT.
>>HAROLD: YOU KNOW IF PEOPLE
THOUGHT THESE THINGS THROUGH
MAYBE WE WOULDN'T HAVE
THESE KINDS OF PROBLEMS.
>>RED: HOW MANY TIMES HAVE
I WISHED THAT YOUR PARENTS HAD
THOUGHT THINGS THROUGH HAROLD.
BUT WE MAKE THE BEST OF IT
AND THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT JUNIOR
HAS DONE, HE TOOK THE MOTOR
AND THE BLADE OFF THE HELICOPTER
AND HE MOUNTED THEM SIDEWAYS
ON THE BOAT HOUSE LIKE
A HUGE NUCLEAR FAN,
AND THEN HE TOOK WHAT WAS LEFT
OF THE HELICOPTER, ADDED A
COUPLE OF CANOES TO IT AND
MADE HIMSELF A GLIDER.
>>HAROLD: WOW!
SO HOW DOES THIS WORK LIKE NOW?
DOES THE NUCLEAR FAN JUST KIND
OF BLOW THE GLIDER AWAY?
>>RED: NO, BUSTER HADFIELD
TIED A ROPE TO THE GLIDER
AND ANCHORED IT TO THE DOCK,
SO JUNIOR KIND OF FLOATS OVER
THE LAKE JUST LIKE THAT,
HE CAN FLY IN A STRAIGHT LINE
FOR 5 OR 6 HOURS AND NEVER
BE MORE THAN 89 FEET
FROM THE LODGE.
AND HE DOESN'T NEED A LICENCE
BECAUSE IT'S NOT REALLY
AN AIRPLANE, IT'S CLASSIFIED
AS A MANNED KITE,
OR MAYBE A MANNED
LIGHTNING ROD, WE'LL SEE.
>>HAROLD: WHATEVER IT IS
IT SOUNDS COOL!
I'D LOVE TO TRY THAT,
DO YOU THINK I COULD
TRUST YOU GUYS NOT
TO CUT THE ROPE?
>>RED: NOT A CHANCE HAROLD.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH IT'S MEETING TIME,
I'M GOING TO GO DOWN TO THE
MEETING AND I'M GOING TO GET
THOSE GUYS TO SWEAR THEY'RE
NOT GOING TO CUT THE ROPE.
>>RED: WELL YOU USUALLY GET
THE GUYS TO SWEAR HAROLD
BUT IT GENERALLY LACKS FOCUS.
GO GIVE IT A TRY AND I'LL
BE DOWN IN A MINUTE
ALL RIGHT.
>>HAROLD: OKAY, YEAH.
>>RED: WELL I GUESS THE
HELICOPTER THING WASN'T
A TOTAL DISASTER,
I MEAN JUNIOR GOT A NEW TOY
OUT OF IT AND NOW WE'RE
GUARANTEED A BREEZE ON
POSSUM LAKE EVEN IF IT DROWNS
OUT ALL CONVERSATION AND
SHREDS THE OCCASIONAL DUCK.
ANYWAY IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
I HOPE YOU NOTICED WHAT
HAPPENED HERE TONIGHT,
JUNIOR WENT OUT AND SPENT
A WHOLE LOT OF MONEY ON
A HELICOPTER AND THEY'RE
STILL MARRIED...
SO SURELY I SHOULD BE ABLE TO
BUY A FISHING ROD WITHOUT
CALLING THE MARRIAGE COUNSELLOR
WOULDN'T YOU THINK?
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
♪ ♪ ♪
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT I KNOW A LOT
OF YOU WERE DISAPPOINTED ABOUT
HOW THAT HELICOPTER THING
TURNED OUT.
>>GROUP: YEAH.
>>RED: WE CAN'T GET AWAY
FROM THE REALITY THAT WE HAVE
LEVELLED OVER 200 ACRES OF BUSH.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca