LOTS OF GUYS TRY TO
MAKE CUT-OFF SHORTS
OUT OF THEIR
OLD WORK PANTS.
THE PROBLEM IS GETTING
THE LEGS THE SAME LENGTH.
SOMETIMES, YOUR TIN SNIPS
OR YOUR PRUNING SHEARS
JUST AREN'T SHARP ENOUGH
TO DO A GOOD, CLEAN JOB.
NOW, HERE'S AN IDEA.
JUST TAKE YOUR OLD PANTS
AND DUCT TAPE THEM TO
A PIECE OF SCRAP PLYWOOD.
LET THE TABLE SAW DO THE WORK.
[saw cutting]
[laughter and applause]
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW!!!
HERE'S THE MAN WHO'S FORGOTTEN
MORE THAN HE'LL EVER REMEMBER.
YOUR HOST, YOUR HERO,
BUT HE'S MY UNCLE:
RED GREEEEEN!!!
[applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
WELL, GUESS WHAT?
THE POSSUM VAN GOT TOWED AGAIN.
WHAT KIND OF WORLD IS THIS
WHERE YOU CAN'T EVEN DOUBLE
PARK IN YOUR OWN HOMETOWN?
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO REMEMBER
TO TURN THE POSSUM VAN OFF.
YOUR EXHAUST FUMES
KILLED THAT FLORAL CLOCK.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
NONE OF THE VEHICLES ARE EVER
GOING TO GET TOWED AGAIN.
LISTEN TO THIS.
THE TOWN COUNCIL HAS
PUT OUT TENDERS
AND POSSUM LODGE IS GOING TO
GO AFTER THE TOWING CONTRACT
'CAUSE WE PUT IN THE LOWEST BID.
WE'RE GOING TO GET 'ER.
YEAH.
YOU DON'T HAVE
A TOW TRUCK.
THAT'S WHY OUR
BID IS SO LOW.
WE GOT NO OVERHEAD.
YOU GOT NO INHEAD.
STOP IT.
WHAT?
IT'S TIME TO PLAY
"THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME."
AND TODAY'S GRAND PRIZE IS
A PAIR OF CHINESE FINGER CUFFS.
[laughter]
AND THEY WORK!
OUR SPECIAL GUEST
TODAY IS RANGER GORD.
[applause]
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET RANGER GORD TO SAY
THE FOLLOWING WORD:
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
GO!!!
GORD, FILL IN THE BLANK.
YOU CAN'T SEE THE SOMETHING
FOR THE TREES.
THE BEAR.
NOT THE BEAR.
THE PULL-OUT COUCH?
YOU'RE ONE OF THESE, OKAY?
YOU ARE A BLANK RANGER.
[laughter]
I'VE NEVER BEEN SO INSULTED!
OH, OH...
...LONELY?
NO, NO.
UH... SEXY?
NO.
Harold:
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT
OF TIME, UNCLE RED.
A BUNCH OF TREES.
A FLOCK.
YOU'RE THINKING BIRDS.
A QUIVER.
A GAGGLE.
TREES TRAVEL IN GAGGLES.
GORD...
TREES DON'T TRAVEL IN ANYTHING.
OH, REALLY?
WHAT ABOUT A LOGGING TRUCK?
[laughter and applause]
I'VE SEEN A WHOLE FOREST
GOING DOWN A HIGHWAY.
FIRE! FIRE!
[ring! ring! ring !]
WELL, I THINK
THAT WENT WELL.
THAT'S WHAT
YOU WANTED?
WE GOT THE TOWING
CONTRACT, DIDN'T WE?
YOU GOT A LOT
MORE THAN THAT.
THAT WAS THEIR IDEA.
I DIDN'T REALIZE
THAT ALL THE TOWN'S SERVICES
CAME UNDER THE ONE CONTRACT.
BUT, WE'LL
MAKE IT WORK.
SO, THE FIRE SERVICES
AND THE SNOW PLOWING
AND EMERGENCY MEDICAL SERVICES
DOESN'T SCARE YOU AT ALL, HUH?
WE'LL FIGURE
IT OUT, HAROLD.
ANYWAY, NOTHING EVER
HAPPENS AROUND HERE.
[telephone ringing]
WELL, WHO DO YOU
SUPPOSE THAT'S FOR?
[phone ringing]
THE TOW TRUCK
WE DON'T HAVE?
THE FIRE TRUCK
WE DON'T NEED?
OR THE AMBULANCE
THAT DOESN'T EXIST?
Red:
DON'T ANSWER!
IT MIGHT BE AN EMERGENCY.
HELLO?
I'VE GOT TO GET
AN UNLISTED NUMBER.
IT'S MOOSE THOMPSON'S MOTHER!
MOOSE HAS GOT HIS HEAD
STUCK IN THE FRIDGE.
SHOULD WE SEND THE AMBULANCE
OR THE TOW TRUCK?
TELL HER TO JUST KNOCK
THE FRIDGE UP A NOTCH
AND ONCE HIS HEAD FREEZES,
IT'LL SHRINK.
[laughter]
OOOOH...
WHEN YOU WISH UPON A STAR
MAKE SURE IT'S
NOT OUR OWN SUN
'CAUSE WISHING ON OUR SUN
ISN'T VERY MUCH FUN
UNLESS YOUR WISH IS
TO BURN OUT YOUR RETINAS
AS WE MEN GET OLDER,
PEOPLE START TO PESTER US
TO EXERCISE MORE.
MOST OF US THINK WE'RE ALREADY
GETTING ENOUGH EXERCISE
WITH THE EQUIPMENT WE
USED FOR YEARS,
A FORK AND A REMOTE CONTROL.
PERSONALLY, I DON'T
WANT BUNS OF STEEL.
STEEL RUSTS
AND WHO WANTS FRIDGE MAGNETS
ALL OVER THEIR BUTT?
NOW, COMMON SENSE TELLS ME:
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO WALK
ANYWHERE YOU CAN DRIVE,
SO THE CAR BECOMES A PERFECT
PLACE TO EXERCISE.
[crash!]
SO, THIS WEEK ON
"HANDYMAN CORNER,"
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW
YOU CAN TURN YOUR CAR
INTO A TOTAL WORKOUT GYM.
LET'S START WITH THE GRIP.
A FIRM HANDSHAKE WILL MAKE
PEOPLE THINK YOU'RE IN SHAPE.
WHEN I DRIVE, I HAVE AT LEAST
ONE HAND ON THE WHEEL.
LET'S JUST ATTACH THE GRIP
TO THE WHEEL USING...
"THE HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON:"
DUCT TAPE.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS DRIVE ALONG THERE,
SQUEEZING ON YOUR EXERCISE GRIPS
[honk!]
AND THE HORN HONKS.
THAT'S GOOD BECAUSE THIS WAY,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO EXERCISE
YOUR BICEPS AND TRICEPS
[hooonk!]
WAVING AT STRANGERS
YOU HAVE STARTLED.
NOW, YOU'LL SEE THOSE EXERCISE
MACHINES ADVERTISED ON TV
WITH THE BUNGIES AND PULLEYS.
'CAUSE THEY'RE INTERESTED IN
GETTING THE SMOOTH TRANSACTION
WITH A VALID CREDIT CARD.
WELL, THAT'S OUT OF OUR LEAGUE.
WE'RE JUST GOING TO ATTACH
THIS AROUND THE DRIVER'S SEAT
USING THE HANDYMAN'S,
WELL, YOU KNOW...
NOW, YOU HOOK YOUR BUNGIES
UNDER THE DRIVERS'S SEAT
AND TAKE THEM UP THROUGH
THE PULLEY, LIKE THAT.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE
WEARING SUSPENDERS,
RULE OF THUMB:
IF YOUR BUTT IS UP WHERE
YOUR ARMPIT SHOULD BE,
YOU'VE GOT TOO MUCH TENSION.
THESE SHOVEL HANDLES MAKE IT
EASIER TO GRIP THE ENDS
AND PROBABLY KEEP YOU
FROM LOSING AN EYE.
PLUS, WHEN YOU'RE DISCUSSING
YOUR EXERCISE PROGRAM,
A SHOVEL CAN COME IN HANDY.
[clang!]
WELL, YOU SHOULD BE WATCHING.
WE NEED TO EXERCISE THE LARGEST
AND MOST OFTEN USED MUSCLE
OF THE BODY.
THIS MUSCLE RIGHT HERE.
SO, WE'RE GOING TO
BUILD A SIT-UP STATION
INTO OUR "TOTAL WORKOUT CAR"
BY CAREFULLY REMOVING
THE BACK SUPPORT OF THE SEAT.
[whack!]
I'VE LOOSENED OFF THE SEAT.
NOW, I CAN DO FULL SIT-UPS
WHILE DOING MY ARM EXERCISES.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GIVE HER A TEST RUN.
[breathing out]
UNNGHHH!!!
UNNGHH!!!
UNGHHH!!!
NINETY-NINE...
OOOH!
THAT WORKED PERFECT, DIDN'T IT?
YOU MIGHT WANT TO KIND OF...
[creaking sounds]
...WORK UP TO THAT SLOWLY.
IN SMALL STEPS OVER...
50 OR 60 YEARS.
YOU KNOW, I THINK WE NEED
TO GET OUR LOWER BODY
FEELING JUST AS GOOD
AS OUR UPPER BODY.
SO, WE'RE GOING TO MODIFY
THE VEHICLE A LITTLE BIT
AND GIVE OUR LEGS
A LITTLE BIT OF A WORKOUT.
WHAT I'M GOING TO DO IS...
[creaking]
...TAKE THE TRANSMISSION FLUID
AND I'M GOING TO POUR IT ALL
OVER THE BRAKE SHOES AND DRUMS.
THAT WAY, WHEN I WANT
TO PUT ON THE BRAKES,
I'VE REALLY GOTTA HORSE 'ER ON
USING BOTH FEET.
THAT'LL BE GREAT FOR THE QUADS,
AND THE PECS,
AND THE TRAPS,
AND THE GLUTES.
AND ESPECIALLY...
THE INSURANCE POLICY.
[sound of running liquid]
NOW, I CAN EXERCISE
WHILE I'M DRIVING.
LIKE SAY, DOWN TO
THE ICE CREAM STORE.
I CAN EVEN GET THAT
"SUPER-DUPER SCOOPER CONE"
WITHOUT FEELING
THE LEAST BIT GUILTY.
SO, REMEMBER...
"IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY."
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
IT'S TIME FOR MY WORKOUT.
[CRASH!!!]
SOONER OR LATER,
SOME MISGUIDED RELATIVE IS GOING
TO BUY YOU A GIFT BOX OF SOAP.
AND I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT
USEFUL, REGULAR, NATURAL SOAP.
I'M TALKING ABOUT STUFF LIKE...
SCRUFFING LOTION,
HYDROLOGIZING MOISTURE GEL,
EXFOLIATING CREAM.
MEN DON'T NEED THAT.
WE HAVE A VERY SIMPLE APPROACH:
IF IT'S DIRTY - WASH IT.
IF IT'S HAIRY - CLIP IT.
IF IT NEEDS EXFOLIATING,
EITHER CALL YOUR PLUMBER
OR YOUR LOCAL CLERGYMAN.
[laughter and applause]
MAYBE YOU WANT TO GET FANCY.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO PUT ON
SOME AFTERSHAVE AND DEODORANT.
MAYBE A FRESH PAIR OF SOCKS.
BUT, YOU'VE GOT TO ASK YOURSELF:
WHO AM I TRYING TO IMPRESS?
IF THE ANSWER IS MY WIFE'S
BEST FRIEND CHANTEL,
YOUR LIFE'S ABOUT TO GET
WAY TOO COMPLICATED.
IF YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT
GETTING A LITTLE FANCY,
HERE'S A LITTLE TIP.
CLEANLINESS IS NEXT
TO GODLINESS,
BUT SCRUFFING IS NEXT
TO A HEART ATTACK
AND JUST THIS SIDE OF A DIVORCE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YA.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
OKAY, WE'VE GOT THE SNOW PLOW.
WE'RE GOING TO USE
STINKY PETERSON'S K-CAR.
THE K-CAR ISN'T STRONG ENOUGH
TO BE A PLOW.
NO, WE'RE GOING TO USE
THE K-CAR AS THE BLADE.
[loud laughter]
OH, YEAH.
[applause]
WE'LL DUCT TAPE IT ONTO
DOUGIE'S MONSTER TRUCK.
AND FOR THE AMBULANCE,
WE'RE JUST GOING TO USE
THE POSSUM VAN.
WHAT ABOUT THE FIRE ENGINE?
AAAH!!!
WE'RE GOING TO USE
WINSTON'S SEWAGE TRUCK.
[laughter]
THERE GOES THE OZONE LAYER.
[phone ringing]
WE GOT AN EMERGENCY CALL!!!
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
TRY ANSWERING THE PHONE.
[phone ringing]
EXCELLENT CHOICE.
THIS IS SO EXCITING!
THIS IS GREAT!
POSSUM LODGE EMERGENCY CENTRE.
YOUR DISASTER IS OUR PLEASURE.
OH MY -- OH BOY!
IS IT FOR WINSTON
OR FOR DOUGIE?
YEAH, OKAY.
NO PROBLEM.
WE'LL BE THERE
AS FAST AS WE CAN.
WE'LL BE IN A BLUE VAN WITH
A POSSUM PAINTED ON THE SIDE.
BUT, IT'S ALL WE HAVE.
WELL, I SAID THAT TO HIM...
SORRY!!!
THANKS FOR CALLING!
C'MON, UNCLE RED.
[laughter]
[applause]
SHE HUNG UP.
[laughter]
TIME TO FIRE UP
THE AMBULANCE.
C'MON, LET'S GO.
HAROLD, YOU KNOW I HATE
THE SIGHT OF BLOOD.
HOW ABOUT THE SIGHT OF BABIES?
THAT'S WHAT SHE'S HAVING.
COME ON, COME ON!!!
AS YOU KNOW, THIS
IS NEW MEMBER NIGHT
AND DALTON HAS BROUGHT A FELLOW
HE WOULD LIKE TO PRESENT.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO GET
ALL DRESSED UP FOR THIS.
THANK-YOU, RED.
I WOULD LIKE TO INTRODUCE
MY GOOD FRIEND, SID LARSON.
Dalton:
I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU,
SID IS MY KIND OF GUY.
[lodge members]
AAAh!!!
SETTLE DOWN, STOP THAT.
NOW, I'M HOPEFUL THAT SID COULD
BECOME MY DAUGHTER'S BOYFRIEND.
BUT AS A FIRST STEP,
I WOULD LIKE YOU TO SUPPORT ME
IN GETTING SID INTO THE LODGE.
AS YOU WELL KNOW,
MY DAUGHTER HAS
BAD TASTE IN MEN.
Dalton:
SO, I'M THINKING THAT SYD
HAS GOT A REAL SHOT AT IT.
OF COURSE, IT'S BOUND TO
BE A BIG IMPROVEMENT.
I'D LIKE TO SAY THAT
HER CURRENT BOYFRIEND
IS BETWEEN JOBS.
BUT, HE'S NEVER HAD ONE.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
SID HAS BEEN RUNNING
THE WEIGH STATION
FOR 15 YEARS.
GETTING MY DAUGHTER
ON THAT WEIGH SCALE
MIGHT NOT BE
A BAD IDEA, SID.
[laughter]
YESIREE, MY DAUGHTER HAS
NO CONCEPT OF SAVING MONEY,
NONE AT ALL.
SID, ON THE OTHER HAND,
IS THE CHEAPEST MAN I'VE MET.
HOOKING THEM TWO TOGETHER
IS GOING TO BE LIKE
THE CLASH OF THE TITANS
THAT MOST MARRIAGES
COULD ONLY DREAM ABOUT.
I'M ASKING YOU
TO SUPPORT ME
IN MAKING HIM A MEMBER
AND DOING ME A FAVOUR.
THANK-YOU, VERY MUCH.
ALL THOSE IN FAVOUR?
BY THE WAY...
THE BANK SAYS AS SOON
AS SID IS A MEMBER,
WE GET THAT LODGE LOAN.
[lodge members]
AYE!!!
[narrated by Red]
I'M NOT SURE WHAT BILL HAS
IN MIND FOR TODAY.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
LET ME SEE IT.
I CAN'T READ IT.
OH, WILD HONEY.
WHAT'S THE HOCKEY STICK FOR?
OH, NO!
BILL, NO!
NOT A HOCKEY STICK.
THAT'S JUST NOT SMART.
THERE'S A HIVE!
THAT'S NOT SMART, BILL.
YEAH, YOU GOT 'EM.
THERE THEY ARE.
[bees buzzing]
I THINK I'LL JUST STAND HERE.
QUIETLY.
NOW, HE'S TRYING TO
GET SOME SMOKE GOING.
THERE'S NOT TOO MUCH SMOKE
COMING OUT OF THAT FIRE.
I HOPE THAT'S WATER.
ALL RIGHT, PUT THAT
ON THE GRASS AND...
I SEE...
THAT'S NOT MUCH SMOKE, BILL.
GET SOME MORE WATER.
YOU NEED MORE WATER.
BILL, THAT'S A GAS CAN.
BILL...
[boom!!!]
WHERE'S THE GAS CAN?
THERE IT IS.
WHAT'S THIS NOW?
OH...
YOU'RE GONNA GET THE HIVE?
[crash!]
I THINK I'LL STAND HERE.
QUIETLY.
OH, BOY!
THIS IS GOING TO WORK.
OH, YEAH!
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK I'LL DO?
RIGHT!
[bees buzzing furiously]
WHAT NOW, BILL?
OH, YES.
STANDING QUIETLY.
THAT'S GREAT.
I THINK I'LL JUST...
YOU KNOW.
NO PROBLEM.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU GOT THE HONEY?
OH! OH! OH!
STAND STILL, BILL.
DON'T MOVE!
WE GOT THE HIVE OFF.
WHAT THAT, BILL?
STOP THAT!
WHAT IS IT?
OH, IT'S HONEY.
I'M GLAD I DON'T
DO YOUR LAUNDRY.
I'M JUST GOING TO STAND HERE.
QUIETLY.
THE "EXPERT PORTION"
OF THE SHOW.
WHERE WE LIKE TO EXAMINE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY:
[studio audience]
I DON'T KNOW!!!
JOINING MY UNCLE RED
IS HIS BEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE WIDE ROOM:
MR. MIKE HAMAR.
[applause]
TODAY'S LETTER GOES:
"DEAR EXPERTS..."
LA-LA-LA
WE'D LIKE TO MAKE OUR HOUSE
SAFE FROM INTRUDERS,
BUT WE CAN'T AFFORD AN
EXPENSIVE ALARM SYSTEM.
SO, WE'VE WIRED OUR OUTSIDE
DOOR KNOBS TO THE STOVE.
[laughter]
WE DON'T HAVE
ANY INTRUDERS,
BUT WE'VE BEEN
ELECTROCUTED
SO MANY TIMES
THAT WE'VE BURNED ALL
THE HAIR OFF OUR ARMS.
[laughter]
ANY SUGGESTIONS?
YEAH, WEAR OVEN MITTS.
I THINK IT'S TERRIBLE
WE LIVE IN A SOCIETY
WHERE PEOPLE BREAK INTO
OTHER PEOPLE'S HOMES.
I RESENT THAT, HAROLD.
I WASN'T ANYWHERE
NEAR THE PLACE.
I WAS WITH FLINTY McCLINTOCK.
MIKE, FLINTY'S
OUT OF TOWN.
SEE, THERE YOU GO.
I WAS OUT OF TOWN.
WE'RE NOT
ACCUSING YOU.
WE'RE RESPONDING TO
THE VIEWER'S QUESTION.
OH, RIGHT.
I THINK THAT ALARM SYSTEMS
ARE REALLY UNNECESSARY
BECAUSE NICE PEOPLE COULD...
NICE PEOPLE COULD GET
ACCIDENTLY HURT, OR SOMETHING.
NICE PEOPLE
LIKE YOU, MIKE?
NOT LIKE ME,
MR. GREEN.
'CAUSE I WAS
OUT OF TOWN.
OH, RIGHT.
I'LL TELL THIS VIEWER WHAT
ONE OF MY DADS TOLD ME.
WHICH ONE OF YOUR DADS?
IT WAS MY FRIDAY DAD.
TWO WEEKS RUNNING.
HE ONCE SAID:
"DO UNTO OTHERS BEFORE
SOMEONE DOES IT TO YOU."
HE SAYS THAT'S IN THE BIBLE.
NOT IN THE KING JAMES VERSION.
MAYBE THE JESSE JAMES VERSION.
WELL...
THIS DAD WAS A CLERGYMAN,
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
'CAUSE HE PLAYED DRUMS
IN A
JUDAS PRIEST
TRIBUTE BAND.
HE ALWAYS USED TO SAY
THAT PEOPLE SHOULD FOLLOW
"THE GOLD CARD RULE."
I THINK HE MEANT
"THE GOLDEN RULE."
NO, "THE GOLD CARD RULE."
"IF YOU WANT TO
PROTECT YOUR STUFF,
DON'T LEAVE HOME WITHOUT IT."
[laughter]
THAT WAS SO FANTASTIC!!!
THAT WAS AWESOME!
THE MIRACLE OF BIRTH!!!
IT WAS A BABY
AND I WAS IN CHARGE.
I DID IT ALL!
WELL, I GUESS THE MOTHER
HELPED OUT A LITTLE BIT,
BUT I WAS THERE!
AND THANK-YOU FOR NOT
BUTTING IN AND TAKING OVER.
THAT WAS GREAT.
NO PROBLEM, HAROLD.
DID YOU SEE THE BIRTH?
NOT ON PURPOSE.
THE HEAD CROWN,
THE MOTHER WAS PUSHING.
HAROLD...
WE DON'T NEED TO
KNOW THE DETAILS.
MOTHER AND SON
ARE DOING FINE.
THAT'S ALL
THAT MATTERS.
THAT WAS A GIRL.
NO, NO, NO.
THAT WAS DEFINITELY A BOY.
NO, YOU WERE LOOKING
AT THE UMBILICAL CORD.
I'M SO GLAD I'M A GUY.
ME TOO!
I NEVER WANT TO GO
THROUGH THAT AGAIN.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO HAVE TO.
WE'VE RIPPED UP
OUR SERVICE CONTRACT
WITH THE TOWN COUNCIL
BEFORE ANYONE GETS HURT.
WOW, THAT'S VERY
MATURE OF YOU.
HAVE YOU TOLD
THE TOWN COUNCIL?
IT WAS THEIR IDEA.
[squeal of the Possum]
IT'S MEETING TIME.
AH, YOU GO AHEAD,
DR. STRANGEGLOVE.
I'LL BE DOWN IN
A FEW MINUTES.
I'M REALLY GLAD
I'M A GUY, HAROLD.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
SO GLAD I'M A GUY!
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE NOT.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE GANG AT POSSUM LODGE:
"KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE."
[applause]
ALL RISE.
[lodge members]
QUANDO, OMNI, FLUNKUS, MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
WE JUST GOT OUR VEHICLE
SERVICE REPORT UPDATED.
WE NO LONGER HAVE
ANY SERVICE VEHICLES.
IT SEEMS THAT
WINSTON'S FIRE ENGINE
WAS BEING TOWED BY
DOUGIE'S MONSTER TRUCK
WHEN IT GOT PLOWED
BY THE SNOW PLOW
AND BURST INTO FLAMES.
BUT, THERE IS AN UPSIDE
BECAUSE DOUGIE'S BRAKE LET GO
AND THE ENTIRE FIREBALL ROLLED
RIGHT INTO POSSUM LAKE.
WHICH IS A WIN/WIN.
THE WATER PUT THE FIRE OUT
AND THE LAKE IS UP
ABOUT A FOOT OR SO.