YOU KNOW ONE OF THE SIGNS
OF A TRUE HANDYMAN
IS TO FIGURE OUT
HOW SOMETHING WORKS
AND THEN BE ABLE TO USE
THAT SAME TECHNOLOGY
IN AN ENTIRELY
NEW APPLICATION;
FOR EXAMPLE, THIS GATE.
I GOT A SPRING
AND I GOT A LATCH.
NOW, I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE THINKING,
HOW IS HE GOING TO USE
A SPRING AND A LATCH?
OR HOW DID HE GET SO SMART?
OR WHY DOES HE
WALK LIKE THAT?
WELL, HERE'S YOUR ANSWER,
THIS ROPE OPERATES THE LATCH,
WHICH I'VE GOT ATTACHED TO
THIS END OF MY EAVESTROUGH.
I ATTACHED THE SPRING
WAY DOWN THE OTHER END
OF THE EAVESTROUGH.
NOW, IF YOU'RE
SITTING THERE BAFFLED,
THINK ABOUT SOMETHING
YOU HAVE TO DO EVERY YEAR
ONCE THE LEAVES FALL
OFF ALL THE TREES.
NO, NO, NOT
MOVE TO FLORIDA
I'M TALKING ABOUT CLEANING
OUT YOUR EAVESTROUGHS.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU. ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
KIND OF AN ODD PROBLEM
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK,
THE WATER IN POSSUM LAKE IS
REAL HIGH AND GETTING HIGHER.
IT'S GOING UP ABOUT
A FOOT A DAY.
MIND YOU, THE LODGE
NEVER LOOKED BETTER,
WITH SO MUCH OF OUR
CRAP UNDER WATER.
HEY, Mr GREEN, WE FOUND OUT
WHAT'S MAKING THE LAKE RISE.
THERE'S A BIG ANIMAL
INFESTATION PROBLEM, RED.
HOW CAN AN ANIMAL
INFESTATION MAKE
THE LAKE GO UP,
UNLESS THEY
ALL HAVE SERIOUS
BLADDER PROBLEMS?
NO, THEY BUILT A BIG
DAM ACROSS THE LAKE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
DARN SQUIRRELS.
IT'S BEAVERS!
NO, THE BEAVERS HAVE THE
LONG NARROW TAILS
AND THE FANGS,
AND THE BIG HUMP
ON THE BACK.
LEAST THEY DO UP AT
THE NUCLEAR PLANT.
YOU WOULDN'T KNOW
A BEAVER IF IT
BIT YOUR BUTT.
I DID SO.
NO, IT'S BEAVERS, Mr GREEN.
THEY BUILT THIS BIG DAM SO
THE WATER CAN'T GET OUT.
WELL, THEN SURELY YOU
CAN JUST GO DOWN THERE
AND TAKE THE DAM
APART, CAN'T YOU?
WELL, I SUPPOSE I COULD,
IF I LOST MY MIND.
RED, THOSE ARE VERY
DANGEROUS ANIMALS.
OH, COME ON, THEY DON'T
ACTUALLY BITE, DO THEY?
NO, THEY GNAW.
ALL THE PAIN OF BITING,
BUT VERY, VERY SLOW.
WELL, SOMETHING'S GOT
TO BE DONE, THAT'S
FOR SURE.
WELL, WHILE THEY'RE OUT
GATHERING THEIR TREES AND
BRANCHES DURING THE DAY,
WE COULD BREAK IN
AND TAKE THEIR DAM APART
WITHOUT THEM BOTHERING US.
WELL, THEY MIGHT NOT
BE IN THERE, MIKE,
BUT THEY HANG AROUND.
THEY LURK WITH
THEIR BIG TEETH,
JUST LURKING AND WAITING
FOR YOU TO MAKE ONE SLIP,
THEN THEY JUMP ON YOU
AND GNAW YOUR FACE OFF
BUT SLOWLY.
VERY SLOWLY.
COME ON, ED,
THIS IS CANADA'S NATIONAL
EMBLEM YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YEAH, CANADIANS ARE
VERY PROUD OF
THE BEAVER.
NOT THAT PROUD.
IT'S ONLY ON
THE NICKEL.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
I'M GUESSING THAT
ANY ANIMAL WE'VE CHOSEN
TO REPRESENT CANADA,
WILL LET US WALK IN THERE
AND TAKE ITS HOME,
AS LONG AS WE CALL
IT FREE TRADE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
GET IT?
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER WILL RECEIVE
A GIFT CERTIFICATE
FOR A FREE ENTREE AT
FELICIA'S FONDUE PALACE,
HOME OF THE WORLD'S ONLY
BLINDFOLDED FONDUE.
FELICIA'S REGRETS THAT
THEY ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE
FOR ANY SUPERFICIAL
FACE WOUNDS.
OKAY, ED,
COVER YOUR EARS.
RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET ED FRID, HERE,
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, ED, THIS IS
SOMETHING THAT YOU HAVE
TO GIVE YOU CONFIDENCE.
AN ELECTRIC CATTLE PROD.
[ LAUGHTER ]
NO, OKAY, NO.
PEOPLE WHO DO
DANGEROUS THINGS
WITHOUT EVEN THINKING ABOUT
THE RISK, HAVE THIS.
A WILD SEX LIFE.
NO, OKAY, NO.
THIS IS SOMETHING YOU CALL ON
WHEN YOU KNOW YOU SHOULD
GET BACK ON THE HORSE.
OH, A GENTLER HORSE.
OKAY, A PERSON WHO WORKS WITH
LARGE DANGEROUS ANIMALS,
REQUIRES PLENTY OF...
MEDICAL ATTENTION.
YOU'RE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME, RED.
OKAY, ED, IF YOU STICK
YOUR HEAD INSIDE A
LION'S MOUTH,
THAT TAKES A LOT OF...
BREATH MINTS.
NO, I'M TALKING
ABOUT BRAVERY.
BRAVERY KILLS.
WE DON'T ENCOURAGE THAT.
THERE WE GO!
[ BELL RINGING ]
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
I'M NOT A
CONSTRUCTION WORKER,
OR A FISHERMAN.
I DON'T LIVE IN THE
BASEMENT OF AN OUTHOUSE,
I CAN'T BRING BACK YOUR PET
GOLDFISH, FROG OR HAMSTER,
ACTUALLY WHEN I GET TO 'EM,
YOU WOULDN'T WANT 'EM ANYWAY.
I OPERATE A STATE OF THE ART
SEPTIC REMOVAL VEHICLE,
NOT A HONEY WAGON.
I BELIEVE AN OUNCE
OF PREVENTION IS WORTH
3,000 GALLONS OF CURE.
I WORK WITH A SNAKE,
NOT A SNAKE.
AND DAD, IF GOD HAD MEANT
FOR ME TO BE A LAWYER,
HE WOULD HAVE GIVEN
ME MORE BRAINS,
AND A WAY BETTER
SENSE OF SMELL.
I'M WINSTON ROTHSCHILD III,
AND I SUCK SEWAGE!
THANK YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IF YOU HAVE
KIDS IN YOUR FAMILY,
THEY'RE EVENTUALLY GOING TO
COME TO YOU WITH A TOY,
WANTING YOU TO BLOW IT UP,
AND THEY MEAN IN A GOOD WAY.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
DOING THAT BY HAND.
YOU COULD COUGH UP A LUNG
OR HYPERVENTILATE.
YOU DON'T WANT YOUR KIDS
SEEING YOU ALL DIZZY
AND PASSING OUT
THIS FAR FROM NEW YEAR'S.
SO THIS TIME,
ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
A QUICK, EASY, EFFORTLESS
WAY TO BLOW UP ALL THESE TOYS.
ALL YOU NEED IS
SOME RUBBER HOSE,
AN OLD TENT AND A FLUTE.
OKAY, FIRST THING YOU GOTTA DO,
YOU GOTTA MAKE THE TENT
AIRTIGHT,
WHICH IS DANGEROUS
IF YOU'RE CAMPING WITH
ANY OF THE GUYS UP HERE.
BUT WE'RE NOT GOING TO BE
SLEEPING IN THIS TENT.
OKAY, I'VE MADE
MY TENT AIRTIGHT
BY LAYING ON THE
OLD TABLECLOTHS AND
RAINCOATS ON THERE,
OF COURSE, WHATEVER
LITTLE GAP I HAD,
I JUST FILLED UP WITH
THE HANDYMAN'S SECRET
WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
NOW, TO FILL UP THE TENT,
WE'RE GOING TO USE THE
MAGIC OF THE INTERNAL
COMBUSTION ENGINE.
SEE, I'VE RUN THE EXHAUST
FROM THE POSSUM VAN
STRAIGHT INTO THE TENT,
THAT SHOULD FILL HER
UP IN NO TIME.
I WOULDN'T RECOMMEND
DOING THIS
WITH A TENT THAT YOU
EVER PLAN TO USE AGAIN.
'CAUSE YOU SLEEP A LONG,
LONG TIME WHEN YOU'RE
THAT EXHAUSTED.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OKAY, THAT'S DONE.
AND WHILE I WAS WAITING FOR
THE TENT TO FILL UP
WITH EXHAUST,
I HOOKED UP AN OUTPUT
HOSE FROM MY TENT,
THROUGH THIS
DISTRIBUTION CENTRE.
WELL, I CALL IT A
THE NON-HANDYMAN TYPE
MIGHT CALL THAT A FLUTE.
THEN I'VE RUN OTHER HOSES
OUT OF THE FINGER HOLES,
INTO EACH OF MY
INFLATABLE TOYS.
NOW ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO SQUEEZE THE EXHAUST
OUT OF THE TENT,
THROUGH MY FLUTED
DISTRIBUTION CENTRE,
AND MY WORK HERE IS DONE.
AND TO HELP ME
SQUEEZE THE TENT --
AS WE USED TO SAY
IN HIGH SCHOOL --
ALL I NEED IS A COUPLE
OF PIECES OF PLYWOOD,
TO LAY ON TOP OF
IT AS A RAMP.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
I WANT TO TALK TO ALL
YOU GUYS OUT THERE
WHO LEARNED YOUR SOCIAL SKILLS
BY WATCHING THE "W.W.F."
I'M BETTING ABOUT NOW,
YOUR WIFE IS BUGGING YOU
TO GET BETTER MANNERS.
NOT A BIG PROBLEM.
MANNERS ARE NOT VERY
COMPLICATED AT ALL.
IF YOU WANT TO HAVE
GOOD MANNERS,
JUST TAKE SOMETHING THAT
YOU WANT TO DO FAST
AND DO IT SLOW.
OR SAY THE EXACT OPPOSITE
OF WHAT YOU MEAN.
IN OTHER WORDS,
LIE THROUGH YOUR TEETH
SO YOU DON'T LOSE 'EM.
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO
DO THAT FOR LONG,
BECAUSE SOCIETY DICTATES
THE RULES OF ETIQUETTE,
AND AS SOCIETY CHANGES,
SO DO THE RULES.
REMEMBER HOW RUDE
YOU WERE AS A KID?
LOOK AT THE KIDS TODAY,
THEY'RE TEN TIMES WORSE.
THINK HOW BAD IT'S GOING
TO GET IN 20 YEARS.
NO MATTER HOW
RUDE YOU ARE NOW,
IF YOU LIVE LONG ENOUGH
THE MASSES WILL WORK THEIR
WAY DOWN TO YOUR LEVEL.
SO THE NEXT TIME
YOUR WIFE CRITICIZES
YOU FOR SLURPING YOUR SOUP,
YOU JUST SAY, HONEY,
I'M NOT RUDE,
I'M JUST AHEAD OF MY TIME.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
BUT BE POLITE ABOUT IT.
DON'T SAY IT OUT LOUD.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
[ HORN HONKING ]
Anne Marie:
WHO'S THERE, DALTON?
OH, IT'S NOTHING, DEAR.
IT'S MIKE AND RED
SAYING HELLO.
Anne Marie: I WISH YOU'D
MAKE NEW FRIENDS.
YEAH, YEAH.
ME TOO.
COME ON, DALTON,
THE FISH ARE WAITING.
YEE HOO!
LOOK, I'M GONNA NEED
ABOUT TEN MINUTES
I'VE GOT TO DO
A LITTLE FINESSING
WITH THE "IFE-WAY."
YOU DIDN'T
TELL HER YOU WERE
GOING, DID YOU, DALTON?
LOOK, I WAS GONNA.
JUST WITH A WOMAN
LIKE ANNE MARIE,
YOU REALLY GOTTA PICK
YOUR SPOTS.
SAME AS FISHING.
WE HAD A GUY LIKE THAT
IN THE SLAMMER, EH.
IF HE DIDN'T LIKE YOU HE'D
STICK HIS FORK IN YOUR NOSE.
AND IF HE DID LIKE YOU HE'D
STICK YOUR FORK IN HIS NOSE.
LOOK, DALTON, IF YOU
CAN'T GO JUST SAY SO.
NO! I CAN GO.
I CAN GO.
JUST GIVE ME TWO MINUTES.
Anne Marie: DALTON,
THESE DISHES AREN'T
GONNA WASH THEMSELVES!
Just two minutes.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
AH,
THEY'RE SO CLOSE.
IT'S SO NICE TO SEE A
LOVING COUPLE LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW, MY MOM NEVER CARED
WHERE ANY OF MY DADS WERE.
LET'S GO SEE IF WE
CAN SPEED DALTON UP A
LITTLE BIT, MIKE, HUH?
OKAY, SURE.
[ TIRES SCREECHING,
ENGINE REVVING ]
WHO WAS THAT?
WELL, IT LOOKED
LIKE ANNE MARIE,
BUT THAT WOMAN
WAS SMILING.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
ANNE MARIE'S
GOT A HEADACHE.
SHE'S GONE UP TO BED.
I'M A FREE MAN.
OKAY, DALTON,
WHATEVER YOU SAY.
BOY, SOME PEOPLE
ARE SO GULLIBLE,
THEY HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW?
HE'S RIGHT,
[ APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, WE'VE COME UP WITH
A PLAN TO GET RID OF
THE BEAVER DAM.
IT'S HARD TO
GET CLOSE TO IT,
SO WE'RE MAKING A RAFT.
WE TOOK THE TOP OFF
THE PING PONG TABLE,
DUCT TAPING THAT ON A
COUPLE OF HOT WATER HEATERS.
WE FIGURE THAT BABY'LL FLOAT
IN ABOUT TWO INCHES OF WATER,
AND WE CAN GET RIGHT IN
CLOSE AND TAKE HER APART.
WE'RE HAVING A LOT OF
TROUBLE GETTING VOLUNTEERS
'CAUSE ED FRID IS
GOING ALL OVER TOWN,
TELLING EVERYBODY THAT HIS
UNCLE WAS ATTACKED BY BEAVERS,
WELL, IT SERVES HIM RIGHT,
HE HAD A WOODEN LEG.
[ LAUGHTER ]
RED, RED, I GOT JUST
WHAT YOU NEED.
GUESS WHAT THAT IS.
BAD FRENCH PERFUME.
I'D SAY EAU DE
STINKY PETERSON.
NO, IT'S BEAVER REPELLENT.
BOY, YOU SPRAY THIS ON,
YOU'VE SEEN YOUR LAST BEAVER.
AND YOUR LAST SUNRISE,
I'M GUESSING.
HEY, Mr GREEN,
I GOT IMPORTANT NEWS --
( sniffing )
OOH, FRENCH.
WHAT'S GOING ON,
MIKE?
OH, OKAY, REMEMBER THAT
ONE PONTOON ON THE --
IS THE RIGHT SIDE THE
PORT OR THE STARBOARD?
OKAY.
STARBOARD.
REMEMBER THAT PONTOON
ON THE STARBOARD SIDE?
IS THAT THE
RIGHT OR THE LEFT?
THE LEFT.
NO, NOW YOU'RE
TALKING PORT.
JUST TELL US
WHAT'S WRONG WITH
THE PONTOON, WILL YA!
IT'S NOT A PONTOON.
WELL, OKAY, IT'S A
HOT WATER HEATER, BIG DEAL.
NO, NO, BUSTER HADFIELD GOT
IT AT THE PORT ASBESTOS
ARMY AND NAVY STORE.
IT'S NOT EVEN A
HOT WATER HEATER.
IT'S A TORPEDO!
FORM WORLD WAR II.
YOU KNOW, I SAW THAT.
I WONDERED WHY SOMEONE
HAD PUT A WARHEAD ON
A HOT WATER HEATER.
I THOUGHT MAYBE IT WAS
JUST A WAY TO SPEED UP
A TEENAGER IN THE SHOWER.
YOU KNOW, IF THAT
TORPEDO STILL WORKS,
WE COULD SEND THE RAFT
RIGHT AT THE DAM,
AND BLOW THE WHOLE THING
UP WITH NOBODY ON BOARD.
WOW, YEAH, JUST LIKE
THEY DID IN THAT MOVIE.
OH, YEAH, AFRICAN QUEEN.
HUMPHREY BOGART.
YOU SURE IT WAS
HUMPHREY BOGART?
I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
AFRICAN QUEEN WAS
RU PAUL.
[ LAUGHTER ]
HEY, HEY!
GET AWAY FROM ME!
GORD, GORD?
GORD. GORD. GORD.
OH, RED GREEN.
GORD, GORD, YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN IN TOUCH WITH ME
FOR SO LONG,
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE
SURE EVERYTHING
WAS OKAY.
YOU KNOW IT'S
TWO O'CLOCK IN
THE AFTERNOON?
YOU'RE NOT JUST WAKING
UP NOW, ARE YOU?
WHEN DID YOU GO TO SLEEP?
UH, MID OCTOBER.
OCTOBER?
YEP.
YEAH, WHY?
WELL, IT'S MAY.
WHAT MONTH IS IT NOW?
OH, FOR HEAVEN'S SAKE.
THAT STUPID
ALARM CLOCK.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN
UP TWO WEEKS AGO.
ARE YOU TELLING ME YOU
SLEPT ALL WINTER, GORD?
WELL, I WASN'T
ACTUALLY SLEEPING,
TO USE THE CORRECT
TECHNICAL TERMINOLOGY,
I WAS IN HIBERNATION.
GOT SOME BREATH
ON YOU THERE, GORD.
YOU COULD PROBABLY
REFINISH FURNITURE
WITH THAT, YOU KNOW?
REALLY?
OH! OH, GOSH.
I'M SORRY, RED.
HOW EMBARRASSING.
ACTUALLY, HUMANS
AREN'T SUPPOSED
TO HIBERNATE.
YEAH.
REALLY?
OH, MAYBE THAT'S WHY I KEPT
WAKING UP ALL THE TIME.
I SWEAR I WOKE UP
EVERY MONTH.
AND I KEPT HAVING THESE
WEIRD RECURRING DREAMS.
I DREAMT THAT I WAS LYING UP
HERE IN MY FIRE TOWER,
STARING UP AT THE CEILING,
AND SHIVERING.
GORD, YOU KNOW, WHY DON'T
YOU COME AWAY WITH ME,
AND WE'LL TAKE
YOU TO A DOCTOR,
MAYBE A WHOLE
TEAM OF DOCTORS.
I DON'T KNOW, RED, I'VE HEARD
ABOUT PEOPLE BEING TREATED
EVEN THOUGH THEY WERE
PERFECTLY NORMAL.
WELL, SEE, YOU DON'T
HAVE THAT RISK.
AND IF YOU LIKE, WE CAN
GET YOU A FEMALE DOCTOR.
I WOULD LIKE THAT.
I'D LIKE THAT VERY MUCH.
OH, YEAH, YES.
AND I NEED A COMPLETE
PHYSICAL EXAMINATION.
A COMPLETE
YEAH.
I HEAR YA, GORD.
WHICH END OF ME DO YOU
THINK SHE'LL START WITH?
DEPENDS ON
IF YOU BRUSH
YOUR TEETH FIRST.
YES.
Red: YOU KNOW, THE RABBIT
EARS JUST AREN'T WHAT
THEY USED TO BE.
ACTUALLY, THEY NEVER WERE
WHAT THEY USED TO BE.
ED TRIES EVERYTHING --
NO, THAT'S NOT GOING TO WORK.
I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
THERE'S SOMETHING COMING,
A LITTLE TREAT.
I KNOW YOUNG WALTER WENT OUT
AND GOT US A LITTLE UPGRADE
IN THE TV AREA WITH
A SATELLITE DISH.
HERE HE IS.
LEAVE HER THERE.
NO, TIE DOWN STRAPS TO
WORRY ABOUT, GOOD.
AND HE'S GOT ALL THE CABLE,
JUST MOUNT HER ON TO ONE
OF OUR BUILDINGS THERE,
POINTING TOWARDS
THE SATELLITE.
AND, OKAY, SO WALTER'S
GONNA GO UP ON THE ROOF,
AND WE'LL TOSS HIM UP
THE VARIOUS PARTS.
WELL, HE'S AN ATHLETIC
YOUNG FELLOW, ISN'T HE?
WE'LL SEE HOW THAT GOES.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, THIS IS A HEAVY UNIT.
AND UP SHE GOES.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
WE ACTUALLY THREW THAT
STRAIGHT UP IN THE AIR,
WHICH IS NOT REALLY --
OKAY, I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
THE SATELLITE DISH
HAS A CONCAVE SHAPE
MAYBE WE CAN USE THAT
TO OUR ADVANTAGE.
I'M TELLING ED JUST TO PUT
THE
CABLE DOWN ON THE ONE SID
COME ON ROUND,
OKAY, READY NOW,
WE'RE GONNA GO ONE, TWO --
AND THEN GIVE 'ER --
GIVE 'ER --
THERE WE GO!
OH, OH, TOO MUCH.
TOO MUCH.
ALL RIGHT, SO WE
WENT BACK INSIDE,
AND WALTER MEANWHILE
WENT AND GOT THE CABLE,
AND HE WAS HOOKING UP
THE SATELLITE DISH,
AND HE LET THE CABLE GO
AND WE DIDN'T REALIZE THAT
HE WASN'T COMPLETELY FINISHED
AND WE THOUGHT WHEN
THE CABLE CAME IN
THAT MEANT SHE WAS
ALL HOOKED UP,
SO, ALL WE HAD TO DO NOW
WAS ATTACH IT
BUT NOT REALIZING THAT
WALTER WAS ACTUALLY
STILL WORKING ON IT
AND WE WERE HOOKING IT UP
TO THE HYDRO OUTLET
ON THE TV THERE
AND THEN -- OH, BOY.
OH, AND THAT'S IT.
H, CAREFUL, CAREFUL.
NOW I'M GETTING WALTER
ON THE TV.
WHAT THE HECK'S THAT ABOUT?
OH, MAN.
HEY, LOOK, ED,
IT'S A FISHING SHOW.
YEAH, THERE WE GO.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN OFTEN
JUDGE A HANDYMAN
BY THE NUMBER
OF EMPTY DUCT TAPE
ROLLS HE HAS LYING AROUND.
ESPECIALLY AFTER
A LONG WEEKEND.
THE QUESTION THEN IS
WHAT DO YOU DO WITH
ALL THESE CORES?
THROW 'EM OUT?
BURN 'EM?
JUST IGNORE 'EM?
NOT IF YOU'RE MARRIED.
NO, NO, THE REAL
HANDYMAN RECYCLES,
AND HE DOES IT IN A WAY THAT
BEST SUITS HIS NEEDS
AND HIS LIFESTYLE.
ANYBODY CAN HAVE
A WINE CELLAR.
WITH THESE BABIES,
YOU CAN HAVE A BEER CELLAR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU'VE BEEN
LETTING ON YOU'RE A
CAR EXPERT FOR YEARS.
YEAH, WHENEVER A CAR
WAS ON THE FRITZ,
PEOPLE WOULD RELY ON
YOU TO SAY SOMETHING LIKE
"SOUNDS LIKE A
CLOTTED MANIFOLD."
YEAH, OR
"YOUR CARBURETOR'S
THROWN A ROCKER PANEL."
YEAH, BUT NOW YOUR
SISTER-IN-LAW'S IN THE
MARKET FOR  A USED CAR,
AND SHE'S COUNTING ON
YOU TO GIVE IT THE
ONCE-OVER.
BUT YOU DON'T
HAVE A CLUE, DO YOU?
UNLESS THAT CAR'S UNDER
TEN FEET OF WATER,
OR ON FIRE,
YOU'RE LOST.
SO HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT.
YEAH, JUST STAND AND
LISTEN TO THE SALESMAN
DO THE WORK OF
SELLING THE CAR.
KEEP YOUR MOUTH SHUT.
LOOK LIKE YOU'RE
DOUBTING EVERY WORD.
BUT KEEP
YOUR MOUTH SHUT.
FOR ALL HE KNOWS YOU'RE
A CLASS "A" MECHANIC
WAITING TO POUNCE ON
EVERY NOSE PULLER HE
CAN COME UP WITH.
NOW YOU'VE GOT HIM
ON THE DEFENSIVE,
AND THAT'S JUST WHERE
YOU WANT HIM TO BE.
NOW, HE MAY IN FACT
SUSPECT YOU'RE A
COMPLETE IDIOT,
BUT HE'LL
NEVER PROVE IT.
AS LONG AS YOU KEEP
YOUR MOUTH SHUT.
YEAH.
AND DON'T THANK US.
THAT'S WHAT
FRIENDS ARE FOR.
WELL, OPERATION DAM BUSTERS
IS WELL UNDER WAY,
WE GOT BUZZ SHERWOOD TO
FLY OVER THE DAMS
AND SPRAY IT WITH
BEAVER REPELLENT.
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN THEM ALL
COME STAMPEDING OUT OF THERE,
50 SETS OF BUCK TEETH
GLISTENING IN THE SUN.
LOOKED LIKE CLOSING TIME
AT THE COMPUTER CLUB.
[ LAUGHTER ]
BUT ONCE THEY
CLEARED THE AREA,
WE JUST AIMED THE
RAFT AT THE DAM
AND STARTED THE OUTBOARD
MOTOR ON THE BACK OF HER.
WELL, THE RAFT
IS STILL ON TARGET,
BUT IT'S STILL GOT
A LITTLE WAYS TO GO.
GEE, YOU KNOW,
IT SURE LOOKS WEIRD GOING
ACROSS THE LAKE AT FULL SPEED
WITH NOBODY DRIVING IT.
JUST OLD MAN SEDGWICK
WATER SKIING BEHIND IT.
WHAT?
OH, IT'S OKAY, HE FELL.
IT WAS PRETTY HARD, THOUGH.
YEAH, HIS BATHING SUIT
CAME OFF OVER HIS HEAD.
WOW, THAT'S GONNA SLOW
DOWN HE RESCUE TEAM,
I'LL TELL YA.
WELL, THAT RAFT SHOULD
HIT PRETTY SOON,
DON'T YOU WANT TO
GO BACK AND WATCH?
YEAH.
OH, MAN.
WHERE IS IT?
OH, THERE IT IS.
OH, MAN!
OH, MAN! OH MAN!
JUST A MINUTE.
LET ME SEE IT.
WHAT?
HOLY DINAH.
IT BLEW THAT DAMN
TO SMITHEREENS.
LET ME SEE THAT.
THAT'S NOT THE DAM.
THAT'S MOOSE
THOMPSON'S HOUSE.
THERE'S THE DAM,
AND THE RAFT IS
HEADING RIGHT FOR IT.
IT'S GOING TO
BE A DIRECT HIT.
HOW DO WE KNOW THE
TORPEDO'S STILL ARMED?
WELL, WE DON'T SO
EDGAR FILLED THE OTHER HOT
WATER HEATER WITH DYNAMITE
JUST TO BE ON
THE SAFE SIDE.
OH, OKAY.
BOY, IS IT EVER
GETTING CLOSE.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
[ EXPLOSION ]
OH, MAN.
[ SOUND OF BOMB WHISTLING ]
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
WELL, MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
YEAH, WE SURE DID IT.
AND HEY, WE GOT A BONUS.
LOOK AT ALL THIS
EXTRA FIRE WOOD.
WE'RE GONNA NEED IT WITH
THAT HOLE IN THE ROOF.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ POSSUM SQUEAL ]
OH, MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD, MIKE.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I LEARNED A LOT THIS WEEK.
'COURSE YOU ALWAYS LEARN A LOT
WHEN YOU SEE NATURE AT WORK.
I'M REALLY LOOKING
FORWARD TO NIGHT SCHOOL.
AND FOR THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR
STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, EVERYONE, SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, GUYS.
SIT DOWN. HAVE A SEAT.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
WINSTON.
YEAH.
UH, MEN, WE HAVE A
BEAVER DAM FOR SALE.
SOME ASSEMBLY REQUIRED.