IF YOU'RE AS FED UP SCRAPING ICE
OFF YOUR WINDSHIELD IN WINTER
AS I AM, YOU'RE PRETTY TICKED.
WE CAN PUT A MAN ON THE MOON--
AND DON'T GIVE ME
THAT
EL NINO
CRAP--
WAIT...LET ME
START AGAIN, HAROLD.
JUST EDIT THAT, EDIT THAT OUT.
IF YOU'RE AS FED UP SCRAPING ICE
OFF YOUR WINDSHIELD
IN WINTER AS I AM,
WELL, TRY MELTING IT OFF.
HOW?
JUST TOP OFF YOUR
WINDSHIELD WASHER FLUID
TANK WITH GASOLINE.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO USE
THE UNLEADED GAS ON THAT
BECAUSE FUMES FROM THE LEADED
GAS CAN WRECK YOUR BRAIN
AND AFFECT YOUR...SOMETHING.
AND THEN TO IGNITE THAT STUFF,
JUST USE YOUR CIGARETTE LIGHTER.
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW!
AND NOW HERE HE IS, THE MAN
WHO PUTS ON HIS PANTS ONE BREATH
AT A TIME, YOUR HOST AND HERO,
BUT HE'S MY UNCLE, RED GREEN.
[cheering]
WOW.
BY GOLLY, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE IT.
I DIDN'T THINK I'D GET HERE
IN TIME FOR THE SHOW.
I WAS RUNNING SO LOW ON GAS...
I'VE JUST BEEN RUNNING ON
FUMES IN THE POSSUM VAN.
HA, IF THE POSSUM
VAN JUST RAN ON FUMES,
THAT THING COULD GO FOREVER.
IT STINKS.
I WAS TRYING...HAROLD,
I WAS TRYING TO STOP FOR GAS.
I THOUGHT I'D
HAVE TIME TIME, BUT
I GOT BEHIND THESE CYCLISTS --
HAVE YOU SEEN THESE CYCLISTS?
THEY GOT THEIR
SPANDEX LONGJOHNS ON.
THEY'RE TAKING
UP THE WHOLE LANE.
THEY'RE DOING ABOUT 11 CLICKS.
SO, I JUST PLAIN
RUN OUT OF TIME.
DON'T PICK ON BIKE RIDERS --
WHAT THEY DO IS GOOD
FOR THE ENVIRONMENT,
FOR THEIR HEALTH.
NOT WITH MY ATTITUDE,
IT ISN'T, HAROLD.
CYCLISTS ARE A NUISANCE.
THEY SHOULDN'T BE ON THE ROAD.
WHAT? WHAT?
THEY CAN'T RIDE ON THE SIDEWALK.
THERE'S NO BIKE LANES.
WHERE ARE THEY SUPPOSED TO RIDE?
HOW DOES ENGLAND SOUND?
BIKES ARE WAY MORE
EFFICIENT THAN CARS ARE.
THEY'RE WAY MORE CHEAPER TO RUN,
AND THEY RUN A LOT FURTHER, TOO.
ALL RIGHT, WHY
DON'T YOU PUT
YOUR MONEY WHERE
YOUR MOUTH IS?
OR DO YOU HAVE
THAT MUCH MONEY?
I'LL BET YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS GOOD
BECAUSE THE POSSUM VAN
RIGHT NOW IS
COMPLETELY EMPTY OF GAS.
SO, THAT'S A GOOD START, OK?
SO, WHAT WE'LL DO IS...
WE HAVE $10 EACH TO SPEND, OK?
OK.
I'LL TAKE THE POSSUM VAN,
YOU GET ON YOUR
TRICYCLE, ALL RIGHT?
AND WE'LL SEE WHO GOES
FARTHEST IN A 24-HOUR PERIOD.
OK, YEAH, DEAL.
DEAL.
HA, HA.
CAN YOU
LEND ME $10.
YEAH, SURE...NO!
GET OUT, NO!
ALL RIGHT.
TIME TO PLAY THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
AND TONIGHT'S SPECIAL
GUEST IS MR. MIKE HAMAR.
YEAH, MIKE WILL BE PLAYING
FOR A SPECIAL PRIZE OF
5 POUNDS OF CHOPPED BEEF.
YEAH, SUPPLIED BY
WALLY'S BUTCHER SHOP.
AND WALLY HAS INCLUDED
A LITTLE NOTE, HERE.
IT READS: "IF YOU COME ACROSS
A FINGER, YOU CAN KEEP IT."
"BUT HE WOULD LIKE
THE RING BACK." OH, BOY.
WHOA, OK.
UNCLE RED YOU HAVE
30 SECONDS TO GET
MR. MIKE HAMAR TO SAY THIS WORD:
"SHOPPING."
YEAH, ALL
RIGHT, HAROLD.
GO!
YOU NEED SOMETHING
SO, YOU GO DOWN
TO THE STORE
AND YOU GO...
CASE THE JOINT?
NO, NO, OK, YOU GO IN,
YOU PICK UP WHAT YOU WANT,
YOU GO TO THE CASH REGISTER --
NOW, YOU ARE...
RUNNING?
YOU KNOW, UH, WHEN YOU
SEE PEOPLE IN THE MALL,
THEY GOT THEIR ARMS FULL
OF PURCHASES -- THEY ARE...
MARKS.
LET'S GO A DIFFERENT WAY, MIKE.
YOU KNOW THOSE CARTS IN FRONT
OF GROCERY STORES --
YOU'VE SEEN THEM
IN THE RACKS -- WHAT ARE THEY?
MOBILE HOMES?
OK, THIS IS SOMETHING
PEOPLE SEE AS FUN.
THEY GO INTO A MALL,
AND THEY GO...
PANHANDLING?
OK, OK, BUT ONCE YOU'VE
PANHANDLED FOR A WHILE,
YOU TAKE THE MONEY,
YOU GO INTO THE MALL
AND YOU MAKE A PURCHASE.
YOU ARE...
IN A LIQUOR STORE?
ALMOST OUT OF TIME, UNCLE RED.
OK, MIKE.
STORES, OK?
YOU'RE NOT BROWSING, YOU'RE
NOT PANDHANDLING, YOU'RE NOT
SHOPLIFTING, YOU'RE NOT
CASING THE JOINT, YOU ARE...
IN CUSTODY?
YEAH, BUT...YOU KNOW WHAT I DO,
UH, MR. GREEN,
I JUST SAY, "HEY, OFFICER,"
"I WASN'T DOING NOTHING WRONG,
I WAS JUST SHOPPING."
[bell ringing]
YEAH, ALL RIGHT!
HA, HA, I'VE GONE 100 KILOMETRES
ON MY 10 BUCKS WORTH
OF GAS, AND THE POSSUM VAN
IS JUST STARTING TO SPUTTER NOW.
I FIGURE I'VE GOT HAROLD BEAT
EIGHT WAYS TO
SUNDAY ON THIS ONE.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, I THINK
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO LEAVE THE SEAT
ON THE BICYCLE.
HOW FAR HAVE YOU
GONE, ANYWAY?
UM, 117
KILOMETRES.
WHAT?
UH-HUH, HA.
YES, AND I HAVEN'T
EVEN SPENT MY $10 YET.
YOU STILL GOT ALL THE MONEY?
YEAH, YEAH, THEY
RAN OUT OF LINIMENT.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
WELL, I'M GETTING THERE.
I'M DOING FINE.
I'M JUST WARMING UP,
ACTUALLY, HAROLD.
AND DON'T FORGET, WE
STILL GOT TWO HOURS LEFT,
AND I'M NOT OUT OF GAS.
WELL, I
PRETTY MUCH AM.
YEAH, I THINK MAYBE YOU ARE.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
I WAS THINKING MAYBE WE SHOULD
HAVE A PRIZE OF SOME
KIND FOR THIS CONTEST.
YEAH, OK, YEAH.
IF I WIN, I'D LIKE A TROPHY.
OK, ALL RIGHT, AND,
IF I WIN, WELL, UM...
WE'LL EXCHANGE
VEHICLES FOR A DAY.
HA, HA, I'LL GET THE POSSUM VAN,
AND YOU'LL GET THE BIKE.
WELL, HEY, THAT'S
FINE WITH ME, HAROLD,
BECAUSE IT WILL
NEVER EVER HAPPEN.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I HAVE A TROPHY TO WIN.
IF YOU FIND YOURSELF
AT THE GATES OF HEAVEN
AND THERE DOESN'T
SEEM TO BE ANYONE AROUND
IT'S PROBABLY JUST A FINAL
TEST TO SEE IF YOU'RE PATIENT
SO, DON'T JUST WALK
IN AND SIT DOWN
YOU KNOW, WOMEN NEVER
GET TIRED OF HEARING
MEN SAY THOSE
THREE LITTLE WORDS:
"I'LL MAKE DINNER."
ESPECIALLY IF THE KIDS HAVE BEEN
WAILING AND FIGHTING ALL DAY,
AND THE DOG'S TRYING TO
FIREPROOF THE FURNITURE.
SO, TODAY, ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU A RECIPE
TO MAKE A BEAUTIFUL POSSUM
LODGE FIRE ENGINE CHILI.
YOU KNOW ALL CHILIES PRETTY
MUCH HAVE THE SAME INGREDIENTS.
SO, THAT'S NOT
REALLY THE SECRET.
THE SECRET...
IS TO MAKE EVERYTHING
IN BIG BATCHES.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A LOT CHEAPER,
AND YOU GET LEFTOVERS, WHICH IS
REAL HANDY WHEN YOU GET
RELATIVES DROPPING OVER
UNEXPECTEDLY, AND YOU WANT TO
SERVE THEM SOMETHING THAT WILL
CONVINCE THEM
THEY SHOULD REALLY LEAVE.
I'M GOING TO NEED A BIGGER POT.
YOU KNOW, THE BEAUTY OF THIS
RECIPE...IF YOU MAKE ENOUGH,
YOU CAN ACTUALLY MOVE
THE WHOLE PROJECT OUTSIDE
WHERE YOU'LL BE MORE COMFORTABLE
WITH YOUR SURROUNDINGS
AND YOUR EQUIPMENT.
YEAH, JUST FIRE
THAT UP ON THERE.
THERE WE GO.
GET THAT IN.
NOW, FOR THE ONIONS.
OH, NO, NO, NO, WAIT A MINUTE.
SAFETY FIRST, EH?
IT'S BAD ENOUGH THE
GUYS SEE YOU'RE COOKING.
YOU DON'T WANT THEM TO
SEE THAT YOU'RE CRYING TOO.
ONCE YOU'VE GOT
ALL THE STUFF IN THERE,
JUST LET HER SIMMER SO THE
INGREDIENTS CAN
MARRY EACH OTHER.
DON'T TRY AND TALK
THEM OUT OF IT.
YOU DIDN'T LISTEN;
NEITHER WILL THEY.
OH, THIS IS GOING
TO BE A GOOD BATCH.
NOW, YOU KNOW THERE'S
A WIDE VARIETY OF SEASONINGS
YOU CAN USE IN YOUR CHILI,
JUST TO YOUR OWN PERSONAL TASTE.
BUT I ALWAYS LIKE TO START
WITH THE RED HOT CHILI POWDER.
THIS IS CALLED CHILI, HUH?
HA, HA.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S GOOD.
NOW, WHAT ELSE?
LET'S SEE...
AH, WE'LL PUT A LITTLE
MORE CHILI IN THERE.
OK, WHAT ELSE DO WE GOT?
WELL, WHAT THE HECK.
IT IS CALLED CHILI...OH,
OH!
I'M NOT GOING IN THERE.
THAT'S FIBRE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW FOR MY SECRET
INGREDIENT, HUH -- KEROSENE.
OH, I..I KNOW YOU'RE...
THAT'S POISON, RIGHT?
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE POISON PART BURNS OFF.
I'M PRETTY SURE -- AND IT GIVES
THE CHILI A REAL KICK TO IT.
BESIDES, A LITTLE BIT OF
KEROSENE IN A BATCH THIS SIZE
ISN'T GOING TO HURT ANYBODY.
WELL, IT ISN'T GOING
TO HURT EVERYBODY.
REMEMBER NOW,
PRESENTATION IS EVERYTHING.
SO I SUGGEST YOU SERVE
THE CHILI IN A BOWL
RATHER THAN A BUNCH OF YOU
STANDING IN A CIRCLE
EATING IT STRAIGHT
OUT OF THE POT.
OH, MAN.
YOUR WIFE'S GOING TO
LOVE YOU FOR THIS, EH?
NOTHING SAYS MY HEART BURNS
FOR YOU LIKE POSSUM LODGE CHILI.
ALL RIGHT, I THINK, NEXT TIME
ON HANDYMAN CORNER, I'M GOING
TO SHOW YOU HOW TO TURN
A SHOP VAC INTO A STOMACH PUMP.
UNTIL THEN, REMEMBER: IF THE
WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
ANYBODY WANT ANY CHILI?
TO GO?
I WANT TO TAKE
A FEW MINUTES TO SHOW
YOU MIDDLE-AGED GUYS SOMETHING.
WHEN YOU GET TOO OLD
TO MEMORIZE THE EYE CHART,
IT'S A LEAD-PIPE CINCH YOU'RE
GOING TO BE ISSUED
A PAIR OF THESE.
THESE ARE CALLED EYEGLASSES
AND THEY ARE GIVEN TO PEOPLE
LIKE US SO WE WON'T BE
A SAFETY HAZARD
TO THE GENERAL PUBLIC.
REMEMBER, A LONG TIME AGO,
YOU SAID YOU'D DO IT
TILL YOU NEED GLASSES?
WELL, GUESS WHAT?
THAT TIME HAS COME.
SO, OFF YOU GO WITH YOUR
PRESCRIPTION DOWN TO
THE OPTICIAN, THERE.
AND BESIDES THE FACT
THAT YOU NEED GLASSES
TO SEE HOW YOU LOOK IN GLASSES,
YOU'RE GOING TO GO CRAZY
TRYING TO FIND A PAIR
THAT DON'T MAKE YOU
LOOK LIKE A GEEK.
WELL, I CAN SAVE YOU
A LITTLE BIT OF TIME, THERE.
ALL GLASSES MAKE
YOU LOOK LIKE A GEEK.
HERE'S THE GOOD PART:
ONCE YOU'RE OUT OF THE STORE,
IT'S NOT YOUR PROBLEM BECAUSE
YOU'RE ON THE INSIDE
LOOKING OUT.
SO, IF YOU NEED
GLASSES, GET THEM.
REMEMBER WHAT DOROTHY PARKER
SAID, "MEN WHO NEED GLASSES"
"SOMETIMES MAKE PASSES AT WOMEN
WHO ARE ALREADY THEIR WIVES."
HEY, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
OH, OH, OH, MAN.
I'M SO SMART MY BRAIN
SHOULD BE REGISTERED
IN THAT PLACE, YOU KNOW...
YOU KNOW, THEY HAVE THAT,
THEY HAVE THAT PLACE
WHERE THEY HAVE THE THINGS.
I HAD ENOUGH GAS TO GET
TO THE TOP OF ROCK REEF POINT.
AND THEN WHEN
THE POSSUM VAN STALLED,
I TURNED HER AROUND AND
I COASTED ALL THE WAY DOWN.
NEVER WENT NEAR THE BRAKES.
I MEAN, IT WAS A HAIRY RIDE,
BUT I ADDED ANOTHER
37 KILOMETRES TO MY TOTAL.
I'M GOING TO BEAT
HAROLD SO BAD, HA, HA, HA.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
ROCK REEF POINT.
HERE'S YOUR
BACK BUMPER.
YOU WERE ON YOUR BICYCLE,
HANGING ONTO MY BACK BUMPER?
WHOO!
THAT'S CHEATING, BUDDY.
OH, NO, NO, NO,
IT'S NOT CHEATING.
I WAS...WHAT I WAS DOING
WAS NOT WHAT--
I WAS MONITORING YOU CHEATING.
NO, NO, NO, YOU
SLOWED ME DOWN.
I WANT CREDIT
FOR THAT.
NO, WE LANDED ON THE BOTTOM
SIMULTANEOUSLY, SO THAT STILL
GIVES ME MY 17-MILE LEAD;
THEREFORE, YOU OWE ME
THE POSSUM VAN KEYS
S'IL VOUS PLAIT.
[laughing]
TREAT HER
NICE, HAROLD.
OK, AND HERE'S
THE KEY TO MY BIKE.
THAT'S FOR THE SADDLE BAG.
THERE'S A SANDWICH IN THERE,
YOU CAN HAVE THAT.
THIS WILL BE A REAL
ADJUSTMENT FOR YOU.
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN ON TWO WHEELS
IN A LONG TIME.
EVERY TIME I TURN A CORNER.
WELL, WELCOME
TO THE MEN ANONYMOUS.
AS ALWAYS I'D LIKE TO ASK
MY UNCLE RED TO COME UP
AND LEAD US IN THE MEN
ANONYMOUS PLEDGE...UNCLE RED.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
THANK YOU.
WHOO.
ALL RIGHTY.
NOW, JUST TO REMIND YOU,
HERE AT MEN ANON, UH, YOU KNOW,
THERE WILL BE NO NAMES,
NO LAST NAMES,
NO MIDDLE NAMES,
NO NICKNAMES, NOTHING.
PRIVACY IS THE UTMOST,
ALL RIGHTY?
OK, TONIGHT'S GUEST SPEAKER,
MR. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD. WINSTON?
HI, GUYS.
HI, MR. ROTHSCHILD.
AS MOST OF YOU KNOW,
I HAVE A SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING BUSINESS.
OUR MOTTO IS, "WE MAKE SURE
BYGONES ARE BYGONES."
BUT I HAD A REAL BREAKTHROUGH
LAST WEEK, GUYS.
I WAS ON A FLIGHT FROM
PORT ASBESTOS TO HOGAN'S HUMP,
I HAD A YOUNG LADY
SITTING BESIDE ME.
NOW,
ORDINARILY,
WHEN I MEET A STRANGER,
ESPECIALLY A LADY, I JUST
GO ON AND ON AND ON
ABOUT MY LINE OF WORK, EH?
'CAUSE I FIND MY CAREER
SO FASCINATING.
AND I USUALLY HAVE
A FEW HUMOROUS ANECDOTES
ABOUT THE SEPTIC SUCKING
BUSINESS AS A WHOLE.
WHICH REMINDS ME,
HAVE I TOLD YOU THE ONE
ABOUT THE BOOT, YOU KNOW,
UP THE TUBE THERE?
WITH THE SHREDDING
AND...YOU KNOW,
AND THE PRESSURE PIPE COMES
DOWN AND SUCKS THE BOOT UP...
IT GOES UP THERE,
JUST A FLAPPING AWAY
LIKE...LIKE THAT..
BUT ANYWAY, THE POINT IS
I MANAGED TO GO
THE ENTIRE FLIGHT
WITHOUT TALKING
ABOUT MY BUSINESS...
WHICH, AS YOU KNOW,
IS OTHER PEOPLE'S BUSINESS.
NO, SIREE, I, I...
I ASKED HER QUESTIONS
ABOUT HERSELF.
AND I GAVE HER SOME
HELPFUL HINTS
IN THE EVENT OF A PLANE CRASH.
OH, IT WAS HARD,
BUT I'LL TELL YOU,
NOT ONCE DID I EVEN MENTION
THE CONCEPT OF SEWAGE,
EVEN WHEN THEY
BROUGHT US OUR MEALS.
ALL RIGHT. CONGRATULATIONS.
[ RED ]: THAT FELLA'S TRYING
TO GET AN AXE OUT OF A STUMP.
GIVE HER A GOOD YANK
THERE, BILL.
OH, WELL, LATER MAYBE.
OH, HI, RED,
HOW YOU DOING?
I TOLD YOU, LATER.
ALL RIGHT, WHAT ARE WE DOING?
UH-OH, I DON'T LIKE IT WHEN
HE PUTS HIS HANDS IN HIS PANTS.
BETTER THAN HIM PUTTING
HIS HANDS IN MY PANTS, I GUESS.
WATCH OUT, EASY, EASY, OH!
WATCH THE KNOTS, HA, HA, HA.
OH, BOY, THAT'S A LOT OF ROPE
FOR AN OLDER GENTLEMAN.
WHAT DID YOU--
WHAT DO YOU GOT IN MIND HERE?
OK, I'LL TAKE--
WHAT ARE WE DOING, BILL?
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
OH, OH, OH!
I DON'T THINK I COMPLETELY
UNDERSTAND OR ENJOY THE GAME,
BUT THANKS FOR-- WHAT? WHAT?
OH, A TUG OF WAR.
OH, YOU WANT A TUG OF WAR.
ALL RIGHT, AWAY YOU GO,
YOU GO OFF.
YOU GO THAT WAY,
YOU GO THAT WAY.
DON'T LOOK BACK, ALL RIGHT?
HEH, HEH, HEH.
I GOT A LITTLE PLAN
I'M WORKING ON.
HEH, HEH, HEH,
JUST A LITTLE HELPER
FOR MY END OF THE ROPE.
HEH, HEH, HEH, OH, BOY.
JUST TAKE A LITTLE EXTRA SLACK.
IT CAN GO AROUND THE CAR --
EVEN A K-CAR, I THINK,
WOULD BE BETTER
THAN MOST HUMANS.
GO ROUND THERE
AND CHUCK THAT UNDER...
AND WHAT I CAN DO--
OH, OH, OH, OH, MY.
TIE HER OFF AT THE DOOR HANDLE
THERE, AND WE'RE ALL SET.
I THINK I'M
GOING TO DO WELL HERE.
GET RID OF THE PAIL.
OW!
THAT'S UNFORTUNATE.
ALL RIGHT, BILL,
I'M ALL SET, I'M ALL SET.
PULL AWAY, I'M ALL SET,
I'M READY, LET HER GO.
YEAH, LET HER GO.
GIVE HER A YANK. OH, YEAH.
OH, OH, BOY, OH,
OH, OH, OH, OHHH, OH, OH!
CHANGE THE GRIP.
OH, OH...
HI, HAROLD,
HOW YOU DOING?
HAROLD, HE WANTS YOU--
NO, NO, NO, NO.
HI, HAROLD.
LOOK AT THIS. OH, BOY!
BRING IT ON, BRING IT ON.
HEY, HEY, TAKE IT EASY GUYS,
GUYS, TAKE IT EASY.
TAKE IT EASY NOW, TAKE IT EASY,
TAKE IT EASY, COME ON NOW.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
OH, OH!
OHHH!
YOU WANT FRIES WITH THAT?
THE WINDOW
WAS OPEN.
HI, I'M RANGER GORD,
I'M MOTHER NATURE'S BEST FRIEND.
BUT I'M ACTUALLY
HOPING THAT ONE DAY
WE CAN BE MORE
THAN JUST FRIENDS.
I'M HERE TODAY BECAUSE
RED'S ASKED ME TO DO
A SCIENTIFIC
DEMONSTRATION FOR YOU.
I'M HERE TO RID THE WORLD
OF AN OLD WIVE'S TALE.
YOU KNOW, IF THERE'S
ONE THING I KNOW
EVERYTHING THERE IS
TO KNOW ABOUT, IT'S ABOUT...
OH, YEAH, FACTS
ON FIRE.
I'M SURE RED AND HAROLD
CAN BACK ME UP ON THAT ONE.
YOU KNOW...YOU DON'T SPEND 18
YEARS UP IN A FIRE WATCHTOWER
WITHOUT LEARNING ONE THING.
AND WHATEVER THAT ONE THING IS
THAT YOU'VE LEARNED...
IT'S ALL YOU'VE GOT TO CLING TO.
ANYWAY, WE'VE ALL HEARD
THE EXPRESSION
"FIGHT FIRE WITH FIRE."
WELL, I'M HERE TODAY TO TELL YOU
THAT THAT DOES NOT WORK...OK?
ALL YOU GET WHEN YOU FIGHT FIRE
WITH FIRE IS EXTRA FIRE. NOW...
TO PROVE THIS POINT...
OH, BOY.
I'LL SET THIS SIGN ON FIRE...OK?
THEN I'M GOING TO
FIGHT THIS FIRE
BY USING THIS FLAME-THROWER.
NO, UH, GORD,
GORD, GORD...
YOU CAN'T-- NO, YOU CAN'T HAVE
A FIRE GOING ON THE TABLE.
NO FIRE, NO.
OK, WELL, THEN HAROLD
CAN HOLD THE SIGN...
[shrieking]
NO, GORD, NO.
I GOT AN IDEA...I GOT AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T YOU PROVE
THAT YOU CAN'T FIGHT FIRE
WITH FIRE WITH FIRE WITH FIRE?
OHH...OK, I GOT YOU. ALL RIGHT.
REALLY?
YEP -- OK, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
THIS IS OBVIOUSLY
NOT GOING TO WORK OUT,
BUT I WANT TO RID THE WORLD
OF ANOTHER OUTDOORSMAN MYTH.
THE ODDS OF KILLING TWO BIRDS
WITH ONE STONE IS ASTRONOMICAL.
OK? ONE STONE PER BIRD, PEOPLE.
ONE STONE PER BIRD. THANK YOU.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH.
YEAH, JUST CRUISING
THE STREETS OF POSSUM LAKE.
THE OLD VAN-MEISTER AND ME
CHECKING THE GIRLS--
CHICKS...B-BABES.
HONKING THE HORN, WAVING,
AND THEM YELLING THINGS
BACK AT ME AND...
IT WAS GREAT, WOW...
WONDER HOW UNCLE RED'S DOING ON
THE BIKE -- HE'S
BEEN GONE FOREVER.
I SHOULD HAVE LEFT THE MONSTER
WHEEL TRAINING WHEELS ON IT.
[horn honking]
OH, EXCUSE ME.
WHAT? HEY!
YOU CAN'T BE IN HERE WITH THAT.
THAT'S NOT A-- DON'T
YOU'RE GOING TO HIT THE BEAR.
UNCLE RED!
I LOVE IT, HAROLD,
I LOVE IT...HUH?
NO.
NO, THAT'S NOT-- NO.
DON'T EVEN DO THAT.
DON'T ENCOURAGE HIM --
THAT'S NOT MY
BIKE.
IT'S A BIKE, HAROLD, UH?
IT'S A TWO-WHEELER.
THAT WAS THE DEAL.
NO, YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE, LIKE,
GETTING IN SHAPE
AND PROTECTING THE OZONE.
HAROLD, THIS THING GETS ABOUT
A THOUSAND MILES TO THE GALLON.
YOU ARE MISSING
THE POINT.
I DON'T LIKE POINTS.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT? MAYBE
I'LL JUST KEEP THE POSSUM VAN.
MAYBE I'LL JUST
RUN OVER YOUR FOOT.
[squealing]
MEETING TIME.
IT'S MEETING TIME.
GO AHEAD, I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
COMING TO GET YOU SOON.
YOU WON'T GET
ME BACK HERE.
I'LL GET YOU, I'LL GET YOU.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I HOPE YOU'LL BE MY BIKER CHICK
IN MY NEW MOTORCYCLE GANG,
SATAN'S SECOND CHOICE.
AND THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT THE LODGE...
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
OK, ALL RIGHT.
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
CAN WE HAVE-- SIT DOWN,
THERE WE GO.
HA, HA, HA...
[cheering]
ALL RIGHT,
GET 'EM UP, HAROLD.
ALL RISE, ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IS IT PRETTY OBVIOUS
THAT SOMEONE'S
GOING THROUGH A MID-LIFE CRISIS?
[muttering]
WHO WANTS
TO GO NEXT?