(Snoring and sputtering)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
NOW, THE MAN WHO CHANGED
THE FACE OF TELEVISION,
GIVING IT A FAT LIP
AND A BLACK EYE,
YOUR HOST, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause)
(Cheering and whistling)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU -- APPRECIATE IT.
GOT SOME REALLY GOOD NEWS.
I AM SO TOTALLY EXCITED.
WAAAAHH!
FINE, THAT'S FINE, HAROLD.
YEP, YEP, THIS WEEK,
WE'LL HAVE THE FIRST EVER
POSSUM LODGE
INFLATED HIP-WADER CONTEST.
WHAT? WHAT? NO.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE FACT
THAT AN AMERICAN NETWORK
IS MILDLY INTERESTED
IN OUR SHOW.
WHAT?
YEAH, OH, YES,
HOW TRUE, HOW TRUE.
ONE OF THE BIG THREE.
THEY MIGHT PICK US UP.
YOU COULD BE FAMOUS.
THE NETWORK EXECUTIVES THINK
YOU'RE QUIRKY.
I'M NOT QUIRKY, HAROLD.
THE BUNCH OF GUYS
ARE GONNA PUT ON HIP-WADERS,
PACK 'EM FULL OF DRY ICE,
AND WHEN THE CO2 TURNS TO GAS,
WOOF! OUT THEY GO,
AND WHOEVER GETS
THE BIGGEST DIAMETER
WITHOUT BLOWING 'EM UP... WINS!
SEE, I'M NOT QUIRKY.
RIGHT, YEAH, RIGHT.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): THIS WEEK, WE GOT
A REAL SURPRISE FOR YOU.
YOU THINK THAT'S IT?
NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
WE'RE GETTING CLOSE,
BUT THAT'S NOT IT.
I'LL GIVE YOU A GREAT BIG HINT.
IF I'M GONNA WIN THE INFLATED
HIP-WADERS CONTEST,
BETTER MAKE SURE
I HAVEN'T GOT BLISTERS.
YOU DON'T WANT A WEAK SPOT.
SHE LETS GO AT FULL PRESSURE,
BLOW YOU ACROSS THE LAKE.
JUNIOR SINGLETON, TO TEST HIS,
HE POURED IN
A 2-4 OF THE LIGHT BEER,
LET 'ER FIZZ AROUND--
EXCUSE ME,
UNCLE RED.
"2-4" IS
LOCAL SLANG.
IF WE WANT
A BIG NETWORK DEAL,
WE HAVE TO TAILOR THE SHOW
A BIT THAT WAY.
SO CAN YOU SAY "CASE"
INSTEAD OF 2-4, OK?
YOU SAID I WOULDN'T HAVE TO
CHANGE THE SHOW.
NO, NOT CHANGE, NEVER CHANGE.
THE NETWORK EXECS
THINK YOU'RE QUIRKY.
KEEP THE QUIRK, KEEP THE QUIRK.
JUST TAILOR IT A BIT -- TAILOR.
ALL RIGHT, JUNIOR POURED
A
CASE
OF BEER IN,
AND IT WAS ALMOST FREEZING.
IT WAS ONE OR TWO DEGREES--
EXCUSE ME, UNCLE RED.
IS THAT, LIKE, CELSIUS?
YEAH.
CELSIUS MIGHT CONFUSE
AMERICAN VIEWERS.
THEY STILL USE FAHRENHEIT.
CAN YOU USE FAHRENHEIT?
FAHRENHEIT DOESN'T CHANGE
THE STORY.
YEAH, SEE? WORKS FOR ME.
WAIT A SEC, HAROLD.
TOOK ME 12 YEARS
TO CHANGE OVER.
I WON'T CHANGE BACK.
NOT CHANGE, NEVER CHANGE.
JUST SAY, UH...
JUST SAY "FAHRENHEIT".
LET ME TELL
YOU SOMETHING.
I LOVE THE AMERICANS --
I'M REALLY HAPPY
AMERICANS ARE WATCHING
OUR SHOW.
I WON'T CHANGE MY TUNE.
MY TUNE HAPPENS TO BE
"O CANADA", ALL RIGHT?
(Applause and cheering)
THAT'S WONDERFUL,
THAT'S FANTASTIC.
I THOUGHT I MIGHT MENTION
AT THIS PARTICULAR JUNCTURE
THAT AMERICAN T.V. STARS
GET $50,000 AN EPISODE.
ALL RIGHT, MY NEW TUNE IS
"I'M A YANKEE DOODLE DANDY".
(Red): IN HONOUR
OF MOVING TO THE NETWORKS,
WE'RE ADDING VIOLENCE
TO THE SHOW.
BILL'S GONNA DO SOME BOXING.
HE'S SPONSORED
BY THE NOTEL MOTEL.
HE TOOK THAT
AS A FREE SAMPLE THING.
WE'VE GOTTEN OURSELVES
INTO GOOD SHAPE,
AND I THINK WE'RE READY.
NOT THAT I DO A LOT OF BOXING
BUT WE WORKED OURSELVES INTO...
WE HAVE PRETTY FIRM,
PRETTY HARD BODIES--
WE'RE TIRED NOW,
BUT YOU GET TO REST.
WHERE IS HE?
OH, CAREFUL, THERE --
EASY, EASY, EASY.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL BE BACK
WHEN BILL LEARNS THE ROPES.
THIS IS THE BIG ONE.
THE GRAND PRIZE IS STUFF WE
PICKED UP BESIDE THE HIGHWAY.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MY UNCLE TO SAY--
(Shrieking)
(Audience laughing)
W-W-WHAT...
(Clearing
throat)
(Whooping)
S-S-S-S-S....
(Laughing)
S-S-S-S-S...
(Whooping)
(Clearing
throat)
(Coughing)
SEX?
(Shrieking)
(Laughing and applause)
(Strums acoustic guitar)
WAS A GUY
NAMED GEORGIE O'BRIAN
WHOSE MONEY
WAS ALWAYS SPENT
HE TRIED TO BUY
WHATEVER HE COULD
AND WHATEVER HE COULDN'T,
HE'D RENT
THE POOR FOOL WENT BANKRUPT
SO MANY TIMES
HE WAS DOWN
TO HIS VERY LAST CHANCE
WHEN HE GOT HIRED ON
BY THE GOVERNMENT
AS AN ADVISOR TO
THE DEPARTMENT OF FINANCE
IF THIS NETWORK DEAL
COMES THROUGH,
I'LL DO A LOT OF TRAVELLING --
PROMOTIONAL TRIPS,
PERSONAL APPEARANCES,
AVOIDING RELATIVES,
THAT KIND OF THING.
I TELL YOU ONE THING.
I DON'T WANT TO BE CARRYING
40 SUITCASES,
SO I THOUGHT I'D TAKE THIS WEEK
IN "HANDYMAN CORNER"
TO SHOW YOU HOW THE HANDY
TRAVELLER PACKS A SUITCASE.
FIRST, YOU GOT
YOUR BAG OF TOILETRIES.
YOU GOT SHAMPOO AND SOAP
AND MOUTHWASH
AND DEODORANT AND FOOT POWDER.
WELL...
(Crash)
YOU DON'T NEED THAT.
YOU'RE ON THE ROAD.
PEOPLE EXPECT YOU
TO SMELL A BIT OFF.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, SHOES.
SHOES ARE NICE
BUT THEY TAKE UP SPACE.
SO I SAY GET YOURSELF
SOME TIN SNIPS.
CUT THE SHOE WHERE THE UPPERS
ARE MEETING THE SOLE.
I DON'T KNOW
WHOSE SHOES THESE ARE,
BUT I'M SURE THEY'LL THANK ME.
AH... DONE!
JUST TAKE ONE PAIR OF SANDALS
WITH YOU,
AND EVERY DAY, YOU WEAR
A DIFFERENT PAIR OF SHOES
BY PUTTING THE UPPER HALF
OVER THE SANDAL.
YOU GOT YOUR FORMAL,
YOU GOT YOUR RUNNING SHOE,
YOU HAVE YOUR SEMI-CASUAL,
AND PROBABLY THE MOST POPULAR,
THE CASUAL.
IT ALLOWS YOU TO THROW
THE SOLES AND HEELS AWAY.
(Crash)
YOU CAN START PACKING
SHIRTS, PANTS,
JACKETS, WHATEVER,
AND REMEMBER,
ONE PAIR OF SOCKS AND UNDERWEAR
FOR EVERY WEEK YOU'RE AWAY.
I KNOW HOTELS HAVE TOWELS BUT
THEY DON'T SEEM TO DRY WELL,
SO I LIKE TO BRING MY OWN.
SAME THING WITH SHEETS.
I DON'T WANT TO SLEEP
ON SOMETHING
THAT 8,000 STRANGERS
HAVE SLEPT ON... OR WHATEVER.
I FEEL THE SAME
ABOUT HOTEL PILLOWS.
I DON'T LIKE 'EM
AS MUCH AS MY OWN.
DON'T KNOW WHETHER
IT'S THE SMELL OR THE FEEL...
OR... MAYBE THEY'RE JUST NOT
AS SANITARY AS THEY NEED TO BE.
SO I LIKE TO BRING MY OWN.
I CAN SAY THE SAME THING
ABOUT HOTEL MATTRESSES.
TOO FLAT, TOO SMOOTH.
I LIKE TO BRING MY OWN.
(Grunting)
BERNICE IS PROBABLY NOT
GONNA BE COMING WITH ME,
SO ACTUALLY, I ONLY NEED
HALF A MATTRESS.
(Starting chainsaw)
(Stopping chainsaw)
OK, BUT HOW DO WE GET
THE SUITCASE SHUT?
TECHNOLOGY.
A FEW C-CLAMPS, SOME OTHER
CLAMPS, AND A COME-ALONG...
WE'LL GET 'ER CLOSED.
IT WILL TAKE A WHILE
TO HORSE THIS BABY DOWN,
SO LET'S GET BACK TO THE SHOW.
STAY TUNED -- BUZZ IS WIRED
BUT HIS PLANE ISN'T.
LET'S RETURN TO THE MIRTH
AND MAYHEM
OF THOSE WACKY GUYS
UP AT POSSUM LODGE,
WITH MY UNCLE, YOUR HOST...
RED GREEN!
(Plays piano)
(Applause and cheering)
GET AWAY, GET AWAY!
GO ON, GET OUT OF HERE!
GO ON, BEAT IT!
HAROLD, WHAT THE HECK
IS THAT ABOUT?
IT'S NOT ME --
IT'S THE NETWORK.
IF WE WANT
AN AMERICAN AUDIENCE,
WE GOTTA KEEP THIS MOVING.
SOME PACE -- NEAT, EH?
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT STUFF.
YOU MADE ME FORGET
WHAT I WAS GONNA SAY.
RELAX -- WE GOT CUE CARDS.
CUE CARDS? SINCE WHEN?
SINCE NOW --
YOU JUST CAN'T BLAB.
IT'S GOTTA BE TIGHTLY SCRIPTED
AND NETWORK-APPROVED.
(Whispering): OK.
ALL RIGHT, "WHEN THE GODS ARE
IMPALING THEIR HOG WOOFERS..."
OH.
(Audience laughing)
"WHILE THE GAYS ARE INFORMING
THEIR HIP WAFERS..."
OH, NOW I GOT IT.
OH, YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
"WHILE THE GUYS ARE INFLATING
THEIR HIP-WADERS,
"LET'S HAVE A LITTLE VISIT
FROM OUR SPECIAL GUEST,
"GEORGE CLOONEY, STAR
OF THE NETWORK SERIES 'E.R.',
"ABOARD HIS FISHING YACHT.
"TALK ABOUT LUXURY."
I DON'T WANT TO DO THIS.
I GOT THE HIP-WADING CONTEST
GOING ON.
THE NETWORK FEELS
THE HIP-WADING CONTEST
ISN'T WHAT YOU'D CALL...
WHAT?
ENTERTAINING, SO...
ARE YOU
KIDDING ME?
I GOT 20 GUYS
PACKING THEIR SHORTS
FULL OF DRY ICE.
IF THAT'S NOT ENTERTAINMENT,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
THE POLITE TERM
IS "QUIRKY".
GOT A SPECIAL FEATURE
WITH BUZZ THIS WEEK.
A HOBBY THING HE'S GOT GOING.
MODEL-AIRPLANE FLYING
IS SWEEPING THE NATION,
AND IS IT ANY WONDER?
EVEN IF YOUR LICENCE
IS UNDER SUSPENSION,
YOU CAN STILL ENJOY
THE THRILL OF AVIATION.
WHOA, LOOK AT THAT!
HOW FAR CAN YOU GET
THESE THINGS TO GO?
IT'S IN THE INSTRUCTIONS.
I DIDN'T READ 'EM.
UM, WHOSE PLANE IS THIS?
THAT'S MINE, BUT
IT'S A LITTLE WUSSY FOR ME.
I RIPPED THE GUTS OUT AND
PUT IT IN MY PLANE, "BEAUTY".
YOU'RE FLYING A PLANE
WITH RADIO CONTROLS?
(Laughing)
WHOO!
HERE SHE COMES!
WHOA, LOOK AT THAT!
"BEAUTY"!
MAN, LOOK AT THAT TURN.
FLIES BETTER WITHOUT YOU IN IT.
IT DOES -- MAN!
WO LOOK AT THAT.
FLYING STRAIGHT --
WATCH ME SAY "HI".
ISN'T THAT COOL?
HOW DO YOU SLOW HER
FOR LANDING?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
I DIDN'T READ THAT PART.
GIVE ME THAT A SECOND.
OH... OH, BUZZ.
UM...
"CONNECT SOLENOID 4-A
TO CHANNEL 5..."
BUZZ?
HOW'S THAT GONNA HELP ME?
YOU GOT A PROBLEM!
I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO LAND.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY!
(Crash)
OHHHH!
COOL!
NOW, THEN, TUCK IT IN THERE
AND CLOSE 'ER UP...
AND THERE WE ARE.
YOU CAN TAKE WHATEVER YOU WANT,
IF YOU KNOW HOW TO PACK.
ALL I GOTTA DO IS
GET THESE CLAMPS OFF OF HERE...
AND I GOT SO MUCH STUFF WITH ME
THAT WHEREVER I GO,
IT WILL BE JUST LIKE HOME.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
SO LONG.
AHHH...
(Grunting)
I MAY HAVE PUT
TOO MUCH STUFF IN THERE.
I MAY HAVE TO RE-PACK...
UH-OH, I THINK
SHE'S GONNA BLOW!
YEAH, LOOKS JUST LIKE HOME.
MY MAMA ALWAYS SAID,
"BUZZ, LIFE IS LIKE
A BOX OF CHOCOLATES,
"SO PIG OUT!"
(Laughing)
WELL...
(Audience laughing)
THE INFLATED
HIP-WADER CONTEST HAS BEGUN.
FIVE GUYS ARE OUT
OF THE RUNNING.
(Rubber
snapping)
(Shrieking)
SIX GUYS.
SIX GUYS OUT OF THE RUNNING.
WHEN THOSE HIP-WADERS GO,
THAT RUBBER LEAVES A WELT
YOU CAN LIGHT MATCHES ON.
(Audience laughing)
HAROLD!
WHAT IS
WITH YOU?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU'RE DRESSED FUNNY.
I'M TRYING TO LOOK NICE
FOR THE NETWORK.
THAT'S TOO
BAD, HAROLD.
THERE'S ONLY 40 GUYS
LEFT IN THE CONTEST.
(Rubber
snapping)
(Shrieking)
THIRTY-NINE.
(Audience laughing)
SOME HIP-WADERS ARE GARBAGE.
THERE'S ONE BRAND--
UNCLE RED, DON'T MENTION
WHICH BRAND-NAME
IS THE CHEAPEST.
YOU MIGHT OFFEND
A POTENTIAL NETWORK SPONSOR.
HAROLD, I DON'T THINK THAT MANY
HIP-WADER COMPANIES ADVERTISE
ON NETWORK TELEVISION.
BETTER SAFE THAN SORRY.
THE SAFER WE GET,
THE SORRIER WE SOUND.
UNCLE RED, THIS AMERICAN
NETWORK DEAL IS A BIG THING.
WHAT ABOUT MICHAEL J. FOX?
HE'S A CANADIAN
WHO MADE IT IN HOLLYWOOD,
AND SO IS JASON PRIESTLEY,
AND WHAT ABOUT KEANU REEVES?
I COULD BE
THE NEXT KEANU REEVES.
(Audience laughing)
WELL, WHAT ABOUT ME?
OH, YOU, TOO.
YOU COULD BE... MARY PICKFORD.
(Laughing and applause)
MARY PICKFORD?
(Red): BACK AT THE BOXING RING,
HAROLD'S HELPING BILL.
OH, BOY.
HAROLD WAS HELPING BILL
GET HIS GLOVES ON
OVER AT THE BIG SQUARED CIRCLE.
OH!
THIS IS TAKING SOME TIME,
BUT I BROUGHT SOME WAY
OF FILLING IN THE PATIENT WAIT.
SO GETTING THE HELMET ON.
BOXING'S A LOT SAFER THAN
IT USED TO BE, BUT STILL...
STILL NOT TOTALLY SAFE.
AND, UH... THAT NINE WILL GO--
THAT NINE WILL GO ON THE--
YEAH, ON THE 10, ON THE 10.
OK, THAT'S GOOD.
AND NOW WITH THE SAFETY THING.
THEY GOT THE MOUTH GUARD
SO YOU DON'T WORRY ABOUT
YOUR TEETH GETTING DAMAGED
OR DRIVEN DOWN YOUR THROAT
OR UP YOUR NOSE.
YOU DON'T WORRY ABOUT
BRUISED GUMS, IN BILL'S CASE.
ALL RIGHT WITH THAT?
HAROLD, JUST GET--
OOH, YUCK.
HAROLD, GET RID OF THOSE--
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
NICE TEETH.
JUST HANG ON A MINUTE.
YOU THINK OF THE TRADITION
OF BOXING,
THERE'S A LOT OF DIGNITY
TO THE SPORT,
AND A LOT OF POMP
AND CIRCUMSTANCE.
YOU THINK OF THE GREATS --
THE MUHAMMAD ALIS,
THE JOE LOUIS's,
AND YOU'RE JUST PROUD.
YOU'RE PROUD TO BE
A PART OF THIS SPORT
THAT HAS BROUGHT SO MUCH HONOUR
TO A GREAT MANY ATHLETIC PEOPLE
AND THERE'S SOMETHING
ALMOST SPIRITUAL ABOUT IT,
YOU KNOW?
IT'S BORING, THOUGH, AT TIMES.
BUT YOU STAY TUNED, 'CAUSE
THE MAIN BOUT IS COMING UP.
WE GOT A SURPRISE, AND,
OBVIOUSLY, A DISAPPOINTMENT.
(Audience laughing)
(Applause)
YEAH, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
(Cheering)
(Applause)
(Whistling)
THE POSSUM LODGE
INFLATED HIP-WADER CONTEST
IS INTO THE HOME STRETCH,
AND I DO MEAN "STRETCH".
WE'RE DOWN TO FOUR GUYS.
EXCUSE ME -- "PEOPLE".
FINAL FOUR PEOPLE.
THE NETWORK FEELS THAT
REFERRING TO GUYS AS GUYS
IS A LITTLE BIT SEXIST.
THEY ARE GUYS, HAROLD.
CAN'T YOU CALL THEM PEOPLE?
NOT WITH A STRAIGHT FACE.
WE DON'T WANT TO OFFEND
THE WOMEN.
WE DON'T WANT THEM
TO FEEL EXCLUDED.
MAYBE JUST NOT BE SO SEXIST.
HAROLD, NOBODY'S EXCLUDED HERE.
POSSUM LODGE IS OPEN
TO ALL RACES, COLOURS,
CREEDS, AND SEXES.
WOMEN DON'T ENJOY THINGS
LIKE INFLATING HIP-WADERS.
IT'S JUST THE WAY IT IS,
SO WHAT WE GET IS GUYS.
SEE, THAT IS SEXIST.
NO, THAT IS REALITY.
OK, WELL, NETWORK TELEVISION
ISNOT REALITY.
IS IT, AUNT BERNICE?
WHAT?
(Swinging jazz music)
(Audience): WHOOOO!
(Whistling)
(Applause and cheering)
STAY TUNED
TO "THE RED GREEN SHOW"
FOR MORE GREAT FUN.
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M BERNICE.
THAT'S MY
WIFE'S NAME.
HAROLD?
SHE'S BERNICE?
YES.
I AM, AND WE'RE GONNA HAVE
LOTS OF ZANY ADVENTURES,
AREN'T WE, DEAR?
WELL, IF YOU CAN CLEAR IT
WITH MY REAL WIFE,
I'M WILLING TO GIVE IT A TRY.
(Applause and cheering)
(Red): WE FINALLY GOT
THIS BOXING MATCH UNDER WAY.
I'VE A LITTLE DIFFERENT
TECHNIQUE THAN BILL HAS.
HE'S MORE INTO
THE BOB AND WEAVE
AND BOB AND WEAVE AND BOB-BOB,
BOB-BOB AND WEAVE-WEAVE.
I JUST KIND OF...
HE TELEGRAPHS
HIS PUNCHES, BILL.
HE CAN MAIL 'EM TO YOU,
THEY GET THERE SO SLOW.
WHAT IS THIS, BILL?
OH, HEY, WAIT!
HEY, HEY, TIME OUT!
TIME OUT, TIME OUT...
EXCEPT FOR YOU.
I'M KIDDING, I'M KIDDING.
I FIGURE, LET'S GET HAROLD--
HAROLD, YOU'LL BE FINE.
HAROLD WILL FIGHT BILL.
NO GLASSES -- THAT'S DANGEROUS.
YOU NEVER HIT A GUY
WITH GLASSES,
AND I WANT BILL TO GET HIT.
I PUT THEM OVER THERE.
OK, AWAY YOU GO, BOYS.
OH, HAROLD, COME ON.
OH, YOU BIG WUSS.
WHAT I'M REALIZING IS
BILL REALLY DOES HAVE
A VISION PROBLEM.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, BILL?
THAT'S NOT-- OH, I SEE.
NO, THAT'S NOT HAROLD.
IT'S JUST A PAIL,
FOR GOSH SAKES!
OH, MY!
YEAH, YEAH,
HE'S THE BIG WINNER.
YOU'RE THE BIG WINNER.
EVER HAD A KNOCK-OUT BEFORE?
THERE'S ONE.
WAY TO GO, HAROLD!
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION.
ON THIS WEEK'S EXPERT PORTION,
WE HAVE MY UNCLE RED
AND WATER-TAXI CAPTAIN,
MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSY!
(Applause and cheering)
(Whistling)
THIS WEEK'S LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS:
(Singing) BA-DUM-BUM-BUM
"DEAR EXPERTS, WHAT IS
"THE GREATEST
ROCK 'N' ROLL BAND EVER?"
EASY -- R.E.M. -- AHHH!
(Audience laughing)
NO, NO, NO, HAROLD,
THE GREATEST BAND EVER,
CANADIAN BAND, THE GUESS WHO.
I DON'T KNOW -- WHO?
(Audience laughing)
WELL, PERSONALLY, I'D HAVE
PICKED THE ROLLING STONES,
BUT SINCE I WAS ONCE
PART OF THEIR BAND...
(Laughing)
I GUESS... I GUESS
THE STONES SHOULDN'T COUNT.
DID YOU CHAUFFEUR THEM AROUND
ONCE OR...
NO, NO, PLAYED LEAD GUITAR
FOR A FEW MONTHS.
WHEN KEITH RICHARDS WAS TOO ILL,
YOU KNOW, WITH HIS...
DIDN'T THE AGE DIFFERENCE
GET IN THE WAY,
MR. SHAUGHNESSY?
THEY WEREN'T MUCH
OLDER THAN ME.
OH.
WHEN KEITH WOULD GO
UP TO HIS ROOM,
I'D HAVE TO TAKE CARE
OF THOSE WOMEN
WHO WANTED TO MEET HIM --
THE "GROPIES".
(Audience laughing)
IT WAS A GOOD JOB, THOUGH --
350 BUCKS A NIGHT.
I WOULD HAVE PAID THEM
TWICE THAT MUCH.
OH, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT HAVE WE GOT HERE?
FOR GOSH SAKES -- A GUITAR!
THERE
YOU GO, HAP.
PLAY US A LITTLE
ROLLING STONES MUSIC.
ARE YOU TRYING TO EMBARRASS ME
IN FRONT OF MY FANS, RED?
JUST TRYING TO GET
A LITTLE SATISFACTION.
(Audience laughing)
(Whistling)
(Applause and cheering)
(Whooping)
WE HAVE A WINNER IN
THE INFLATED HIP-WADER CONTEST,
AND OBVIOUSLY IT ISN'T ME.
I GOT 'ER UP TO FULL PRESSURE
AND SAT ON MY CAR KEYS.
NOW ALL I GOT
IS THIS RUBBER KILT.
(Laughing)
(Audience laughing)
THAT'S GREAT, UNCLE RED.
SO, WHAT DID WE LEARN
FROM THIS WEEK'S EPISODE?
WHO THE HECK ARE YOU?
(Laughing)
I'M HAROLD.
YOUR NEPHEW?
YOUR NETWORK-APPROVED NEPHEW.
OH, WELL,
GOLLY.
MAYBE THIS IS WORKING OUT
AFTER ALL.
ALL RIGHT,
HERE'S WHAT I LEARNED.
NEVER HOLD AN INFLATED
HIP-WADER CONTEST
NEXT TO A GAME OF LAWN DARTS.
(Laughing)
AND I'VE LEARNED THAT
IF YOU TELL A LIE,
THE ONLY PERSON YOU HURT
IS YOURSELF.
AND YOU KNOW?
UNCLE RED, IT'S THE WORST KIND
OF HURT.
OH, NO, IT ISN'T.
CUT!
CUT! WHOA! CUT!
THAT'S NOT WORKING, UNCLE RED.
I'M NOT MAKING ANY MORE CHANGES.
THERE WON'T BE CHANGES.
THE NETWORK ISN'T INTERESTED
ANY MORE.
WHY NOT?
THEY FINALLY WATCHED
AN EPISODE.
I'M GONE.
I'M HISTORY,
TOO.
COME ON.
OK, UNCLE RED, MAYBE YOU
DON'T GET A NETWORK TIME SLOT,
BUT YOU GET ME BACK.
A GOOD NEWS, BAD NEWS THING?
ONE BEING GOOD NEWS
AND ONE BEING BAD NEWS?
THAT'S HOW I SEE IT.
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
WHAT A DAY.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
THAT WIFE THE NETWORK GAVE ME
WASN'T HALF THE WOMAN YOU ARE,
IN AGE OR WEIGHT...
OR SENSE OF HUMOUR --
RIGHT, BERNICE?
LAUGH IT UP.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE NON-NETWORK GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
ALL RISE, ALL RISE!
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.