[punching]
[bell ringing and cheering]
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S A MAN WHO'S IN TOUCH
WITH HIS FEMININE SIDE,
EVERY TIME HE PHONES HIS WIFE,
YOUR HOST, MY HERO,
UNCLE RED GREEN!
[cheering]
ALL
RIGHT!
YOU'RE THE MAN!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WELL, IT'S SPRING TRADING DAY
UP AT THE LODGE.
WHY CAN'T YOU SPRING CLEAN?
JUST THROW OUT JUNK.
WITH SPRING TRADING
YOU CAN GET RID OF STUFF
YOU'VE HOARDED OVER THE WINTER.
THE TRICK IS TO MAKE
THE BEST TRADES.
HOW COME EVERYTHING HAS TO BE
A COMPETITION?
THERE HAS TO BE
A WINNER AND A LOSER.
YOU CAN'T CHEER
FOR YOUR HOCKEY TEAM!
YOU GOT TO MAKE A POOL.
EVERYBODY CHEERS FOR EVERYBODY
THAT WAY -- HA HA.
YOU BUY
THE SPORTS LOTTERY TICKETS.
YOU DON'T CARE
WHO WINS THE GAME.
IT'S JUST STUPID.
YOU LOST
AGAIN, EH?
TWENTY WEEKS IN A ROW.
[horns honking]
[geese honking]
[quacking]
(Red): HAP TRIES TO CONVINCE US
HE WRESTLED ELEPHANTS,
I'LL SCOUR MY WORKBENCH
FOR A SPECIAL KIND OF TAPE,
DALTON TALKS ABOUT
THE FACTS OF LIFE,
AND I'M GONNA
FISH SOMETHING OFF THE BOTTOM
OF POSSUM LAKE.
THIS WAS MY WORST TRADE --
I GOT THERE LATE.
THE ONLY GUY WITH STUFF LEFT
WAS OLD MAN SEDGWICK.
HALF A RAILING,
A BENT HOSE CLAMP,
A BUNCH OF VANILLA BEANS,
I HOPE.
LOOK AT THIS.
A PICTURE OF A POSSUM.
HEY, THIS COULD BE
THE POSSUM LODGE POSSUM.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
NO, IT COULD BE.
THIS PICTURE IS LIKE A PIECE
OF HISTORY TO A COLLECTOR.
IT'S WORTH 70, 80 CENTS.
HAROLD, THAT'S AN AERIAL PHOTO
OF POSSUM LAKE.
IT'S THE POSSUM --
THAT "X" IS HIS EYE.
WOULDN'T THE "X" BE IN THE HEAD?
OK, WELL THEN, WHAT'S THIS "X"?
I GUESS THAT'S
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S SIGNATURE.
TREASURE, IT'S TREASURE!
THAT "X" MARKS THE SPOT
OF VALUABLE TREASURE
AT THE BOTTOM OF POSSUM LAKE.
NO, HAROLD, NO.
WE THOUGHT OF THAT -- OH.
BUT WHAT COULD OLD MAN SEDGWICK
HAVE HAD OF VALUE 50 YEARS AGO?
MAYBE HIS MIND.
DO OTHER LODGE MEMBERS
KNOW ABOUT THIS?
THEY DON'T CARE.
WE'RE TOO BUSY.
WE GOT IMPORTANT THINGS TO DO.
LIKE WHAT SPECIFICALLY?
JUST THINGS, THAT'S ALL,
IMPORTANT THINGS.
YOU WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND.
IT'S THINGS MEN DO.
OVEREATING, SLEEPING,
WATCHING T.V.,
DRINKING BEER, FIXING CARS.
PRETTY MUCH COVERS IT, YEAH.
[audience laughing]
(Red): TO GET READY FOR
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL",
BILL IS BUILDING A DUCK BLIND.
THE POINT IS TO BE
TOTALLY INVISIBLE.
I THINK HE'S DONE
AN EXCELLENT JOB.
I DON'T THINK I SAW HIM, DID I?
NO, NO.
YOU ALL RIGHT, BILL?
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT, AREN'T YOU?
IT'S A DUCK BLIND.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO DUCK.
OH, YOU'RE FINE.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW.
THIS WEEK WE HAVE EXPERTS,
MY UNCLE RED,
AND HIS FRIEND DALTON HUMPHREY.
[applause]
GOT A QUESTION.
OK, FIRST QUESTION
GOES AS FOLLOWS: "DEAR EXPERTS,"
LA LA LA
"HOW OLD"-- EXCELLENT ONE!
"HOW OLD SHOULD A CHILD BE
"BEFORE YOU EXPLAIN
THE FACTS OF LIFE?"
WELL, THIS REALLY DEPENDS ON
THE MATURITY OF THE CHILD.
SOME ARE READY AT 13.
OTHERS AREN'T READY UNTIL...
HOW OLD
NINETEEN.           ARE YOU?
UNTIL THEY'RE 21.
THIS IS ONE JOB
THAT NO PARENT WANTS.
I'M GLAD I WON'T HAVE TO EXPLAIN
THE FACTS OF LIFE TO ANYBODY.
HOW OLD WAS YOUR DAUGHTER
WHEN YOU TOLD HER?
THAT'S A WIFE'S JOB.
THE DAD TELLS THE SON,
WIFE TELLS THE DAUGHTER.
THE NATURAL ORDER OF THINGS.
YOUR DAD TALKED TO YOU, RIGHT?
NO, HE GAVE ME A BOOK
BY MICKEY SPILLANE
CALLED "KISS ME DEADLY".
AND SAID "THIS IS WHAT
MARRIED PEOPLE DO."
I THOUGHT HE MEANT SHOOT
EACH OTHER AND HAVE CAR CHASES.
THAT'S WHAT HIS RELATIVES DID.
MR. HUMPHREY,
HOW OLD
WAS YOUR DAUGHTER
WHEN YOUR WIFE TOLD HER
ABOUT THE FACTS--
ABOUT THE...
UH, YOU KNOW, THE... THE...
ABOUT IT?
HOW OLD?
SHE HASN'T YET.
TABITHA'S ONLY 20.
THERE'S NO RUSH.
BUT SHE HAS A BOYFRIEND,
DOESN'T SHE?
SO?
YOU KNOW, IT'S PUPPY LOVE, RED.
TOTALLY INNOCENT.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK
THEY EVEN KISS YET.
I JUST THOUGHT 'CAUSE
THEY'D MOVED IN TOGETHER.
WELL, YEAH, BUT THAT, THAT,
DOESN'T M-M-MEAN ANYTHING.
HE SLEEPS ON THE COUCH.
HA HA HA HA.
[audience laughing]
HER MOTHER WILL TALK TO HER
WHEN THE TIME'S RIGHT!
WELL, I HOPE SHE CAN GET HER
ATTENTION IN THE DELIVERY ROOM.
[audience laughing]
I'VE ASKED LOTS OF MEN
WHAT'S THE THING
THEY LIKE MOST
HUNTING OR FISHING
OR PEANUT BUTTER ON TOAST
THE MOST POPULAR ANSWER
FROM EACH TIME I'VE ASKED
IS WHATEVER I'M DOING,
I LIKE TO GO FAST
HE LIKES TO GO FAST
DRIVING A CAR
OR RIDING A BIKE
EATING MY DINNER
OR TAKING A HIKE
SPEED IS THE THRILL
THAT MAKES ALL MEN GLAD
EXCEPT WHEN
WE'VE FALLEN OFF THE ROOF
IN WHICH CASE
WE'D LIKE GRAVITY TO
JUST EASE OFF
ON THE THROTTLE A TAD
MAYBE I DIDN'T HAVE MUCH LUCK
AT THIS YEAR'S SPRING TRADING,
BUT, THE TRUE HANDYMAN
MAKES HIS OWN LUCK,
AND OFTEN HIS OWN BANDAGES.
ALL RIGHT, I COULDN'T GET RID
OF THESE TWO CLOTHES DRYERS,
AND THIS BICYCLE.
SO YOU COULD SAY
I'M STUCK WITH THEM.
WELL THEN, WHY NOT TURN THEM
INTO SOMETHING USEFUL?
I THINK IT WAS SHAKESPEARE
WHO SAID...
YOU CAN'T MAKE A SILK EAR
OUT OF A SOW'S PURSE.
MAYBE THAT WAS
SIR FRANCIS BACON.
DIDN'T HE ALSO SAY
YOU CAN MAKE
AN ELECTRIC LAWN ROLLER
OUT OF JUST ABOUT ANYTHING.
AND IT'S DEAD EASY.
FIRST, YOU GOT TO
CHOP 'EM DOWN A LITTLE BIT...
SO THE DRUM WILL SIT
RIGHT THERE ON THE GROUND.
THIS IS HOW THEY LOOK
WHEN THEY'RE CHANNELLED
WITH CHROME LIFTERS
AND THE HURST SHIFTER.
A COUPLE OF LAPS ON YOUR YARD
AND YOUR GRASS WILL BE
SMOOTH ENOUGH TO GOLF ON.
ONCE I GET THAT DONE,
I NEED SOMETHING TO
CONNECT THE TWO.
I'M GONNA USE THIS BIKE.
KIND OF STICK HER IN HERE.
I COULD ATTACH IT WITH
SPOT WELDING OR STOVE BOLTS,
OR, HOW ABOUT THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
I GOT THE BICYCLE MOUNTED
ONTO MY DRYERS.
HERE'S A WORD OF CAUTION.
GET A COMFORTABLE SEAT.
WE'RE LOOKING AT A MAJOR WEDGIE
IN MY FUTURE.
THEY CALL THEM BANANA SEATS
BECAUSE THEY HAVE TO
PEEL YOU OFF OF THEM.
ANOTHER THING YOU WANT TO
THINK ABOUT IS
THAT THE DRYERS' EXHAUST
GIVES OFF A LOT OF
FABRIC SOFTENER FUMES.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BREATHE THAT.
SO I'LL MOUNT
A COUPLE OF EXHAUST PIPES
USING SOME DUCT WORK
FROM THE DRYER.
I JUST NEED SOMETHING TO
TAPE THE DUCT WORK TOGETHER.
UH.
SOME KIND OF TAPE
FOR DUCT WORK.
HERE WE GO.
ADHESIVE TAPE.
THAT WILL BE PERFECT.
I'LL MOUNT THESE ON HERE.
LOOK AT THAT.
NOTHING SAYS POWER
LIKE DUAL EXHAUSTS.
JUST SCREAMS "EAT MY LINT."
THERE WE GO.
I'LL BE ROLLING THE LAWN,
SO I GOT HER SET ON
PERMANENT PRESS.
WHEN I GET TO THE GARDEN,
I'LL FLIP HER OVER TO
THE DELICATE CYCLE.
INSIDE THE DRYER,
YOU'VE GOT AIR BLOWING AROUND.
YOU GOT A LINT FILTER.
THROW SOME GRASS SEED IN THERE.
POP THAT BABY IN,
AND YOU CAN ACTUALLY BE
ROLLING AND SEEDING
AT THE SAME TIME.
I GOT HER HARD-WIRED
INTO THE HOUSE
WITH PLENTY OF CORD
FOR MANOEUVRABILITY.
SHE'S A BEAUTY, ISN'T SHE?
ALSO MAKE A DANDY STEAMROLLER,
EVEN A LEAF PRESS.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME...
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I GOT TO GET ROLLING.
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH!
WELL, SHE ROLLED.
FIND OUT ABOUT RANGER GORD'S
IMAGINARY FRIEND.
THIS PHOTO WITH THE "X"
HAS EVERYBODY CONVINCED
THERE'S SOMETHING VALUABLE
AT THE BOTTOM OF POSSUM LAKE.
YOU SAID THEY
WEREN'T INTERESTED.
THEY WEREN'T UNTIL
THEY HEARD YOU WERE.
THAT COMPETITION THING
KICKS IN.
IT'S NOT THAT THEY THINK
THEY'LL FIND TREASURE.
THEY CAN'T STAND THE THOUGHT
THAT SOMEBODY ELSE MIGHT.
THEY HAD
THEIR CHANCE.
THEY WEREN'T
INTERESTED.
THEY DON'T WANT TO
LOOK LIKE IDIOTS.
REALLY
WOW.
NOW THERE'S A COMPETITION
TO SEE WHO CAN DIVE
THE DEEPEST.
I SWAM THERE AND
MY FEET TOUCHED BOTTOM.
NO, THAT WASN'T THE BOTTOM.
THAT WAS JUST STUFF.
OH, AW.
OK, FINE -- I'LL LOWER
MY VIDEO CAMERA DOWN THERE.
NO, I TRIED THAT, HAROLD.
ALL I GOT WAS DARKNESS.
OK, MAYBE YOU JUST HAD
THE WATERPROOF CASE
ON BACKWARDS.
WATERPROOF CASE --
WHERE'S THAT?
FOR ALL THE FOREST'S BEAUTY,
IT CAN BE ONE OF
THE MOST DANGEROUS PLACES
ON EARTH.
THEN I'M THINKING
WE JUST HOLD EVERYTHING,
AND YOU GIVE PEOPLE SOME RULES
ABOUT BEING IN THE FOREST.
SOME OF YOU FOLKS MAY WANT TO
JOT A FEW OF THESE DOWN.
THERE'S REALLY ONLY ONE RULE
THAT WILL SAVE YOUR LIFE
IN THE FOREST.
NEVER COME OUT ALONE.
ALWAYS HAVE A BUDDY WITH YOU.
IN CASE SOMETHING BAD HAPPENS.
YOUR BUDDY WILL HELP YOU,
OR YOU'LL HAVE
SOMEBODY TO BLAME.
[laughing]
NO, I'M SERIOUS.
I'M THINKING SOME OF THE VIEWERS
WILL BE SAYING, "THIS IS IRONIC.
"RANGER GORD CAN'T EVEN TAKE
HIS OWN ADVICE."
YOU DON'T HAVE A BUDDY.
I SEE WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
AND, IN FACT, I DO.
COME OVER HERE,
I'LL SHOW YOU MY BUDDY.
RIGHT OVER THERE
ON THE HORIZON.
THE PORT ASBESTOS LOOK-OUT.
THAT'S MY BUDDY.
THAT'S RANGER VINCE.
EVERY NIGHT FOR 12 YEARS,
RANGER VINCE AND I HAVE BEEN
TURNING ON LIGHTS.
I'LL TURN ON MY LIGHTS.
HE TURNS ON HIS.
TWO RANGERS SAYING "HEY, BUDDY,
I'VE NEVER MET YA,
"BUT I'M THERE FOR YA."
I'VE NEVER MET RANGER VINCE,
BUT, I FEEL I KNOW HIM.
HE'S MY BUDDY.
UH, UM, THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TELL YOU.
RANGER VINCE,
HE'S ACTUALLY NOT,
HE'S NOT ACTUALLY IN THERE.
HE LEFT THAT TOWER
12, MAYBE 13 YEARS AGO.
THE LONELINESS --
HE WASN'T LIKE YOU.
HE COULDN'T TAKE IT
AND HE-- THAT'S--
THAT'S A RADIO TRANSMITTER.
EVERY NIGHT I SEE HIM
TURN ON HIS LIGHTS.
FAIR ENOUGH, BUT THAT WOULD BE
A REMOTE CONTROL UNIT.
THEY CLICK THE LIGHTS ON
FROM SOMEWHERE ELSE
SO THE PLANES WON'T SMACK
INTO THE TOWER
AS MUCH AS THEY USED TO.
VINCE IS GONE, HE'S TOAST,
HE'S IN THE WIND.
HE'S GONE, HE'S OUT OF THERE.
THERE'S NO VINCE OVER THERE
AS FAR AS I KNOW.
VINCE!
NO, NO, WASTE OF TIME.
I'VE BEEN ALONE FOR 12 YEARS.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
[sobbing]
YOU'RE DOING REALLY WELL.
SOMEBODY PLEASE HUG ME.
[sobbing]
NO, NO, LET'S NOT.
HEY, I KNOW, I KNOW.
GO HUG MY BUDDY, HAROLD.
[sobbing]
SORRY, HAROLD.
YOU'RE IN THE SOUP THIS TIME,
AREN'T YOU?
YOU AGREED TO MEET HER
AT A CERTAIN TIME AND PLACE
AND YOU FORGOT?!
YOU REMEMBERED
AN HOUR AFTER THE FACT.
BY THEN YOU WERE OVER
THE OTHER SIDE OF TOWN
HALFWAY THROUGH A HAMBURGER.
SHE'S STOMPING AROUND
KNEE-HIGH IN THE SNOW,
AND YOU'RE IN DEEP SLEET,
BUDDY.
HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
GIVE YOURSELF A FLAT TIRE.
POKE IT.
SLASH IT.
WHATEVER.
SHOOT IT.
IF YOU'VE GOT
AN UNUSED SPARE TIRE,
FLATTEN THAT AS WELL.
THIS MAKES YOUR SITUATION
MORE MISERABLE THAN HERS.
AND THAT GIVES HER
ALL THE POWER TO BE FORGIVING,
WHICH GETS YOU OFF THE HOOK.
BY THE TIME YOU GET HOME,
YOU'LL BE THE ONE
GETTING SYMPATHY.
SURE, YOU'LL HAVE TO GET TOWED
TO THE GARAGE.
WAIT -- THAT'S FUN.
DON'T TELL HER THAT.
RIGHT.
UNCLE RED,
LOOK AT THIS.
THIS PICTURE IS DATED 1943.
GUESS WHAT OLD MAN SEDGWICK
WAS DOING IN 1943.
AVOIDING WORLD
WAR II?
NO, NO, NO,
HE WAS TOO OLD TO SERVE.
HE WAS WORKING
ON THE RAILROAD.
SO I FIGURE I'LL CHECK OUT
NEWSPAPERS FROM 1943,
CHECK THE HEADLINES.
SOMETHING LIKE
"RAILWAY PAYROLL VANISHES."
"TREASURE TRAIN TOPPLES
INTO LAKE".
OOO.
WE GOT NEWSPAPERS
IN OUR MATTRESSES YOU CAN USE.
NO, BUT, THANK YOU.
I'LL GO DOWN TO
THE LIBRARY IN TOWN.
THERE'S NO LIBRARY IN TOWN.
ACROSS FROM THE GREAT HALL,
THAT YELLOW BUILDING.
THAT'S A LIBRARY?
YES, IT'S A LIBRARY.
WHY ARE YOU DRESSED LIKE THIS?
WE'RE GOING
SCUBA DIVING FOR THE TREASURE.
NOBODY HAS RUBBER CLOTHING,
AT LEAST NOT THAT THEY'D USE
FOR SCUBA DIVING.
SO NOW WE'VE GOT
A COMPETITION
TO SEE WHO CAN MAKE THE MOST
WATERPROOF WET SUIT.
THAT'S A SNOWMOBILE SUIT.
YOU CAN'T WEAR THAT
INTO POSSUM LAKE.
I DO EVERY WINTER.
[audience laughing]
RANGER GORD AT
FIRE WATCH-TOWER 13
REMINDING YOU
NEVER EVER TRY TO FEED A BEAR,
NEVER TEASE A BEAR,
AND NEVER EVER
TRY TO DANCE WITH A BEAR.
TRUST ME.
(Red): AS I EXPLAINED EARLIER,
BILL BUILT THE DUCK BLIND
BECAUSE HE'D GOTTEN STUFF
IN THE SPRING TRADING.
HE'D GOTTEN SOME OPTICAL STUFF.
SOME LITTLE BINOCULARS
WHICH HE LENT TO ME.
LOOK AT THE UNIT HE HAD.
WELL, DON'T LOOK AT
THE SUN, BILL.
THERE'S A BIRD!
OH!
BY GOLLY, AND THEY'RE HEAVY.
YOU HIT ME, BILL.
YOU HIT ME.
SHH.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
THERE'S ANOTHER ONE.
OH, OH!
HOW'S THAT FEEL?
HOW DO YOU LIKE THAT?
GIMME THOSE, BILL.
UH-OH.
[bird
cawing]
OH MY GOSH.
WELL, THERE'S ONE LESS BIRD.
OW, OW!
HEY, THOSE ARE MINE.
YOU GAVE ME THOSE, BILL.
GET SOMETHING ELSE.
NOT MY PROBLEM.
HE'S GOT A CAMERA.
YOU GOT NO LENS IN THAT CAMERA.
YOU GOTTA PUT A LENS
IN THAT THING.
YOU HAVEN'T
GOT A LENS, HAVE YA?
OH YES, YOU DO.
OH MY GOSH, LOOK AT THAT.
HOLY MACKEREL.
THAT'S A BEAUTY.
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO TAKE
THE TELEPHOTO SHOTS WITH THAT.
BE CAREFUL WITH THAT.
OH, OH.
YOU'RE DANGEROUS --
GIMME THAT, GIMME THAT.
I'LL GET RID OF THAT.
HOW'S THAT FEEL?
GET RID OF IT.
[bird
cawing]
THERE GOES ANOTHER ONE.
WHERE'S ALL THE BIRDS, BILL?
I DON'T HEAR ANYTHING.
WHERE DID THEY GO?
YOU LOOK THAT WAY.
I'LL LOOK THIS WAY.
NO BIRDS.
WELL, NOW WE GET INTO
WHOSE FAULT IT IS.
I DON'T WANNA BLAME--
I'M NOT GOING...
I KNOW IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
I'M NOT SAYING THAT...
NECESSARILY...
OK, I MIGHT HAVE IMPLIED--
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
SHH.
BOY, THEY SOUND CLOSE.
WHAT THE HECK IS--
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES,
I'M GETTING OUT OF HERE.
[bird squawking]
BILL, THEY WENT THAT WAY.
OH.
HE'S ON THEIR TRAIL.
MIGHT BE FOLLOWING
A LITTLE TOO CLOSE THERE, BILL.
STAY TUNED FOR
AN AMAZING STORY.
THE HOME-MADE WET SUITS
WERE ALL A DISASTER.
JUNIOR SINGLETON MADE HIMSELF
AN ELECTRICALLY-HEATED UNIT.
HE WAS DOWN THERE AND CAUGHT
THE CROTCH ON A STOVE.
LIT THE WHOLE PLACE UP.
YOU COULD SEE THE WHOLE LAKE.
IT'S LIKE
A JUNK YARD DOWN THERE.
WE'VE NOW SWITCHED TO PLAN "B".
THAT'S GOOD,
YEAH, PLAN "B's" GOOD.
MOOSE THOMPSON AND I
HAVE A 100-FOOT SEWER PIPE.
WE'LL GET THAT UP ON ITS END,
DROP IT ONTO THE TREASURE.
THEN WE'LL PUMP THE WATER OUT,
CLIMB DOWN AND PICK
THE TREASURE OFF THE BOTTOM.
WELL, THAT'S SOUNDS, UM... GOOD.
DO YOU HAVE A PLAN "C"?
WE DON'T NEED IT.
IS THERE ANYTHING
IN THE OLD PAPER
TO GIVE US A CLUE?
THERE'S NOTHING
ABOUT SUNKEN TREASURE.
NO MENTION OF ANYTHING,
NOT EVEN THE WAR.
LOOK AT THIS.
"LOCAL FARMER DIES OF SCURVY."
"TOWN COUNCIL VOTES DOWN
ELECTRIC POWER."
"1932 PACKARD FOR SALE."
HAROLD, THAT'S TODAY'S PAPER.
OH YEAH, RIGHT.
[audience laughing]
WELL, HERE I AM
WITH HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
WHAT ARE WE TRYING TO CATCH?
PICKEREL, RED.
A REAL FIGHTING FISH.
WOULD YOU SAY PICKEREL IS
THE HARDEST FIGHTER
YOU'VE EVER FACED?
THE HARDEST FIGHTING FISH
I'VE FACED.
MIND YOU, THEY'RE NOT AS HARD
AS WRESTLING ELEPHANTS.
NO, I GUESS NOT.
BEEN A WHILE SINCE
I'VE DONE THAT.
THAT WAS BEFORE THEY BANNED
ELEPHANT WRESTLING.
IT WAS A LOT OF FUN
FOR AWHILE THOUGH.
THE PAY WAS GOOD.
BUT WE NEVER GOT THE RESPECT
THAT WE SHOULD HAVE GOT
FROM OTHER ATHLETES.
THIS IS AFTER THEY MADE US
A DEMONSTRATION SPORT
AT THE 1956 OLYMPICS
IN OSLO.
OSLO, NORWAY?
THAT WOULD BE
THE WINTER OLYMPICS, HAP.
I BELIEVE WRESTLING
IS A SUMMER EVENT.
WRESTLING IS A SUMMER EVENT.
THIS IS ELEPHANT WRESTLING,
RED.
DONE ON ICE TO MAKE IT
MORE EXCITING.
WOW, I'D THINK
THAT WOULD BE VERY TIRING
TO BRING DOWN AN ANIMAL
THAT SIZE BY YOURSELF.
LUCKILY, IT WAS A TAG MATCH.
I'D WEAR HIM DOWN.
MY PARTNER, WALLY, WOULD
GET HIM TO THE BREAKING POINT.
THEN I'D GO IN
FOR THE TAKE-DOWN.
YOU PINNING AN ELEPHANT.
THAT'S GOT TO BE
THE BIGGEST WHOPPER
YOU'VE EVER LAID OUT.
IT'S ALL IN THE TECHNIQUE.
YOU GET HIM OFF BALANCE.
YOU GET UNDER THE TUSK
AND YOU PULL ON THE TRUNK
AND YOU PUSH UP,
AND OVER HE GOES.
OR HER, OR THEM.
I'VE SEEN ME DO A COUPLE.
YOU'VE GOT TO FIND A NEW
TECHNIQUE FOR THE NEXT MATCH
BECAUSE AN ELEPHANT
NEVER FORGETS.
NO, I ENVY THEM THAT.
THIS IS A SMALL PIPE WRENCH.
THIS IS A MEDIUM PIPE WRENCH.
[ WATER SPLASHING ]
THIS IS A LOST PIPE WRENCH.
YOU FOUND IT!
YOU FOUND THE TREASURE!
OH, THAT'S EXCELLENT!
OH, LET'S SEE, LET'S SEE.
GET READY FOR IT, HAROLD.
GET READY, GET READY.
YOU READY, HAROLD?
HERE WE GO.
HUH?
THAT'S IT?
YEAH, I GUESS IT JUST
SHOWED UP IN THE PHOTO
BECAUSE IT WAS THERE.
I GUESS POSSUM LAKE WAS
A LOT CLEARER IN THOSE DAYS.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO BE
WORTH MUCH.
WE FOUND IT AND YOU DIDN'T,
SO THAT HAS SOME VALUE.
[laughing]
YEAH, OK,
TO A MORON.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE SAYING,
BUT IT'S NOT FOR SALE.
[laughter and applause]
[squealing]
MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
AWAY YOU GO, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
I'LL BE HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M LESS CONCERNED ABOUT WHAT'S
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE LAKE
THAN WHAT'S AT
THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
ONIONS DO THAT TO ME.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF,
AND HAROLD,
AND THE WHOLE GANG
AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause and cheering]
[possum squeal]
(Harold): OK, ALL RISE.
SERIOUSLY, HE'S HERE NOW.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Harold): THERE WAS A CAR LEFT
IN POSSUM LAKE.