MAN!
YOU KNOW ON COLD
DAYS LIKE THESE
YOU END UP LOOKING AROUND
YOUR HOUSE FOR EAR MUFFS,
THEN YOU REMEMBER HOW YOU RIPPED
'EM IN HALF TO USE AS COASTERS
FOR THE PIANO LEGS?
WELL, DON'T PANIC.
HERE'S A WAY YOU CAN
MAKE YOUR OWN EAR MUFFS.
GET YOURSELF A COUPLE OF
COTTAGE CHEESE CONTAINERS.
SEEM TO HAVE A LOT OF
THESE AROUND OUR HOUSE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
I DON'T EAT COTTAGE CHEESE
OR ANYTHING ELSE YOU
SCRAPE OFF A COTTAGE.
THEN WHAT YOU WANNA DO
IS HOOK THESE TOGETHER
WITH A CROQUET HOOP.
ACTUALLY, JUST LIKE THIS.
I SUPPOSE I COULD'VE DONE
THIS WITH A COAT HANGER,
BUT, YOU KNOW, I LIKE TO GO
HIGH END WHENEVER I CAN.
NOW, YOU NEED TO PUT SOMETHING
INSIDE THE CONTAINERS
TO KEEP YOUR EARS WARM.
HOW ABOUT INSULATION?
THERE'S A NO-BRAINER, HUH?
YOU CAN GO R-12 WITH THESE
OR R-24.
ACTUALLY, IF YOU'RE
FIGHTING MIKE TYSON,
YOU MIGHT WANNA USE STEEL WOOL.
[shouthing]
AND IT'S JUST --
I SAY IT'S JUST THAT SIMPLE.
I'LL TELL YOU,
YOUR EARS'LL NEVER BE WARMER.
OR ITCHIER!
[cheering and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
BOY, I DO APPRECIATE THAT,
BUT TO BE HONEST WITH YOU,
IT'S BEEN KIND OF A ROUGH
DAY AT THE LODGE.
POSSUM VAN BROKE DOWN RIGHT
IN THE MIDDLE OF TOWN,
AND IT WAS RUSH HOUR, SO I HELD
UP TWO OTHER VEHICLES.
I MEAN THE VAN'S A BIT FINICKY,
BUT I CAN USUALLY GET HER GOING.
I MEAN, WIGGLE THE IGNITION
WIRES UNDER THE DASH THERE,
OR EMPTY A 3 OUGHT 3
INTO THE CARBURATOR.
BUT BOY, NOTHING SEEMED
TO WORK ON HER.
WE ENDED UP HAVING TO PUSH THE
VAN ALL THE WAY BACK HERE
TO THE LODGE.
[groaning]
[applause]
YOU KNOW, I WENT TO
SET THE EMERGENCY
BRAKE ON THE VAN,
BUT IT WAS
ALREADY ON.
I WONDER IF THAT'S WHY
THE VAN WAS SO HARD TO PUSH?
NO, NO, NO, THE
EMERGENCY DOESN'T
WORK ON THAT THING.
I LEAVE IT
ON FOR SHOW.
YOU GUYS LOOK
A LITTLE SORE.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
WELL, WE ARE SORE
'CAUSE, SEE,
WE WERE ON THE
OUTSIDE PUSHING
WHILE YOU WERE ON
THE INSIDE DRIVING.
YEAH,
BUT DON'T FORGET,
THE POWER STEERING
WASN'T WORKING.
WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST
CALL A TOW TRUCK?
A TOW TRUCK?
THAT'S 100 BUCKS, DALTON.
I CAN REPLACE THE VAN FOR 75.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I THINK I SMELL
AN ENTREPRENEURIAL
OPPORTUNITY HERE.
I DON'T LIKE IT
WHEN YOU SMELL THINGS.
NO, WHAT IF THERE
WAS A CHEAPER WAY
FOR PEOPLE TO GET HELP
WITH THEIR VEHICLES?
OH, I KNOW,
LIKE AN AUTO CLUB.
BOY, WE COULD START
OUR OWN AUTO CLUB.
WE COULD GET PEOPLE
TO PAY FIVE BUCKS A MONTH,
AND IF THEY HAD A PROBLEM,
THEY'D CALL US,
AND WE'D COME!
OH, YEAH, 'CAUSE WE'VE
GOT ENOUGH SERVICE
VEHICLES AMONG US.
I MEAN, LOOK AT
MY SEWAGE TRUCK.
THAT THING GOES LIKE STINK!
THAT THING IS STINK.
YOU KNOW, I GOT THE K-CARS.
I USE THE ARIES
'CAUSE IT'S A WAGON,
AND, OF COURSE,
YOU CAN'T TRUST THE RELIANT.
YOU KNOW,
YOU GUYS MAY BE ON
TO SOMETHING HERE.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
YOU MIGHT THINK ABOUT
JOINING YOURSELF.
YEAH, WELL, YOU GUYS
GET THE VAN RUNNING,
I'LL GIVE YOU
THE FIVE BUCKS.
NO, NO.
NICE TRY.
NICE TRY, RED.
NO, I'M IN THE
SEWAGE BUSINESS.
I TAKE ALL MY MONEY UP FRONT.
WELL, NO, I CAN'T PAY YOU
UNTIL YOU GET RUNNING
BECAUSE I NEED IT TO
TAKE BACK THE EMPTIES.
[applause]
IT'S TIME TO PLAY THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
[cheering and applause]
AND WHAT A GREAT PRIZE.
MIKE, HAVE YOU EVER
WON A TRIP TO FRANCE?
NO, NO, I HAVEN'T!
WELL, IF YOU EVER DO,
YOU'LL WANT TO TAKE
THIS FRENCH-ENGLISH
DICTIONARY WITH YOU.
OKAY, RED, YOU HAVE
30 SECONDS TO GET MIKE HAMAR
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, ED.
ALL RIGHT!
OKAY, AND GO!
OKAY, MIKE, THIS IS
SOMETHING YOU TOOK IN SCHOOL.
UH, BIKES?
WALKMANS?
UH, LUNCH MONEY?
NO.
LUNCHES THEMSELVES?
NO, NO.
CHALK.
MIKE!
TROPHIES.
UH, LIGHT BULBS.
OVERHEAD PROJECTORS.
THOSE ARE HEAVY.
NO, NO, MIKE.
NO, OKAY, THIS IS WHY
YOU HAD TO CRAM.
OH, TO GET EVERYTHING
IN MY BACKPACK.
THIS IS SOMETHING YOU HAD TO
PASS TO GET OUT OF SCHOOL.
OH, OKAY.
THE HALL MONITOR.
THINK OF A BIG ROOM,
LOTS OF DESKS,
LOTS OF STUDENTS IN THERE.
NOBODY'S ALLOWED TO TALK.
DETENTION?
THIS IS A TEST, AND YOU
HAD TO PASS THIS TEST,
OR YOU WOULDN'T GRADUATE.
OH, OH, THE POLYGRAPH!
YOU'RE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME, RED.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
GRADUATED HIGH SCHOOL.
HOW DID YOU PASS?
I CHEATED ON EVERY EXAM.
THERE WE GO!
YES! YES!
[applause]
HEY, HAROLD!
C'MON, LET'S GO.
WHAT? WHAT? WHAT?
LET'S GO.
WHAT? NO, HEY, NO!
NO I WORK HERE NOW.
THIS IS WHERE I WORK.
I'M WORKING HERE NOW.
OH, EVERYBODY'S IN A SUIT HERE.
YOU ALL DRESS THE SAME.
NOBODY'S GONNA NOTICE
THAT ONE SUIT IS GONE.
NOW, COME ON.
WE ARE NOT ALL JUST SUITS.
EACH AND EVERY
ONE OF US
IS AN INDEPENDENT
FUNCTIONING INDIVIDUAL.
JUST BECAUSE WE ALL
HAPPEN TO DRESS WELL
AND WORK IN A CORPORATE
ENVIRONMENT
THAT'S SIMILAR TO EVERY
CORPORATE ENVIRO --
WHERE DO YOU WANNA
TAKE ME, ANYWAY?
UP TO THE LODGE, OF COURSE.
OH, NO, NO.
I'M NOT GOING
TO THE LODGE.
WHAT'S SO IMPORTANT
I HAVE TO GO NOW?
WELL, HAROLD, WE'VE COME UP
WITH THIS GREAT IDEA.
EVERYBODY'S ALL FOR IT.
WE'RE READY TO GO.
AND?
HERE, LET ME
TELL YOU.
WE GOT NO
OPPOSITION, HAROLD.
WE'VE GOT NO
DIFFERENT POINT OF VIEW.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU USED
TO PLAY DEVIL'S ADVOCATE,
YOU'D PRETEND YOU DIDN'T LIKE
THOSE IDEAS I CAME UP WITH?
I WASN'T PRETENDING.
THEY WERE BAD IDEAS.
THEY WERE ALL BAD.
YOU NEVER HAD A GOOD IDEA.
JUST BAD IDEAS.
WHAT'S THE IDEA
YOU HAVE NOW?
WE'RE THINKING ABOUT TURNING
THE LODGE INTO A PART-TIME
DAYCARE CENTRE
FOR PRE-SCHOOLERS.
NO, NO, NO!
SEE, THAT'S A BAD IDEA.
THAT'S BAD ON SO MANY LEVELS.
WELL, THIS IS EXACTLY
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT,
THIS DISAPPROVAL THING.
WE NEED THIS.
NO, UNCLE RED,
THE LODGE MEMBERS,
THEY'RE INCOMPETENT,
THEY'RE IRRESPONSIBLE,
THEY'RE DANGEROUS.
THEY DON'T KNOW A THING
ABOUT WATCHING OVER
CHILDREN.
THIS IS GREAT.
YOU HAVE A REAL KNACK
FOR THIS KIND OF THING.
UNCLE RED, YOU'VE GOTTA
HAVE GOVERNMENT FORMS.
IT'S GOTTA BE LEGAL.
ALL SORTS OF STUFF!
JUST COME UP TO
THE LODGE WITH ME,
AND TELL THE GUYS
THIS STUFF, EH?
THEY NEED TO HEAR
ALL THIS, HAROLD.
COME ON.
DO YOU THINK I'LL
REALLY BE ABLE TO CHANGE
SOMEONE'S POINT OF VIEW?
NO, NO, BUT JUST KNOWING
YOU'RE AGAINST THIS
MAKES US ALL FEEL
SO MUCH BETTER.
THAT'S THE IMPORTANT THING.
[applause]
OH! OH!
RED GREEN.
WELCOME.
YEAH.
YOU ARE
WELCOME HERE, SIR.
LISTEN, CAN I BOUNCE
SOMETHING OFF YOU?
IT'S NOT AN
ANIMAL, IS IT?
NO.
PLEASE.
I'M THINKING OF INSTALLING
FIRE ALARMS IN ALL THE TREES.
THAT WAY, IF THERE'S
EVER A FIRE,
THE ANIMALS THEMSELVES WOULD
HAVE THE POWER TO SAVE
THEIR OWN HOMES.
GORD, YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT GOOD TO
SPEND YOUR WHOLE LIFE ALONE.
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I BET THE ANIMALS WOULD
PULL THE ALARM JUST
TO GET ATTENTION.
FIRE OR NO FIRE, I BET YOU
THE SQUIRRELS WOULD PULL IT
IF THEY WERE HAVING
TROUBLE FINDING NUTS.
YEAH, THEY'RE
SO ANAL, YOU KNOW.
NO, I'M ABANDONING THE
WHOLE FIRE ALARM IDEA.
OKAY, THAT'S
A START.
YEP.
I'M GOING TO GO WITH A
HEAT-ACTIVATED WATER
SPRINKLER SYSTEM.
TOTALLY AUTOMATIC.
THAT WAY THE ANIMALS WOULDN'T
HAVE TO PULL ANYTHING.
OKAY, GORD, DO YOU EVER
TAKE A BREAK FROM THIS JOB?
VACATION OR A LONG WEEKEND,
HOLIDAY, THAT KINDA THING?
DOES LIGHTNING
TAKE A BREAK, RED?
DOES FIRE TAKE
A HOLIDAY?
DO YOU THINK I WANT
TO DO THIS JOB?
HOW LONG DO YOU THINK IT'S BEEN
SINCE I HAD A PAY CHEQUE?
TAKE A GUESS!
I HAVE NO --
TAKE A GUESS!!
SEVEN --
NEVER HAD A PAY CHEQUE!
NEVER, EVER!
THEY GAVE ME THE UNIFORM.
THEY SAID, "HERE, TRY IT
OUT FOR A MONTH."
THEN THEY SAID,
"SEE YOU LATER, BUD."
OH, YEAH.
YOU MEAN YOU'VE BEEN WORKING
FOR FREE HERE FOR 18 YEARS?
THAT'S RIGHT, RED.
AND WHY DO YOU THINK I
WOULD'VE DONE THAT,
Mr SMARTY PANTS?
LACK OF ALTERN --
BECAUSE I CARE!
BECAUSE I CARE ABOUT
PEOPLE LIKE YOU,
ABOUT THE ANIMALS,
ABOUT THOSE THINGS
THAT BURN OUT THERE.
I'VE GIVEN MY LIFE
FOR YOUR SAFETY.
AND ALL I ASK FOR IS SOME
LOUSY WATER SPRINKLERS,
AND ALL YOU TELL ME IS NO.
NO, NO, NO.
NO, I'M JUST SAYING
THIS IS NOT --
[weeping]
GORD, GORD,
I WANT YOU TO COME
BACK WITH ME NOW,
AND I WANT YOU TO BE WITH
PEOPLE FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
NO, I CAN'T, RED.
I'M SORRY, I CAN'T.
IT'S COMING INTO
THE DRY SEASON,
AND I'VE GOT A LOT
OF CANNED CORN LEFT.
ONLY A FEW YEARS LEFT
BEFORE IT'S EXPIRING.
NO, AS MUCH AS I'D LIKE
TO GO WITH YOU, I CAN'T.
I CAN'T LEAVE THE TOWER,
NOT FOR ANYTHING.
NOT FOR YOU,
NOT FOR ANYONE.
REALLY? 'CAUSE BERNICE HAS
LINED UP A GIRL SHE'D
LIKE YOU TO MEET.
REALLY?
WHAT'S SHE LIKE?
WELL, SHE'S REAL.
GOOD ENOUGH.
I KNOW IF ANY OF YOU
GUYS ARE LIKE ME,
WHEN YOU WERE A KID,
YOU JUST DREAMED ABOUT DRIVING
A DUMP TRUCK, DIDN'T YOU, EH?
AND A LOT OF YOU GUYS,
AS YOU GOT OLDER,
YOU HAD TO ABANDON YOUR
CHILDHOOD DREAMS,
AND THE REST OF YOU
ARE BACHELORS.
SO I THOUGHT, AS A PUBLIC
SERVICE THIS WEEK,
I WOULD SHOW YOU HOW TO
TURN AN ORDINARY CAR
INTO A DUMP TRUCK.
THIS CAR ACTUALLY HAS TWO
THINGS THAT MAKE IT THE
PERFECT DUMP TRUCK...
FRONT-WHEEL DRIVE AND
ABSOLUTELY NO RE-SALE VALUE.
I'LL EXPLAIN ABOUT THE
FRONT-WHEEL DRIVE IN A MINUTE,
BUT FIRST OF ALL, I'VE GOT TO
CUSTOMIZE THE BODY A LITTLE BIT.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, UH, HERE'S THE
BEAUTY OF THE CREATIVE PROCESS.
I NEED SOMETHING TO
USE AS A DIVIDER
BETWEEN THE DRIVER AND THE LOAD
THAT I'LL BE DUMPING.
NOW, I'M NOT JUST GOING TO HEAD
DOWN TO THE AUTO SUPPLY STORE
WITH A CHEQUEBOOK
'CAUSE THE BANK MANAGER WARNED
ME ABOUT DOING THAT AGAIN.
NO, I'M GONNA SEARCH FOR
SOMETHING WE CAN USE OUT OF OUR
EXISTING INVENTORY,
LIKE, SAY, THIS PERFECTLY
GOOD TRUNK LID.
ALL RIGHT, UH --
OKAY, YOU WANNA WEAR THE
WELDING GOGGLES WHEN YOU
DO THAT KIND OF WORK.
BERNICE MUST'VE PUT MINE
SOMEWHERE WHERE I
CAN'T FIND 'EM.
SHE DOESN'T LIKE
ME WELDING,
EVER SINCE WE
LOST THE GARAGE.
ANYWAY, NOW WE'RE READY TO
ACTUALLY INSTALL THE
DUMPING MECHANISM,
AND FOR THAT, YOU'VE GOTTA PUT
SOME STUFF ON THE FRONT WHEELS.
UH, GET YOURSELF A COUPLE
OF EXTRA RIMS LIKE THIS,
AND THEN YOU WANNA ATTACH SOME
HEAVY PIPE IN A CRISS-CROSS
ON THE OUTSIDE EDGE.
JUST WELD THAT ON THERE TOO.
SURE WISH I HAD
THOSE GOGGLES.
SEE NOW, THESE SPECIAL WHEELS,
ONCE I LINE THEM UP WITH A
COUPLE OF STEPLADDERS,
THEY BECOME MY
DUMPING MECHANISM.
'CAUSE WHEN I
THROW HER IN DRIVE,
THE SPECIAL WHEELS
CLIMB THE LADDER, SEE?
THAT'S WHY THE CAR HAD TO BE
FRONT-WHEEL DRIVE.
I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE THINKING.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
AND NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
IT'S TIME TO DUMP.
I WANNA TALK TO YOU OLDER
GUYS WHO MAYBE FEEL BAD
BECAUSE YOU DON'T HAVE
A LOT OF FANCY THINGS,
NO BIG MANSION ON THE HILL;
NO FANCY SIX-FIGURE LUXURY CAR;
NO SHIRTS WITH A COLLAR.
YOU KNOW, WHEN PEOPLE SPEND A
LOT OF MONEY ON SOMETHING,
THEY CALL THAT
CONSPICUOUS CONSUMPTION.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
FIRST OF ALL, CONSUMPTION,
I BELIEVE, IS A DISEASE
THAT TOOK MY GREAT-GRANDMOTHER
OUT OF TOWN.
AND THE LAST THING I WOULD WANT
TO BE IS CONSPICUOUS.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S THE REASON
I DRESS LIKE THIS
RATHER THAN LIKE LIBERACE.
AND THERE'S OTHER
REASONS TOO.
BUT TO ME, THE SIGN OF WEALTH IS
NOT HOW MUCH MONEY YOU SPEND,
IT'S HOW MUCH
MONEY YOU WASTE.
BECAUSE, LIKE, A BIG HOUSE
OR A FANCY CAR OR EVEN ART,
WELL, THAT HAS VALUE.
THAT'S WORTH SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S
AN INVESTMENT.
THAT'S FOR COWARDS!
YOUR REAL HIGH-ROLLER
BUYS CRAP.
SO WHEN SOMEBODY TELLS
YOU ABOUT SOME GUY
WITH A ROLLS ROYCE AND A
12-BEDROOM PALACE, OR SOMETHING,
YOU JUST SHOW HIM YOUR GARDEN
WEASEL AND YOUR THIGH-MASTER
AND YOUR STAR TREK PLATES.
AND YOU CAN JUST SAY,
"YEAH, THEY'RE NOT
WORTH ANYTHING,
"BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
"I DON'T CARE."
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[phone ringing]
HELLO, POSSUM LAKE AUTO CLUB.
YEAH.
WELL, WHAT'S IT DOING?
YOU PUT GAS IN IT?
HOLY COW, THAT'S A
LOT OF GAS!
YEAH, THAT COULD
CATCH ON FI --
IT HAS?
OKAY, YOU BETTER CALL A
FIRE TRUCK BECAUSE YOU --
IT IS A FIRE TRUCK?
OKAY, WELL, SOMEONE WILL
BE RIGHT OVER, OKAY.
JUNIOR SINGLETON
NEEDS A SERVICE CALL.
SAYS THE FIRE TRUCK'S
ON FIRE AGAIN.
WELL, HOW DOES THAT
AFFECT US, DALTON?
WE'RE AN AUTO CLUB.
WELL, JUNIOR SAYS IT'S
AN IGNITION PROBLEM.
WELL, I'M NOT
GOING OVER THERE.
I'VE BEEN UP ALL NIGHT
DOING SERVICE CALLS,
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
WELL, SOMEBODY BETTER
GO OVER THERE.
WELL, SOMEBODY'S
GONNA GO OVER THERE.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
I'LL GET
WINSTON TO GO.
ALL RIGHT.
WE GOTTA RE-THINK THIS
WHOLE AUTO CLUB.
FIRST OF ALL,
24 HOURS A DAY?
[phone ringing]]
THAT'S TOO MANY HOURS
IN TOO MANY DAYS.
AND THEN WE GOT
THE ACTUAL VEHICLES.
[phone ringing]]
THE MEMBERS, THEY ALL
GOT CRAP VEHICLES.
YOU GOTTA HAVE
A GOOD VEHICLE,
AND YOU GOTTA
MAINTAIN IT PROPERLY;
OTHERWISE,
YOU'RE NOT --
AND FIVE BUCKS
A MONTH!
HELLO?
WHERE'D WE COME UP
WITH FIVE BUCKS?
EXCUSE ME, Mr GREEN.
NOT RIGHT NOW,
MIKE, OKAY?
SOMEONE'S EXPECTING YOU.
WELL, TOUGH BEANS!
I'M NOT GONNA LET THEM
RATTLE MY CHAIN.
I'M TAKING THE DAY OFF.
TELL 'EM I'M TAKING THE DAY OFF.
OKAY.
NO, NO,
WAIT A MINUTE.
TELL 'EM I'LL COME
OVER THERE WHEN I'M
GOOD AND READY.
AND MEANWHILE, WHY DON'T
THEY GO SUCK EGGS!
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
THEY HUNG UP.
DOESN'T IT FEEL GOOD TO
STAND UP FOR YOURSELF
ONCE IN AWHILE?
WELL, YOU BETTER ENJOY
IT WHILE YOU CAN.
OH, YEAH?
WHO WAS THAT?
IT WAS YOUR WIFE.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO PICK
HER UP AT THE GROCERY STORE.
Red: WELL, WE HAD A BIG
COOKOUT PLANNED OUT
BEHIND THE LODGE,
MIKE AND DALTON AND MYSELF.
MAKING A LITTLE
CAMPFIRE AREA THERE,
AND WE NEEDED SOME WOOD,
SO WE HAD A BUNCH OF AXES.
CAREFUL NOW.
CAREFUL.
OH!
HERE'S A SAFETY --
OH.
NOT SURE WHAT KIND OF WOOD THA
IS OR WHAT KIND OF AXE THAT IS
ALL RIGHT, MIKE,
YOU GIVE HER A GO.
STAND BACK, DALTON.
CAN'T BE TOO
CAREFUL AROUND MIKE.
YEAH, IT WENT OVER
IN THE OTHER AREA.
LOOK ON THE GROUND.
IT SHOULD BE --
THERE IT IS.
NOT SURE HOW WE'RE GONNA
GET THAT, UH, TREE DOWN.
CAN'T HAVE A FIRE WITHOUT WOOD
OKAY, DALTON,
YOU GIVE HER A GO.
HE'S A LITTLE SHAKY.
DALTON, NO, DON'T!
OKAY, WELL, THERE'S OUR WOOD.
OKAY, NOW, WE HAD
ALL THE VEGETABLES,
AND MIKE WAS
BRINGING THE MEAT.
BOY, THERE'S ENOUGH
FOR ALL OF US THERE.
THERE'S NOTHING
LIKE FRESH PORK, IS THERE?
WE HAD THE CORN AND THE
POTATOES AND THE BEANS
AND EVERYTHING.
WE'RE WONDERING HOW
WE'RE GONNA COOK THIS.
YOU GOTTA BE CREATIVE,
AND THESE WERE CRUHES
FROM OUR EARLIER ADVENTURE.
YOU STICK THEM IN THE GROUND,
ONE ON EACH SIDE OF THE
CAMPFIRE.
AND THEN WHAT YOU DO IS YOU RU
A HOCKEY STICK RIGHT THROUGH -
SEE THAT'S --
AND THEN TO KEEP HER WARM,
YOU PUT HER ON TOP, SEE.
SO ALL WE GOTTA DO NOW, OF
COURSE, IS, UH --
WHAT'VE YOU GOT THERE, MIKE?
AND APPLE FOR US
FOR THE PIG'S MOUTH.
OH, OKAY, OKAY, GREAT.
SO WE'RE ALL SET.
OKAY, MIKE, GOOD IDEA.
YOU BROUGHT THE PIG,
SO AWAY YOU GO.
AWAY YOU GO.
OH, YEAH.
WE CAN'T COOK HIM ALIVE, MIKE
AWAY YOU GO.
COME ON, AWAY YOU GO.
GO ON.
OH, FOR GOSH SAKE.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, DALTON,
YOU GET IT.
COME ON, DALTON,
JUST GIVE IT A QUICK ONE,
AND IT'S OVER WITH.
COME ON.
AWAY YOU GO.
COME ON, YOU CAN DO IT.
YOU CAN DO IT.
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES.
WHAT? OH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
BOY, I TELL YOU,
IT ALL WORKED OUT IN THE END.
IT WAS A GREAT DAY,
AND WHAT A GREAT MEAL WE HAD.
JUST SOMETHING ABOUT THE
COMRADERIE OF THE WHOLE DEAL.
EVERYBODY HAD A GOOD MEAL.
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING.
JOINING ME TODAY
IS DALTON HUMPHREY.
WHAT CAN I
DO FOR YOU, DALTON?
WELL, RED, I WAS HOPING
YOU COULD UNJAM THIS
GUM BALL MACHINE.
BOY, I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
HAD GUM BALLS AT THE
EVERYTHING STORE.
NO, NO, I DON'T.
NO, THIS IS FROM
THE MALL.
YEP, MY QUARTER
GOT STUCK IN IT.
TRYING TO GET A GUM BALL
OUT, THE MACHINE JAMMED.
NOW I GOT NO GUM BALL;
I GOT NO QUARTER.
WELL, PUT HER UP ON THE BENCH.
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
YOU GOT
YOUR, UH --
ALMOST LOOKS LIKE YOU GOT
YOUR THUMB CAUGHT IN
THERE, DALTON.
MAYBE.
WELL, I CAN SEE
THE COIN.
DON'T YOU JUST WANNA SMASH
IT IN A MILLION PIECES?
THIS MIGHT JUST --
THERE WE GO.
GOT IT.
THAT'S NOT A QUARTER.
THAT'S A PENNY!
WELL, WILL YOU LOOK
AT THAT, HUH?
THAT'S HOW
YOU WRECKED IT.
YOU JAMMED A PENNY IN THERE
BECAUSE YOU'RE TOO CHEAP
TO PUT A QUARTER IN.
HOLY MACKEREL.
YOU KNOW WHAT
MUST'VE HAPPENED?
I MUST'VE ACCIDENTALLY
PUT A PENNY IN,
WHEN I WAS GOING
FOR A QUARTER.
OH, OH, YEAH.
HERE'S THE QUARTER
RIGHT HERE.
THAT'S WHAT MUST'VE HAPPENED.
I USED THE WRONG COIN.
I'M GONNA USE IT TO GET
YOUR THUMB OUTTA
THERE, DALTON.
EASY, EASY, YEP.
OKAY, YEP, YEP, YEP.
OH, YEAH,
SHE'S WORKING GREAT.
THAT'S MY GUM!
OH, SORRY.
WELL, OKAY.
WE'RE HAVING
A DISAGREEMENT ABOUT
THE WHOLE AUTO CLUB.
BOY, THE VAN BREAKS DOWN,
HE CALLS THE AUTO CLUB,
WHICH HE'S
THE BOSS OF,
AND THEN HE MAKES US PUSH
THE VAN ALL THE WAY BACK
INTO TOWN AGAIN.
WELL, I'M NOT JUST
THE AUTO CLUB PRESIDENT,
I'M ALSO A CLIENT.
[laughter and applause]
YEAH, BUT THAT'S
THE CUSTOMER TAKING
ADVANTAGE OF THE MERCHANT,
WHICH IS A
COMPLETE REVERSAL OF
THE ENTREPRENEURIAL SPIRIT.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY WE
NEED AN AUTO CLUB ANYWAY.
I MEAN, WHEN MY
CAR DOESN'T GO,
I JUST HOT WIRE
ANOTHER ONE.
YES, MIKE,
BUT FOR THOSE OF US
WHO DON'T ENJOY
PRISON FOOD,
I THINK WE MAYBE HAVE TO
COME UP WITH A BETTER
SOLUTION, GUYS.
WELL, I THINK WE SHOULD
JUST ABANDON THE
AUTO CLUB.
OH, NO REFUNDS,
THOUGH.
I'M NOT GIVING PEOPLE
THEIR MONEY BACK.
OH, NO, WE'LL
JUST TELL 'EM
TO GET JUMPER CABLES
AND A CAN OF GAS
AND LET 'EM SOLVE THEIR
OWN DARN PROBLEMS.
YEAH, THEY CAN HELP
ONE ANOTHER OUT.
EXACTLY.
I MEAN, GEESH,
ON ANY GIVEN DAY,
SURELY THERE'S ONE CAR
AROUND HERE THAT WORKS.
THAT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
I MEAN, CAN YOU IMAGINE A WORLD
WHERE PEOPLE HELP ONE ANOTHER
WITHOUT CHARGE OF MONEY?
THAT ONLY HAPPENS
IN DISASTER MOVIES.
WELL, I DON'T THINK
WE COULD MAKE THAT
BIG A DISASTER.
WELL, THE SHOW'S
GETTING THERE.
[possum squealing]
OH, MEETING TIME.
LET'S GO, GUYS.
OKAY, YOU GUYS GO --
I'LL BE DOWN IN A SEC.
UM, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
UM, SORRY I DIDN'T PICK YOU UP
AT THE GROCERY STORE THERE.
WE'RE HAVING A PROBLEM
WITH THE PHONES.
APPARENTLY THERE'S
A LITTLE PHRASE
THAT'S KIND OF A RANDOM --
JUST COMES ONTO THE LINE.
APPARENTLY -- THEY TELL ME IT'S
THE DIGITAL CONVERGENCE
TO AN ANALOGUE SOURCE
ON A ROTARY PHONE,
SO IT'S POSSIBLE THAT YOU
MIGHT'VE HEARD
WHAT YOU THOUGHT WAS ME SAYING,
"GO SUCK EGGS."
SO -- BUT I --
BUT I'VE LOOKED INTO IT,
AND -- AND I FOUND THE PROBLEM.
AND IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
I PROMISE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
OKAY, EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, GUYS.
COME ON.
SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY DOWN.
ALL RISE!
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
BUT IF YOUR TIRE NEEDS A CHANGE,
YOU CAN DO IT YOURSELF.
AMEN!