STARRING THE OLD RED GREEN.
HERE HE IS, POSSUM LODGE'S
SELF-MADE MAN
WITH NO WARRANTY --
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU! THANK YOU VERY MUCH!
APPRECIATE IT -- THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
DID YOU HURT YOUR NECK
OR DID YOU GO
TO DON CHERRY'S TAILOR?
I HAD
AN ACCIDENT ON MY BIKE.
I WAS RIDING DOWN HOLLER HILL.
JUNIOR SINGLETON
PULLED HIS VEGA OVER
TO ANSWER A CALL OF NATURE.
NATURE MUST HAVE BEEN YELLING,
'CAUSE HE DIDN'T SEE ME.
I WENT WHAM! INTO HIS DOOR!
MY INSURANCE AGENCY SAYS
I SHOULD TAKE LEGAL ACTION.
SO I'M GONNA SUE
JUNIOR SINGLETON
FOR EVERYTHING HE'S WORTH!
$50,000!
HAROLD, THAT'S EVERYTHING
HE'S WORTH... PLUS $50,000!
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MAIN MESSAGE BEING,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
FOR THOSE AT HOME ADJUSTING
THE SOUND ON YOUR T.V.,
YOU HEARD RIGHT.
HAROLD IS SUING
JUNIOR SINGLETON FOR $50,000.
HOPE YOU HAVEN'T
HIRED A LAWYER.
HA-HA! NO!
I'M REPRESENTING MYSELF.
I DON'T HAVE A LAW DEGREE
BUT I'VE READ
EVERY JOHN GRISHAM NOVEL
SO I'LL BE OK.
ABRAHAM LINCOLN SAID
PEOPLE WHO ACT
AS THEIR OWN LAWYER
HAVE A FOOL FOR A LAWYER
AND AN ASS FOR A CLIENT.
OUR COUNTRY'S ONLY AS STRONG
AS ITS LEGAL SYSTEM.
IT'S LIKE A MUSCLE.
IF YOU DON'T USE IT,
IT GETS OUT OF SHAPE.
WHEN YOU USE IT,
YOU GET THIS HUMONGOUS CRAMP.
YOU SPEND GYM CLASS
HUDDLED AROUND THE TOILET.
(Audience laughing)
I DON'T KNOW WHY
YOU'RE SUING JUNIOR.
HE DOESN'T HAVE MONEY.
I'LL PUT A LIEN ON HIS HOUSE.
ANY MORE "LEAN"
AND SHE'LL FALL OVER.
I'M PROVING
TO THE PEOPLE OF POSSUM LAKE
THAT YOU CAN SETTLE DISPUTES
WITHOUT THROWING VEGETABLES
OR DEFLATING TIRES
OR LEAVING FLAMING BAGS
OF MANURE ON PORCHES.
I SAID I WAS SORRY.
WRECKED MY BEST SHOES.
SUE ME!
WAHAHH! I WILL!
(Red): HERE THEY ARE.
EACH HAS A HALF
OF MOOSE THOMPSON'S HALTER TOP.
OH, BOY... OH, MAN.
THEY'RE DOING GLIDING.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU HAD
THOSE GLIDERS?
HAD A LOT OF FUN... OH!
(Laughing)
THE FUN YOU CAN HAVE...
OH, BY GOLLY.
YEAH, IT'S SO SIMPLE,
SOMETIMES,
THE MOST ENJOYABLE
THINGS IN LIFE.
FUN, FUN, FUN, EH? YEAH!
(Laughing)
BOY, I'M ENJOYING THIS.
THIS IS A STEP UP.
THESE ARE THE KIND,
YOU WIND UP THE PROP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GOT THE ELASTIC THERE.
I THOUGHT THIS WAS
HIGH-TECH STUFF.
ELECTRIC DRILL, THERE,
AND HE'S...
HE'S REALLY BEEN WORKING OUT.
EITHER THAT, OR THE BLADE
IS MADE OF SOLDER, PERHAPS.
THAT'S GONNA WORK GREAT,
ISN'T IT, EH?
GONNA WORK GREAT.
WE'LL CHECK ON THEM LATER
AFTER THEY SMARTEN UP!
IF YOU FIND YOURSELF
LOOKIN' FOR A FAMILY PET
I'D SAY
GET YOURSELF A HOG
THEY'RE SMART AND FRIENDLY
AND THEY WON'T RUN AWAY
AND THEY'RE EASIER TO TRAIN
THAN A DOG
AND WHEN THE TIME COMES
WHEN A DOG PASSES ON
YOU'LL FIND
YOUR HEART IS ACHIN'
BUT THE PAIN OF LOSIN'
A HOG IS EASED
BY THE BONUS
OF ALL THAT BACON
(Imitating
pig squealing)
WELCOME TO THE WORD GAME!
TONIGHT'S PRIZE IS FROM
THE WE-POLL-IT
TELEPHONE SOLICITATION COMPANY
WHO WILL PHONE YOU
AT DINNERTIME
TO ASK YOU QUESTIONS.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MIKE HAMAR
TO SAY THIS WORD.
"BED".
(Laughing)
"BED."
(Audience laughing)
ALL RIGHT, UH...
MIKE.
AT NIGHT, YOU SLEEP IN A...
... CELL.
BUT YOU LIE THERE IN A...
... COLD SWEAT.
YOU LIE ON A...
... COT.
BUNK...
CEMENT FLOOR.
YOUR MATTRESS FITS ON
A QUEEN-SIZED...
... CELL-MATE.
(Audience laughing)
AFTER YOU MADE PAROLE,
YOU SLEPT IN
A WARM, DRY...
... DUMPSTER.
OK, NO, ALL RIGHT,
IF YOU'D GONE HOME,
YOUR MOM WOULD LET YOU SLEEP
INOUR...
... DUMPSTER.
WE'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME.
OK, THERE'S AN
EXPRESSION, OK?
YOU MADE
YOUR SOMETHING.
NOW YOU HAVE TO
LAY IN IT.
I GET IT -- "GETAWAY"!
OK, YOU TRIED YOUR GETAWAY BUT
THE ESCAPE ROUTE WAS BLOCKED
SO YOU HID
UNDER...
... HER BED.
YEAH!
(Ringing bell)
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
I'LL TALK ABOUT
WINTERIZING YOUR VEHICLE.
IF YOU'RE ANYTHING LIKE ME --
AND IF YOU WATCH THIS SHOW,
YOU ARE --
YOUR VEHICLE IS SUFFERING
FROM WHAT I CALL
RECEDING TREAD-LINE.
(Audience laughing)
MALE-PATTERN TIRE WEAR.
WE GOT SPACE-AGE TECHNOLOGY,
PUT A MAN ON THE MOON.
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO GET
A FEW HUNDRED THOUSAND MILES
OUT OF A TIRE.
I SAY YOU CAN -- LOOK AT THIS.
WE'RE NOT OUT OF RUBBER.
WE'RE JUST OUT OF TREAD.
BEING A RETREAD MYSELF,
I SAY LET'S CUT OURSELVES
A NEW GROOVE.
GET YOURSELF ONE OF THEM
AUTOMOTIVE MAGAZINES,
PICK OUT A TREAD PATTERN
THAT SUITS YOUR LIFESTYLE.
THEN PLUG IN YOUR ROUTER
AND START ROUTIN'.
I GET MY KICKS ON "ROUT" 66.
(Coughing)
MAN! SMELLS LIKE I DROVE
THE INDY 500
WITH THE EMERGENCY BRAKE ON.
I WAS HAVING SOME PROBLEMS
FOLLOWING THE PATTERN.
HARDER THAN
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
I'VE DONE
A TOTAL RE-THINK ON 'ER.
(Banging)
WHAT I'VE GOT NOW
IS SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE THIS.
PERSONALIZED SNOW TIRES.
SEE THAT?
NOT JUST A FASHION STATEMENT.
IT ACTUALLY PROVES
WHERE YOU WERE,
IF THE COPS SHOULD ASK.
NOT JUST A TIRE --
IT'S AN ALIBI...
HOPEFULLY, AN AIRTIGHT ALIBI.
OR MAYBE YOU'RE THE KIND
OF PERSON WHO GETS LOST.
HOW ABOUT THIS UNIT?
GOT ARROWS CARVED INTO 'ER.
YOU MOUNT THESE
SO THE ARROWS ARE BACKWARDS.
NO MATTER WHERE YOU GO,
YOU'LL FIND YOUR WAY HOME.
MAYBE YOU GOT A GIRLFRIEND
YOU'RE TRYING TO IMPRESS.
WHO ISN'T, HUH?
EVEN SOME OF YOU MARRIED GUYS.
HOW ABOUT THIS? "I LOVE TRUDY".
ISN'T THAT BEAUTIFUL?
IF YOU BREAK UP WITH TRUDY,
JUST PEEL RUBBER
FOR A FEW MILES.
YOU'LL ERASE HER OFF
YOUR RADIALS AND YOUR LIFE.
HERE'S SOMETHING SPECIAL
I'M WORKING ON FOR MY WIFE.
A LITTLE SURPRISE FOR HER.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I'M GONNA DOT THAT "I".
I'LL USE THAT ONE AS A SPARE.
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
THE BIGGEST PROBLEM
YOU KIDS GOT
IS "WHO AM I GONNA ASK
FOR ADVICE?"
CAN'T GO TO YOUR DAD --
HE BOTCHES EVERYTHING.
HE BOUGHT THAT PACER, SAID
THAT WAS THE CAR OF THE FUTURE.
YOUR MOM'S TOO NICE.
SHE'LL TELL YOU
EXACTLY WHAT YOU WANT TO HEAR.
MAYBE YOU GOT AN OLDER BROTHER,
BUT HE'S SPENT FIVE YEARS
ON THE COUCH,
SO HE HAS A DIFFERENT AGENDA.
IF YOU ASK ME,
YOU WANT THE RELATIVE
THAT DRIVES YOUR PARENTS CRAZY.
TELL YOU SOMETHING.
NINE TIMES OUT OF 10,
IT'S AN UNCLE.
UNCLES GIVE GREAT ADVICE.
GO FIND THAT UNCLE, SEE?
HE PROBABLY THINKS
YOU'RE BEING RAISED BY MORONS
SO HE'S MOTIVATED
TO GIVE YOU GREAT ADVICE
AND HE WANTS YOU TO DO IT WELL.
NOT ONLY WILL HE GET CREDIT
FOR DOING SOMETHING GOOD,
HE'LL DRIVE YOUR PARENTS CRAZY.
YOU SEEK OUT THAT UNCLE.
HE'S SMARTER THAN HE LOOKS.
HE'S GOTTA BE.
YES, YOU CAN LEAVE THE ROOM.
PUT YOUR
ARM DOWN.
WAHHHH!
WHAT A MESS THIS GUY'S CREATED.
HE'S SUING JUNIOR FOR $50,000.
$75,000! EVER SINCE
THE ACCIDENT,
MY ARM'S BEEN TINGLY.
MY UPPER BODY STRENGTH
ISN'T WHAT IT USED TO BE.
IT WENT UP?
MAN!
JUNIOR'S SUING BUSTER,
WHO HAD THE PARTY,
HEREINAFTER REFERRED TO
AS THE PARTY OF THE FIRST PART.
BUSTER IS SUING
"HUMPHREY'S EVERYTHING STORE"
FOR SELLING HIM THE COFFEE
THAT CAUSED JUNIOR
TO HAVE TO RELIEVE HIMSELF
AND CAUSED THE ACCIDENT,
HEREINAFTER REFERRED TO
AS WHAT THAT IDIOT HAROLD DID.
I DON'T THINK EVERYBODY
SHOULD BE MAD AT ME.
THEY'RE NOT MAD AT YOU.
THEY'RE GONNA SUE EVERYBODY
AND USE YOU AS THEIR LAWYER.
REALLY? OH, THAT'S EXCELLENT!
I'D NEED A RETAINER.
YOU'RE WEARING
A RETAINER.
RIGHT, OK... I'M GONNA NEED
A LEGAL POSITION ON THIS.
I'M ADVISING EVERYBODY
TO PLEAD INSANITY.
THAT CAN BE DIFFICULT
TO SUBSTANTIATE.
PICKING YOU AS A LAWYER
IS ALL THE PROOF THEY NEED.
(Laughing)
WHOA! OH!
HOLY MACKEREL!
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE FINE.
OK.
(Laughing)
WELCOME TO "AUTO BIOGRAPHY",
WHERE MEMBERS OF POSSUM LODGE
TALK ABOUT REMEMBRANCES
OF CARS GONE BY.
GOT DOUGIE FRANKLIN HERE.
HOW MANY VEHICLES
HAVE YOU OWNED?
13, 14...
100.
THAT'S QUITE A FLEET.
YOU HAVE A FAVOURITE
OUT OF THAT PACK?
I THINK MY FAVOURITE
WOULD HAVE TO BE
MY METAL-FLAKE BLUE
1968 DODGE CHARGER.
METAL-FLAKE BLUE EXTERIOR...
METAL-FLAKE BLUE INTERIOR...
METAL-FLAKE BLUE
TINTED WINDOWS.
WAS A BEAUTIFUL THING
TO BEHOLD.
WHEN YOU PUT YOUR PEDAL
TO THE METAL,
IT WOULD SNAP YOUR NECK
LIKE A TWIG
AND YOUR HAIR WOULD END UP
IN THE BACK!
(Laughing)
THAT'S GOTTA REDUCE
THE RESALE VALUE.
WAHHH... NOTHIN'.
YOU COULD BE DRIVIN' DOWN
THE MAIN STREET ON A GOOD NIGHT
AND THAT ENGINE, SHE'D...
SHE'D JUST BE HUMMIN'.
(Burbling)
(Sputtering)
RACING CAM.
YEAH.
OH, BOY.
THEN I'D DO THAT THING.
I'D PUT ONE FOOT ON THE BRAKE
AND THE OTHER ONE
ON THE ACCELERATOR...
THOSE BACK TIRES
WOULD BE SCREAMIN'!
WHOO-HOO! WHOO-HOO!
THEN I'D TAKE MY FOOT
OFF THE BRAKE
AND SHE'D... WHOA!
FIRST GEAR!
(Screaming)
SECOND GEAR!
THEN I'D... LOOK OUT!
PEDESTRIANS!
(Screaming)
THEN I'D HIT THE BRAKE!
(Applause)
(Siren)
POSSUM 911 --
HOW CAN WE HELP YOU?
I'VE FALLEN AND I CAN'T GET UP!
THAT YOU,
DALTON?
IT'S ME, DALTON HUMPHREY.
ANY BROKEN
BONES?
CAN YOU GET TO A PHONE?
(Audience laughing)
(Moaning)
I'M FEELING FAINT.
I... I CAN'T BREATHE!
I GOT A PIANO ON MY CHEST!
WELL, THERE'S
YOUR PROBLEM.
YEAH, TRY AN ACCORDION ON
YOUR CHEST -- THEY'RE LIGHTER.
NO, RED, MY WIFE
WAS GONNA HIRE MOVERS
TO DRAG THE PIANO UPSTAIRS,
AND, YOU KNOW...
I DON'T PAY PEOPLE
TO MOVE FURNITURE.
LET ME GUESS --
YOUR WIFE WENT OUT,
YOU FIGURED YOU COULD MOVE
THE PIANO YOURSELF.
WELL, YEAH... UGH!
OHHHH! I GOT IT
AS FAR AS THE FIRST LANDING.
IT DIDN'T FIT
AROUND THE CORNER.
SORT OF LOST MY MOMENTUM AND...
OOOH! AND, UH...
WELL, WE CAME BACK DOWN AGAIN.
NOW I'M PINNED AND
I CAN'T REACH THE PHONE BOOK.
WE GOT A PHONE
BOOK HERE.
I COULD LOOK
SOMETHING UP.
I COULD PHONE
SOMEBODY FOR YOU.
OH, THANKS, HAROLD.
CALL FIVE DIFFERENT PIANO
MOVERS AND GET ESTIMATES.
AND THEN CALL BACK
THE SECOND CHEAPEST
AND SAY THE CHEAPEST
WILL DO IT FOR LESS.
"CAN YOU BEAT HIS PRICE?"
THEN CALL THE CHEAPEST AND SAY
"CAN YOU GIVE ME A BREAK?"
AND KEEP ARGUING 'EM DOWN.
THEN TELL THE CHEAPEST
TO RUSH OVER
AND GET THIS PIANO
OFF MY CHEST!
YOU SHOULD CALL AN AMBULANCE
OR THE FIRE DEPARTMENT!
THE FIRE DEPARTMENT -- THEY'RE
BIG FELLAS, AREN'T THEY?
PRETTY BIG,
SOME OF THEM.
AND I PAY TAXES --
THEY'LL MOVE THIS FOR NOTHIN'!
(Red): MEANWHILE, THE BOYS
ARE STILL WINDING THEIR...
... ELASTICS.
BILL LIKES TO CRANK 'ER UP.
(Laughing)
OH, BILL.
COME ON, BILL, COME ON.
COME ON!
YOU'LL GO BLIND.
WHAT THE HECK...?
OH, YEAH, THAT WILL WORK GREAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, BILL?
I WOULD SUGGEST
JUST A COUPLE MORE.
ONE MORE? ALL RIGHT.
JUST ONE MORE -- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN ALWAYS GET ONE MORE.
(Laughing)
BOY, THERE'S A SURPRISE.
NOW... OH! THAT'S NICE.
YOU TAKE YOUR FRIEND'S --
BEAUTIFUL.
HE'S GONNA CRANK THAT UP.
NOW HE'S PREPARED
TO LAUNCH THAT.
THESE THINGS ARE SO REALISTIC.
SETS 'ER DOWN AND...
THE FLIGHT'S ALREADY DELAYED.
IT'S SO REALISTIC.
OH, YOU'RE CLEARED
FOR TAKE-OFF!
YOU CAN SHAVE WITH THAT.
OH, HAROLD! OH, HAROLD!
OH, BOY! OH, BOY!
EASY, BOYS, EASY!
EASY, EASY, EASY, EASY!
SEE WHAT HAPPENS NOW?
SOME OF THESE MEN, THEY PANIC.
COME ON, THAT'S NOT FAIR.
OHHHH!
YOU KILLED-- UH-OH!
UH-OH!
REVENGE IS A DARK THING.
SUDDENLY, GLIDERS ARE COMING
FROM EVERYWHERE.
I DON'T LIKE THE LOOK OF THIS.
I DON'T LIKE THE FEEL OF THIS.
I'M GLAD I'M NOT THERE.
GUYS? GUYS, YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHAT'S THAT? WHAT IS IT?
(Bill): WHOA!!
(Red): SUDDENLY
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF SOME HORROR MOVIE
OR SOMETHING, AREN'T WE?
SHH!
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
OH, THEY'RE GONNA ESCAPE!
THEY'RE FOLLOWING YOU!
RUN LIKE THE WIND!
RUN! OH, BY GOLLY!
WHOA!!
(Gliders squeaking)
HOPE THEY DON'T HAVE
A BALSA ALLERGY.
GET IN! CLOSE THAT DOOR!
(Gliders squeaking)
OH, THAT WILL HELP --
THE WIPERS.
BILL, WHERE ARE YOU GONNA GO?
BILL'S GOING INTO THE BARN!
THEY'RE STILL AFTER HIM!
MY GOSH!
(Gliders squeaking)
(Red): THIS IS SCARY.
WHOA! OHHHH!
(Red): OH!
(Screaming)
(Red): OHHH...
FINALLY, IT'S OVER.
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT.
THE GLIDERS HAVE ALL SPENT
THEIR ELASTICS.
BILL OK IN THE BARN?
OHHHH!
CAREFUL, HAROLD, CAREFUL!
CAREFUL, CAREFUL!
OHHH! AHHHH! OHHHH!
OHHH...
OH, NO, HE'S FINE.
SPEAKING OF VOODOO,
HERE'S DOLLS
MADE BY A FRIEND
IN LONDON, ONTARIO.
"A POEM BY
ROBERT FROST BITE GREEN.
"WHEN THE WIND WORKS
AGAINST US IN THE DARK
"AND PELTS WITH SNOW
"THE LOWLY CHAMBER WINDOW
ON THE EAST,
"AND WHISPERS WITH
A SORT OF STIFLED BARK,
"'HEY, GENIUS,
ARE YOU STILL GLAD
"'YOU DIDN'T BUY
THAT CONDO IN PORT CHARLOTTE?'"
EVER SINCE HAROLD
HAD HIS BIKE ACCIDENT--
ARE YOU AUDITIONING
FOR "THE MUMMY'S CURSE"?
I WENT TO THE TOWN HALL
TO FILL OUT THE WRIT
OF HABEUS CORPUS
AGAINST JUNIOR SINGLETON.
I TRIPPED GOING UP THE STAIRS.
ON THE WAY DOWN,
I GOT MY FEET CAUGHT
IN THE BANDAGE
MY MOM PUT AROUND MY LEG.
I'M SUING THE TOWNSHIP
FOR $500,000
AND MY MOM FOR $1 MILLION!
HI, MOM.
THAT FIGURES --
EVERYBODY'S SUING EVERYBODY.
MOOSE THOMPSON IS SUING
STINKY PETERSON
FOR AIR QUALITY VIOLATIONS
RESULTING IN LOSS OF APPETITE.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S GOT
A CLASS-ACTION GOING
'CAUSE NOBODY WARNED HIM
TO TAKE CARE OF HIS TEETH.
PEOPLE ARE SUING ME 'CAUSE
THERE'S NO FISH IN THE LAKE,
89 COUNTS
OF RECKLESS ENDANGERMENT,
SO I'M COUNTER-SUING
THE WHOLE SHEBANG --
WHAT THE HECK, EH?
WE GOT EACH PERSON
SUING EACH OTHER PERSON
FOR HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS
OF DOLLARS!
WOW! UNCLE RED!
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS MEANS?
I SURE DO --
WE'RE ALL GONNA BE RICH!
(Laughing)
WELCOME TO THE PORTION
WHERE WE EXAMINE
THOSE THREE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
(Audience):
"I DON'T KNOW!"
EXCELLENT! "I DON'T KNOW!"
ON THE EXPERT PORTION,
JOINING MY UNCLE RED,
HIS BEST FRIEND IN THE ROOM,
MR. FERRYBOAT CAPTAIN HIMSELF,
HAP SHAUGHNESSY!
(Applause and cheering)
ALL RIGHT!
A LADY VIEWER WRITES,
"DEAR RED" -- HA-HA-HA!
"WHEN I GROW UP,
I WANT TO BE FAMOUS.
"WHAT IS IT LIKE TO BE FAMOUS?"
WELL, YOU KNOW, IT'S--
"AND DO YOU KNOW ANYONE
WHO ACTUALLY
IS
FAMOUS?"
(Audience laughing)
I THINK I AM FAMOUS
IN THIS AREA.
I CERTAINLY HAVE A REPUTATION.
I DON'T THINK SHE'S TALKING
ABOUT COLLECTION AGENCIES.
(Audience laughing)
FAME!
AHHH!
RATHER THAN LOVE,
THAN MONEY, THAN FAME...
... GIVE ME TRUTH.
(Audience laughing)
WELL, ONCE IN HOLLYWOOD,
YOU CAN BE
THE TOAST OF THE TOWN --
STAR OF COMEDIES, WESTERNS,
ACTION FILMS.
THE NEXT MINUTE, YOU'RE RUNNING
A FERRYBOAT SERVICE
IN SOME GODFORSAKEN TOWN
IN NORTHERN ONTARIO.
(Audience laughing)
(Laughing)
YOU'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT YOURSELF, ARE YOU, HAP?
(Laughing)
30 FILMS,
AN OSCAR
NOMINATION,
AND WHO
REMEMBERS?
NO ONE ON THIS PLANET!
SO, MR.
SHAUGHNESSY,
YOU WERE
IN MOVIES?
YOU BREAK MY HEART WHEN YOU
HAVE TO EVEN ASK THAT QUESTION.
IT'S NOT EASY
FOR ME, EITHER.
I PLAYED THE FARMER IN "SHANE".
I PLAYED THE MAD BOMBER
IN "AIRPORT".
WAIT A SEC, WAIT A SEC.
I SAW THOSE MOVIES
AND THAT ACTOR...
WELL, IT WASN'T
HAP SHAUGHNESSY,
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
THE STUDIO PUBLICIST
CALLED ME "VAN HEFLIN".
(Audience laughing)
VAN HEFLIN?
YEAH.
YOU WERE TALLER THEN,
WEREN'T YOU?
IF I REMEMBER RIGHT,
YOU HAD A DIFFERENT... FACE.
JUST PART OF MY CRAFT, HAROLD.
I DON'T WANT TO BRAG,
BUT NO LESS AN ACTOR
THAN CHARLTON HESTON TOLD ME
THAT I COULD REALLY ACT.
HE SAID THAT
WITH A STRAIGHT FACE,
SO I'M CONVINCED.
(Audience laughing)
EVERYONE SETTLED THEIR CASES
OUT OF COURT, WHICH IS GOOD,
'CAUSE WE COULDN'T AFFORD
TO BUILD A COURT.
I WAS SUING MOOSE THOMPSON
FOR 30 GRAND.
WE SOLVED THAT --
HE GAVE ME BACK MY FISH FINDER.
STINKY GAVE ME BACK MY DRILL
AND I GAVE HIM HIS GOOD BOOTS.
I WON MY SUIT AGAINST BUSTER.
WHAT SUIT IS THAT?
MY BATHING SUIT --
I WONDERED WHERE THAT WENT.
SO EVERYBODY'S HAPPY.
LAW AND ORDER
HAS BEEN RESTORED.
BUT WHAT ABOUT MY LAWSUIT
AGAINST THE TOWNSHIP
AND JUNIOR AND MY MOM?
GOOD NEWS -- I GOT BACK YOUR
DIP NET AND THE VIDEO GAME.
OK, EXCELLENT -- GOOD WORK.
THIS SUING WAS A LOT OF FUN.
MAYBE I'LL BE A LAWYER, 'CAUSE
EVERYBODY HATES ME ALREADY.
THAT WOULD BE OK.
MAYBE I CAN GET ON
ONE OF THOSE BIG FIRMS,
LIKE ON "L.A. LAW"
OR "PERRY MASONRY"
OR I COULD BE
A COOL CORPORATE LAWYER
LIKE IN THAT SHOW "TRADERS".
(Laughing and applause)
THAT'S COOL.
(Possum squeal)
SQUEAL
OF THE POSSUM!
IT'S MEETING
TIME, UNCLE RED.
YOU GO AHEAD --
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
AWAY YOU GO.
OHHH!
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
ALL THIS LEGAL STUFF
GOT ME THINKING.
LATER, IF YOU PRESENT ME
WITH YOUR BRIEFS,
I'LL PROBABLY RECOMMEND
A MERGER.
THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): OH, OK.
STAND UP -- HE'S IN THE ROOM!
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN.
I HAVE A SERIOUS ANNOUNCEMENT.
LAST NIGHT AT THE BANQUET,
A BUNCH OF US WENT THROUGH
400 GALLONS OF BEER.
THIS MORNING, WHEN WE EMPTIED
THE HOLDING TANK,
THERE WAS 500 GALLONS IN THERE.