You know, the morning coffee is as much a
part of the Canadian experience as two
official languages 10 provinces or one work
in helicopter, according to the encyclopedia
Possam Logica.
We have more drive thru coffee joints than
public urinals.
I wonder if we lose so many trees every
year.
And there's even a coffee drinkers lingo.
For example, you got regular black cream
only double double or in Harold's case,
single single. And they have these contests
where if you drink enough coffee, you win a
year supply of sleeping pills.
All you got to do is flip up the lip to see
what you win.
Hey, I want something here.
It's like a three wheeled all terrain
vehicle, some type C, it's a tri engine.
I know that says try again.
They great big, big wake up at the lines
this week.
You know, a lot of people in our area like
to collect string.
A lot of people in our area like to collect
dust every 10 years.
The town has a competition to see who has
the biggest string ball
Rid of the red.
Check this out.
What is that hair? It's nothing.
Wait, a second, is that your string ball,
huh?
I had a bad year.
I hope you weren't expecting to win the
competition with that unit there.
No, no, no.
I know what I was thinking.
I was always thinking that, Oh, we can all
combine our string and then we'd have one
giant entry from the lodge.
Yeah. All right, but I'm not going 50 50 on
prize money with that little dust money, you
got there.
No, no, no, but but maybe something like 80,
20.
How about 90, 10?
Ok, how about we meet in the middle?
Ok. Eighty five, 20.
Yeah. Ok, good. Yeah.
You know, these remind me of planets, they
look like planets, that they look like
planets,
They look like planets. Yeah, yeah.
This is like Neptune and Pluto.
No, no, no, no. I'm normal in your goofy.
It's time for the Possum Lodge word game.
Today's price is a coupon for a possum lake
boat crews on the historic steamboat.
The Maryland bell duration of cruise subject
to performance of bilge pump.
Ok, cover your ears there, Dalton Red.
You've got 30 seconds to get Dalton Humphrey
to say this word.
A bout of blow.
All right,
Whiskey and goat.
Ok, Dalton, this is an expression you hear a
lot.
Get out and stay out.
Ok. Ok. When a soldier turns around and goes
in the opposite direction, they call that the
French. No, no.
Ok. Ok.
Ok, if you're sailing and the boom swings
hard from one side to the other, that means
that soon you'll be coming to.
Ok. No. Oh, I know, I know Americans make
fun of the way Canadians say this.
Please register your firearms.
I read almost out of time. I know, I know.
Ok, OK, don't remember last week you and
Marie were sparring a little and I said, What
was all that yelling?
You know, we were sparring, right?
You know, I mean, when school's more than
three rounds, that's about.
Yeah. Rothschild
sewage and septic
Sucking services, because your fruit should
get right, not your lawn.
Well, see, you're probably familiar with
these garbage disposal units in my books,
there's no better appliance for taking care
of vegetables.
It grinds them up in that kind of a compact
form and then fires them down the drain.
Kind of like what the human body does, but
I'm thinking, wouldn't it be great to be able
to do the same thing with outdoor junk like
trees or old school buses?
All it takes is a little imagination, some
mechanical ability and neighbors who mind
their own business. Ok, now for us to grind
up all this junk you see here, we're going to
need a pretty powerful garbage disposal.
Whereas all we have is this old cement
mixer.
But to me, this is like when a woman marries
the wrong man rather than starting over with
somebody new. She just makes a few
modifications that an agitator in there for
mix it up the cement. But it's not strong
enough to grind up, say, cast iron.
So we're going to augment the blades by
sticking a couple of prospecting tools on
them. Ok, now see these babies here.
These are made for a pound and rock, I mean,
these are strong.
They got diamond dust in there and titanium
plutonium and kryptonite.
I think we just got to make sure that we
attach some real solid.
May. Ok.
I think we're pretty much ready to go here,
I cut some holes in the bottom of her so that
the pulverized scrap can just run right
through the bottom of our garbage disposal.
And of course, we got our garden hose in
here.
This is so the water will run throughout the
entire garbage disposal process.
Otherwise, this could be dangerous.
And as you know, safety is what I'm all
about.
Ok, but of course, the key to the whole
process is to mount the unit over an open
manhole. That way, the output in your
garbage disposal will flow safely and
smoothly into the sewer system that you pay
for out of your tax dollars.
Oh, sure, I guess I could come out of this
thing over the kitchen sink, but I've been
married too long to make that mistake again.
Oh, yeah, I had that little more power to
the unit, so I took off the little belt that
ran to the electric motor and I put it on a
big belt.
Knock on wood, small block ain't here, but
if you're were grinding, say I-beams might
want to go with a Hemi or even a V12.
See, the beauty of this system is you can
gear the power to the size of the job.
Ok, I've had to rethink the strategy a
little bit here.
I'm actually not going to start the unit up
until after I put the scrap metal in it and
after I put this lid on it first with the
lid on there and I can't run the water
through it. So I'm pre cleaning all the
mechanism with some gasoline.
But of course, cleanliness is not enough,
you know, we also need to add some
lubrication. We've all been there, haven't
we?
Well, I'm just going to cover the blades
with oil.
We're good to go. I'll tell you one thing, I
have this yard cleaned up in no time to
remember the women don't find you handsome.
They should at least find your handy.
When a man gets close to retirement age, he
starts having some weird thoughts.
No, not those weird thoughts.
I mean, the ones about him having all this
free time, and if he doesn't use it for
something productive, he's going to feel
like somehow he wasted it.
The next thing you know, he's signing up for
mambo lessons, learning how to cook and
carving letter openers out of cow patties
with a chainsaw.
This is a huge mistake.
Don't be swayed by what the other retired
guys are doing.
Don't join a gym, don't get together with a
bunch of other retired guys and form a Motown
cover band.
Most importantly, do not write a book about
your life.
You only have enough good stuff or maybe two
chapters.
Most of the interesting things you've done,
you can't even spell.
And for sure, you're not going to like the
ending, so just continue to do exactly what
you did that brought you to this point.
Northam. Happy retirement, remember, I'm
pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
Rothchild, sewage and septic sucking services
satisfaction guaranteed for double your
sewage back.
Well, Harold and I put our two string balls
together, and it's a pretty decent size, then
come on here, I'll show them what we got.
Ok, I'm coming. You're going to love this.
Well, that should fill in your afternoon.
And Dalton's bringing his string ball over
to Atari's, and according to Emory, he's got
a fair sized one, too.
I hope I didn't misunderstand her on.
Oh, that would be him now.
And where's the string box?
It's right behind me.
For me, and
Now we're OK, we're OK.
It's stopped at the hill ow, ow ow ow, ow
ow.
Rolling back. Oh.
Know spring can be so dangerous.
I've never seen so much string in my life,
this would be like a dream if it was a good
thing.
Herald this is a good thing. That baby is a
winner.
Don't yeah, just got to figure out how to
get it down to the community center.
Maybe we had a vehicle. We could push it down
there.
I mean, it rolls pretty good.
Of course, the possum van.
All right. Look, I'll go around outside and
I'll pull on it.
You guys push on. Push Dalton.
Come on, Harold. You can help out.
Just like a big wedgie.
All right, push, don't push.
Ok, OK. All right.
All right. Stand back up, Karen Dalton, look
out.
I don't want anybody to get hurt. It's
common.
Yeah.
First, meet Dale Annatto behind the lines
down by the lake, we're going to do a little
fishing bill pulled in just a little snug, I
felt, Yeah.
And I was giving him a little grief on that
next thing, you know, had does exactly the
same thing. We really got to widen that
road.
So that comes around, we're giving him
grief.
He didn't put that thing in park, he didn't
put the emergency brake on and he's got a
carburetor problem. And actually we just
found that just grab anything, grab it.
Oh oh. See, that's what that's what Russell
can do to if you're going to she's actually
starting to pick up speed and heading right
for the lake and then.
That is our local car wash, but you don't
get your car back.
So we're enjoying that, but we don't want
to.
No, no, we're good. No. That's a shame.
That's a shame. No, that's a shame.
Yeah, yeah. And that tells us why he's
upset.
Because actually, walls are still in the
vehicle.
So I tell him to just calm down, that's all
right.
Don't worry, we'll get you out.
You know what? This is a modern age of
technology, and what I have on the front of
the possam van is a 50 tonne power winch.
And if you just just wait.
Everything's going to be great.
Don't worry, you got nothing to worry about.
Got her all under control.
Everything's fine. Just give me a couple of
minutes and I'll have him right out of there.
Not a problem. Not a problem.
All right, boys. Oh, taken care of.
But of course, these two can't trust
technology, they figure they better rescue
Walter on their own. They don't trust the
winch and all that, so on.
So first thing they do is they try a ladder.
And how did that go?
Know you just got to relax sometimes in
life, just kind of go.
Oh, a little inflatables, wading pool and a
pickaxe.
Yeah, and I saw that one coming.
Did you get them? Are you OK, boys?
And I come up there and just hope the winds
just casually on to the rear axle of a unit
and you won't believe the power of this
thing is unbelievable.
And what do you got the whole canoe in a
life jacket or two?
It's not necessary, boys, but you know, you
do what you want.
I think we'll be fine. Any luck?
So I'm wheeling her in.
Everything is going great, and I was a
little surprised, did not get the complete
vehicle. But I'm thinking, you know, if we
if we line up the bumper assembly and the
tail lights, you know, starting, you know,
she's starting to take shape.
So let's go back and get the rest of her.
And again, it's it's just a bit of a waiting
game, but everything's fine.
What do we got here? That's a that's a flare
gun bell.
Careful, careful with that bill.
Careful now.
Ok, fine. So and I'm going to hook her just
right on to the bumper, and she should be a
lot lighter with that rear assembly out of
there.
I think will be good. That would be the
trunk lid.
I don't know what that was.
And that is the front quarter panel.
We're getting there, we're making progress
here.
A bucket seat. Turning into a bit of a
jigsaw puzzle, this unit and there's the
hood, and I got her together pretty good.
And the guys are just one last attempt, I
think.
What are they going to take this time?
You know, really not necessary fellows.
I can I can bring Walter up.
He's in pretty much the same technique.
So you're safe, the car is back together,
and there's an important lesson in all of
this. You can either be patient or you can
be a patient.
You know, my wife says that I have this bad
habit of generalizing about things, so I
throw a trick question at her.
I ask her, Is it always wrong to generalize?
Yeah. That's Dr.
That's called a conundrum.
She stuck for an answer.
But then I'm stuck for a place to sleep.
But there is one thing I can generalize guys
like myself.
We can tell you which page of the newspaper
has the sunshine girl on it.
We can tell you the hours of operation of
every bare star within the two hour drive.
We can't seem to remember to replace the
empty toilet paper roll.
So I have come up with a way to do it
automatically.
I put a cap on the bottom end of this little
piece of ductwork here, cut a hole in her the
same size as the core in the center of the
toilet paper roll.
Now, whenever I come to the end of a roll,
the weight of the other rolls versus the
cardboard out and drops the new roll into
place.
It's a gravity feed like most Thompson at a
buffet.
But of course, now it's not enough to have
something practical in your home.
It also needs to be decorative.
Huh? Don't worry.
I even got that one figured out Bernice is
going to love this.
It's not just the toilet paper dispenser,
it's what I call my jumbo model.
Ladies and gentlemen, we interrupt the
Red-Green show so that I may bring you the
following important environmental message.
Greetings, campers, ranger Gord here with
another one of my patented wilderness safety
tips, say now here's a sight to see a couple
of happy go lucky noodle heads getting ready
to leave their campfire.
But what's this?
Look closer, everyone smoldering embers just
waiting to burst into a raging inferno.
All it will take is a single gust of wind.
I'm Erin's newspaper
And, of course, a carelessly tossed five
gallon can of gasoline.
Unfortunately, these two were smart.
They're wearing flame retardant clothing
perfect for smothering the flames.
Well, that's flannel ranger gore Wesley.
Oops.
Good thing I brought this bucket of sand.
So remember, folks never parade around naked
in a public campground.
It's just common sense, isn't it?
Well, that could have gone better.
Well, it was a bad plan.
It was a great plan, Harold Van had no
trouble pushing that gigantic string ball.
You know, if the community center had it
been uphill from here, we'd have no problem.
But oh
No. Why didn't he just step on the gas, get
the van in front of the ball and then at
least you could have slowed it down
And pass on a solid line, Harold.
That is illegal.
Well, so he's knocking down the community
center.
Oh man, we got trouble, boys.
No, we do not have trouble.
There's nothing about that string ball that
ties us to the crime.
Oh, really?
Well, when the ball hit the peak of the roof
of the community center, it started to one
unwind and it started to come back the same
way it went, which means it's leaving a trail
that leads right
To the lodge.
Well, I don't want to spend my sexually
active years in prison.
Now, Harold, actually it might be best.
But don't panic. I'm just going to get rid
of the evidence.
Now you guys go ahead, I'll be right down.
My wife is watching, I'll be coming straight
home.
After the meeting today, I learned all about
sharing.
I shared my string ball or shared my of van
almost shared a cell.
And you I'm kind of hoping that sharing
continues on into the night, but again,
that's your call. And the rest of you,
thanks for watching on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole gang up here for some
lunch.
Keep a stick on the ice.
All right. Hongkongers hardly know any value,
hence from the
mantra a I'm a man that I could change if I
have to.
I guess I am good news.
Man spoke with the police chief and they're
not going to press any charges.
Apparently, they have laws against strings
of crime, but nothing against crime of
strings.