IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW!"
THE TELEVISION SHOW THAT
DARES TO ASK, "IS THERE
ANYTHING ELSE ON T.V.?"
AND NOW HERE HE IS,
YOUR HOST BY CHOICE,
MY UNCLE BY BIRTH,
RED GREEN!
ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU.
BOY, OH, BOY.
WELCOME TO POSSUM LODGE.
BIG, BIG, BIG WEEK UP AT THE
LODGE THIS WEEK, I TELL YOU.
THE KIND OF THING THAT HAPPENS
MAYBE TWICE IN A LIFETIME.
HAROLD, DO YOU THINK
I SHOULD TELL THEM,
OR DO YOU THINK I SHOULD SORT OF
BUILD THE SUSPENSE LIKE THEY
DO ON THOSE BIG CHEESY
NETWORK SHOWS?
NO, NO, NO, YOU
TELL THEM NOW.
TELL THEM NOW BECAUSE
THIS IS BIG; THIS IS HUGE!
THIS IS BIG AND HUGE.
I DON'T THINK WE COULD
SIT ON THIS MUCH LONGER.
HAROLD, I DON'T THINK
YOU SHOULD SIT ON
ANYTHING RIGHT NOW.
CAN I GIVE THEM
A CLUE?
LET ME GIVE
THEM A CLUE.
OKAY, I'M GOING
TO GIVE YOU A CLUE.
TOM HANKS, TOM CRUISE,
SANDRA BULLOCK.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, HAROLD?
I'M TALKING ABOUT A BIG MOVIE
STAR BUYING A COTTAGE RIGHT
HERE AT POSSUM LAKE.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
BRUNO'S BUTCHER SHOP.
WHAT?
HE'S GOT A NEW
BACON SLICER.
HIS OLD BACON SLICER GOT
PREGNANT AND MOVED TO
PORT ASBESTOS.
SO BRUNO HAS REPLACED HER WITH
AN AUTOMATED UNIT.
I'M DETERMINED TO GET THE
NUMBER ONE SIDE OF BACON
WHEN I GO UP THERE.
WHAT ABOUT TOM HANKS AND TOM
CRUISE AND SANDRA BULLOCK?
WELL, THEY MIGHT BE NUMBER ONE
AT THE BOX OFFICE, BUT THEY'LL
BE NUMBER TWO AT BRUNO'S.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
HERE ARE A FEW SCENES FROM
THIS WEEK'S SHOW, AND THESE
ARE ALL FRESH GOODIES.
BUT NONE OF THIS STUFF HAS EVER
BEEN SEEN BEFORE ON TELEVISION.
YOU KNOW, I'M GUESSING
THERE'S PROBABLY A PRETTY
GOOD REASON FOR THAT.
WELL, FOR ONCE, PUBLICITY
AND HYPE WAS NOT JUST
EXAGGERATION.
BRUNO'S BACON SLICER
IS INCREDIBLE.
YOU KNOW WHAT, HAROLD?
IT ALSO SHAVES HAM.
YEAH, WE CAN BUY SHAVED HAM NOW,
WHICH IS GOOD 'CAUSE THE HAM
THAT BRUNO WAS SELLING
HAD HAIR ON IT.
UNCLE RED, NOBODY REALLY CARES
ABOUT A BACON SLICER.
OH, YEAH?
WELL, HOW COME EVERYBODY AND
THEIR COUSIN IS UP THERE IN
THE BUTCHER SHOP?
THEY'RE NOT THERE FOR
THE BACON SLICER.
THAT'S THE OVERFLOW FROM THE
REAL ESTATE AGENCY NEXT DOOR.
YEAH, NOBODY CARES ABOUT
HOW WELL YOU CAN SLICE
BACON OR SHAVE HAM.
REALLY?
YEAH!
WHAT A WORLD!
IT'S BEEN FANTASTIC. A MOVIE
STAR RIGHT UP HERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU KNOW THAT COTTAGE THAT
KEVIN BLACK BUILT UP ON
BLUFF'S POINT?
OH, YEAH.
A HOLLYWOOD STAR BOUGHT IT.
HOLLYWOOD?
LIKE, HOLLYWOOD?
YEAH, AS IN FREDERICK'S OF...
WOW!
IT'S FANTASTIC.
A HOLLYWOOD STAR RIGHT
HERE IN POSSUM LAKE.
AND THE RUMOUR IS IT'S LIKE
TOM HANKS OR TOM CRUISE OR
SANDRA BULLOCK.
OH, HAROLD,
COME ON, RELAX.
THEY'RE JUST
PEOPLE, OKAY?
MOVIE STARS ARE NO DIFFERENT
THAN ANYBODY ELSE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY EVERYBODY HAS
TO TREAT THEM SPECIAL.
LIKE, IF SANDRA BULLOCK COMES
UP TO YOU ON THE STREET, WHAT
WOULD YOU DO, HAROLD?
OH!
WELL --
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
GIRL, ME BOY.
AND SHE...
SEE? THAT'S GOOD.
YOU JUST
BE YOURSELF.
OH, SHE WORKED AT
THE LOCAL LIBRARY
SO WE HAD NEVER MET
BUT I WAS OUT WALKING
IT STARTED TO RAIN
I'D RATHER BE BORED THAN WET
SO I DUCKED INSIDE
THE LIBRARY DOOR
AND SAW HER STAMPING
SOME BOOKS
MY DECIMALS ALL GOT
DEWEY WHEN SHE GAVE ME
THAT LITERARY LOOK
OH, I PRETENDED I
LIKED READING BOOKS
AS I ASKED HER TO THE DANCE
SHE CLASSIFIED ME AS FICTION
AND THEN LATER THIS
MOVED TO ROMANCE
YOU CAN'T JUDGE A
BOOK BY ITS COVER
THAT LIBRARIAN HAD
ME ASTOUNDED
SHE HAD BOTH BRAINS
AND BEAUTY
NOT JUST WELL-READ,
BUT WELL-ROUNDED
LOVE IS HARD TO READ
AND LIBRARIANS ARE
OFTEN FICKLE
I RETURNED HER HOME
TEN MINUTES LATE
AND SHE HAD THE NERVE
TO FINE ME A NICKEL
IT'S THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
AND WE'RE PLAYING FOR A VERY
SPECIAL PRIZE TONIGHT.
CAN YOU SAY MILLION
DOLLAR AMETHYST?
WELL, NOW YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
SPELL IT TOO WITH THIS BRAND NEW
DICTIONARY FROM STAPLES N' SUCH.
UNCLE RED.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET Mr. MIKE HAMAR, TODAY'S
CONTESTANT, TO SAY THIS WORD.
BABY.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
30 SECONDS... GO!
ALL RIGHT, MIKE, WHEN A WOMAN IS
PREGNANT, SHE'S EXPECTING HER --
SOCIAL WORKER.
OKAY.
NO.
SHE'S A MOTHER.
SHE HAS A --
PROBLEM.
COME ON.
OKAY.
FINISH THIS SONG, OKAY?
YES, SIR, THAT'S MY --
STORY.
OKAY.
WHEN A PERSON IS VERY YOUNG,
THEY TALK, THEN THEY WALK,
THEY'RE A --
OH, A STOOLY.
NO.
OKAY.
THINK A LITTLE PERSON,
CRIES IN THE NIGHT.
YOU GO OVER TO COMFORT THEM.
BRING THEM A BOTTLE.
MY CELLMATE.
ALMOST OUT OF TIME, UNCLE RED.
OKAY.
WHEN YOU WERE YOUNG
YOU WERE --
SHOOTING CRAPS.
YEAH, YEAH, AND WHAT
DID YOU YELL?
COME ON, BABY!
THERE WE GO.
ISN'T SHE A BEAUTY?
YOU KNOW, THERE'S ONLY TWO
THINGS THAT COME INTO
YOUR LIFE ONCE...
TRUE LOVE AND A GOOD
USED POLICE CAR.
OH, SURE SHE MIGHT HAVE
700,000 MILES ON HER,
BUT IT'S ALL HIGHWAY
HIGH-SPEED CAR CHASES,
SO YOU'VE GOT NO CARBON
BUILDUP IN THERE.
UNFORTUNATELY, NOW, THERE ARE
SOME PEOPLE WHO DON'T SEE THE
VALUE IN OWNING A SECONDHAND
CAR FULL OF BULLET HOLES.
THEY DON'T APPRECIATE
THE HISTORY, THE EXCITEMENT,
THE ODOUR OF THE BACKSEAT.
SO TODAY ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I THOUGHT I'D SHOW YOU HOW
TO TURN YOUR POLICE CAR
INTO SOMETHING YOUR FAMILY
ACTUALLY DOESN'T MIND
RIDING AROUND IN.
WE'LL START BY CLEANING THE
INSIDE OUT A LITTLE BIT.
THERE THAT'S GOT MOST OF IT.
BY GOLLY, THERE WERE A FAIR
NUMBER OF COFFEE CUPS AND
DOUGHNUT BOXES IN THERE.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS GOING
TO BE SUCH A THRILL FOR
THE LODGE MEMBERS.
NOT SO MUCH RIDING IN A POLICE
CAR, BUT BEING IN THE FRONT
SEAT FOR A CHANGE.
NOW, THERE IS ONE
DOWNSIDE HERE.
THE LAW REQUIRES THESE GUYS
GOT TO TAKE THE SIREN OFF
THERE AND CHUCK THAT AWAY.
BUT THEY LEAVE THE
WIRING ON THERE.
SO WHAT YOU NEED IS TO GET
YOURSELF A SPEAKER --
MAYBE YOU GOT ONE OF THESE
IN YOUR ATTIC OR GET ONE
AT A YARD SALE,
OR MAYBE GO DOWN TO YOUR LOCAL
WATERING HOLE AND PORK ONE WHEN
THE BAND IS ON THEIR BREAK --
AND YOU WANT TO ATTACH THE
SPEAKER TO THE ROOF RACK,
USING THE HANDYMAN SECRET
WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT. ONCE YOU GET
THE SPEAKER WIRED UP,
YOU CAN REALLY START
TO HAVE SOME FUN.
HEY, JERK, PULL OVER!
GET OUT OF THE VEHICLE.
SPREAD 'EM!
NO, NOT THOSE.
ALL RIGHT.
SING SOMETHING IRISH.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
FOR THE BIG FUN,
YOU'VE GOT TO GET
YOURSELF A SIREN.
SEE WHAT THIS IS HERE?
THIS IS ONE OF THESE LITTLE
DOLLS, AND WHEN YOU SQUEEZE
IT, IT CRIES.
YOU'LL HAVE TO GO OUT
AND BUY ONE OF THESE.
IF YOU ALREADY HAVE ONE,
YOU OUGHT TO BE ASHAMED
OF YOURSELF.
(BABY CRYING)
THAT WILL WHIP YOU
THROUGH TRAFFIC.
THAT COULD BE A REAL LIFESAVER
WHEN YOU REALIZE THAT CHOCOLATE
BAR WAS ACTUALLY A LAXATIVE.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT YOU CAN DO?
YOU CAN ACTUALLY WEDGE THE
DOLL AND THE MICROPHONE
UNDER THE GAS PEDAL,
AND THEN WHEN YOU FLOOR IT, THE
SIREN WILL GO ON AUTOMATICALLY.
THERE ARE A FEW OTHER FEATURES
YOU GET WITH A COP CAR.
FOR EXAMPLE, IN THE TRUNK THERE,
YOU'VE GOT THE GUN RACK.
WHAT A GREAT PLACE TO CARRY
ALL OF YOUR GARDEN TOOLS.
THEN IF YOU GET SOME OF
THIS POLICE TAPE,
SUPER FOR MARKING OFF
YOUR PICNIC AREA.
AND YOU CAN PLAY THAT
GREAT PARTY GAME
WHERE EVERYBODY LIES
DOWN AND YOU DRAW
AROUND THEM WITH CHALK.
THEN IF YOU'RE LUCKY
ENOUGH TO GET YOURSELF
A COUPLE OF BODY BAGS,
MAKE GREAT PONCHOS
FOR THE KIDS.
AND SPEAKING OF KIDS, THIS
UNIT IS IDEAL FOR FAMILIES
BECAUSE WITH THE BUILT-IN
DIVIDER THERE, THEY CAN'T
GET AT YOU.
AND SEE, ON THE INSIDE OF THE
BACK DOOR THERE, THERE'S
NO DOOR HANDLE.
THERE'S NO WINDOW WINDER,
SO SHE'S EXTRA SAFE.
AND YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT THE KIDS DOING
DAMAGE BACK HERE.
THIS BACKSEAT HAS SEEN FIVE
YEARS OF FELONS, AND THEY CAN
JUMP AROUND ALL THEY WANT.
OH, BOY!
NOW, YOU KNOW WHAT
PEOPLE SAY TO ME?
WHAT DO YOU DO ABOUT
THE WEIRD PAINT JOB?
AND I ALWAYS SAY...
NOTHING.
LOOKS FINE TO ME, BUT IF YOU
HAPPEN TO BE A WHINER, YOU CAN
CHANGE THE DESIGN REAL CHEAP
WITH A ROLL OF WHITE
ADHESIVE TAPE AND BLACK
ELECTRICAL TAPE.
IS IT A MUSTANG?
IS IT A COLT?
NOPE, IT'S A ZEBRA.
AND WITH ALL OF THESE STRIPES
ON HERE, YOU LOOK MORE LIKE A
CONVICT THAN A COP
WHICH LETS YOUR FRIENDS KNOW
YOU'RE STILL ONE OF THEM.
SO, REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
YOU KNOW, I'M FEELING HUNGRY,
AND I THINK IT'S AN EMERGENCY.
(BABY CRYING)
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU OLDER
FELLERS OUT THERE.
YOU KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
YOU GUYS WHO USED TO MAKE SPLIT
DECISIONS ABOUT BUYING OR
SELLING, HIRING OR FIRING.
NOW IT TAKES YOU TEN MINUTES
TO FIGURE OUT WHETHER TO PAY
BY CASH OR CREDIT CARD.
DON'T WORRY, YOU'RE NOT
LOSING YOUR MIND!
THIS SUDDEN INABILITY TO MAKE
DECISIONS IS ACTUALLY KIND OF
A SAFETY MECHANISM,
'CAUSE YOUR MIND DOESN'T WANT TO
MAKE COMMITMENTS THAT YOUR
BODY CAN'T KEEP.
WHEN YOU WERE 21,
AND YOUR BODY SAID,
"RACE YOU TO THE CORNER,"
YOU WOULDN'T HESITATE.
NOW YOUR MIND FORCES YOU TO, SO
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE PICKING
UP PIECES OF YOUR HAMSTRING
ON THE WAY BACK.
SO IF YOU FIND YOURSELF AT THE
HARDWARE STORE WELL INTO THE
SECOND HOUR OF DECIDING
WHETHER TO BUY AN ELECTRIC
LAWN MOWER OR A GAS UNIT,
HEY, LET YOUR SON
MAKE THE CHOICE.
IT'S ONLY FAIR. HE'S THE ONE
THAT WILL BE PUSHING IT!
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
AND IF IT IS SANDRA BULLOCK WHO
BOUGHT THAT PROPERTY UP THERE,
I'M JUST GOING TO GO UP
AND SEE IF SHE NEEDS A
PERSONAL MASSEUSE.
OR MAYBE, YOU KNOW, JUST
A GUY TO STARE AT HER.
I COULD DO THAT.
HAROLD, HAROLD, I FOUND OUT WHO
BOUGHT THE BIG COTTAGE.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE IT.
HOLD ON.
MY UNCLE FOUND OUT WHO BOUGHT
THE BIG COTTAGE. HOLD ON.
WAS IT SANDRA BULLOCK?
NO, NO, NO, THINK REALLY,
REALLY FAMOUS.
SHARON STONE?
OH, THE SPICE GIRLS.
MADONNA.
NO, NO, NO.
THINK NOT A WOMAN.
RUE PAUL.
A GREAT ACTOR.
TOM HANKS.
TOM CRUISE!
NO, SOMEBODY I THINK
IS A GREAT ACTOR.
OH, TOM ARNOLD.
NO!
FLIPPER.
YOSEMITE SAM.
STOP!
I WILL TELL YOU WHO IT IS.
OKAY.
WERNER KLEMPERER.
WERNER KLEMPERER RIGHT
HERE, HAROLD.
WOW!
IT'S WERNER KLIMPNER.
WERNER KLIMPNER BOUGHT A
COTTAGE RIGHT HERE!
I DON'T KNOW.
I'LL ASK HIM.
WHO IS HE?
OH, HAROLD, YOU KNOW
COLONEL KLINK.
YOU KNOW.
HOGAN! NOBODY ESCAPES
FROM STALAG 13.
BOY, THE GUYS ARE
GOING TO GO NUTS.
WERNER KLEMPERER RIGHT HERE.
I'VE GOT TO GO TELL THEM.
THIS IS THE BIGGEST THING
SINCE HUGH BEAUMONT WENT
FISHING IN MERCURY CREEK.
DOING A LITTLE GOLF.
WELL, ACTUALLY, THE DRIVING
RANGE THING FOR ADVENTURES
WITH BILL TODAY.
BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL DAY.
OH, OH, OH. BY GOLLY.
SHOULD HAVE BROUGHT MY
STEEL-TOED GOLF SHOES.
EASY NOW.
WITH THE GOLFER, YOU GET OUT --
OH, BOY, BILL HAS
A LOT OF BALLS.
YOU GET OUT IN THE GOLF RANGE
THERE, AND YOU KNOW YOU ENJOY
THE WEATHER AND --
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES.
STILL HASN'T FIXED THE HOLE
IN THAT POCKET, OBVIOUSLY.
CAN WE START NOW, BILL?
OH, OH, OH! OH!
FOR YOU YOUNGSTERS OUT
THERE, CHEW YOUR FOOD.
ALL RIGHT?
OH, NO, HERE HE GOES
WITH HIS TRICKS.
OH, MAN.
I THINK BILL REALLY WANTED TO
BE A VAUDEVILLE PERFORMER WITH
HIS LITTLE MAGIC ACT AND
EVERYTHING.
THIS IS HIS FIRST
PERFORMANCE, I BELIEVE.
AND THERE'S HIS FIRST REVIEW.
ALL RIGHT. SO WE'VE GONE UP
TO THE DRIVING RANGE AND PUT
THE BALLS UP THERE.
THAT LOOKS KIND OF NEAT LIKE
SYNCHRONIZED SWIMMING, EXCEPT
WITHOUT THE NOSE PLUGS.
OH. OH, EASY. EASY.
HOW IS THAT LEATHER
HIP WORKING OUT?
THERE YOU GO.
HIT A BEAUTY.
OH, LOOK AT THAT, 200 YARDS
IF YOU'RE METRIC,
THAT'S AS FAR AS WHATEVER
200 YARDS IS.
OKAY. AND THEN, BILL -- LET HER
GO THERE, BILL.
BOY, OH, BOY.
LIKE I SAY, IT'S A
BEAUTIFUL DAY.
AND I GUESS YOU'RE DONE FOR
THE DAY, ARE YOU, BILL?
OH, NO. NO, DON'T WORRY.
IT WAS A RENTAL.
ALL RIGHT, LET HER GO.
NICE SHOT.
OH, THAT'S A BEAUTY.
BEHIND YOU, BILL.
OH, HE'S GOT AN IDEA. OH.
IF HE HITS THE OTHER WAY --
OKAY, GOING TO HIT
IT THE OTHER WAY,
AND THEN IT WILL
COME BACK AND GO FORWARD.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO MOVE
THE BUCKET OF BALLS.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
MOVE THAT BUCKET.
HE DIDN'T. OH!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, BILL.
BEAUTIFUL DAY.
BEAUTIFUL DAY OUT.
DON'T LET IT BOTHER YOU.
YOU'VE GOT TO RELAX IN GOLF.
YOU'VE GOT TO STAY WITHIN
YOURSELF.
ANOTHER BEAUTY.
NOTHING TO THIS GAME.
HIT THE TREE!
OH! BY GOLLY.
FORE!
HEAD.
FORE HEAD.
I LOVE THE GAME, REALLY.
OH, NOW HE'S CHALLENGING ME.
OH, I SEE, ACCURACY.
ACCURACY, NOT JUST DISTANCE.
WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
I DON'T GET THAT.
OH, WELL.
I CAN HIT THE TREE.
WATCH THIS.
I'LL NAIL THIS PUPPY.
HERE WE GO.
THERE WE GO.
OH! OH, I SEE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HE
HAD IN MIND THERE.
ALL RIGHT. NOW BILL WANTS
ME TO DO IT AGAIN.
OH, A DIFFERENT TREE.
DIFFERENT TREE.
YEAH, SURE, I CAN DO THAT.
I DON'T GET THIS.
OH, OH, HE'S GOING TO PUT
THE HELMET ON. OH, OKAY.
WELL, I'LL REALLY GET IT THEN.
OH, GOSH.
JOHN DALEY.
OH, OFF THE VAN.
OH, WELL.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
OH, WELL, BILL, YOU CAN ADOPT.
ALL RIGHT, IT'S STARTED!
COLONEL KLINK HAS
BEEN -- SORRY,
WERNER KLEMPERER HAS BEEN
SPOTTED UP AT HIS NEW
PROPERTY THERE.
YOU SEE, ALL THE GUYS ARE UP
THERE HIDING IN THE BUSHES.
GOT THE BINOCULARS, THE
TELESCOPES THERE.
JUNIOR SINGLETON, HE SAID
COLONEL KLINK LOOKS EXACTLY
THE SAME AS HE DID ON
"HOGAN'S HEROES,"
EXCEPT HE'S A LOT OLDER AND
DOESN'T HAVE THE NAZI'S
UNIFORM ON.
YOU KNOW, UNCLE RED,
I DON'T THINK HE WANTS
TO BE DISTURBED.
HE'S GOT NO TRESPASSING SIGNS
AND BIG HIGH FENCES AND
ELECTRICAL ALARM SYSTEM
AND GUARD DOGS.
HAROLD, HE JUST WANTS THE PLACE
TO LOOK LIKE STALAG 13,
SO EVERYBODY WILL KNOW
WHERE HE LIVES.
THAT'S ALL.
YOU WANT TO COME
UP WITH US?
NO!
ANYBODY WHO DID ONE T.V. SERIES
LONG BEFORE I WAS BORN
IS NO CELEBRITY TO ME.
WELL, HAROLD, HE MIGHT HAVE
SOME FRIENDS THAT YOU LIKE.
MAYBE BRUCE WILLIS MIGHT BE
UP THERE OR CLINT EASTWOOD,
MAYBE ARNOLD SCHWARZENEGGER.
OR SANDRA BULLOCK?
SURE! OKAY.
I'M COMING.
HANG ON.
OKAY.
I'M READY.
WHOA.
HE WON'T AUTOGRAPH ALL THAT
MANY PIECES OF PAPER.
AUTOGRAPH! YOU'RE
SO NAIVE.
YOU'RE LIKE THE NAIVEST
OF THE NAIVE.
THIS IS MY SCREENPLAY. I'M
GOING TO SHOW IT TO HIM.
"HAROLD IN BIKINI LAND."
IT'S A ROMANTIC COMEDY.
COULD BE MY BIG BREAK.
SANDRA BULLOCK'S TOO!
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU YOUNGER
VIEWERS WHO ARE STILL IN YOUR
TEENS AND STILL HAVE A CHANCE
TO SAVE YOUR LIFE.
YOU HEAR A LOT OF KIDS TODAY
SAYING THEY WANT TO BE FAMOUS.
NOW, I'M NOT A CAREER
COUNSELOR OR ANYTHING,
BUT THAT SOUNDS LIKE A GOAL
THAT'S DANGEROUSLY VAGUE.
THERE'S A GUY WHO IS FAMOUS NOW,
EVEN GOT HIS PICTURE
IN THE GUINNESS BOOK
OF WORLD RECORDS
BECAUSE HE WEIGHS OVER
A THOUSAND POUNDS.
I'M GUESSING WHEN HE WAS
15 AND SAID SOME DAY I'M
GOING TO BE FAMOUS,
HE WASN'T PICTURING HIMSELF
SPREAD OVER A COUCH WITH A
CHIN THE SIZE OF A PILLOW.
ACTUALLY, MOST PEOPLE THAT ARE
FAMOUS ARE TRULY INFAMOUS.
YOU LOOK DOWN THROUGH THE
FAMOUS PEOPLE IN HISTORY.
YOU'VE GOT A LOT OF DICTATORS
AND DESK POTS IN THERE.
AND EVEN THE WELL-KNOWN
ATHLETES NOW ARE USUALLY
FAMOUS FOR SOME SCANDAL
INVOLVING STEROIDS OR
FISTS OR LINGERIE.
I TELL YOU SOMETHING, FAME
IS NOT AN HONOURABLE GOAL.
YOU'VE GOT TO AIM
A LITTLE HIGHER.
GO FOR THE MONEY.
WELCOME TO THIS WEEK'S
INSTALLMENT OF MEN'S ANONYMOUS.
AS USUAL, AT THIS TIME, I'D LIKE
TO INVITE MY UNCLE RED UP HERE
TO LEAD US ALL IN THE MEN
ANONYMOUS PLEDGE.
UNCLE RED.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
OKAY. TO START US OFF THIS WEEK,
I HAVE AN OLD FRIEND THAT HASN'T
BEEN AT THE LODGE IN 17 YEARS.
HI, EVERYBODY. MY NAME
IS RANGER GORD.
WAIT. HO, HEY,
NO LAST NAMES.
HI, EVERYBODY. MY
NAME IS RANGER.
AS YOU KNOW, I'VE SPENT THE LAST
18 YEARS UP AT FIRE WATCHTOWER
13 LOOKING OUT FOR FIRES.
UNTIL, OF COURSE,
I ATE THE TOWER.
DURING THAT TIME, I DID
SOMETHING THAT I'M VERY
ASHAMED OF,
ESPECIALLY DURING MY
LAST FEW YEARS.
YOU SEE, BEING UP THERE ALONE
FOR AS LONG AS I'VE BEEN,
WITHOUT ANY VISITORS --
WELL, EXCEPT, OF COURSE,
FOR YOU, RED.
I DO THANK YOU FOR THAT.
IT WAS GREAT.
I MEAN, THEY WERE REALLY,
REALLY HELPFUL.
BUT LET'S BE HONEST, RED.
YOU'RE NOT A WOMAN.
YOU'RE NOT. YOU NEVER WERE,
AND THAT'S NOBODY'S FAULT.
THE THING IS, WHEN I WAS UP
THERE, I MADE A VOW TO BE
TRUE TO MY DREAM GIRL,
JULIE KOTTER.
GABE KOTTER'S WIFE FROM "WELCOME
BACK KOTTER," THE HIT T.V. SHOW.
OH, I WANTED TO BE HER
SWEAT HOG, I TELL YOU.
I MEAN, SHE WAS MY DREAM
GIRL, YOU KNOW.
ANYWAY, ONE NIGHT, AND I'M --
I'M NOT VERY PROUD OF THIS.
ONE NIGHT, I HAD A DREAM
ABOUT MARCIA BRADY.
AND THEN NIGHT AFTER NIGHT,
IT WAS MARCIA, MARCIA, MARCIA.
AND THEN I GET BACK HERE -- I
GET BACK HERE AND I SEE THAT
MARCIA BRADY IS INCREDIBLY
FAMOUS AND JULIE KOTTER IS GONE!
SHE'S GONE, NOT EVEN
DOING DINNER THEATRE.
AND NATURALLY I BLAME MYSELF
BECAUSE I DREAMT ABOUT MARCIA,
NOT JUST JULIE.
I CAN'T HELP THINKING
IT'S ALL MY FAULT!
I RUINED JULIE'S LIFE!
LET'S SHOW A LITTLE
BIT OF SUPPORT, GUYS.
(APPLAUSE)
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
WELL, POSSUM LAKE IS NO LONGER
HOLLYWOOD NORTH.
WERNER KLEMPERER IS GONE!
OH, GOD, NO ONE ESCAPES
FROM POSSUM LAKE.
HOW WAS THAT?
I KNOW!
I GUESS THERE'S JUST NOT
ENOUGH EXCITEMENT UP HERE
FOR A BIG STAR, HAROLD.
EXCITEMENT?
THAT'S WHAT HE CAME UP
HERE FOR IS TO GET AWAY
FROM THE EXCITEMENT.
YOU GUYS RUINED IT FOR HIM.
OH, HOW DID WE RUIN IT?
BY ASKING FOR HIS AUTOGRAPH.
WELL, BIG STARS ARE USED TO --
WHEN HE WAS IN THE SHOWER.
ASKING HIM HOW COME HE DIDN'T
DO ANY GOOD WORK AFTER
"HOGAN'S HEROES."
ARE YOU REALLY A NAZI
IN REAL LIFE?
EVERYBODY STEALING BITS
OF CHROME OFF HIS CAR
FOR SOUVENIRS.
HAROLD, WE WERE JUST TRYING TO
SHOW HIM THAT HE WAS ONE OF US.
I EVEN SAID THAT TO HIM,
"YOU'RE ONE OF US."
THAT HURT HIM DEEPLY.
YOU COULD SEE THAT.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
MADE HIM ANGRY, HAROLD.
ME?
YEAH, ASKED HIM IF HE
KNEW SANDRA BULLOCK,
OR IF HE COULD GET YOU A DATE
WITH HER -- OR WITH ANYONE.
(POSSUM CALL)
WELL, IT'S MEETING
TIME, UNCLE RED.
I'M GOING TO GO AND
TELL THE GUYS THAT
WERNER KLEMPERER HAS
LEFT.
ALL RIGHT.
UNLESS YOU WANT
TO DO IT.
I KNOW NOTHING!
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT DO YOU WANT
TO TELL THE GUYS --
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING, I'LL
BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I'M GOING TO BRING
YOU SOME SLICED BACON.
BUT IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR SOME
SHAVED HAM, I'M SORRY, THE
BEARD STAYS.
FOR THE REST OF YOU, THANKS
FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE AT
POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTER]
THE VEST. OKAY.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
OKAY. WE'VE GOT SOME
ANNOUNCEMENTS.
THIS IS FIRST ANNOUNCEMENT.
TYLER AND TYLER INSURANCE
BROKERS WANT TO REMIND
EVERYONE THAT
DUE TO THE EXTENSIVE FIRE
DAMAGE, THEY WILL NOT BE
ABLE TO HANDLE ALL OF YOUR
INSURANCE NEEDS UNTIL THEY FIND
A NEW LOCATION AND SOMEBODY TO
INSURE IT.
TYLER AND TYLER INSURANCE, AND
THEIR NEW SLOGAN IS, HEY, IT
CAN HAPPEN.