I LIKE POPCORN.
I LIKE IT A LOT.
I'VE SEEN MOVIES WHERE POPCORN
WAS THE BEST PART.
NOW, OF COURSE, THAT I'M
MARRIED, WE DON'T GO TO MOVIES.
WE DON'T GO OUT
AT ALL, IN FACT,
UNLESS THERE'S A GREASE FIRE.
SO I JUST MAKE
MY OWN POPCORN AT HOME.
WHAT I DO IS I'LL TAKE
A CUP OF KERNELS LIKE THIS,
PUT 'EM INTO A POT,
SHAKE HER ON THE STOVE
'TIL MY ARM FALLS OFF,
AND THAT'LL MAKE ME ABOUT A
BOWL OF POPCORN LIKE THAT.
BUT WHEN FRIENDS OR MAYBE
MOOSE THOMPSON DROPS OVER,
WELL, I NEED TO
MAKE A BIGGER BATCH.
[ LAUGHTER ]
YOU KNOW, I'M THINKING I NEED
A MACHINE TO DO THE
WORK FOR ME.
DO YOU KNOW THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
HAPPENED IN THE INDUSTRIAL
REVOLUTION?
I NEED SOMETHING INDUSTRIAL
THAT HAS REVOLUTIONS.
I'M THINKING CLOTHES DRYER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
AH, YAH!
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT, POP A STICK OF
BUTTER IN THE LINT HOLDER,
AND IT'S SHOW TIME.
[ MACHINE BUCKING ]
[ POPPING SOUND ]
[ BELL RINGS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
[ APPLAUSE AND WHISTLES ]
THANK YOU. THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YEAH, APPRECIATE THAT.
WELL, IT'S A BIG, BIG WEEK
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
IT'S THE ANNUAL POSSUM LAKE
SAUSAGE CARNIVAL.
YOU SEND IN YOUR HOMEMADE
SAUSAGE,
BRATWURST OR KNOCKWURST
OR WHATEVER,
AND THE JUDGES DECIDE
WHO HAS THE BEST WURST.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WE ENTER IT EVERY YEAR,
BUT IT GUYS AT CARIBOU LODGE
ALWAYS BEAT THE STUFFING
OUT OF US,
I GOT A FEELING THAT
THIS YEAR IS OUR YEAR.
WELL, I GOT THE
SAUSAGE CASING.
WOW! THAT'S A PRETTY
BIG WAD OF TUBING
YOU GOT THERE.
WHERE'D YOU GET THAT?
WELL, YOU KNOW, I KNOW A GUY WHO
WORKS AT THE EXPERIMENTAL FARM.
[ LAUGHTER ]
HOW DID THAT
EXPERIMENT GO,
DO YOU THINK?
I HAVE NO IDEA, RED.
YOU KNOW WHEN A GUY HANDS YOU
50 FEET OF INTESTINE ON
A SILVER PLATTER,
YOU DON'T WANNA
ASK QUESTIONS.
HEH, HEH, NO.
YOU DON'T LOOK A GIFT
HORSE IN THE MOUTH, HUH?
YOU'RE NOT
EVEN CLOSE.
ALL RIGHT,
LIKE I'M SAYING,
OUR CHANCES OF WINNING THE
SAUSAGE CARNIVAL ARE
BETTER THAN EVER.
YEAH, AND THE WINNER
GETS HIS PICTURE
IN THE PAPER,
POSED TASTEFULLY
BESIDE HIS SAUSAGE,
PLUS A YEAR SUPPLY OF
BICARBONATE OF SODA.
YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH!
AND THEY GET TO
WEAR THE SAUSAGE CROWN.
IT'S A HAT SHAPED LIKE
A CROWN COVERED
WITH SAUSAGE.
PROBABLY FIGURED
THAT ONE OUT ALREADY.
WE HAVEN'T WON YET.
NO.
WELL, WE BETTER
GET PACKING.
IT'S GONNA TAKE A FAIR
WHACK OF MYSTERY MEAT
TO STUFF THAT PUPPY.
NO GUTS,
NO GLORY!
[ APPLAUSE ]
Intercom: Miss Cook,
Mr. Green to see you.
OH, COOL.
SEND HIM IN.
Mr. GREEN.
YEAH.
THANK YOU FOR COMING IN.
I'M KELLY COOK.
YOU KNOW, YOU ARE A LOT OLDER
THAN I HAD BEEN EXPECTING.
ISN'T THIS A
SCHOOL DAY?
I'M THE NEW PROGRAMMER
HERE AT THE NETWORK.
OH.
PLEASE HAVE A SEAT.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, I HAVE A FEW
SUGGESTIONS FOR YOUR SHOW.
AND BY SUGGESTIONS,
I DO MEAN INSTRUCTIONS,
OKAY?
YOU EVER SEEN MY SHOW?
NOT ALL THE WAY THROUGH.
LET'S SEE.
FIRST OF ALL,
THE LODGE ITSELF.
HOW SHOULD I PUT THIS?
IT'S GROSS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT NEEDS TO
BE CLEANED UP.
OKAY.
OKAY?
OR DESTROYED.
IT'S UP TO YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY?
SECONDLY,
LET'S SAY THIS OVER HERE
IS POLITICAL CORRECTNESS
AND THIS OVER HERE
IS POLITICAL INCORRECTNESS --
GOTCHA.
YOU'RE ABOUT ...
BEYOND THAT WALL OVER THERE.
WOW.
OKAY?
Mr. GREEN, UM, SHOULDN'T
YOU BE WRITING THIS DOWN?
WELL, ACTUALLY, I CAN'T
READ MY WRITING VERY WELL.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OKAY, WELL, IT'LL BE
IN THE NEXT MEMO, ANYWAYS.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
I'M ALSO LOOKING FOR SOME
INCREASED SAFETY AWARENESS
ON YOU'RE LITTLE, UM --
HOBBY FIXIT THINGS.
A MAN LIKE YOU HOLDING A
POWER TOOL IS NOT A
COMFORTING IMAGE.
WELL, I WAS JUST HAVING
A LITTLE FUN, YOU KNOW.
YOU'RE TOO OLD TO
BE HAVING FUN, Mr. GREEN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OH, AND ONE
MORE THING...
THERE SEEMS TO BE THIS
GRAINISH, SILVERY TAPE
ALL OVER EVERYTHING
IN YOUR SHOW.
IT'S DISGUSTING.
IF YOU NEED US TO FIRE
SOME OF YOUR TECHNICAL
PEOPLE, WE WILL.
OKAY, OKAY, SO NO DUCT TAPE,
NO HANDYMAN CORNER,
NO LODGE.
PERFECT.
WELL, THAT SHOULDN'T
BE A PROBLEM.
GREAT.
SAY, YOU SEEN THAT
NEW HIP-HOP RAP
MOSH JAM THING
WITH BRITNEY SPEARS
OVER ON CHANNEL 97?
NO WAY!
WHAT TIME IS THAT ON?
WELL, IT'S ON
IN MY TIME SLOT.
THEY RUN IT
AGAINST MY SHOW.
OH, AND, UM,
WHEN IS THAT AGAIN?
8:30 FRIDAY NIGHT.
EXCELLENT.
THAT SOUNDS EXCELLENT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S PRIZE IS FROM MERCURY
CREEK BAIT AND TACKLE.
IT'S A COMPLETE
ICE FISHING KIT!
AND PLAYING FOR THIS
MUCH SOUGHT AFTER PRIZE,
Mr. MIKE HAMAR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
CLOSE YOUR EARS.
OKAY, RED, YOU HAVE
30 SECONDS TO GET MIKE
TO SAY THIS WORD.
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON.
BYE BYE.
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT, WHEN ONE OF YOUR
DADS WOULD LEAVE HOME
TO GO TO WORK,
YOU WOULD SAY, "GOOD ..."
RIDDANCE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OKAY, IN THE OLYMPICS,
WHEN A COMPETITOR
IS AUTOMATICALLY
PUT INTO THE FINALS,
THE OFFICIALS
SAY THEY GOT A ...
BRIBE?
[ LAUGHTER ]
OKAY, NOW, THINK ABOUT THIS.
THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO CAN
BE INTIMATE WITH BOTH
MEN AND WOMEN.
AND WE SAY THEY ARE
BLANK-SEXUAL.
VERY.
NO. NO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
RUNNING OUTTA TIME.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE,
IF YOU SOMETHING
FOR SALE IN A STORE,
AND IT'S CHEAPER
THAN IT SHOULD BE,
YOU SAY,
"THAT'S A REAL ..."
STEAL!
NO! YOU DON'T STEAL IT.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
WELL, I'D PRETEND I FORGOT
THE THING WAS IN MY POCKET.
SOMETIMES THE COPS BUY IT.
THERE WE GO!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
HI, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
IF YOU'RE DOWN IN THE DUMPS
BECAUSE YOU'RE LAWN'S
FULL OF LUMPS,
CALL ME, WINSTON, AND I'LL BE
THERE WITH MY PUMPS.
[ APPLAUSE AND LAUGHTER ]
YOU KNOW ONE OF THE MAJOR
CHALLENGES THAT FACES ANY
HANDYMAN IS...
HOW CAN YOU HAVE SOME OF
THE LUXURIES IN LIFE
THAT YOU KNOW YOU
REALLY CAN'T AFFORD,
LIKE, SAY, A SNOWMOBILE?
WELL, YOU KNOW THE VALUE AND
BEAUTY OF A SNOWMOBILE,
BUT MAYBE YOUR WIFE IS A
LITTLE RELUCTANT TO LET YOU
SPEND MONEY ON ANYTHING
UNTIL YOU FINISH PAYING OFF
THAT HOVERCRAFT.
SO THIS TIME ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW YOU
CAN MAKE YOUR OWN DARNED
SNOWMOBILE
OUT OF WATER SKIS, A TOBOGGAN,
A FEW ARTIFICIAL FIRE LOGS
AND A HOT WATER HEATER.
THIS HERE IS REALLY
THE ENGINE FOR THE UNIT.
IT'S A ROCKET ENGINE.
IT'S A STEAM ROCKET ENGINE.
I BET WITH A 50-GALLON
YOU COULD GO 60,
BUT THAT WOULD
JUST BE SHOWING OFF.
OKAY, FIRST THING YOU WANNA
DO IS PUNCH A HOLE IN THE
END OF HER HERE.
SOMEWHERE UP HIGH.
THAT'S YOUR STEAM PORT, EH?
THAT'S WHERE THE
STEAM'S GONNA COME OUT,
SO YOU GOTTA KEEP
THE HOLE HIGH,
OTHERWISE THE WATER'LL
ALL LEAK OUT.
RIGHT IN HERE.
OH, MAN.
NOW, WAIT NOW.
I GOT AN IDEA.
A HANDYMAN NEVER PANICS.
A PROBLEM IS JUST AN
OPPORTUNITY WAITING TO HAPPEN.
LAY THAT IN THERE.
MAKE A LITTLE ADJUSTMENT.
PERFECT.
NOW, YOU WANNA ATTACH THE
POWER PLANT TO THE TOBOGGAN.
AND YOU GOTTA HAVE SOMETHING
THAT WILL HOLD EVERYTHING
TOGETHER,
PLUS BE ABLE TO ABLE TO
WITHSTAND THE SHOCK
OF A SKI JUMP,
PERHAPS THE INSENSITIVE
COMMENTS OF NEIGHBOURS.
I RECOMMEND THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT, THESE ARTIFICIAL
LOGS ARE BASICALLY MY
ROCKET FUEL.
THEY BURN FOR
SIX HOURS, YOU KNOW,
WHICH WILL GET ME ALL THE WAY
TO PORT ASBESTOS AND BACK.
IF I WAS ONLY GOING ONE WAY,
I'D CUT 'EM IN HALF.
I LIKE USING THE
ARTIFICIAL LOGS, THOUGH,
BECAUSE THEY LIGHT UP
NO PROBLEM,
AND THEY GIVE OFF THOSE
COLOURED FLAMES.
A LOT EASIER FOR THE
RESCUE PLANES TO SPOT.
OKAY, THAT'S THE POWER
PLANT DONE ON HER.
THIS BABY'LL GO FASTER THAN A
TEENAGER'S ALLOWANCE.
NOW ALL WE GOTTA DO
IS ADD THE STEERING,
WHICH IS BASICALLY ME SITTING
ON THE FRONT WEARING A PAIR
OF WATER SKIS.
IS THAT BRILLIANT
OR WHAT, HUH?
YOU KNOW, IT'S THAT KIND OF
SIMPLICITY THAT MAKES ME
WHAT I AM.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ HUFFING AND PUFFING ]
[ STEAM HISSING ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ TRAIN WHISTLE BLASTING ]
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
ANY GUY WHO'S WAITED IN HIS CAR
WHILE HIS WIFE GOES INTO THE
STORE JUST FOR A MINUTE
KNOWS THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
THE WAYS MEN AND WOMEN SHOP.
SEE, A MAN IS SORT OF
LIKE A PLANNER.
LONG BEFORE HE GOES TO THE
STORE, HE KNOWS EXACTLY
WHAT HE WANTS.
HE KNOWS EXACTLY
WHERE TO GET IT.
THE LAST THING HE WANTS IS
TO GET STUCK
IN SOME EMBARRASSING
CORNER OF THE STORE
WHERE THEY HAVE
UNDERWEAR OR CURTAINS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
'CAUSE WHEN A GUY
GOES SHOPPING,
HE WANTS TO LOOK COOL.
YOU KNOW, LIKE THE SHOPPING
EXPERIENCE IS NO STRESS
TO HIM WHATSOEVER.
HIS WIFE, HOWEVER,
TENDS TO BE A LITTLE LOOSER.
SHE'LL GO TO A STORE WITH NO
IDEA WHAT IT IS THAT SHE NEEDS.
SHE'LL FIGURE OUT WHAT
IT IS SHE DESPERATELY WANTS
AFTER SHE GETS THERE.
SHE'S MORE OPEN;
SHE'S MORE RECEPTIVE.
SHE'S NICER.
SHE'LL READ ALL THE LABELS
FROM SIX DIFFERENT KINDS
OF TOOTHPASTE.
SHE'LL TRY ON EVERY SIZE EIGHT
SHOE IN THE STORE.
SHE'LL LISTEN TO THE WHOLE
GASTROINTESTINAL HISTORY
OF THE SALESPERSON'S DOG.
CENTURIES FROM NOW, I FIGURE
ARCHAEOLOGISTS ARE GOING
TO UNCOVER SOME GUY
STILL SITTING IN HIS CAR
BY THE CURB,
WAITING FOR HIS WIFE,
WHO WENT INTO THE STORE
JUST FOR A MINUTE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, I'VE MET PEOPLE WHO
DON'T APPRECIATE SAUSAGES.
I NEVER REALLY
UNDERSTOOD WHY.
THEY SAY TO ME, "WELL, IT'S
PIGS' ENTRAILS STUFFED WITH
FATTY MEAT AND SUET."
AND I SAY, "YEAH."
[ LAUGHTER ]
BUT AFTER WHAT
I'VE BEEN THROUGH TODAY,
I'M STARTING TO LOSE MY
ENTHUSIASM FOR IT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHERE DID YOU GO?
WELL, DALTON, I DIDN'T
MIND HELPING YOU
STUFF THE THING,
BUT WHEN YOU TIED
THAT KNOT IN THE END,
I THOUGHT I WAS
GONNA LOSE IT.
YOU'RE NOT HAVING SECOND
THOUGHTS, ARE YOU?
I'M NOT HAVING ANY THOUGHTS.
WELL, GOOD.
'CAUSE IF WE WANT TO BEAT
THOSE YAHOOS DOWN AT
CARIBOU LODGE,
WE GOTTA GET THIS DOWN
TO THE SAUSAGE CARNIVAL.
TONIGHT'S THE COOK-OFF!
I'M NOT PUTTING
THAT IN MY VAN,
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
WE CAN'T JUST DRAG
IT DOWN.
WE MIGHT HIT A NAIL,
AND WE DON'T HAVE A SPARE.
WELL, MAYBE WE COULD FLOAT
IT DOWN OVER THE LAKE.
YOU THINK THE WATER
WOULD RUIN THE FLAVOUR?
NOTHING WOULD RUIN
THAT FLAVOUR.
I GOT AN IDEA!
TAKE A COUPLE OF
BOAT TRAILERS,
PUT THEM END TO END
BEHIND THE POSSUM VAN.
JUST LAY THE SAUSAGE OVER
THE WHOLE DEAL THERE.
WELL, WHAT IF THE
COPS STOP US?
WELL, WE'LL TELL 'EM
IT'S A BIODEGRADABLE
TELEPHONE POLE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OH, YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU COULD SAY?
I BET YOU NEVER "SAUSAGE"
(saw such) A THING.
[ LAUGHTER ]
DON'T MAKE ME
KILL YOU, DALTON.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
Red: DWIGHT!
Dwight: HOW'S IT GOIN', RED?
Red: CATCH ME, WILL YA?
THANKS FOR YOUR
HELP THERE, DWIGHT.
SORRY FOR THE
INCONVENIENCE.
I'M IN THE SERVICE
BUSINESS, RED.
YEAH?
WELL, GOOD.
'CAUSE THIS OUTBOARD
YOU SOLD ME ISN'T WORKING.
NO REASON TO RAISE
YOUR VOICE, RED.
WELL, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HEAR ME
OVER THE SOUND OF A MOTOR
RUNNING, DO YOU?
KEEPS CUTTING OUT ON ME,
ESPECIALLY IN THE WET WEATHER.
OF COURSE IT RAINED LAST
NIGHT OVER AT THE LODGE.
DID IT RAIN OVER HERE AT ALL?
ARE YOU TELLING ME YOU'RE
TOO LAZY TO EVEN GET
OUTTA THE RAIN?
I PREFER TO CALL IT PASSIVE
ENVIRONMENTAL INTERACTION.
WHATEVER YOU CALL IT,
I NEED YOU TO FIX
THIS OUTBOARD
THAT YOU SOLD ME.
HOW MUCH DID
I SELL IT TO YOU FOR?
75 BUCKS.
WELL, THAT WAS
A GOOD DEAL.
YOU WANNA
BUY IT BACK?
NO CHANCE.
SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
OKAY, I GUESS IF YOU WANNA
CARRY IT UP INTO THE SHOP,
I MIGHT TRY AND
TAKE A LOOK AT IT.
YOU EXPECT ME TO CARRY
THE MOTOR THAT YOU SOLD ME
TO THE SHOP BY MYSELF?
CAN YOU HEAR
YOURSELF, RED?
IT'S ALL ME, ME, ME.
YOU'RE THE CENTRE
OF THE UNIVERSE.
AND THAT TONE.
YOU SOUND LIKE A HEART ATTACK
JUST WAITING TO HAPPEN.
WELL, YOU KNOW, DWIGHT,
I DON'T THINK ANYONE ON THE
VERGE OF A HEART ATTACK
SHOULD BE CARRYING AN
OUTBOARD BY HIMSELF.
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
HEART DISEASE
RUNS IN MY FAMILY.
MAN.
NOTHING RUNS IN
YOUR FAMILY, DWIGHT.
THAT'S WHY THEY ALL
HAVE HEART ATTACKS.
HOW SOON WILL YOU HAVE THIS
THING FIXED, DWIGHT?
OH, HARD TO SAY.
THIS IS OUR
BUSY TIME.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
Red: A BUNCH OF US
WERE OUT IN DALTON'S CAR,
AND HE WAS HAVING SOME
KIND OF AN EMERGENCY.
TURNED OUT TO BE SOME
KIND OF FIRE IN THE
GROINAL CROTCHAL AREA.
YOU REALLY DON'T WANNA HAVE
THAT IN YOUR DRIVER.
I DON'T KNOW.
SO I HAD TO --
I HAD THE THERMOS OF --
I BELIEVE THAT WAS ICE WATER.
YEAH, IT DID THE JOB.
AND, OF COURSE, WALTER
HAD ANOTHER PLAN,
BUT I SAID, "NO, NO."
AND THEN HE FOUND THIS.
MIKE HAD APPARENTLY THROWN THA
OUT THE WINDOW AND IT WENT IN.
WELL, THAT'S UNFORTUNATE.
NO, IT'S OUT, MIKE.
IT'S OUT.
NOW, UNFORTUNATELY,
WE HAD JUMPED OUTTA
THE CAR SO QUICKLY,
AND WE HAD ALL
LOCKED OUR DOORS,
AND THE WINDOWS WERE UP.
AND, UH, THAT'S NOT
THE WORST PART.
SHE WAS RUNNIN'.
SO, UH, DALTON'S WASTING
GAS BY THE SECOND.
HE'S TRYING THEM ALL.
HE DOESN'T BELIEVE US.
HAD TO TRY ALL
THE DOORS HIMSELF.
WE'RE THINKING WE GOTTA
TRY SOMETHING HERE.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
I'M TELLIN' WALTER IF HE GETS
OUT SOME KIND OF WIRE.
GO DOWN THROUGH THE WINDOW,
HOOK ON --
SO HE SEES A WIRE FENCE,
AND OF COURSE, THE SIGN WE
KNOCKED OVER TURNED OUT
TO BE IMPORTANT.
[ AUDIENCE REACTS ]
AND WALTER HAD --
OH!
AND OF COURSE, UH,
WE'RE NOT PAYING ANY
ATTENTION TO HIM AT ALL.
ALL OF A SUDDEN ... OH!
[ APPLAUSE AND LAUGHTER ]
OH, MAN, THAT WAS --
THAT WAS A KILLER.
SO I DECIDED TO GO WITH
PLAN "B" ON THAT.
TOOK THE GUYS OVER.
DALTON WANTED TO WORK
ON IT HIMSELF.
EASY, WALTER.
EASY. EASY.
THOUGHT WE'D GET
SOMETHING MAYBE WE COULD
BREAK INTO THE
CAR ANOTHER WAY.
OH, GOSH.
IF YOU'D MOVED OUTTA
THE WAY, DALTON.
DALTON'S UP --
WHAT ARE YOU SO UPSET ABOUT?
IT'S NOT THAT BIG A DENT.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM, DALTON?
OH!
IT'S YOUR WIFE'S CAR.
ALL RIGHT.
I GOT AN IDEA.
WE CAN JUST STICK A ROCK
INTO THE EXHAUST PIPE,
AND IT'LL --
OH, THAT'S HOT!
OH, THAT'S HOT.
THAT'S HOT.
OH, MIKE'S GOT THE
RUBBER GLOVES ON.
SUMMER JOB, MIKE?
OR WHAT IS THAT?
THING IS IT'LL
STALL THE ENGINE.
JAM THAT IN THERE.
NOW, THE ENGINE WILL STALL.
WELL, ONE OF TWO
THINGS WILL HAPPEN...
ONE OF THEM WILL BE
THE ENGINE WILL STALL.
AND THIS IS THE OTHER.
OH, MAN.
OH, WELL.
ALL RIGHT, UH,
THIS GAVE ME AN IDEA.
I SAW THE RUBBER GLOVES,
AND I'M THINKING,
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING WITH A
LITTLE GIVE TO IT --
DUCT TAPE THAT ON THERE.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
AND UH, THAT'S FILLED UP
PRETTY GOOD WITH EXHAUST.
I'M EXPECTING THAT THE
ENGINE'S GONNA CONK
OUT ANY SECOND,
BUT THE GLOVE'S GETTING
BIGGER AND BIGGER.
AND, UH, WE DIDN'T
KNOW WHAT TO DO,
AND, UH, SUDDENLY I THOUGHT,
WHAT WOULD MY GRANDFATHER DO?
HE'D SAY, PULL MY FINGER.
[ ROAR OF LAUGHTER ]
[ AUDIENCE CHEERING ]
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
THERE YOU GO, DALTON.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
[ EXPLOSION ]
YOU KNOW, THE HARDEST PART
OF WASHING A CAR
IS BENDING OVER AND
DOING THE WHEELS.
HERE'S A SHORT-CUT FOR YOU.
SOAP 'EM UP REAL GOOD.
AND GET YOURSELF A
BOWL OF HORSE MEAT.
THIS IS ONE I
BET ON LAST WEEK.
YOU ALSO NEED A FRIENDLY DOG
WITH A GREAT BIG BUSHY TAIL.
COME ON.
THERE YOU GO.
[ RED CHUCKLES ]
BOY, IF ONLY HE FOUND SOME
WAY OF RINSING OFF WHEN
HE WAS DONE.
[ SOUND OF DOG PEEING
AGAINST TIRE ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
WE LOST.
WE'RE LUCKY
TO BE ALIVE.
OH, I DUNNO.
THAT'S TOO CLOSE
TO CALL.
WHAT HAPPENED EXACTLY?
IT'S A BLUR.
WELL, DO YOU REMEMBER HOW
WE LAID THE SAUSAGE
ON THE GRILLS,
ALL THOSE BARBECUES
SET UP END TO END?
YEAH, I REMEMBER THAT PART.
AND I REMEMBER THE SMELL
OF IT COOKING.
EVERYBODY IN THE TRI-COUNTY
AREA REMEMBERS THE
SMELL, DALTON.
THEY THOUGHT THE PULP
MILL HAD RE-OPENED.
REMEMBER HOW THE PRESSURE
BUILT UP INSIDE
THE SAUSAGE?
YEAH!
YEAH, IT GOT REAL BIG,
JUST LIKE THE HINDENBURG.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THEN YOU WENT AND POKED
A HOLE IN THE END
WITH THAT FORK.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OH, THE HUMANITY!
APPARENTLY, WE DIDN'T
GET THE INTERIOR OF
THE SAUSAGE
AS STERILE AS
IT NEEDS TO BE.
GETTING A METHANE
BUILD-UP IN THERE --
THOSE OF YOU IN
A COLLEGE FRATERNITY
KNOW THAT METHANE
IS FLAMMABLE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I REMEMBER A HOT
BLAST OF FETID AIR,
AND THEN SOMETHING WENT
OFF LIKE A FIRECRACKER.
MORE OF A CRUISE MISSILE,
REALLY, DALTON.
WE STILL DON'T KNOW
WHERE IT CAME DOWN.
BOY, IT WAS LUCKY IT
ARCED OVER THE CROWD.
OTHERWISE, PEOPLE COULD HAVE
BEEN SERIOUSLY SAUSAGED.
YEAH, IT WAS BAD.
YEP, IT WAS THE WORST.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, IT'S MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD,
WIENER BOY.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND IT TURNS OUT ALL THOSE
THINGS YOU SAID ABOUT MEN
AND SAUSAGES
WERE ABSOLUTELY CORRECT.
AND LET'S JUST
LEAVE IT THERE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND THE
WHOLE GANG UP HERE AT
POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Dalton: EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
SIT.
Mike: SIT DOWN, EVERYBODY.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, GUYS.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
All: I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
Red: OKAY, GUYS, I KNOW YOU'RE
ALL DISAPPOINTED
ABOUT THE SAUSAGE
CARNIVAL AND SO ON,
BUT, UH, WINSTON HAS A LITTLE
BIT OF GOOD NEWS FOR US.
Winston: WELL, UH, GUYS,
AS YOU KNOW, OUR SAUSAGE DIDN'T
REALLY IMPRESS THE JUDGES,
BUT IT SCORED A HIT WITH
THE CARIBOU LODGE.
A DIRECT HIT!