OH, MAN.
I'VE GOT A FLAT TIRE.
MUST'VE CAUGHT A NAIL.
WHAT A SHAME.
I WAS HOPING TO GET
ANOTHER 20K OUTTA THIS BABY.
OH, WELL.
JUST HAVE TO GET THE SPARE.
I THINK IT'S ONE OF
THOSE SPACE SAVER SPARES.
YEAH, YEAH,
THERE IT IS.
NO, THAT'S A DOUGHNUT.
NOW WHAT?
A LITTLE HANDYMAN
INGENUITY, THAT'S WHAT.
I COULD ONLY GET TWO OF THE
BOLTS TO LINE UP,
SO I REALLY HAD TO HORSE
THIS BABY ON HERE.
I WON'T BE NEEDING
THAT AGAIN ANYWAY.
THIS BABY'LL NEVER GO FLAT.
TALK ABOUT A STEAL-BELTED
RADIAL, HUH?
LOOKS LIKE ALL THOSE
YEARS OF PAYING ROAD TAX
IS FINALLY PAYING OFF.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
OH, YEAH.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG NEWS UP AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK.
THIS TIME YOU CAN CHALK ONE UP
FOR THE LITTLE GUY,
BECAUSE OUR LOCAL PAPER,
"THE POSSUM LAKE DAILY
MOVEMENT,"
HAS BEEN RUNNING THIS REPORT FOR
ABOUT A MONTH NOW
HOW THE CITY OF TORONTO HAS RUN
OUTTA PLACES TO PUT THEIR
GARBAGE,
AND THEY'VE DECIDED
TO DUMP IT ALL
INTO AN OLD ABANDONED QUARRY
UP NEAR PORT ASBESTOS.
WELL, I DON'T THINK SO.
Red: SO IS THAT
ANY GOOD OR WHAT, EH?
WE ARE THE MAN!
DALTON, TELL 'EM
WHAT WE DID.
OKAY, WE WENT UP TO THE QUARRY
TO PROTEST TORONTO DUMPING ITS
GARBAGE AT PORT ASBESTOS.
AND IT WORKED.
THEY CANCELED
THE PROJECT.
TELL 'EM WHY, DALTON.
WELL, BECAUSE WE GAVE THEM
A BETTER ALTERNATIVE.
YES, WE DID INDEED.
AND WHAT WAS THAT
BETTER ALTERNATIVE?
THEY'RE GONNA DUMP THEIR
GARBAGE RIGHT HERE
AT THE LODGE.
IS THAT ANY GOOD?
[ APPLAUSE ]
NOW ALL THAT HIGH-TONE
TORONTO GARBAGE
IS GONNA GET
DELIVERED RIGHT HERE.
ALL THOSE B.M.W. PARTS.
THE UNUSED POWER TOOLS.
THE HALF ASSEMBLED
IKEA FURNITURE.
WE'RE GONNA BE SITTING
ON A GOLD MINE.
DALTON,
KA-CHING!
I'M TEARING UP.
DALTON,
HE NEEDS A HUG.
IT'S THE POSSUM
LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
AND TODAY'S PRIZE IS
A ONE-YEAR SUBSCRIPTION
TO THE LOCAL PAPER,
THE DAILY MOVEMENT.
BELIEVE ME, THERE'S NO BETTER
WAY TO START A MORNING.
ALL RIGHT, WINSTON,
COVER YOUR EARS.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS TO
GET WINSTON TO SAY THIS WORD.
ALL RIGHT, DALTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, WINSTON, WHEN YOU
HAVE A CAR ACCIDENT,
THE FIRST THING YOU DO
WITH THE OTHER DRIVER IS
YOU EXCHANGE...
EXCUSES?
OKAY, YOU DRIVE BY SOMEBODY'S
HOUSE AND IT'S ON FIRE.
YOU THINK TO YOURSELF, BOY,
I SURE HOPE THAT GUY HAS...
ANOTHER HOUSE.
OKAY, YOU WANT YOUR FAMILY
TO BE LOOKED AFTER
WHEN YOU DIE,
SO YOU BUY...
A PITBULL?
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
DOCTORS BUY A LOT OF.
GOLF BALLS!
TIME'S ALMOST UP.
OKAY, OKAY, THIS IS
SOMETHING SMART PEOPLE BUY
TO PROTECT THEM
FROM A DISASTER.
OH, A PLUNGER.
YOU KNOW YOUR SELF-HELP GUY,
ANTHONY ANTHONY?
WHAT DOES HE HAVE SO
THAT HE CAN MAKE ALL
THOSE PROMISES?
LIABILITY INSURANCE.
THERE WE GO.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
GORD?
OH, RED.
RED GREEN.
WHO ARE ALL THOSE
PEOPLE DOWN THERE?
OH. THEY'RE
FRIENDS OF MINE.
YEAH, I'M JUST TRYING TO FIND
THEM SOMETHING TO MUNCH ON.
THEY'RE GETTING
HUNGRY AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT. YEAH.
OH, HERE WE GO.
AH, IS THAT A
GOOD IDEA, GORD?
OH, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THEY HAVE CAN OPENERS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ CRASHING SOUND ]
THEY WON'T NEED THE
OPENER FOR THAT ONE.
CARRY ON!
HAVE A SEAT.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING
DOWN THERE, GORD?
OH, THEY'RE JUST
ENJOYING MY COMPANY.
WE'RE ALL JUST
SHOOTING THE BREEZE.
WE'RE JUST HANGING
OUT TOGETHER.
NO. NO. NO.
THEY'RE NOT HANGING OUT.
THEY'RE CHAINED TO
THE TREES DOWN THERE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THEY'RE ENVIRONMENTAL
ACTIVISTS.
THEY'RE DOING THEIR
PART TO SAVE THE TREES
FROM THE LOGGING COMPANY
THAT PLANS TO
CLEAR CUT THIS FOREST.
AND EACH ONE OF
THOSE DEDICATED INDIVIDUALS
HAS GIVEN ME
THE KEY TO THEIR FREEDOM,
WITH EXPLICIT INSTRUCTIONS
NOT TO UNCHAIN THEM
UNTIL I SEE THE LOGGING
COMPANY PACK UP AND GO HOME.
YEAH, WELL THEY LEFT
A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO.
THE LOGGERS ARE OUT OF HERE.
DIDN'T YOU NOTICE THE
BULLDOZERS ARE GONE?
YEAH, I WONDERED
ABOUT THAT.
YEAH.
THEY'RE GONE.
I MEAN, ALL THE
LOGGERS HAVE LEFT.
YEAH. WELL, MAYBE.
MAYBE THEY LEFT.
MAYBE THEY'RE JUST HIDING.
HAD YOU THOUGHT OF THAT?
GORD, YOU CAN'T HAVE
PEOPLE CHAINED UP TO TREES
JUST TO KEEP YOU COMPANY.
OH, COME ON.
WE'RE JUST GETTING
TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
BESIDES, ONE OF THEM
IS A W-W-W --
A WOMAN?
YEAH!
[ LAUGHTER ]
AT LEAST I THINK
SHE'S A WOMAN.
I HOPE SO ANYWAY.
AND SHE LISTENS TO ME.
YOU KNOW, SHE DOESN'T JUST
TAKE OFF IN MID-SENTENCE,
UNLIKE SOME PEOPLE I KNOW.
WELL, SHE CAN'T TAKE OFF.
SHE'S CHAINED TO A TREE.
YEAH, THAT MIGHT
BE PART OF IT.
BUT I ALSO THINK SHE FINDS
MY STORIES EXTREMELY ENGAGING.
BRING YOUR KEYS.
WE'RE GOING TO UNCHAIN ALL
THOSE TREE HUGGERS RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, WE CAN
JUST THROW THEM THE KEYS.
ALL RIGHT.
THROW THEM THE KEYS.
[ SPLASHING SOUND ]
OH, DARN, THEY WENT
IN THE LAKE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I GOT A CHAIN CUTTER.
NO-O-O!
YOU KNOW, FOR MOST
MIDDLE-AGED GUYS,
THE BEST LABOUR-SAVING DEVICE
IS A TEENAGER.
THERE AREN'T AS MANY
AROUND AS THERE USED TO BE.
NOT EVEN KIDS
OF ANY AGE, ACTUALLY.
THIS ABANDONED PLAYGROUND IS
ANOTHER INDICATION THAT
THE BIRTH RATE'S BEEN GOING
DOWN OVER THE LAST FEW YEARS.
I GUESS THIS ISN'T THE
ONLY PLAYTIME EQUIPMENT
THAT'S NOT GETTING MUCH USE.
SO INSTEAD OF WHINING ABOUT
NOT HAVING A TEENAGER,
WHICH WOULD BE TAKING IRONY
TO A WHOLE NEW LEVEL,
I'M GOING TO TAKE ALL THIS
BABY BOOM PLAYGEAR
AND TURN IT INTO A DANDY
AUTOMATIC FIREWOOD SPLITTER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
FIRST, I'LL TURN THIS
SLIDE INTO A CHUTE
TO USE AS A HOPPER
FOR THE WHOLE UNIT.
NOT MUCH OF A
STRETCH, REALLY.
IF YOU GO DOWN THIS BABY WITH
A PAIR OF SHORTS ON A HOT DAY,
YOU'LL TURN INTO A BIT
OF A HOPPER YOURSELF.
ALL I GOT TO DO NOW IS ATTACH
THE OIL DRUM ONTO THE SLIDE.
I GOTTA TAKE THE BOTTOM
OUT OF HER FIRST.
THERE'S A LUCKY BREAK.
THE BOTTOM'S ALREADY
RUSTED OUT OF THIS UNIT.
TOXIC WASTE
CAN BE OUR FRIEND.
YOU KNOW, IF DUCT TAPE IS THE
HANDYMAN'S BEST FRIEND,
THEN THE BUNGEE CORD HAS
GOT TO BE HIS GOLFING BUDDY.
WE'LL USE A
COUPLE OF THEM HERE
TO MAKE A SPRING-LOADED
TRAP DOOR ON THE SLIDE.
IT'S REALLY A STOPPER
FOR THE HOPPER ON MY CHOPPER.
NOW ALL I GOT TO DO IS
GET THE SLIDE HIGH ENOUGH
AND AT THE RIGHT ANGLE
SO THAT THE BARS ON THE
CAROUSEL WILL HIT THE
HOCKEY STICK.
OF COURSE,
YOU KNEW THAT.
OKAY, THERE'S MY
HOPPER/FEEDER.
NOW WE NEED THE
CHOPPER/SPLITTER.
AND FOR THAT ALL
I NEED TO DO
IS TO MOUNT SOMETHING HEAVY ON
THE END OF THE TEETER-TOTTER
AND THEN MOUNT THIS AXE UNDER
THE SEAT FACING DOWN LIKE THAT.
THEN WHEN THE LOG COMES
ROUND ON THE CAROUSEL,
SHE'LL DROP DOWN AND
SPLIT HER RIGHT IN HALF.
I SUPPOSE I COULD
HAVE MOUNTED THIS UNIT
ON THERE INSTEAD OF AN AXE,
BUT THEN IT WOULDN'T BE
A TEETER-TOTTER, WOULD IT?
IT WOULD BE A SEE-SAW.
I'M USING A CAR
ENGINE AS MY WEIGHT.
AN OLD FLAT-HEAD FOUR
'CAUSE I'M SPLITTING
PINE AND BIRCH.
BUT IF YOU'RE WORKING IN OAK
OR ANY OF THE FRUIT WOODS,
YOU MIGHT WANT TO GO WITH
A BIG BLOCK HEMI OR A
DIESEL ON THAT.
YOU CAN SEE HOW THAT MUCH
WEIGHT IS GOING TO BRING
THE AXE DOWN
HARDER THAN A C.E.O.
AFTER A BOARD MEETING.
THE TRICK IS HOW DO I GET
THE AXE TO GO BACK UP?
OH, THERE WE GO.
A ROUND-TOP
PICNIC TABLE.
PERFECT.
THEY MUST HAVE KNOWN WE
WERE GOING TO DO THIS
WHEN THEY BUILT IT.
OKAY, NOW, AS THE
CAROUSEL GOES AROUND,
THESE ARMS ARE GOING
TO LIFT UP THE TEETER-TOTTER,
RAISE THE AXE UP INTO
POSITION TO COME DOWN
AND SPLIT THE NEXT LOG.
REMEMBER WHEN THIS CAROUSEL
WAS JUST A WASTE OF TIME
AND ENERGY?
OH, I KNOW.
SOME OF YOU HANDYMEN ARE
THINKING, "WAIT A SEC, RED.
"SOMEBODY'S STILL GOT
TO TURN ON THE CAROUSEL,
"AND THAT'S WAY
TOO MUCH WORK FOR ME."
OH, YE OF LITTLE FAITH.
THAT'S WHY THIS CAR
IS FRONT-WHEEL DRIVE.
[ CIRCUS MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, YOU SEE
THOSE YOUNG GUYS ON TV,
SKATEBOARDING DOWN
THE FREEWAY,
JUMPING OFF OF
OFFICE BUILDINGS
WITH NOTHING
TO SAVE THEM
EXCEPT SPECIAL SPORT
SUNGLASSES
AND SHOES THAT COST
MORE THAN YOUR CAR.
WATCHING THOSE IDIOTS
RISK THEIR LIVES
CAN MAKE US HIGH MILEAGE GUYS
FEEL A LITTLE STODGY.
ESPECIALLY IF YOU HAVE TO
REST TWICE WALKING UP
YOUR OWN DRIVEWAY.
WELL, DON'T BE FOOLED.
WE ARE EVERY BIT
AS BRAVE AS THEY ARE.
HOW CAN YOU COMPARE BUNGEE
JUMPING OFF A BRIDGE
WITH THE RISK YOU RUN EVERY
TIME YOU DOZE OFF ON THE COUCH
IN A HOUSE FULL OF TEENAGERS?
THINK OF THE TIMES
YOU DELIBERATELY PUT
YOURSELF IN HARM'S WAY
JUST BY TRUTHFULLY ANSWERING
YOUR WIFE'S QUESTIONS.
DO I LOOK FAT?
HOW DO YOU LIKE MY NEW HAT?
WHY DON'T YOU EVER
LET ME DRIVE?
THAT TAKES GUTS;
NOT MUCH GLORY.
BUT AT LEAST YOU DON'T NEED
SPECIAL SUNGLASSES TO DO IT.
THESE YOUNGSTERS DON'T HAVE
HALF THE JAM THAT WE HAVE.
SO THEY RISK THEIR LIVES FOR A
FEW SECONDS IN A CHEAP THRILL.
AT OUR AGE, YOU AND I
RISK OUR LIVES CONSTANTLY.
EVERY TIME WE PICK UP A
SHOVEL OF WET SNOW
OR EAT A BACON SANDWICH
OR GO TO BED
BEFORE WE'RE TIRED.
REMEMBER.
I'LL PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, OUR BIG CITY GARBAGE
PROJECT IS MOVING FORWARD.
WE'RE CLEARING ALL OUR
LOW-CLASS COUNTRY JUNK
OFF OF THE LODGE PROPERTY
SO WE CAN MAKE ROOM FOR THE
HIGH-QUALITY MEGA-CITY GARBAGE.
RED, I FOUND THIS TIE
DOWN BY THE HORSESHOE PIT.
IT WAS HOLDING UP A
LEG OF A PICNIC TABLE.
CAN I HAVE IT?
UH, NO,
BUT I TELL YOU WHAT.
I'LL TRADE IT
FOR YOUR TIE.
YOU DON'T NEED A TIE.
YOU'VE GOT A BEARD.
HEY, DID YOU GUYS SEE THIS
LETTER FROM THE TORONTO
SANITATION DEPARTMENT?
WE'RE GOING TO GET
MONEY ON THIS DEAL.
LET'S SEE THAT.
HOW MUCH MONEY?
100 BUCKS.
OH, 100 BUCKS.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING
TO SAY A FEW THOUSAND BUCKS.
100 BUCKS
IS NOTHING.
OH, OKAY, MAYBE TO
A SMALL-TIME OPERATOR --
TO YOU IT'S A BIG DEAL,
BUT TO AN ENTREPRENEUR
LIKE MYSELF
THAT'S CHICKEN FEED.
NO, NO, NO, NO, GUYS.
WE GOTTA PAY THEM 100 BUCKS.
WHAT?
100 BUCKS
IS A LOT OF MONEY.
WHAT DO WE OWE
THEM MONEY FOR?
OH, THEY SAY THE LODGE
IS TOO FAR FROM
THE HIGHWAY.
THEY'VE GOTTA BRING
THE GARBAGE
IN SMALLER TRUCKS
OR SOMETHING.
OH, Mr GREEN, I HAD MY
HEART SET ON THAT GARBAGE.
IT SERVES AN EX-CON
RIGHT FOR HAVING A DREAM.
IT'S A STINKING,
LOUSY WORLD.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I BET OTHER CITIES
HAVE A GARBAGE
PROBLEM, TOO.
MAYBE THEY'D
BE INTERESTED.
WHAT?
LIKE NEW YORK OR RENO?
CLEVELAND!
WHAT?
NO, NO, I'M
THINKING OF HOUSTON.
GET SOME OF THAT NASA ROCKET
GARBAGE UP HERE TO THE LODGE.
WE COULD HAVE SOME FUN
WITH THAT, WOULDN'T WE?
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
THAT WOULD PUT POSSUM LAKE
RIGHT ON THE MAP.
ABSOLUTELY.
I CAN SEE THE HEADLINE.
"NASA ROCKET GARBAGE
LANDS AT POSSUM LODGE."
"ONE SMALL DUMP FOR MAN,
"ONE GIANT DUMP FOR MANKIND."
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELCOME TO THE
EXPERTS PORTION OF THE SHOW,
WHERE WE EXPLORE THOSE
THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
Audience: "I DON'T KNOW."
AND JOINING RED TODAY, WE HAVE
MARINA OPERATOR --
WELL, SOMETIMES OPERATOR,
DWIGHT CARDIFF.
[ APPLAUSE AND CHEERING ]
TODAY'S LETTER
READS AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS.
I AM ENCLOSING A
PHOTO OF MY NEW PUPPY.
"HIS NAME IS SPOT.
"I'VE NEVER OWNED
A DOG BEFORE,
"BUT I KNOW THEY NEED
A LOT OF EXERCISE.
"HOW OFTEN SHOULD
I WALK SPOT?"
AND IT'S FROM ADAM.
OKAY, WELL, ADAM,
I WOULD SUGGEST YOU WALK
YOUR PUPPY AFTER EVERY MEAL;
OTHERWISE, YOU'RE GOING TO
FIND OUT WHY HE'S CALLED SPOT.
OKAY, ADAM, I SUGGEST
IF YOU STILL HAVE
THE RECEIPT,
THAT YOU RETURN SPOT
AND GET YOURSELF
AN OLDER DOG.
OLD DOGS DON'T NEED
TO BE WALKED
BECAUSE THEY HAVE NO
EXTRA ENERGY IN THEIR
SYSTEMS WHATSOEVER.
PLUS THEY'VE PROBABLY
BEEN FIXED,
WHICH ACCOUNTS FOR THEIR
LACK OF INTEREST IN
LIFE WHATSOEVER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I GUESS THAT'S WHY OLD
DOGS CAN'T TURN NEW TRICKS.
LEARN NEW TRICKS.
BETTER YET, RETURN SPOT
AND MAKE FRIENDS WITH
YOUR NEIGHBOUR'S DOG.
THAT WAY YOU STILL HAVE
A FRIEND TO PLAY FETCH WITH,
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO
FEED IT OR WALK IT OR
CLEAN UP AFTER IT.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK
ADAM IS GOING TO BE TAKING
HIS NEW PUPPY BACK, DWIGHT.
OKAY, IF HE INSISTS
ON KEEPING THE DOG,
THEN MY ADVICE IS TO PROP THE
DOOR OPEN WITH SOMETHING.
THAT WAY HE CAN COME
AND GO AS HE PLEASES.
DOGS'LL WALK THEMSELVES
IF YOU LET THEM.
JUST REMEMBER TO
LEAVE HIS COLLAR OFF
SO NOBODY KNOWS HE'S YOURS.
SO YOU'RE TELLING ADAM
TO LET SPOT RUN AROUND
LIKE A WILD ANIMAL?
WELL, NOT WILD.
TAME BUT WITH A LOT OF
INDIVIDUAL DISCRETION.
WELL, YEAH, BUT DWIGHT,
IF HE DOESN'T HAVE
HIS COLLAR OR TAGS
HE'S GOING TO BE CONSIDERED
A STRAY AND JUST END UP
BACK IN THE POUND.
THEN WHAT?
THEN ADAM GOES
BACK DOWN TO THE POUND,
ADOPTS IT,
AND IT'S HIS AGAIN.
HAVE YOU EVER
HAD A PET, DWIGHT?
I USED TO
HAVE A SNAIL.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO IT, DWIGHT?
IT RAN AWAY ON ME.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
Red: HAD A LITTLE PROBLEM.
HAD A HOLE IN THE ROOF
OF ONE OF OUR SHEDS.
I DUNNO HOW IT GOT THERE,
BUT, UH, WE HAD TO FIX THAT UP
I HAD SOME SHINGLES
I THOUGHT WALTER WAS
GOING TO HELP, BUT I
DON'T KNOW WHERE WALTER IS.
WAIT A SEC.
THAT'S ABOUT THE SIZE
OF THE HOLE IN THE --
OH, WHAT WAS THAT...
THAT'S A CONCRETE BLOCK THERE
OH, UH, UH --
UH, UH --
WE'RE FINE.
DALTON, DON'T
WORRY ABOUT IT.
OH, THERE IT IS.
SO I SEND WALTER OVER
FOR A LADDER.
HE'S GOING TO CLIMB
UP ON THE ROOF.
NOW, THAT'S NOT THE LADDER
I WOULD HAVE CHOSEN, WALTER.
DID YOU REALLY
THINK THIS THROUGH?
WALTER, GO GET A
DECENT-SIZED LADDER.
IT'S NOT EASY.
DON'T GET UP, DALTON.
ALL RIGHT, THERE YOU GO.
UP YOU GO.
I'LL THROW THE
SHINGLES UP TO YOU.
WAY YOU GO.
GET UP THERE.
UP YOU GO.
OH-H-H.
WELL, NOW YOU'VE
GOT A PROBLEM.
YOU CAN'T --
OH, HERE WE GO.
THERE YOU ARE.
ALL RIGHT.
HE'LL GET UP THERE,
AND I'LL JUST THROW
HIM UP THE SHINGLES.
SHOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM.
CAREFUL NOW,
IT'S SLIPPERY.
OH, OH, OH.
OH. OH!
THERE THEY ARE.
THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT, SO WE'VE GOT
ALL THE SHINGLES LAID OUT.
NOW ALL HE NEEDS IS JUST THE
HAMMER, JUST HAMMER THEM DOWN
OH! OH, BOY.
DALTON'S NO HELP.
THERE YOU GO.
HE'S PUT THE SHINGLES ON SO
WELL, HE CAN'T TELL WHERE
THE HOLE IS.
OH, NO. NO. NO.
THAT'S RIGHT.
NO, NO, NO!
OH-H-H!
THERE WE GO.
JOB'S DONE!
DOESN'T IT BUG YOU WHEN
YOU'RE SITTING DOWN TO
WATCH A FOOTBALL GAME
OR READ THE PAPER
OR JUST TO REDUCE THE SURPLUS
OF FERMENTED BEVERAGES
IN YOUR HOME,
AND THERE'S A
KNOCK AT THE DOOR.
IT'S NEVER ANYTHING
YOU'RE INTERESTED IN.
SOME GUY SELLING SOMETHING
OR RECRUITING YOU FOR HIS CULT.
OR THAT NOSY WOMAN
WITH THE COURT ORDER
TO CLEAN UP YOUR YARD.
WELL, HERE'S A QUICK, EASY
WAY TO MAINTAIN YOUR PRIVACY.
THESE THINGS ARE CALLED
HALF-BRICKS.
THEY'RE CHEAP
AND THEY'RE HANDY;
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE
HALF-A-BRICK SHORT OF A LOAD.
YOU WANT TO COVER THE WHOLE
FRONT OF THE HOUSE WITH
THESE BABIES.
JUST MAKE SURE YOU GO RIGHT
OVER THE DOOR AND EVERYTHING,
THEN YOU'RE READY FOR THE NEXT
GUY WHO COMES A-KNOCKING.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
WELL, WE HAD EVERYTHING
ALL SORTED OUT.
WE AGREED TO PAY TORONTO 100
BUCKS FOR THEIR GARBAGE,
AND THEY GUARANTEED US
THREE CAR PARTS AND 12
APPLIANCES IN EVERY LOAD.
WELL, IT WAS OUR
ONLY ALTERNATIVE.
ALL THE OTHER CITIES WE
CONTACTED WEREN'T INTERESTED.
EXCEPT FOR CHERNOBYL.
SO WE'RE ALL SET
TO RECEIVE THE FIRST LOAD.
THE GUYS ARE ALL
EXCITED AND EVERYTHING.
AND AS USUAL,
THE GOVERNMENT STEPS IN,
SCREWS UP THE WHOLE THING.
RED, NOW, WAIT.
LET'S BE FAIR.
THEY'RE TRYING TO
PROTECT THE ENVIRONMENT.
YEAH, THESE GUYS
COME IN WITH THEIR
FANCY LAB COATS,
START TAKING SOIL
AND WATER SAMPLES.
OH, YEAH, THEY SUSPECTED THE
LODGE PROPERTY CONTAINED
CONTAMINANTS.
WELL, DUH!
YOU'RE ONLY ALLOWED SO
MANY PARTS PER MILLION
OF TOXIC PARTICLES
IN YOUR ENVIRONMENT.
APPARENTLY, WE'D ALREADY
HIT OUR QUOTA.
YEAH, SO THEY KILLED
THE DEAL,
PUT THE KIBOSH ON IT.
NO MORE BIG-CITY
GARBAGE IN OUR FUTURE.
I'M GOING
TO NEED A MOMENT.
Audience: AH-H-H.
IT GETS WORSE.
THEY WON'T EVEN LET
US LEAVE OUR JUNK
LYING AROUND.
THEY ORDERED US TO
CLEAN UP THE LODGE AND
OUR WHOLE END OF THE LAKE.
Audience: AH-H-H.
YOU KNOW,
THEY'RE TRYING
TO SAVE THE PLANET.
IF WE DO THE CLEANUP THEN
THE LODGE AND THE LAKE
WILL BE HERE 100
YEARS FROM NOW.
ISN'T THAT IMPORTANT
TO YOU GUYS?
I DON'T THINK SO.
NO, NOT REALLY.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, MEETING TIME.
YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
TELL EVERYBODY
THE NEWS.
DO YOU NEED A HUG?
I DON'T NEED --
GET OUT OF HERE!
NOT FROM HIM, ANYWAY.
SPEAKING OF HUGS, IF MY
WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU'RE
ALWAYS SAYING THAT THE
CITY IS SO FAR AHEAD OF US
IN CLOTHES AND COFFEE SHOPS
AND YOUTH CRIME.
WELL, APPARENTLY,
WHEN IT COMES TO POLLUTION,
WE'RE SMOKING THEM.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Winston: OKAY, EVERYBODY.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
Mike: YOU GOTTA SIT DOWN.
Dalton: SIT. SIT. SIT.
Mike: SIT DOWN, NOW.
Winston: ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
OKAY, GUYS, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, GUYS, AS YOU KNOW,
WE'VE GOT TO CLEAN UP THE AREA.
I'M LOOKING FOR
THE OWNER OF A CAR.
IT'S A 1982 PACER WAGON.
DIDN'T KNOW THEY WERE THAT --
OKAY, THIS ONE'S BROWN
WITH A DIRTY BROWN INTERIOR.
OKAY, UH, THE LICENSE
NUMBER I-M-A-D-V-8.
OKAY, TEDDY,
YOU'VE GOT 24 HOURS TO GET
YOUR CAR OUT OF THE BOTTOM
OF THE LAKE.