AS MANY OF YOU KNOW,
NOTHING PLEASES ME MORE
THAN TO TAKE
EXISTING TECHNOLOGY
AND USE IT IN AN
ENTIRELY NEW APPLICATION.
YOU KNOW, TO A LOT OF MEN,
THIS IS THE HIGHEST FORM
OF CREATIVITY,
AND IT'S PROBABLY THE REASON
WE NEVER READ INSTRUCTIONS.
LIKE, THIS HERE'S
A WINDOW BLIND, EH?
WHEN YOU PULL THIS DOWN,
YOU CAN COVER THE WINDOW,
AND SHE LOCKS.
THEN WHEN YOU GIVE
HER A LITTLE TUG,
UP SHE GOES.
SEE, THERE'S A SPRING IN THERE
THAT MAKES THIS UNIT INTO
A LITTLE MACHINE.
AND I'M THINKING JUST USING
SOMETHING LIKE THAT TO
COVER A WINDOW
IS A WASTE OF MACHINERY.
ISN'T IT A LOT SMARTER
TO USE A BLIND
AS AN AUTOMATIC
TABLE CLEARER?
[ CHUCKLES ]
SEE WHAT I'VE DONE HERE?
I'VE ACTUALLY ATTACHED A BLIND
TO THESE TWO HOCKEY STICKS.
AND THEN I PULLED HER DOWN
TO THE END OF THE TABLE
AND LOCKED HER BEFORE
WE HAD THE PICNIC.
THIS GOALIE STICK HERE IS TO
STOP THE GARBAGE IN ITS TRACKS
AND THEN DROP HER
INTO THE CAN.
NO DEFLECTIONS.
NO REBOUNDS.
NOW ALL I HAVE TO DO IS PULL
ON THE END OF THE BLIND.
HE SHOOTS...
HE SCORES.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
APPRECIATE IT.
WOW!
HEY, YOU'VE DONE THIS BEFORE.
ALL RIGHT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
ACTUALLY BUSTER HADFIELD
HAD AN ACCIDENT.
HE SLIPPED AND FELL
ONTO THE CONVEYOR BELT
DOWN AT THE SOFT
DRINK FACTORY THERE.
MACHINERY HOSED HIM
DOWN WITH TONIC WATER,
STUFFED BOTTLES ONTO HIS TOES
AND CAPPED ALL HIS TEETH.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I'M JUST OBSERVING.
CARRY ON.
JUST OBSERVING.
I WAS JUST TELLING THEM
ABOUT BUSTER HAVING THE
ACCIDENT AT WORK.
OH! YEAH!
OKAY, SO ANYWAYS,
WE TOOK HIM OVER
TO THE HOSPITAL.
WHEN WE TOLD THE NURSES
WHAT HAD HAPPENED,
THEY ALL
STARTED LAUGHING.
THEY GET ON THE INTERCOM,
THEY PAGE DR. PEPPER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
PARDON ME?
YOU'RE MAKING
THAT UP.
WELL, I'M -- I'M
EMBELLISHING, HAROLD.
BUSTER HAD AN
ACCIDENT AT WORK,
AND I'M JUST KINDA FLESHING
IT OUT FOR THE SHOW.
OH! OH!
OKAY.
OKAY. YEAH.
YEAH. OKAY.
PEOPLE DON'T
LIKE THAT ANYMORE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE
LATEST FAD IS?
KNOW WHAT THE LATEST FAD IS?
JUSTIFIABLE HOMICIDE?
NO! REALITY TELEVISION.
NO MADE UP STORIES.
NO EXAGGERATIONS.
JUST THE RAW TRUTH, BABY.
YOU CAN'T HANDLE
THE RAW TRUTH, BABY.
NO, ACTUALLY
IT'S TRUE.
RED...
HAROLD TELLS ME THAT
YOU'VE BEEN SAYING
ANN MARIE AND I
HAVE A SHAKY MARRIAGE.
WHAT?!
THIS IS GOOD.
IT'S GOOD.
YOU HAVE BEEN SAYING
THAT ANN MARIE AND I
HAVE A SHAKY MARRIAGE!
NO, I HAVEN'T.
WELL, THEN WHO'S
BEEN SAYING IT?
BECAUSE SOMEBODY'S
BEEN SAYING IT!
YOU SAY IT ALL
THE TIME, DALTON.
[ LAUGHTER ]
YEAH.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING, HAROLD?
THE RATINGS ARE GONNA
GO THROUGH THE ROOF.
YOU'LL BE RIGHT
BEHIND 'EM.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TONIGHT'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FOR A FREE SESSION AT
POSSUM LAKE'S ONLY OXYGEN BAR,
TO AIR IS HUMAN.
YOU AND A FRIEND ARE
INVITED FOR A FULL HOUR
OF HEAVY BREATHING.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
EARS THERE, DALTON.
OKAY, RED, YOU'VE
GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON HUMPHRIES
TO SAY THIS WORD...
ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, DALTON, UM, BLONDE
PEOPLE HAVE THIS KIND
OF HAIR.
BLEACHED.
NO, OKAY.
NO. NO.
IF SOMEBODY IS REASONABLE,
RATIONAL, OPEN-MINDED,
YOU WOULD SAY THEY ARE...
NOT MARRIED TO ME.
OKAY. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, IF SOMETHING
IS NOT SO GOOD
BUT, YOU KNOW,
NOT TOO BAD,
JUST KIND OF TOLERABLE,
YOU WOULD CALL THAT...
LIFE?
OKAY, OKAY, NO.
OKAY, NO, IF SOMETHING
IS GOOD,
LIKE IN THE WEATHER, OKAY,
THE WORD FOR THAT IS...
W-W-WAIT A SECOND.
YOU'RE SAYING THAT ONE
WORD MEANS BOTH GOOD
AND NOT GOOD?
YEAH.
ACTUALLY, YEAH.
OKAY, WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT,
I DON'T USE WORDS WITH
TWO DIFFERENT MEANING.
I LEAVE THAT TO MY WIFE.
YOU GUYS ARE ALMOST
OUTTA TIME NOW.
UM, LET'S GO
ANOTHER WAY.
THIS IS A WORD THAT MEANS,
LIKE, TRADE EXHIBITION
OR CARNIVAL.
HAVE YOU BEEN LISTENING
TO THE CLUES, RED?
I MEAN, COME ON.
BLONDE, REASONABLE,
GOOD, NOT GOOD
AND NOW CARNIVAL!
I MEAN, COME ON.
ONE WORD MEANS ALL THAT.
IT'S NOT FAIR!
YES, IT IS!
Mike:
YOU KNOW WHAT I'VE
BEEN THINKING ABOUT?
Red: NEVER.
Mike:
LIFE AFTER DEATH.
I'VE BEEN THINKING
A LOT ABOUT IT.
Dalton:
SOUNDS LIKE HIS
TRIAL GOT MOVED TO TEXAS.
Mike:
AH, COME ON.
DON'T YOU EVER
THINK ABOUT IT?
Red: NOT ME.
BUT IF WE'RE GONNA FOCUS
ON THE THINGS I DON'T
THINK ABOUT,
WE'RE IN FOR
A LONG DAY.
Dalton: WELL, I THINK
ABOUT LIFE AFTER DEATH
EVERY TIME ANN MARIE
AND I HAVE AN ARGUMENT.
Mike: WELL, I DON'T
THINK ABOUT IT THAT OFTEN.
IT'S JUST THAT I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT THIS IS ALL THERE IS.
Red: WHAT IS?
Mike: JUST THIS POND,
THIS BAY, THIS BOAT.
IT CAN'T BE ALL THERE IS.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA STEAL A
BIGGER BOAT, ARE YOU, MIKE?
NO, THAT'S MY POINT.
SEE, WE DON'T NEED
OUR REWARDS IN THIS LIFE.
OH, I DO!
WELL, I DON'T.
WELL, GOOD, THEN I'LL
HAVE YOURS TOO.
NO, SEE, THAT'S WHAT
THE AFTERLIFE IS FOR.
I THINK IT'S A PLACE WHERE
THERE ARE FRIENDLY PEOPLE
WHO KNOW YOUR NAME AND
THINK POSITIVE THOUGHTS
AND HAVE SING-SONGS.
Dalton:
WOW, HOPE I NEVER DIE.
Red:
YOU KNOW, MIKE,
IT SEEMS ODD
THAT A KNOWN FELON WOULD BE
THINKING ABOUT THIS KIND
OF STUFF.
I WOULD THINK YOU'D BE MORE
CONCERNED WITH LIFE
AFTER THEFT.
Mike:
NOW, YOU SEE,
THAT IS HURTFUL, MR. GREEN.
THE AFTERLIFE WILL
NOT BE JUDGMENTAL,
NOT THE WAY
I ENVISION IT.
Red: NOT JUDGMENTAL?
NOPE.
Red: JUDGMENT DAY
WON'T BE JUDGMENTAL?
HE'S TWISTING
MY WORDS.
Dalton:
I'M OKAY WITH IT.
Red:
YOU KNOW, MIKE, MAYBE
REINCARNATION'S THE ANSWER.
MAYBE WE'LL
ALL COME BACK.
MAYBE WE'VE ALREADY
BEEN HERE BEFORE.
Mike:
WELL, NOW, THAT'S
AN INTERESTING CONCEPT.
YOU'D MAKE AN EXCELLENT
CELL MATE, MR. GREEN.
Red: NO, THANKS, MIKE.
[ LOON CALLS ]
Mike:
WELL, I STILL BELIEVE
IN LIFE AFTER DEATH.
Red: THAT'S FINE.
Dalton:
I'M HOPING FOR
LIFE AFTER BIRTH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
MY GRANDFATHER HAD
ONE OF THESE BABIES.
[ GRUNTS ]
IT'S CALLED A PUSH MOWER.
HE USED TO CUT THE
GRASS EVERY SATURDAY.
HE'D USUALLY WAIT
TILL THE AFTERNOON,
WHEN HIS HEAD
HAD STOPPED POUNDING
AND HIS VISION HAD
CLEARED UP A LITTLE BIT.
YOU KNOW, MEN CAN BE VERY
COMPETITIVE ABOUT THEIR LAWNS.
I'M SURE YOU WOULDN'T MIND
HAVING THE NICEST LAWN
ON THE STREET,
BUT IF YOU'RE A
HANDYMAN LIKE ME,
YOU DON'T WANT
A PUSH MOWER.
YOU WANNA PUSH LESS.
SO TO DO THAT YOU'RE
GONNA NEED A FEW THINGS.
FIRST OF ALL, THREE OR
FOUR OF THESE UNITS,
BECAUSE "MOWER" IS NOT LESS;
MOWER IS DEFINITELY MORE.
AND ALONG WITH THAT YOU'LL
NEED A COUPLE OF SALT SHAKERS,
A TOY GUN,
SOME LIQUID FERTILIZER,
SOME GRASS SEED,
SOME WILDFLOWER SEED,
A LITTLE BIT OF
WEED KILLER
AND, OF COURSE,
A FEW HOCKEY STICKS.
AND NATURALLY YOU'RE
GOING TO NEED A K-CAR,
WHICH THESE DAYS ARE PRETTY
MUCH RESTRICTED TO YARD
WORK ANYWAY.
OKAY, THAT TAKES CARE
OF THE GRASS CUTTING,
BUT WE HAVEN'T BEGUN
TO SCRATCH THE SURFACE
IN TERMS OF WHAT
WE CAN DO TO THIS LAWN.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S
REAL GOOD?
AERATING.
OF COURSE, THE SECRET HERE IS
NOT TO LET THE SCREW
GO TOO FAR INTO THE --
[ TIRE DEFLATING ]
SEE, I GOT DISTRACTED THERE.
BUT IT'S OKAY
BECAUSE I ALWAYS HAVE A CAN
OF THIS TIRE SEALANT
RIGHT NEARBY
PERFECT.
OH, AND I MADE A
FEW OTHER ALTERATIONS
THAT I FEEL AWFUL
GOOD ABOUT.
I FILLED THE TRUNK
WITH GRASS SEED.
THAT'LL JUST DROP NATURALLY
THROUGH THE TRUNK FLOOR,
THROUGH WHAT I CALL
THE MIRACLE OF RUST.
AND HERE'S A NICE TOUCH.
YOU KNOW HOW EVERYBODY
LIKES WILDFLOWERS
KIND OF SPREAD RANDOMLY
THROUGH THE YARD?
SO I FILLED THESE SALT SHAKERS
WITH WILDFLOWER SEEDS.
SAFEST WAY I KNOW
TO SOW YOUR WILD OATS.
OKAY, HERE'S A
FUN THING NOW.
I FILLED THE WINDSHIELD WASHER
RESERVOIR WITH WEED KILLER,
AND I RAN THE HOSE
UP THROUGH THIS TOY GUN.
SO NOW WHEN I'M DRIVING
ALONG CUTTING THE LAWN,
AND I SEE A WEED LIKE THAT
DANDELION OVER THERE,
I JUST AIM THE GUN,
LINE HER UP WITH MY
RADIO ANTENNA CONTROL,
AND THEN HIT THE
WINDSHIELD WASHER BUTTON.
THE ONLY TRICKY PART
WAS TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO SPREAD
THE FERTILIZER,
SOMETHING I DON'T
USUALLY HAVE A PROBLEM WITH.
AND THEN I'M THINKING,
HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
YOU KNOW THEY MAKE
GASOLINE SO GOOD NOW
THAT YOU CAN AFFORD TO
DILUTE IT A LITTLE BIT.
SO I FIGURE,
HECK, YOU KNOW,
I'LL JUST FIRE
THIS RIGHT IN HERE
AND LET THE ENGINE
DO THE WORK.
I EVEN ADDED A NOZZLE
TO MY TAIL PIPE
TO TRY TO GIVE ME A
LITTLE MORE COVERAGE.
THE FERTILIZER WON'T BURN,
AND THE GAS JUST
BECOMES A PROPELLANT.
KIND OF LIKE WHAT
KIDNEY BEANS DO FOR CHILI.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I HAVE WORK TO DO,
ALL THE WHILE LISTENING
TO MY FAVOURITE SONG...
"THE GREEN, GREEN
GRASS OF HOME".
[ STATIC ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
I WANNA TALK ABOUT CELLULAR
PHONES FOR A MINUTE.
YOU KNOW, IN THE OLD DAYS,
YOU'D SEE A GUY
WALKING DOWN THE STREET
JABBERING AWAY INTO THIN AIR,
YOU WOULD NEVER THINK
OF THE WORD "PHONE",
JUST THE WORD "CELL".
NOW WE GOT ALL THESE NUTS
DRIVING AROUND
TALKING ON THE PHONE WITH
ONLY ONE HAND ON THE WHEEL --
OH, SURE, I KNOW,
IN A FIT OF ROAD RAGE,
YOU'D OFTEN TAKE ONE
HAND OFF THE WHEEL
TO COMMUNICATE
WITH ANOTHER DRIVER.
BUT THAT WAS A TOTALLY
DIFFERENT KIND OF
DIGITAL SIGNAL.
AND YOU KNOW
THESE CELL PHONES,
THEY DON'T EVEN RING.
THEY PLAY LITTLE TUNES
OR JINGLES OR SOMETHING.
AND THEY ALWAYS GO
OFF AT THE WRONG TIME,
LIKE AT CHURCH, EH?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT
EVEN YOUR PHONE,
BUT EVERYONE TURNS AROUND
TO SEE WHERE THE SOUND'S
COMING FROM,
AND THERE YOU ARE
SITTING THERE SOUND ASLEEP.
SEE, NOW, TO ME A
CELL PHONE IS JUST A LEASH...
IF YOU DON'T COME
WHEN YOU'RE CALLED,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BE TOP DOG FOR LONG.
WHENEVER I SEE A
PERSON ON A CELL PHONE,
THEY'RE ALWAYS
TALKING TO SOMEBODY,
BUT THEY'RE WALKING AROUND
THE ROOM TRYING TO GET
A CLEAR SIGNAL.
IF YOU WANT A CLEAR SIGNAL,
GO OVER TO THE PERSON'S HOUSE,
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
CELL PHONES ARE GREAT FOR
EMERGENCIES OR SOMETHING,
BUT IF YOU'RE USING IT
TO COMMUNICATE WITH YOUR
FRIENDS OR LOVED ONES,
YOU'RE GONNA EVENTUALLY
BE DISCONNECTED,
AND THAT'LL RUIN
YOUR ENTIRE WEEKEND,
NO MATTER HOW MANY
FREE MINUTES YOU GET.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ ROMANTIC ]
[ DIALED PHONE RINGING ]
HELLO?
DAD?
TIM.
HOW ARE YOU?
HEY.
I'M GOOD, YEAH.
HOW'S MOM?
SHE'S FINE.
WE'RE BOTH FINE.
SO YOU COMING HOME
FOR THE HOLIDAYS?
WELL, THINGS ARE PRETTY
BUSY OVER HERE, DAD.
I SEE.
- I JUST --
-
YEAH?
WELL, I WAS JUST
CALLING TO SAY I --
I REALLY MISS YOU GUYS.
THANKS, SON.
IT SURE IS GOOD TO HEAR YOU.
[ TOILET OVERFLOWING ]
WHAT THE --
OH! IT'S EVERYWHERE!
HELLO?
DAD?
SOME CALLS CAN WAIT;
SOME CAN'T.
Harold:
IT'S GONNA BE GREAT.
BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY WE NEED TO DO
THIS AT ALL.
BECAUSE IT GETS PEOPLE
UP TO POSSUM LODGE.
AND THE BEST WAY TO DO
THAT IS THROUGH THE TV SHOW,
BUT IF NO ONE'S
WATCHING THE SHOW,
LA LA LA.
WELL, WE GOT PEOPLE
LIKE ME WATCHING.
WE JUST DON'T HAVE
PEOPLE LIKE YOU WATCHING.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
PROUD OF THAT.
BUT UNCLE RED, I CHECKED WITH
THE NEILSON PEOPLE,
AND OUR RATINGS WHEN YOU WERE
ARGUING WITH DALTON,
OUR RATINGS WERE WAY
UP ON THAT FIRST SEGMENT.
WE'RE DEFINITELY ON
THE RIGHT TRACK HERE.
BOY, I DON'T
THINK SO, HAROLD.
OKAY,
WE ARE WALKING.
YOU COULD USE
THE EXERCISE.
NO, HE MEANS WE'RE
WALKING FROM THE SHOW.
WE DON'T LIKE
THE TENSION;
THE ANIMOSITY;
IT'S TOO MUCH LIKE
BEING AT WORK.
BEING AT HOME.
WELL, I'M SORRY, YOU'RE
BOTH UNDER CONTRACT.
YOU CAN'T LEAVE.
YEAH? WELL, YOU KNOW WHERE
YOU CAN STICK YOUR CONTRACT.
GIVE ME A CALL IF
YOU NEED SOME HELP
GETTING IT BACK OUT.
COME ON, WINSTON.
OH, UNCLE RED,
THIS IS GREAT TELEVISION!
WELL, YOU'LL LOVE
THIS NEXT PART...
I'M WITH THEM.
[ LAUGHTER ]
Red (voice over)
WALTER WAS DRIVING OUT
BY PORT ASBESTOS.
HE HAD A BIG LOAD ON THE
TRAILER AND HE HAD HIS
LITTLE K-CAR.
NOT AS RELIANT AS THE
NAME SOMETIMES.
JUST A LITTLE FOUR-BANGER,
JUST STARTING TO OVERHEAT
A LITTLE BIT,
AND HE PULLED OVER
AND DIDN'T REALLY GET
TOO FAR OFF THE ROAD.
I DON'T KNOW WHY MEN FEEL
THEY HAVE TO OPEN THE HOOD
WHENEVER THEY SEE
SOMETHING BAD HAPPENING.
A LOT OF SMOKE
AND STEAM THERE,
AND DALTON WAS COMING
ALONG UP THE ROAD
AND THE SMOKE WAS KIND
OF COMING OUT THE
WRONG WAY THERE,
ANY HE KIND OF LOST WALTER
IN THE VIEW AND --
NEXT --
SO WALTER --I SHOULD SAY
DALTON WAS FEELING A
LITTLE GUILTY,
AND HE FELT HE SHOULD TOW
THE WHOLE SHABANG,
SO HE TIED THAT UP THERE
AND GOT WALTER IN THERE.
HE HAD A LITTLE
MORE POWERFUL CAR.
BUT HE GAVE HER A FEW
GOOD REVS AND POPPED THE
CLUTCH AND WHAT HAVE YOU,
BUT AS LUCK WOULD HAVE IT
HE ENDED UP DOING THE SAME
THING TO HIS ENGINE,
SO THE TWO OF THEM WENT
OVER AND THEY BOTH THOUGHT
THEY WOULD OPEN THE HOOD
AND SEE WHAT WAS GOING ON,
AND THEY GOT EVEN
MORE SMOKE NOW.
NOW I WAS COMING ALONG.
OF COURSE, I PUT THE WIPERS
ON THINKING THAT MIGHT HELP,
BUT NO.
AND THAT WAS UNFORTUNATE.
SO NOW, UH, MY UNIT A LITTLE
NEWER, A LITTLE MORE POWER,
I FIGURE I CAN PULL BOTH OF
THEM PLUS THE TRAILER.
THIS SHOULD BE GOOD.
SO I REVVED HER UP PRETTY
GOOD AND EVERYTHING,
BUT I THINK I WAS
UNDERESTIMATING THE LOAD.
THEN WOULDN'T YOU KNOW IT,
AS LUCK WOULD HAVE IT,
SHE STARTED OVERHEATING AND
THE BUNCH OF THEM CAME UP,
AND WE ALL OPENED THE HOOD
TO TAKE A LOOK INSIDE THERE,
AND WE'RE GETTING A
LOT OF SMOKE HERE,
MIKE, COME ALONG IN
A POLICE CRUISER HE
BORROWED TEMPORARILY.
AND, WELL,
YOU KNOW THE REST.
THAT WAS UNFORTUNATE.
NOW WE'RE THINKING WITH THE
POLICE CRUISER
WE MAY ACTUALLY HAVE A SHOT
AT PULLING THREE --
NOW WE HAVE FOUR CARS
AND A TRAILER.
BUT THEY GOT THE BIG EIGHT
AND THEY GOT THE RACING
CAM IN THEM.
YOU'D THINK A COP CAR HAS
USUALLY GOT THE KIND
OF POWER --
BUT HERE, AGAIN,
AS LUCK WOULD HAVE IT,
HE ENDED UP--
NO, MIKE!
DON'T -- GOTTA STOP HIM.
GOTTA STOP HIM,
BAD THINGS
HAPPEN WHEN YOU --
HERE COMES WINSTON IN
THE SEWAGE TRUCK.
SO WE'RE THINKING,
OKAY, OKAY.
WE GOT A BETTER IDEA.
THIS WHOLE -- THIS WHOLE
TOWING THING AIN'T WORKING.
HERE'S A BETTER WAY TO GO,
AND SO THERE GOES MIKE,
AND HE'S PULLING UP ON ME,
AND THEN RIGHT BEHIND ME
WE GOT DALTON.
AND THEN, OF COURSE, WE GOT
WALTER WITH THE TRAILER.
AND WE'RE ALL
ON OUR MERRY WAY
BECAUSE WE LEARNED A
IFE LESSON THERE...
IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW
MUCH PULL YOU HAVE,
SOMETIMES, YOU NEED A PUSH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, ONE OF THE PROBLEMS
ABOUT LIVING UP IN THE
NORTHERN REGIONS --
I MEAN, ASIDE FROM THE
BLACK FLIES, THE MOSQUITOES
AND THE LOUSY SERVICES
AND THE BONE-NUMBING COLD --
IS THE SHORTNESS
OF THE SEASONS.
YEAH, ESPECIALLY THE SPRING.
SO EVERY YEAR
MY WIFE BERNICE,
GETS ME TO GET HER SEEDS
STARTED ON THESE LITTLE TRAYS,
YOU KNOW, WITH THE LIGHT
SHINING DOWN OVER TOP.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU, BY THE TIME
THEY'RE READY TO BE PLANTED,
SO AM I.
SO I FIGURE, IF I PUT A CAR
WINDSHIELD ON THERE,
THAT'LL KIND OF
MAGNIFY THE LIGHT
AND GIVE THE SEEDS A TURBO
BOOST OF ULTRA-VIOLET.
YOU KNOW I'M JUST SPEEDING
UP NATURE A LITTLE BIT,
SORT OF LIKE WHAT ALCOHOL
DOES AT A WEDDING.
OKAY, BUT THAT'S
JUST THE BEGINNING.
SURE, WE CAN MAGNIFY
THE LIGHT,
BUT, HEY, LET'S START
WITH A BIGGER LIGHT.
NOW, I'M NOT GOING TO SAY
WHERE I GOT THAT LIGHT,
BUT IF YOU'RE PLANNING TO
LAND A PLANE AT PORT
ASBESTOS AIRPORT,
WELL, I WOULD SUGGEST YOU
ARRIVE DURING THE DAY.
ALRIGHTY, LET'S GIVE MOTHER
NATURE A KICK START.
( in deep talkshow voice )
HEY, EVERYBODY, WELCOME BACK
TO THE NEXT EXCITING AND
CONTROVERSIAL SEGMENT OF
"THE HAROLD GREEN SHOW"!
THANK YOU.
WELCOME BACK TO THE FINALE
OF MY REALITY-BASED SHOW.
WE'VE HAD A LOT OF TENSION UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK,
AND THAT'S GOOD.
BECAUSE TENSION'S GOOD.
IT'S ENTERTAINING.
AND IT'S WHAT PEOPLE
WANT TO SEE.
(whispering)
IT'S WHAT PEOPLE WANNA SEE.
AND THERE'S NOTHING
LIKE THE TENSION
BETWEEN THE CHARACTERS ON
THE SHOW, YOU KNOW THE --
[ LAUGHTER ]
( voice shaking )
BIG WEEK AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK, UM --
BUSTER HADFIELD FELL
ON A CONVEYOR BELT
AT THE SOFT DRINK FACTORY
AND GOT HIS SKULL CAPPED ---
HAROLD, WE CAN'T
LET YOU DO THIS!
ME NEITHER.
THE RATINGS DON'T
MATTER, HAROLD.
YOU CAN'T FORCE
PEOPLE TO CHANGE.
I KNOW THAT NOW.
WE LIKED IT THE
WAY IT WAS BEFORE!
ME TOO.
WHEN YOU'RE IN THE
SEWAGE BUSINESS,
YOU LEARN THAT EVERYBODY
HAS THEIR BAD SIDE.
I'M WITH YOU A 100%.
I REALLY AM.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, IT DOESN'T
MAKE FOR MUCH OF AN
ARGUMENT,
IF YOU DON'T DISAGREE.
PEOPLE MAY
STOP WATCHING.
WELL, I DON'T CARE!
I KNOW I WAS WRONG,
AND I ADMIT THAT, OKAY?
I'D LIKE TO SAY
THAT TO UNCLE RED,
BUT I HAVE NO
IDEA WHERE HE IS.
APOLOGY ACCEPTED, HAROLD.
OH! IT'S UNCLE RED!
IT'S UNCLE RED!
IT'S
ALL RIGHT.
I STARTED
TALKING AND --
IT'S FINE.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
YES, IT IS.
NO, NO.
THAT'S FINE.
IT'S A REAL MEETING AND REAL
PEOPLE AND EVERYTHING.
YOU SHOULD
BE REAL GONE.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING,
AND TODAY WE LEARNED THAT
REALITY IF OVERRATED.
OF COURSE, YOU KNEW THAT
OR YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
MARRIED ME.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF, HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THE MEETING'S COMING TO ORDER.
EVERYBODY GO SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, EVERYBODY.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN. HAVE A SEAT.
SIT DOWN
HAVE A SEAT.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
BOW YOUR HEADS FOR THE
MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, JUNIOR SINGLETON'S
GOT A SCHOOL BUS
HE WANTS TO GET RID OF.
SHE'S ALL RUSTED OUT AND
DOESN'T RUN OR ANYTHING.
GOT ONE HALF DECENT TIRE, BUT
THE WINDOWS ARE OUT OF HER.
BUT IT'S FREE TO ANYONE
WHO'D LIKE TO GO OVER
THERE AND PICK IT UP.
THERE'S A LITTLE REALITY
CHECK FOR YOU, HAROLD.