IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE MAN WHO MAKES IT
LOOK SO EASY,
SO CHEAP AND SO TAWDRY,
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
OK.
OH BOY.
A LOT OF EXCITEMENT
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
THE BUNCH OF US
ARE GOING TO CHARTER A BUS
COME HELL OR HIGH WATER,
WE'RE GOING TO THE BIG SMOKE,
GONNA WATCH A BLUE JAYS GAME.
WHOO! EXCELLENT! EXCELLENT!
WOW!
HOW COME NO ONE TOLD ME
ABOUT THIS TRIP?
YOU HAVE TO ASK?
YOU HAVE TO ANSWER?
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MESSAGE BEING,
DON'T THINK ABOUT
CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
AND MAKE SENSE OUT OF
THIS PROGRAMME, GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
GOOD NEWS, EVERYBODY.
I'VE ARRANGED
FOR TRANSPORTATION
FOR THE LODGE MEMBERS.
YOU CHARTERED A BUS TO TORONTO?
NO, I BOUGHT ON.
I WENT TO SEE THE GUY.
HE WANTED 100 BUCKS TO DRIVE US
IN THIS WRECK OF A SCHOOL BUS.
HIS WIFE SAID "GIMME $200,
TAKE THE THING HOME."
WE GOT THE GUYS
WORKING ON IT.
IT SHOULD TAKE TWO HOURS
TO MAKE IT ROADWORTHY,
FOUR IF WE WANT LIGHTS,
SIX FOR BRAKES.
BUT UNCLE RED,
THINK ABOUT IT.
HUH?
AT THAT RATE
WE'LL LATE FOR THE GAME.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO THE GAME.
WE JUST TOLD THAT
TO THE WIVES.
(Chuckling)
YOU SAID THERE'S A GAME.
YOU SAID HELL OR HIGH WATER.
NOBODY SAID ANYTHING ABOUT
CASINO NIGHT AT THE CHURCH.
GAMBLING,
YOU'RE GOING GAMBLING!
YOU LIED TO YOUR WIVES!
NO, WE DIDN'T.
WE JUST DIDN'T BURDEN THEM
WITH THE DETAILS.
ANYWAY, OUR WIVES WILL BE HAPPY.
THEY WANT US TO HAVE SOME FUN.
I THINK THEY'LL BE PLEASED
TO KNOW WE'RE GOING TO CHURCH.
THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL THEM?
YOU GUYS ARE DISGUSTING.
MEN WHO LIE TO WOMEN
SHOULDN'T HAVE WIVES.
MEN WHO DON'T LIE TO WOMEN
CAN'T GET WIVES.
COMING UP A LITTLE LATER,
HAROLD AND BILL ARE GOING TO
DO SOME CANOEING.
THAT'S HAROLD UNDER THE CANOE.
HE NEVER LOOKED BETTER.
IT'S SO-- OH!
SO BEAUTIFUL AND...
SERENE OUT THERE.
AH!
OH!
HOW CALM THE WATER IS.
JUST TO BE AT ONE WITH NATURE,
I THINK, IT'S GOOD FOR PEOPLE.
LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
OH, BACK IN THE DAYS
OF KING ARTHUR
WHEN CHIVALRY WAS HOT
GUINEVERE LIKED ARTHUR
A LITTLE
BUT SHE REALLY LIKED
LANCELOT
"EVERY DOG
WILL HAVE HIS DAY"
ARTHUR TOLD HER
DURING A FIGHT
SHE SAID "DOGS CAN HAVE
ALL THE DAYS THEY WANT
"AS LONG AS I GET
MY KNIGHT"
(Laughing)
WELCOME TO THE POSSUM LODGE
WORD GAME!
TONIGHT WE'RE PLAYING FOR
SEASONS TICKETS
TO THE WINNIPEG JETS.
DALTON, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MY UNCLE TO SAY
THIS WORD...
TOOL.
AND GO.
A WORKMAN
IS ONLY AS GOOD AS HIS...
UNION.
NO, OK.
YOU ALWAYS WANT TO USE
THE RIGHT SOMETHING
FOR THE JOB.
THE RIGHT HAND.
UH, THE RIGHT SIDE OF THE LAW.
THE RIGHT SCREWDRIVER.
NO, OK.
YOUR SCREWDRIVERS
AND SAWS
AND YOUR HAMMERS ARE ALL...
RUSTED.
YEAH, THEY ARE.
THEY'RE BROKEN.
THEY'RE STOLEN... SMUGGLED.
OK, LOOK, AT MY STORE,
THERE'S SCREWDRIVERS.
I GOT HAMMERS AND SAWS
AND A COMPLETE LINE OF...
CRAP --
IT IS.
BERNICE,
SHE WANTS YOU TO DO A JOB
AROUND THE HOUSE.
YOU MAKE SURE YOU'VE GOT
A GOOD ASSORTMENT OF...
EXCUSES.
NO -- NOW LISTEN TO ME.
WHEN YOU'VE RUN OUT OF EXCUSES,
YOU IMMEDIATELY GRAB
FOR YOUR...
COAT.
LAXATIVES.
A SMART WORKMAN
ALWAYS BLAMES HIS...
NEPHEW!
HEY!
LOOK... THE REASON
YOU NEVER LET HAROLD
HELP YOU IN THE WORKSHOP
IS BECAUSE HE IS A...
I'M IN THE ROOM!
I KNOW,
I KNOW.
CLOSE ENOUGH.
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER"
I WANNA TALK ABOUT TOOLS,
OR, MORE SPECIFICALLY,
TOOL-BOXES.
AS SOON AS YOU GET
A COMPLETE SET OF TOOLS,
NEXT THING YOU KNOW
YOU GOT FRIENDS,
NEIGHBOURS, GUYS YOU WORK WITH,
AND FAMILY MEMBERS
BORROWING TOOLS
AND NOT BRINGING THEM BACK.
SO YOU'RE LEFT HOLDING
THE EMPTY TOOL-BOX.
WHAT DO YOU DO WITH
AN EMPTY TOOL-BOX?
HOW ABOUT YOU BUILD
A SLOW COOKER?
IT'S A NO-BRAINER,
WHICH IS SORT OF MY SPECIALTY.
FIRST THING YOU WANNA DO
AFTER YOU EMPTY
THE COMPARTMENTS,
SPRAY THAT NON-STICK
COOKING STUFF IN THERE.
JUST SOCK THAT IN THERE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO HAVE
BAKED ON PORK AND BEANS
RUINING THE FINISH
ON YOUR TOOL-BOX.
JUST A MINUTE,
JUST A MINUTE.
THERE WE GO.
THIS IS
THE NON-STICK COOKING SPRAY.
THAT WAS BROWN PRIMER.
PEOPLE WILL THINK
IT'S BARBECUE SAUCE.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS
PUT THE VEGETABLES INTO
THE VARIOUS DRAWERS THERE.
I'M GOING WITH
THE FROZEN MATERIAL.
I FIND IT EASIER TO HANDLE.
PUT THE PEAS IN THERE.
AND THEN THE CORN.
OW!
OH.
PUT SOME ICE ON THAT.
I'LL USE THE BRUSSELS SPROUTS.
IT'S THE ONLY THING
THEY'RE GOOD FOR.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL JUST STICK
THE CHICKEN IN THE TOP.
THAT'S GOING TO BE
A LITTLE TOO BIG.
I'M GONNA CUT THAT UP.
THERE WE GO.
A COATING OF OIL
KEEPS YOUR TOOLS FROM RUSTING.
ADD THE POTATOES IN THERE
AROUND THE CHICKEN.
THE FRENCH CALL THESE
"APPLES OF THE EARTH".
I GUESS YOU COULD MAKE
VODKA APPLE SAUCE.
BUT THAT'S ANOTHER DAY.
AND PROBABLY A NIGHT
AND RIGHT THROUGH THE WEEKEND.
GET THOSE IN THERE --
THEN ADD A CAN OF
YOUR FAVOURITE GRAVY.
BUT DON'T OPEN IT.
JUST LIE IT IN THERE
ON ITS SIDE,
AND CLOSE EVERYTHING UP.
YOU WANNA SEAL IN
YOUR JUICES AND FLAVOURING.
FOR THAT JOB,
I RECOMMEND YOU USE
THE GOURMET CHEF'S
SECRET WEAPON... DUCT TAPE.
NOW, ORDINARILY, I WOULD DO
THIS BARBECUING OUTSIDE.
IT'S HOT OUT THERE.
I HATE SUMMER.
THE BEAUTY OF USING A TOOL-BOX
IS YOU CAN HAVE
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
FOR A SMALL EVENT,
OR YOU CAN GET
ONE OF THESE UNITS
AND HAVE THE GANG OVER.
BUT DO NOT USE THE LIGHTWEIGHT
PLASTIC TOOL-BOX TO COOK IN.
OTHERWISE YOU END UP WITH
SOMETHING ALONG THIS LINE.
I DON'T CARE HOW MUCH BOOZE
YOU SLAKE INTO YOUR GUESTS.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO
TAKE A BITE OF THAT.
IF YOU DO WANT TO USE
THE PLASTIC TOOL-BOX,
I'D SUGGEST THAT YOU GO
WITH THE HORS-D'OEUVRE TRAY.
YOU GOT CARROT STICKS,
CELERY, BREADSTICKS, AND SO ON.
YOU GOT A DRAWER
WHERE YOU CAN KEEP DIP,
OR AS WE CALL THEM, "HAROLD".
IT'S NOT THAT YOU'LL EAT THIS.
IT KEEPS THE LADIES BUSY
WHILE YOU GUYS
EMPTY THE BEER COOLER.
THE BEAUTY IS
YOU'VE GOT YOUR DINNER...
SIMMERING AWAY THERE.
IT GIVES YOU TIME
TO DO SOMETHING ELSE.
YOU COULD BUILD SOMETHING.
YOU COULD COME UP WITH A CURE
FOR A DISEASE.
I PREFER TO SIT
AND NOT THINK ABOUT ANYTHING.
I'M GETTING GOOD AT IT.
(Sizzling)
(Snoring)
MY INSTINCTS ARE TELLING ME
THIS IS READY TO GO ANY MOMENT.
THERE WE GO.
THAT'S THE GRAVY
RIGHT ON TIME.
I'M HUNGRY.
LOOKS LIKE THIS LEG
IS THE RIGHT TOOL FOR THE JOB.
REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
(Crunching)
A LITTLE CHEWY.
WAIT, WAIT.
JUST A HOSE WASHER.
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT A LOT MORE OF IT.
I WANNA TALK TO GUYS
WHO'VE GOTTEN MARRIED
FOR THE SECOND TIME.
CHANCES ARE YOU'RE A STEPDAD
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
OK, REMEMBER THIS.
STEPDADS SCARE KIDS.
FIRST OF ALL,
THEY THINK YOU'RE WEIRD
BECAUSE YOU FIND
THEIR MOTHER PRETTY.
IT'S GONNA TAKE THEM A WHILE
TO GET OVER THAT ONE.
PLUS YOU'RE HARD TO
GET USED TO,
THE WAY YOU LOOK
IN THE MORNING,
AND THE WAY YOU LAUGH
AT "DUKES OF HAZZARD".
SO REVEAL YOURSELF SLOWLY,
THE SAME WAY YOU'RE PLANNING
TO DO WITH YOUR NEW WIFE.
SPEND TIME WITH THE KIDS.
I KNOW IT'S A NUISANCE.
IF YOU SPEND TIME WITH THEM
WHILE THEY'RE YOUNG,
IT WILL SAVE YOU SPENDING TIME
DRIVING THEIR MOTHER
TO PENITENTIARIES
ON VISITING DAY.
IT'S A LOT OF WORK.
MAKES YOU WISH YOU'D TRIED
HARDER ON YOUR FIRST MARRIAGE.
HERE'S THE UPSIDE.
IF THESE KIDS DON'T TURN OUT,
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
THEY'RE NOT PART OF
YOUR GENE POOL.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YA.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause)
(Audience laughing)
WELL, I'LL TELL YA,
THE CHURCH CASINO NIGHT
WAS A HUGE SUCCESS.
MIGHT HAVE DROPPED
A COUPLE OF NICKELS, HAROLD.
OH, DIDN'T NOTICE.
THERE'S LOTS MORE
WHERE THAT CAME FROM.
BOY, I HAVEN'T SEEN
THIS MANY NICKELS
SINCE WE INSTALLED A PAY TOILET
ON MEXICAN NIGHT.
(Audience laughing)
BY GOLLY, WE WERE ROLLIN'.
WE BROKE THE HOUSE,
WE BROKE THE CHURCH.
THEY MAY HAVE TO CLOSE.
OUR LADY OF LUCK
IS A DUMB NAME FOR A CHURCH.
I THINK THIS IS TERRIBLE.
WE BANKRUPTED A HOUSE OF GOD.
WE'RE GONNA GET PUNISHED.
WE'LL GET PUT SOMEWHERE EVIL,
DARK, SCARY, SMELLY, AND WET!
WE'RE HERE.
YEAH.
ACTUALLY, IT'S TOO BAD.
THEY WERE RUNNIN' THE CASINO
TO RAISE MONEY FOR A NEW ORGAN.
WE BANKRUPTED THE ORGAN FUND,
THE ORPHAN FUND,
AND THE WINE BUDGET.
LUCKILY, THE VATICAN KICKED IN
SOME EXTRA CASH.
$20,000 -- THAT'S
A LOT OF MONEY...
ESPECIALLY WHEN
IT'S IN NICKELS.
THEY MADE THEIR MISTAKE
BY LETTING THE MOTHER SUPERIOR
PROGRAM THE SLOT MACHINE.
IT JUST KEPT PAYING OFF.
IT'S STILL WRONG, THOUGH.
WE GOTTA RETURN THE MONEY.
WE WON IT FAIR AND SQUARE.
THE TOUGH PART'S
CONVINCING OUR WIVES
WE FOUND 400,000 NICKELS
IN THE SEATS OF THE OLD BUS.
(Audience laughing)
(Siren)
POSSUM 911 -- STATE YOUR
MEMBERSHIP NUMBER, PLEASE.
876,900.
TEDDY, WHAT'S THE EMERGENCY?
IT'S NOT REALLY AN EMERGENCY.
I WANTED TO SHARE SOMETHING
WITH YOUR VIEWERS.
COOL -- INFORMATION
EXCHANGE!
GREAT! GO AHEAD!
OK, SO I'M UNEMPLOYED,
BUT THE WIFE WORKS.
SO I STAY AT HOME AND DO
THE COOKING AND CLEANING.
WOW! WHAT'S
THAT LIKE?
IT SUCKS.
(Audience laughing)
ALL I DO IS FEED PEOPLE
AND CLEAN UP AFTER 'EM.
I'M EVERYBODY'S MAID.
HOW HARD CAN IT BE TO THROW
DIRTY LAUNDRY IN THE HAMPER?
YOU KNOW WHAT'S THE WORST?
WET TOWELS ON THE BATHROOM
FLOOR, WITH HAIR ON 'EM!
YEAH, YOU SHOULD
SEE THE TOWELS
AROUND HERE --
THEY'RE COVERED.
THAT'S NOT HAIR.
ALL DAY LONG,
IT'S "DAD, WHERE ARE MY SOCKS?
"DAD, WHAT'S FOR DINNER?
"DAD, WILL YOU DRIVE ME
TO THE MALL?
"DAD, YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO WASH MY GYM SHORTS."
DOESN'T YOUR WIFE HELP
AT ALL, TEDDY?
SHE SAYS SHE'S TOO TIRED
FROM WORK.
LITTLE MISS IMPORTANT
WANTS TO READ HER PAPER.
THEN SHE ORDERS ME
TO GET SOME FOOD ON THE TABLE.
I DON'T WANT TO BE A NAG.
IT'S SO BORING.
SAME ROUTINE, DAY AFTER DAY,
SO I'VE COME UP
WITH A SOLUTION
THAT I HIGHLY RECOMMEND
TO OTHER GUYS IN MY SITUATION.
WE'RE LISTENING.
WELL, I'VE JUST KINDA
GONE ON STRIKE
IN THE ROMANCE DEPARTMENT,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
OHHHH!
IF I DON'T GET TREATED
WITH RESPECT IN THE KITCHEN,
THEN NOBODY GETS TREATED
WITH ANYTHING IN THE BEDROOM,
IF YOU CATCH MY DRIFT.
HOW'S THAT
WORKING?
EXCELLENT! SHE'S PUTTING IN
LATE NIGHTS AT THE OFFICE,
GOING TO MORE
BUSINESS CONVENTIONS.
SHE'S TRYING TO EARN MORE MONEY
SO SHE CAN HIRE A MAID.
THAT'S WHAT
SHE'S DOING.
RIGHT!
YES, EXACTLY,
YEAH.
(Red): HERE WE ARE,
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL".
THEY GOT THE CANOE
STRAIGHTENED OUT.
HAROLD GOT HIS OWN FORM
OF A LIFE-JACKET ON.
SCARY, ISN'T IT?
YOU MAY NOT HAVE THAT CANOE
FAR ENOUGH INTO THE WATER.
THIS IS GOOD, THOUGH.
THIS IS THE PART
OF THE CANOEING EXPERIENCE--
YOU LEARN ABOUT TEAMWORK.
GET THAT FARTHER IN THE WATER.
THAT SHOULD DO IT.
OK, YOU MAY HAVE GONE--
YEAH, WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU MAY HAVE GONE
A LITTLE OVERBOARD ON--
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
YEAH, YEAH.
REALLY, WHAT'S THE PLAN?
WE DON'T WANT TO WATCH THIS.
GET THE CANOE
WHILE WE'RE NOT WATCHING.
HERE WE GO.
SO THEY'RE OUT THERE CANOEING,
AND HAROLD HASN'T TOTALLY
MASTERED--
OK, ALL RIGHT, SETTLE DOWN!
SETTLE DOWN, SETTLE DOWN!
BOY, OH, BOY!
IF THERE WAS ONE MORE,
WE'D HAVE THE CHIPMUNKS.
WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
THEY'RE GONNA SWITCH ENDS
IN THE CANOE,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
YOU MIGHT ENJOY THIS.
WHOA!
HMMM...
I WONDER WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN HERE.
I'M SENSING A SPLASH
SOMEWHERE IN THE NEAR FUTURE.
YOU GOT A PLAN, BOYS?
THAT'S IT -- RAISE
THE CENTRE OF GRAVITY.
THAT'S ALWAYS A GOOD IDEA.
WHAT THE HECK IS THIS?
OH, BY GOLLY,
THE MIRACLE OF CHILDBIRTH!
WE DO EVERYTHING ON THIS SHOW.
WELL, BY GOLLY!
I JUST LOST 10 BUCKS
ON A BET RIGHT THERE.
THAT WAS VERY IMPRESSIVE.
NICE WORK, GUYS.
YOU DIDN'T GET ANYWHERE,
BUT YOU DIDN'T GO DOWN
WITH THE SHIP.
NOW BILL WANTS HAROLD
TO TURN AROUND.
HAROLD, YOU DON'T WANT TO BE
BACKING INTO STUFF, BELIEVE ME,
NOT WITH YOUR PERSONALITY.
WHEN THEY ACTUALLY GET GOING...
FUNNY HOW YOU COULD HAVE
TWO GUYS WEARING GLASSES
WHO STILL DON'T SEE
A WATERFALL COMING UP.
YEAH, IT'S A BIG ONE.
70, 80 FEET, THERE.
AS THE CANOE STARTS TO GO OVER,
THEY START TO REALIZE--
UH-OH! AHH! AHH!
SEE YOU IN A MINUTE, BOYS!
OHHH! OHHH!
WELL, I'LL TELL YA,
WITH HAROLD AND BILL,
A DAY AT THE BEACH IS OBVIOUSLY
NO DAY AT THE BEACH.
OH, YOU'RE FINE.
GOIN' BACK SHOULD BE TOUGH.
MY FRIENDS IN SOUTH DAKOTA
MADE ME PART OF MOUNT RUSHMORE.
WE'RE TAKING OUR WINNINGS
FROM THE CHURCH CASINO NIGHT
AND ROLLING THEM
INTO COIN ROLLS.
(Audience laughing)
THE LITTLE ONES TAKE FOREVER,
SO WE'RE MAKING OUR OWN.
56 BUCKS' WORTH, EH?
WE FIGURED OUT
HOW TO HIDE THE DEAL
SO OUR WIVES WON'T SUSPECT WE
DIDN'T GO TO THE BASEBALL GAME.
YOU'RE GIVING THE MONEY BACK?
THESE YOUNG PEOPLE
WITH THEIR SENSE OF HUMOUR.
THAT COULD HAPPEN, RIGHT AFTER
WE GIVE EVERYTHING AWAY
AND LEARN TO LEVITATE.
OH, OK.
NO, NO, THE TRICK
TO AVOID SUSPICION
IS TO SPEND THE MONEY SLOWLY.
EACH GUY GETS 25 NICKELS A DAY
TO BLOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU COULD LIVE OFF THE INTEREST
IF YOU PUT THAT IN THE BANK...
IF YOU'RE ALLOWED
BACK IN
A BANK?
NO, NO, THEY'D USE IT
AGAINST OUR LOAN.
WHERE'S THE SENSE IN THAT?
SO WHAT WE'RE DOIN' IS...
WHAT WE'RE DOIN'...
WE'RE HIDING THE NICKELS.
YEAH.
WHERE? WHERE?
PULL UP A CHAIR
AND I'LL TELL YOU.
AHHH!
(Laughing)
YEAH!
YOU PUT THAT MONEY
IN THE CHAIR!
IN THE CHAIRS, IN TABLE LEGS,
IN THE BED FRAMES...
OLD MAN SEDGWICK
IS PINNED UNDER HIS CANE.
WELL, WAIT,
WHOA, HEY...
NOW, HEY, WHOA.
YOU THINK
THAT'S SAFE,
HAVING THINGS
SO HEAVY HERE?
I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANY PROBLEM.
(Roof creaking)
WHAT'S THAT? OH!
(Audience laughing)
BOY, OH, BOY!
IT'S SAGGING UP THERE, TOO!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT!
(Grunting)
GOT IT.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION,
WHERE WE EXAMINE
THOSE THREE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
(Audience):
"I DON'T KNOW!"
JOINING MY UNCLE RED
ON THIS PORTION
IS HIS BEST FRIEND
IN THIS WHOLE WIDE ROOM,
FERRYBOAT CAPTAIN
HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
(Applause and cheering)
ALL RIGHT.
LETTER GOES AS FOLLOWS:
"I'M A UNIVERSITY STUDENT.
"AFTER LIVING IN A FRAT HOUSE,
I'VE BECOME AN EXPERT
"ON ANIMAL BEHAVIOUR
AND WILDLIFE.
"SHOULD I SWITCH MY MAJOR
"FROM TELEVISION ARTS
TO VETERINARY SCIENCE,
"ZOOLOGY, OR WILDLIFE
MANAGEMENT?"
I'D SAY NO, BECAUSE ANIMALS
HAVE SHARP TEETH AND CLAWS.
I WENT TO MARINE WORLD,
JUST OUTSIDE PORT ASBESTOS.
AN OTTER SLAPPED ME SO HARD,
MY TACO CAME OUT MY NOSE.
THAT'S TRUE.
(Audience laughing)
SO I'D SAY NO.
(Laughing)
WELL, BETTER HIM
THAN ME, HAROLD.
YEAH.
NOW THEY HAVE THE TRANQUILLIZER
DARTS AND SPECIAL EQUIPMENT,
IT'S NOT DANGEROUS
TO DO THAT KIND OF WORK.
OHHH, ANIMALS
DON'T NEED TO BE DRUGGED.
THAT'S JUST PURE LAZINESS.
(Audience laughing)
WHEN I WORKED AT
THE WILDLIFE RESERVE IN KENYA,
WE USED TO HAVE TO
TAG THE LIONS,
MEASURE THEM FOR THEIR HEIGHT
AND THEIR WEIGHT,
AND CHECK THEIR TEETH
AND SO ON,
AND I NEVER ONCE USED
A TRANQUILLIZER DART
TO PUT 'EM TO SLEEP.
DID YOU TELL 'EM
ONE OF YOUR STORIES?
(Laughing)
NO.
NO, I'D WAIT
TILL HE WAS NAPPING.
(Audience laughing)
THEN I'D CREEP OUT
AND I'D MEASURE HIM
FROM THE NOSE TO THE TAIL.
I'D WEIGH HIM ON A SCALE,
CLEAN HIS TEETH,
AND STAPLE A TAG TO HIS EAR.
NOW,
MR. SHAUGHNESSY,
I'M NO EXPERT ON LIONS,
AND UNLIKE YOURSELF,
I'VE NEVER CLAIMED TO BE,
BUT I WOULD IMAGINE THAT
STAPLING A TAG TO A LION'S EAR
MIGHT MAKE HIM WAKE UP
AND BE ANGRY.
YEAH, THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
THAT'S WHY
I TAGGED THE EAR LAST, BECAUSE
THEY RARELY SLEPT THROUGH THAT.
IN A GOOD WEEK,
I COULD TAG AND WEIGH
A WHOLE PRIDE OF LIONS.
YEAH, HAP, YOU'RE KNOWN
FOR YOUR PRIDE OF LYIN'.
(Audience laughing)
4,469...
4,600--
FIVE--
SEVEN... NINE...
WHAT DID YOU
DO THAT FOR?
WE'RE GIVING THE STUFF BACK,
ALL THE WINNINGS.
GIVING IT BACK
TO THE CHURCH, HUH?
YOUR CONSCIENCE
CAUGHT UP TO YOU.
CONSCIENCE CAUGHT UP TO YOU.
NO, BERNICE CAUGHT UP TO ME.
YOU WEREN'T GONNA
TELL YOUR WIVES.
WE WEREN'T, BUT BERNICE IS
PSYCHIC OR SOMETHING.
I GO IN THE HOUSE.
YOU KNOW ME, MR. CASUAL,
COOL AS A CUCUMBER.
MR. POKER-FACE, YOU KNOW?
AND I'M SITTIN' THERE
AND SHE SAYS,
"HOW WAS THE BASEBALL GAME?"
I'M GOING, "WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
"WHAT ARE YOU SAYING IT
THAT WAY FOR?
"YOU THINK I DIDN'T GO?
"IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
"YOU'RE ACCUSING ME
OF NOT GOING?
"HEY, HEY! IT'S NOT MY FAULT
"THE GUYS WENT
TO THE CASINO NIGHT."
VERY SMOOTH, UNCLE RED.
(Audience laughing)
SHE SEEMED TO BE ABLE
TO PUT IT TOGETHER.
SHE'S PSYCHIC, I'M TELLING YA.
(Possum squeal)
THERE'S
THE POSSUM SQUEAL
SO IT'S
MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
AND IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I'VE COLLECTED UP
ALL THE NICKELS.
GOT EVERY LAST NICKEL.
THERE ISN'T ONE...
FOR GOSH SAKES.
YOU'RE GOOD, BERNICE.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF HAROLD
AND MYSELF AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): HE'S HERE!
(Harold imitating trumpet)
I SHOULDN'T PLAY THE BAT.
(Red): THERE YOU GO.
GET UP, GUYS.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN, GUYS.
I'VE MANAGED TO COLLECT
ALL THE NICKELS BACK
AND THERE'S NO ADMISSION
AT THE PEARLY GATES.
TO JOIN
POSSUM LODGE
BOY, THIS IS TOO MUCH!