IS PERFECTING THEIR SWING.
MY ADVICE...
DO AWAY WITH THE
SWING ALL TOGETHER
WITH THE RED GREEN HOLE-IN-ONE,
SWINGLESS GOLF CLUB.
ALL YOU DO IS ATTACH THE HEAD
OF YOUR DRIVER AND A REAL
HEAVY DUTY FISHING REEL,
AND TO ONE OF THESE CHEST
EXPANDER UNITS
PERHAPS YOU GAVE TO
A CLOSE PERSONAL FRIEND,
ONLY TO HAVE HER THROW THE WHOLE
THING RIGHT BACK IN YOUR FACE.
THEN ALL YOU DO IS RUN SOME
100-POUND TEST LINE
FROM THE REEL RIGHT DOWN
TO THE HEAD OF THE CLUB.
AND YOU'RE READY TO PLAY.
THE MORE YOU REEL IT IN,
THE MORE POWER IT DELIVERS.
JUST WIND HER IN, 'TIL YOU
GET IT WHERE YOU WANT IT,
THEN LOCK IT.
THEN WHEN YOU'RE READY,
LET 'ER RIP.
[cheering and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
THE LOCAL BANK'S GOT A
BIG DEAL GOING ON.
YOU OPEN UP AN ACCOUNT,
AND THEY GIVE YOU ONE THESE
WEATHER RADIOS FOR FREE!
NO CHARGE. THERE'S NO CHARGE.
IT'S FREE AND THEY JUST GIVE
IT TO YOU.
I MEAN, THERE'S NO CHARGE.
I MEAN --
THIS IS CRAZY, EH?
NO WONDER THE BANKS
AREN'T DOIN' WELL.
RED, IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
IN FOR SOME PRETTY
SERIOUS WEATHER.
YOU BEEN LISTENING TO
YOUR WEATHER RADIO?
NO.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
YOU SHOULD
BECAUSE WE
GOT TROUBLE!
LET ME TELL HIM.
THAT'S RIGHT, RED.
WE GOT A
CYCLONE COMING.
NO, IT'S A HURRICANE.
YEAH, RIGHT,
A HURRICANE.
RIGHT, IT'S A BIG
WIND, AND IT'S, LIKE,
3,000-MILE-PER-HOUR WINDS!
150-KILOMETRE-AN-HOUR.
RIGHT, WITH HAIL STONES
THE SIZE OF GOLF BALLS!
NO, NO HAILSTORM.
JUST HIGH WIND,
LOTTA RAIN.
AND WE GOT A
TORNADO COMIN'!
NO, IT'S A HURRICANE.
IT'S A BIG STORM!
OKAY --
NO.
DALTON, WE DON'T
GET HURRICANES HERE.
WE'RE TOO FAR
FROM THE OCEAN.
WE GET A FAIR
BIT OF WIND,
BUT THAT'S BECAUSE WE'RE
SO CLOSE TO PORT ASBESTOS,
AND IT SUCKS.
NOT THIS TIME, RED.
WE'VE GOT A FORCE 5 HURRICANE.
HURRICANE DOUG
IS COMING OUR WAY!
WE GOTTA HUNKER DOWN.
WE GOTTA BOARD UP THE WINDOWS.
RATION THE WATER!
SAVE ONE BULLET
FOR YOURSELF!
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
AND TODAY Mr ED FRID
IS PLAYING FOR
THIS SPECIAL COUPON,
WHICH ALLOWS HIM TO GET 50% OFF
ON ALL OTHER COUPONS.
Mr GREEN, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS TO
GET Mr FRID TO SAY THIS WORD...
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
OH, OKAY.
AND, GO!
OKAY, ED,
YOU TAKE SOMETHING WILD,
AND YOU FEED IT,
AND YOU LOOK AFTER IT,
AND YOU GET TO THE POINT
WHERE YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT IF IT'S GOING TO
ATTACK YOU ANYMORE.
THAT WILD ANIMAL IS NOW...
YOUR TEEN-AGED SON.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
WHEN THE WILD ANIMAL HAS
BEEN TRAINED TO BE WITH
PEOPLE, IT'S...
JUST WAITING FOR ITS
CHANCE TO ATTACK.
NO, THIS ANIMAL IS NOT
DANGEROUS BECAUSE IT'S...
DEAD.
OKAY, THINK ABOUT AN ANIMAL.
YOU WANT A WORD THAT
RHYMES WITH GAME.
MAIM.
ALMOST OUTTA TIME, Mr GREEN.
ED, I'M TALKING ABOUT,
LIKE, A PET FOR A KID,
A CUDDLY PUPPY
OR A HAMSTER --
WHOA, NO.
NO, DON'T GET A HAMSTER.
THEY'RE EVIL.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, THEY'LL COME INTO YOUR
ROOM WHILE YOU'RE SLEEPING
AND EAT YOUR EYES.
OH, YEAH, YOU CAN'T
TAME A HAMSTER.
THERE WE GO!
[applause]
[Harold cawing]
UNCLE RED.
OH, YOU'RE
BREATHING HEAVY.
THIS BUILDING WAS DESIGNED
BY A MORON, HAROLD.
THE ELEVATOR ONLY GOES
TO THE 19th FLOOR.
HA HA! YOU GOT ON
THE WRONG ELEVATOR.
SOME OF THEM ONLY GO
TO THE 19th FLOOR.
THE OTHERS GO
FROM 20 ON UP.
WELL, I STILL SAY THERE'S A
MORON INVOLVED SOMEWHERE
IN THIS SITUATION.
WELL, I WON'T ARGUE
WITH YOU ON THAT.
PARDON ME, HAROLD?
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME
WATER FOR THAT?
WE HAVE DISTILLED,
SPARKLING, REVERSE OSMOSIS.
I PREFER FAUCET.
REVERSE FAUCET,
IF YOU HAVE IT.
PERFECT.
JUST GONNA USE
THE PHONE HERE.
HELLO?
[Red's voice on intercom]
hello!
PIECE OF CRAP!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WELL, I'M TRYING TO
USE THE PHONE, HAROLD.
IT WAS INVENTED
130 YEARS AGO.
I THOUGHT THEY'D
HAVE IT WORKING BY NOW.
WELL, LINE SIX IS THE DIRECT
LINE TO OUR NEW YORK OFFICE.
OH.
YEAH, SEVEN AND EIGHT'S
OUR TOLL FREE NUMBER;
ELEVEN AND TWELVE IS
OUR I.S.D.N. NUMBER
FOR DATA TRANSFER;
AND IF YOU WANT
AN OUTSIDE LINE,
THAT'S ONE THROUGH FIVE;
YOU HAVE TO DIAL NINE
TO GET OUT.
DO YOU HEAR YOURSELF, HAROLD?
I JUST WANNA
MAKE A PHONE CALL.
YOU'RE RECITING FOUR PAGES
OUT OF THE SPACE SHUTTLE
SERVICE MANUAL.
WHAT'S GOING ON,
HAROLD?
IS IT ME?
WELL, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE
IN THE BIG CITY NOW.
YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE
TO EMBRACE TECHNOLOGY.
YOU DON'T DO
THAT VERY MUCH.
I EMBRACE AUNT BERNICE.
THAT BEATS REVERSE OSMOSIS,
I'LL TELL YOU.
I'LL TRUST YOU
ON THAT ONE.
BUT YOU KNOW,
HERE WHERE I WORK,
WE HAVE TO
EMBRACE TECHNOLOGY
'CAUSE IF WE DON'T,
TECHNOLOGY WILL
PASS US BY.
YEAH, BUT WHAT
ABOUT LIFE, HAROLD, HUH?
WHAT ABOUT LIFE PASSING YOU BY?
WHAT ABOUT THE THRILL OF
MAKING SOMETHING WITH
YOUR OWN HANDS?
WHERE DOES THAT FIT
INTO YOUR WORLD?
REMEMBER THAT
FISHING BOAT I MADE,
USING ALL THOSE HEATING DUCTS
AND THE RECLINER,
DO YOU REMEMBER THAT?
HOW WOULD YOUR DOWNTOWN BUDDIES
PULL THAT ONE OFF, HUH?
THEY'D BUY A BOAT.
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT
I'M SAYING.
EXACTLY.
OKAY, WE GOT OUR NEXT TWO ITEMS
UP FOR AUCTION HERE.
MIKE, WHY DON'T
YOU START US OFF?
UH, OKAY.
THANK YOU, Mr GREEN.
AS YOU CAN SEE, GENTLEMEN,
UH, THIS IS AN AUTHENTIC
DRIVE-IN MOVIE SPEAKER
THAT DATES ALL THE WAY
BACK TO THE '50s.
WHERE'D YOU
GET THAT, MIKE?
AT THE POSSUM LAKE
DRIVE-IN THEATRE.
YOU GOT THAT IN
THE '50s?
NO, I GOT IT ON
SATURDAY NIGHT.
UH, BUT IT IS OLD,
YEAH.
AND THERE WAS A MOVIE FROM THE
'50s PLAYING AT THE TIME,
UH, THE TEN COMMANDMENTS.
I GUESS YOU LEFT BEFORE THEY GOT
TO "THOU SHALT NOT STEAL."
LOOK, I KNOW WE ALL KID
ABOUT MY CRIMINAL RECORD,
BUT, Mr GREEN, I'M ACTUALLY
A LITTLE HURT.
I DID NOT STEAL
THIS SPEAKER.
I JUST HAD TO LEAVE
IN A HURRY,
AND I FORGOT THAT IT WAS
STILL STUCK IN THE WINDOW.
HONEST.
WHAT WAS THE
BIG RUSH?
WELL, THE CAR'S OWNER CAME
BACK FROM THE SNACK BAR.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, WE'LL GET
TO THAT ITEM IN A MINUTE.
NOW LET'S SEE WHAT
HAP BROUGHT FOR US.
THANK YOU, RED.
I FIGURE WHAT THIS
AUCTION NEEDS IS A
TOUCH OF CELEBRITY.
SO I BROUGHT
ALONG SOMETHING JUST
A LITTLE BIT SPECIAL.
OH, MAN!
THAT'S A DAZZLER.
THAT LOOKS LIKE SOMETHING
ELVIS WOULD WEAR, HUH?
IN HIS DREAMS,
MAYBE.
NO, I MEAN, WHO WAS
THE CELEBRITY?
I WAS.
HUH?
I WORE IT TO
FRONT MY BAND
IN THE LATE '50s,
HAP HORNET AND
THE ROCKIN' DRONES.
OH, YEAH, WE HAD
OUR OWN SOUND.
I'M GUESSIN'
PUGET SOUND.
NO, NO, NO.
WE WERE VERY BIG.
WE HAD A GOLD RECORD IN '58,
"GOTTA LOTTA HOTTA WATTA"
(got a lot of hot water).
WE TOURED ALL OVER THE STATES.
DID YOU EVER
MEET THE KING?
WHO'S THAT?
ELVIS?
ELVIS.
ELVIS, NAH.
WELL, I MET HIM,
BUT WE HARDLY SPOKE.
HE OPENED FOR ME IN FRESNO.
I WOULD'VE BEEN THE KING MYSELF,
BUT I WAS CANADIAN,
SO THEY CALLED ME THE PRIME
MINISTER OF ROCK AND ROLL.
[applause]
SO THIS WAS
YOUR JACKET?
YEAH, FANS WOULD GO
NUTS WHEN THEY SAW
ME IN THAT.
I REMEMBER TELLING ANN-MARGRET
I WAS TOO BUSY TO SEE HER.
BROKE HER HEART.
TO CHEER HER UP, I SUGGESTED SHE
GO AND SHOW ELVIS THE ROPES.
I DIDN'T MEAN LITERALLY.
BOY, HAP,
I DUNNO.
YOU AS A ROCK STAR?
I'M HAVING TROUBLE
BELIEVING THIS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, MIKE?
WELL, I THINK YOU SHOULD
SHOW A LITTLE MORE
RESPECT, Mr GREEN.
OH,
THANKS, MIKE.
TAKE IT FROM ME.
YOU CAN'T TOSS OFF A
WHOPPER LIKE THAT AND
KEEP A STRAIGHT FACE, MAN.
THAT'S REALLY HARD.
LOOK, I DON'T CARE WHETHER
YOU GUYS BELIEVE ME OR NOT.
I'M TELLIN' YOU,
I WAS A ROCK STAR.
WHY ELSE WOULD A HETEROSEXUAL
GUY WEAR A THING LIKE THAT?
SO HOW'S IT
GOING, DALE?
I'M ALL DONE
HERE, Mr GREEN.
DO YOU STILL HAVE
THE WASHROOM KEY?
NO, I GAVE IT BACK
TO YOU, DIDN'T I?
I DON'T THINK SO.
OH, NO,
THERE IT IS.
WOW, I WAS AFRAID
I'D LOST IT AGAIN.
I, UH, PUT A DROP OF OIL
IN YOUR HORN RELAY.
YOUR HORN WAS STICKING.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I LIKE IT STICKING.
THAT WAY I CAN LET MORONS
KNOW WHAT I THINK OF THEM
AND STILL KEEP BOTH
HANDS ON THE WHEEL.
YOUR GENERATION IS SO
CONFRONTATIONAL.
NO, WE'RE NOT!
WELL, I MEAN, DOESN'T
YOUR GENERATION EVER LEAN
ON THE HORN ONCE IN A WHILE?
NO, MOSTLY I JUST
USE IT TO SAY HI;
YOU KNOW, BEEP BEEP,
HOW'S IT GOIN', BUDDY?
DALE, A HORN IS NOT
FOR SAYING HELLO.
IT'S FOR SAYING, GET THE
HELL OUTTA THE WAY.
LIKE THIS...
[honking horn]
YOU'RE HOLDING IT FOR
TWO WHOLE NOTES, Mr GREEN.
SEE, IF YOU JUST PLAY
TWO QUARTER NOTES,
[honking horn]
IT SOUNDS CHEERFUL.
YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
IT'LL BE COOL.
OH, WELL, I DEFINITELY
WANNA BE COOL.
THAT'S A TOP
PRIORITY WITH ME.
WELL, GIVE IT
A TRY, Mr GREEN.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
YOU MIGHT SURPRISE YOURSELF.
YEAH, WHY DON'T I
JUST DO THAT, DALE?
AND YOU HAVE YOURSELF
A RAINBOW DAY.
[honking horn]
YOU KNOW SOMETIMES
YOU GO INTO TOWN,
YOU GOT A LIST
OF THINGS TO DO...
MAYBE, PICK UP SOME
GROCERIES FOR THE FAMILY;
GO TO THE POST OFFICE.
AND THE BAD PART IS WHEN
YOU GET THE GROCERIES FIRST,
THEY GOTTA SIT IN THE VAN WHILE
YOU'RE WAITING FOR SERVICE
AT THE POST OFFICE.
ESPECIALLY IF YOU GOT ICE CREAM.
AND DON'T THINK YOUR CAN TRICK
YOUR KIDS BY REFREEZING
ICE CREAM.
BELIEVE ME,
SOMETHING CHANGES.
SO TODAY WE'RE GONNA TURN A VAN
INTO A MOBILE
REFRIGERATION UNIT.
SO YOU'LL NEVER BE IN A RUSH
TO GET HOME WITH THOSE
DARNED GROCERIES.
AND THE BEAUTY OF
THIS PROJECT IS
YOU DON'T NEED TO KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT REFRIGERATION.
WE'RE NOT REINVENTING
THE WHEEL HERE.
WE'RE JUST STEALING
FRIDGE TECHNOLOGY.
SO ALL YOU GOTTA DO
IS GET THE DOOR OFF OF
JUST AN ORDINARY KITCHEN
REFRIGERATOR LIKE THIS ONE.
THAT SHOULD BE NO PROBLEM.
I BELIEVE IT'S JUST
A LIFT AND TUG THING.
MAYBE THIS ONE'S MORE OF
A YANK AND SWING DEAL.
NO, NO, I THINK THIS IS ACTUALLY
THE HYPEREXTEND MECHANISM
ON THIS ONE.
NOPE.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE YOU'VE GOT
THE DOOR OFF THE FRIDGE,
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO IS MAKE AN
OPENING IN THE SIDE OF THE VAN
BIG ENOUGH FOR THE BACK OF
THE FRIDGE TO STICK OUT OF.
AND IF YOU'RE A REAL HANDYMAN
AND YOU GOT A GOOD EYE,
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE TO MEASURE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, I'VE ATTACHED
THE FRIDGE ON THERE,
AS YOU CAN SEE, WITH THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT I'M THINKING?
THIS VAN ISN'T REALLY AIRTIGHT.
I NEED A LITTLE
EXTRA COOLING POWER.
SO I ADDED A COUPLE OF FRIDGES
ONTO THE BACK HERE.
ACTUALLY, MOOSE THOMPSON
GAVE ME THE FRIDGES.
HE ACTUALLY USED TO HAVE ONE IN
EVERY ROOM IN HIS HOUSE,
BUT NOW HE'S UPGRADED TO A
WALK-IN MEAT LOCKER.
OH, AND WATCH THE LIGHT GO ON
WHEN I OPEN THE DOOR.
SEE, JUST LIKE A FRIDGE.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
ONE OTHER THING I
WANNA SHOW YOU.
I'VE WIRED ALL THE FRIDGES UP TO
THIS CIGARETTE ADAPTER HERE.
I ACTUALLY DID THAT MYSELF.
OH, YEAH, I KNOW AS MUCH ABOUT
ELECTRONICS AS I DO ABOUT
REFRIGERATION.
ALL RIGHT, TIME TO
PICK UP THE GROCERIES
AND DO THE ICE CREAM TEST.
TALK ABOUT AIR CONDITIONING.
I'D SAY, IF ANYTHING,
THE ICE CREAM ACTUALLY
GOT HARDER THIS TIME.
SO REMEMBER IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
THAT'S PROBABLY
GONNA HURT LATER.
I WANNA TALK TO YOU
OLDER MARRIED GUYS
ABOUT SOMETHING THEY
DON'T TEACH YOU IN SCHOOL.
THERE'S A LOT OF TALK THESE
DAYS ABOUT STANDING UP
FOR YOUR RIGHTS
AND SPEAKING UP FOR YOURSELF.
THIS DOES NOT APPLY TO ANY
SUCCESSFUL MARRIAGE.
ANY IDIOT KNOWS WHEN TO SPEAK UP
AND SHOOT HIS MOUTH OFF,
BUT A REAL WISE MAN KNOWS WHEN
TO JUST PUT A LID ON IT.
OH, YEAH, THERE ARE CERTAIN
TIMES IN ANY MARRIAGE
WHEN IT'S BETTER
TO JUST SAY NOTHING;
FOR EXAMPLE, WHEN YOU
DO SOMETHING WRONG,
YOU BREAK SOMETHING,
OR YOU LOSE SOMETHING,
OR YOU FORGET SOMETHING,
OR YOU DRINK SOMETHING.
JUST KEEP VERY, VERY QUIET.
I KNOW HONESTY
IS A GREAT POLICY,
SO IS INSURANCE.
THE TRICK IS NOT USE EITHER ONE
UNTIL YOU ABSOLUTELY HAVE TO.
YOU KNOW, LIFE HAS A WAY OF
GETTING YOU INTO TROUBLE.
YOU DON'T NEED TO HELP IT.
SO WHEN YOU SCREW UP,
SHUT UP.
ANOTHER TIME
YOU WANNA KEEP QUIET
IS WHEN YOU DO SOMETHING RIGHT;
LIKE, YOUR WAY WAS
THE RIGHT WAY,
AND YOUR IDEA
WAS THE RIGHT IDEA,
YOUR PLAN WAS THE RIGHT PLAN.
NO ONE THAT YOU'RE MARRIED TO
WANTS TO HEAR THAT.
NOTHING GOOD EVER
FOLLOWS THE PHRASE,
I TOLD YOU SO.
SO WHENEVER YOU
DO SOMETHING WRONG,
OR WHENEVER YOU
DO SOMETHING RIGHT,
TRY JUST KEEPING YOUR TRAP SHUT.
AND IF IT WORKS,
WELL, I --
REMEMBER I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[sound of hammering]
OW!
OH, GEEZ.
UH, OKAY, GIRLS.
GOT THE WINDOWS
ALL BOARDED UP.
ARE YOU GONNA BE OKAY,
OR DO YOU WANT A
TEDDY BEAR TO HUG?
YOU BETTER
TAKE COVER, RED.
THEY'RE EXPECTING
HURRICANE DOUG TO HIT
OUR AREA ANY SECOND!
OH, BOY, A HURRICANE.
GOSH, WHERE AM
I GONNA HIDE?
OH, BOY.
OH, THERE'S
GONNA BE RAIN.
THERE'S GONNA BE WIND.
OH, BOY.
I GUESS I'LL WARN THE OTHERS.
BETTER WARN THE OTHERS.
LOOK OUT, EVERYBODY.
OH, LOOK OUT.
LOOK OUT.
[birds chirping ]
BOY, IT'S VERY, VERY
SUNNY OUT HERE.
BIRDS -- LITTLE BIRDIES,
THERE'S A HURRICANE COMING.
HURRICANE.
OH, LOOK, THERE'S
A PLACE I CAN HIDE.
I'LL GO SIT
IN THE CANOE.
[clock ticking]
KIDS JUST LIKE
TO GET INVOLVED IN
SOMETHING WITH YOU, YOU KNOW,
JUST A SIMPLE BACKYARD GAME OR
AN INTERESTING CONVERSATION.
AND THAT IS THE TYPE OF THING
THAT WON'T COST YOU
ANYTHING BUT TIME.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO OUT
AND BUY A WHOLE BUNCH OF
EXPENSIVE SPORTS EQUIPMENT
OR VIDEO GAMES
OR ALL THAT STUFF.
BUT HERE'S THE THING,
DON'T BE SELFISH ABOUT IT.
JUST A SECOND.
DON'T BE SELFISH.
DON'T JUST DO THINGS
THAT YOU WANNA DO.
YOU SEE YOU HAVE TO BE --
JUST A SECOND.
YOU HAVE TO BE ABLE
TO READ A KID.
AND SUGGEST THINGS YOU
FIGURE HE'D LIKE TO DO.
THAT'S WHAT YOU
WANNA BE ABLE TO DO.
WHOA! YOU SNUCK RIGHT UP
ON ME THERE, DIDN'T YOU?
YOU'RE GETTING PRETTY GOOD
AT THIS GAME, HUH?
OKAY, WELL, I'LL DO
THE COUNTING NOW,
AND YOU RUN
ALONG AND HIDE.
YOU RUN OFF AND HIDE,
AND I'LL DO THE COUNTING.
I'M NOT LOOKING.
DON'T WORRY, I'M COUNTING.
I'M NOT LOOKING HERE AT ALL.
YOU KNOW, I NEVER USED TO PLAY
HIDE AND SEEK WHEN I WAS A KID.
OH, NO, NO, I HAD THE FRIENDS.
NO, I DID.
BUT WE'D ALWAYS GET TOGETHER AT
THE PARENTS' HOUSE, YOU KNOW,
AND THERE WAS NEVER
ANY PLACE TO HIDE.
DAD HAD PRETTY MUCH BLOWN
EVERYTHING FLAT, YOU KNOW.
HAD TO GO A MILE TO FIND
A DOOR TO HIDE BEHIND.
OR JUST DIG A HOLE IN THE
GROUND AND LIE DOWN IN IT.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT,
I LIKE HIDE AND SEEK.
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
HAVE TO RUN.
YOU JUST TAKE YOUR TIME.
YOU'RE LOOKING AROUND CASUALLY.
IT'S NOT LIKE TAG.
GOD, I HATE TAG.
[applause]
[bell ringing]
Red:
WALTER AND I ARE OUT IN THE
BACK BEHIND THE LODGE THERE,
JUST PAINTING THE SHED.
THAT'S A GOOD WAY
TO SPEND A SATURDAY --
OR EVEN BETTER,
LIKE, A WEDNESDAY.
WALTER'S JUST YOUNGER.
HE'S GOT NO PATIENCE.
IT'S NOT DRY YET, WALTER.
IT'S NOT DRY.
IT'S NOT DRY!
WE JUST PAINTED IT.
NO, DON'T BLOW ON IT.
THAT'S NOT GONNA HELP.
THAT MAKES NO DIFFERENCE.
THAT'S GONNA MAKE
YOU LOOK FOOLISH.
IT'S NOT DRY.
JUST RELAX.
TAKE IT EASY.
THE SUN'LL DRY IT.
THE BREEZE WILL --
NO, NOT --
YOU GONNA FAN --
HE'S GONNA FAN --
OKAY, WALTER, OKAY.
IF YOU WANNA USE A FAN,
USE A FAN.
ONE OF THE GREAT
THINGS ABOUT THE LODGE,
WE GOT SO MUCH EQUIPMENT
LYING AROUND THAT HASN'T
BEEN FOUND YET.
LOOK AT THIS, EH?
NOW, THIS BABY WAS A LITTLE
HEAVIER THAN WHAT I --
ALSO WAS BOLTED THE GROUND.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD, WALTER,
AND I'LL BE ALONG IN A MINUTE
WE GOT HER ON THE LAWN MOWER.
SEEMED LIKE A GOOD IDEA TO ME
NOW WE'LL JUST CRANK --
THIS BABY'S GOT ABOUT
700 HORSE, I THINK.
LOOK AT HER JUST --
WHOA! WAIT A MINUTE.
COME ON BACK.
NO, NO, UP AGAINST THE SHED -
OH, THE PEPPER MILL.
UH-OH, UH-OH.
OH, BOY.
OKAY, OH, BOY.
HERE'S TWO OF THE DWARVES,
SNEEZY AND DOPEY.
OH, BOY.
OH, AND IT'S KILLING
THE PAINT JOB.
ALL RIGHT, WALTER YOU TRY --
WHY DID THEY PUT THE ON/OFF
SWITCH ON THE FRONT OF THE FAN
I MEAN, HOW DO YOU --
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
I'LL TRY AND KILL
THE MAIN SWITCH;
YOU WORK TOWARDS IT, WALTER.
ATTABOY.
LEAN INTO IT.
THERE YOU GO.
LEAN INTO HER THERE.
IS THAT THE BREAKER?
NO, NO.
NO, SHE'S STILL GOING.
YEAH, YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
GET UP TO THAT SWITCH.
NOW, I COULDN'T REALLY HEAR -
I THOUGHT THIS MIGHT BE --
BUT I COULDN'T HEAR THAT
IT STOPPED,
SO I JUST TURNED IT BACK ON.
OH, YOU KNOW, OKAY.
THAT WAS MY FAULT.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
HEY, WALTER, GOOD NEWS.
GOOD NEWS.
THE PAINT'S DRY.
OKAY, TIME FOR THE SECOND COAT
AWAY YOU GO.
OH, HI.
OH, YEAH, WELCOME
TO MIKE'S TEEN TALK.
HERE'S THE NUMBER ONE LESSON
YOU CAN LEARN IN YOUR LIFE,
WHETHER IT'S AS YOU'RE
HANGING OUT AT THE MALL
OR, PERISH THE THOUGHT, AT WORK.
ALWAYS LOOK BUSY,
ESPECIALLY WHEN
YOU'RE DOING NOTHING.
LOOKING BUSY IS THE NEXT BEST
THING TO DOING SOMETHING,
ONLY IT'S A HECK OF
A LOT EASIER.
BUT LOOKING BUSY
IS A HARD THING TO LEARN.
I'LL TELL YOU.
YOU KNOW, ONE OF MY DADS
WORKED AT THE POST OFFICE,
AND, UH, HE HAD THIS RULE
THAT HE WOULD NEVER STAND AROUND
LOOKING OUT THE WINDOW
IN THE MORNING
BECAUSE THEN HE WOULDN'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO IN THE AFTERNOON.
SO THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
LEARN HOW TO LOOK BUSY.
'CAUSE IF IT'S
WORTH DOING NOTHING,
IT'S WORTH DOING NOTHING WELL.
THAT'S IT.
[applause]
[thunder crashing]
[huffing and puffing]
HOW'S THE WEATHER?
I THINK IT'S
GONNA RAIN.
ARE WE ALL GONNA DIE?
EVENTUALLY, YEAH.
UH, ANY NEWS ON
YOUR WEATHER RADIOS?
A MINIATURE TWISTER TORE UP
THE THE ANIMAL SHELTER,
AND IT WAS RAINING
CATS AND DOGS FOR A WHILE.
HOW ARE THOSE
BOARDS HOLDING UP?
OH, THE BOARDS ARE GOOD.
I CHAINED ALL THE HOT WATER
HEATERS TO THE TREES.
ALL OF OUR LOOSE JUNK BLEW ONTO
THE NEIGHBOUR'S PROPERTY,
SO THERE'S A BONUS, ACTUALLY.
YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T BOTHER
PUTTING THE CANOE AWAY.
I'M SURE IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
AHHH!
I'M GETTIN'
OUTTA HERE!
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
SEE YOU LATER.
UH, KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheers and applause]
OKAY, GUYS, YOU DON'T HAVE TO
STAND UP IF YOU DON'T WANT TO.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
WHOA!
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OH, I SAID I'LL CHANGE!