YOU KNOW, ONE OF THE
DISADVANTAGES OF LIVING IN A
SMALL TOWN IN THE WINTER
IS YOU NEVER DRIVE FAR
ENOUGH FOR YOUR CAR
HEATER TO WARM UP.
IT ALMOST MAKES ME WISH
THEY'D MOVE THE BEER STORE
TO PORT ASBESTOS.
LUCKILY, THE HANDYMAN
ALWAYS HAS A SOLUTION.
RATHER THAN WASTING
A WHOLE BUNCH OF GAS
WARMING UP YOUR CAR HEATER,
I GOT A BETTER IDEA --
OR AT LEAST I SHOULD SAY
A CHEAPER IDEA.
I'VE LINED THE WHOLE
INSIDE OF MY COAT
WITH TOASTER ELEMENTS.
AND I'VE HOOKED UP THIS PLUG
THAT GOES RIGHT INTO THE
CIGARETTE LIGHTER.
SO IN ABOUT TEN SECONDS,
I'LL BE WARM AS TOAST.
YOU COULD LINE THE INSIDE OF
YOUR PANTS THE SAME WAY,
BUT INSTEAD OF A TOASTER
YOU SHOULD USE A BUN WARMER.
I RECOMMEND YOU
GIVE THIS A TRY.
I GUARANTEE YOU'LL BE
THE TOAST OF THE TOWN.
[timer bell rings]
[cheers and applause]
ALL RIGHT
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
NO, NO. I APPRECIATE THAT.
WELL, I'VE HAD
A PLEASANT SURPRISE,
AND THAT DOESN'T
HAPPEN ALL THAT OFTEN
WHEN YOU'RE A MIDDLE-AGED
MAN IN A WORLD
RIDDLED WITH
FULL-LENGTH MIRRORS.
YOU KNOW, WHEN HAROLD
TOOK ON THE JOB
AS PUBLIC RELATIONS DIRECTOR
FOR THE POSSUM LAKE AREA,
I WAS AFRAID HE WAS
GOING TO WRECK THE LODGE
JUST SO PEOPLE
WOULD LIKE IT.
BUT HERE WE ARE
ALMOST A YEAR LATER,
AND HE REALLY HASN'T
CHANGED ANYTHING.
I MEAN, THAT SUITS ME FINE.
I FIND LIFE GOES BETTER WHEN
PEOPLE DON'T DO ANYTHING.
UNCLE RED, I HAVE SOMETHING
TO DISCUSS WITH YOU.
OKAY, THAT'S FINE,
HAROLD.
YOU KNOW, I WAS JUST
TELLING EVERYBODY
HOW PROUD I AM
OF HOW LITTLE
YOU'VE ACCOMPLISHED.
[laughter]
OH, OH.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
OF COURSE, CITY COUNCIL HAS A
BIT OF A DIFFERENT TAKE ON IT.
OVERALL, MY DEPARTMENT IS
SHOWING A NET LOSS
OF $5,000.
OH, MAN, THAT'S
NOT BAD, HUH?
WELL, THEY WERE
HOPING FOR A PROFIT.
THEY HIRED ME AS
A REVENUE SOURCE,
SO THEY'RE
PRETTY DISAPPOINTED.
WELL, HAROLD, LIFE IS
ABOUT DISAPPOINTMENT.
YOU'D KNOW THAT
IF YOU WERE MARRIED.
WELL, NOW MY CONTRACT'S
UP FOR RENEWAL.
I HAVE TO FIND A WAY TO COVER
THE $5,000 SHORTFALL.
SO I'VE BOOKED
AN APPOINTMENT WITH
THE BANK MANAGER.
WELL, THERE YOU GO.
AND DON'T TAKE ANY
GUFF FROM HIM, HAROLD.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
HE'S THERE TO LEND MONEY.
THAT'S HIS JOB,
OKAY.
AND THERE'S
OTHER BANKS.
LIKE, IF HE DOESN'T
OFFER YOU SOMETHING
YOU LIKE,
YOU JUST GIVE HIM THE
BIG ORANGE AND HIKE
IT ON OUTTA THERE.
OKAY! OKAY!
GOOD. GOOD.
'CAUSE I NEED
YOU TO GO WITH ME.
OH, NO, HAROLD, THAT GUY
SCARES THE CRAP OUTTA ME.
NO.
COME ON!
I'LL DO ALL
THE TALKING.
AND THE LODGE IS A
BIG PART OF THE PROBLEM.
SO I NEED YOU TO
WEAR THIS SPORTS COAT,
BECAUSE IT MAKES A BETTER
PROFESSIONAL IMPRESSION.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
JUST TAKING THIS
TO THE CLEANERS.
ALL SET.
LET'S GO.
YOU WANT ME TO TAKE
IT TO THE CLEANERS
WHEN I'M DONE?
NO.
WHY ARE YOU SO
CONCERNED ABOUT MY JACKET?
WELL, EVERY TIME
I'VE BEEN TO THE BANK,
SOMEBODY ENDS UP
GOING TO THE CLEANERS.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
TODAY'S PRIZE IS A RIDE-ALONG
IN A POLICE CRUISER
WITH ONE OF
POSSUM LAKE'S FINEST.
EXPERIENCE THE THRILLS,
THE HIGH-SPEED CHASES,
THE DRIVE-BYS AND
THE DRIVE-THRUS.
THIS IS A GREAT PRIZE.
I'VE BEEN ON A COUPLE
OF THESE MYSELF.
OKAY, COVER YOUR THINGYS.
OKAY, MR. GREEN,
YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET WINSTON
TO SAY THIS WORD...
DENIAL
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND GO!
OKAY, WINSTON, THIS IS THE
OPPOSITE OF ADMISSION.
SUBTRACTION?
OKAY, SOMEONE WHO'S UNAWARE
OF THEIR OWN WEAKNESSES
OR SHORTCOMINGS
IS OBVIOUSLY IN...
POLITICS.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
IF SOMEBODY IS OUTTA
TOUCH WITH REALITY,
THEY'RE EXPERIENCING...
A BEER BUZZ.
ALMOST OUTTA TIME,
MR. GREEN.
WINSTON, WHAT WAS THAT SLOGAN
YOU CAME UP WITH LAST WEEK?
REMEMBER YOU CAME UP
WITH THAT SLOGAN?
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
I LOVE SUCKING SEPTICS;
IT SUITS MY STYLE.
I'D RATHER BE IN SEWAGE
THAN LIVE IN DENIAL.
THERE WE GO,
BABY!
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW WE CALL
IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING.
JOINING ME TODAY,
DALTON HUMPHREY
OF HUMPHREY'S
EVERYTHING STORE.
YOU GOT ANY BARGAINS DOWN
AT THE STORE THERE, DALTON?
YOU BETCHA, RED.
YOU DROP BY BEFORE
NOON ON SATURDAY,
THE ADMISSION IS FREE.
DO YOU NORMALLY CHARGE
ADMISSION TO YOUR STORE?
IT'S NOT JUST A STORE, RED.
I KIND OF THINK OF IT
AS A THRIFT MUSEUM.
OH, YEAH, AND IS THIS AN
ARTEFACT FROM THE CHEAP
CRAP DISPLAY?
NO, NO, THAT'S MY
WIFE'S WAFFLE IRON.
I WAS WONDERING IF
YOU COULD HELP
ME CLEAN IT.
YOU MAKE WAFFLES OUT OF
PETROLEUM PRODUCTS,
DO YOU?
THERE'S SOME KIND OF
MELTED RUBBER ON HERE.
YEAH, RIGHT.
WELL, I WORE ALL THE
TREADS OFF MY WORK BOOTS,
AND I SAW THAT THE PATTERN
ON THIS WAFFLE IRON
WAS THE SAME,
SO I FIGURED I COULD --
YOU KNOW, I'D JUST --
START TO LIQUEFY
SOME NOXIOUS MATERIALS
IN YOUR KITCHEN TO SAVE
A FEW BUCKS, HUH?
BOY, I NEVER THOUGHT
OF IT THAT WAY.
GEE, I THOUGHT MAYBE
THE BUDGIE JUST DIED
OF OLD AGE.
WELL, I MIGHT BE ABLE TO GET
THAT OFF WITH A SCREW DRIVER.
HOW DID YOU WEAR THE
TREADS OFF YOUR
WORK BOOTS?
WELL, I FINALLY DECIDED
TO BUILD THAT GAZEBO
MY WIFE'S BEEN
ASKING FOR.
SO I HAD TO PICK UP ABOUT
A TONNE OF SHINGLES AND
LUMBER AND STUFF,
SO I JUST THREW IT ALL IN THE
BACK OF MY TRUCK, SEE?
OH, THAT OLD
PICK-UP TRUCK?
YOU FINALLY COUGHED
UP ENOUGH MONEY TO GET THE
BRAKES FIXED ON THAT YET?
NO, NO, THAT'S HOW I WORE
THE TREADS OFF MY SHOES.
SO CAN YOU HELP
ME CLEAN THIS UP?
YEAH, I THINK SHE'S
PRETTY GOOD RIGHT THERE.
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
I WISH I COULD PAY YOU.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU JUST
GIVE ME THE WAFFLE IRON?
NO, NO,
I NEED THIS.
I'M GONNA MAKE
SOME SNOW TIRES.
PEOPLE SOMETIMES
CALL ME A CHUMP.
THEY SAY I'M TOO
SMALL TO HANDLE A DUMP.
BUT I CAN SUCK UP
ANY SIZE LUMP.
IT'S NOT THE LENGTH
OF THE HOSE,
IT'S THE STRENGTH
OF THE PUMP.
DON'T YOU HATE
DRIVING IN WINTER
WHEN YOUR TIRES
JUST SIT THERE AND SPIN?
OH, SURE, IT'S OKAY IF YOU'RE
JUST DRIVING TO SCHOOL
OR WORK;
BUT OTHER THAN THAT,
IT CAN BE A REAL PAIN.
SO THIS TIME ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
YOU CAN CONVERT YOUR CAR
INTO A GO-ANYWHERE
WINTER VEHICLE.
FIRST THING WE GOTTA DO IS
INCREASE THE TRACTION
ON THE BACK WHEELS.
TO DO THAT YOU'RE
GONNA NEED A MAN'S BELT
MADE OUT OF LEATHER AND BIG
ENOUGH TO GO ALL THE WAY
AROUND TIRE.
IF YOU'RE A
MATH WHIZ, NOW,
WHAT YOU DO IS
MEASURE THE DIAMETER
AND MULTIPLY THAT BY PI.
OR YOU COULD JUST GET
YOURSELF A COUPLE OF MOOSE
THOMPSON'S BELTS.
THEY'RE USED TO
BEING AROUND A TIRE,
AND I'M SURE PIE
WAS INVOLVED.
NOW, BEFORE WE MOUNT
THE BELTS ONTO THE WHEELS,
WE NEED TO ADD
SOMETHING TO THEM
TO GIVE US A LOT
MORE TRACTION.
I SUGGEST CUTLERY.
YOU PROBABLY HAVE A BUNCH
OF OLD, USED CUTLERY
AROUND YOUR HOUSE.
WE'RE NOT THAT
LUCKY AT THE LODGE.
WE HAVE LOTS OF
OLD CUTLERY,
BUT HARDLY ANY OF
IT IS USED.
NOW, YOU'LL NOTICE I ATTACHED
ALL THE CUTLERY ON THERE
USING THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
NOW ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS REPLACE THE STANDARD
WHEELS WITH THESE BABIES,
AND I'M GOOD TO GO.
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
NOW YOU'LL BE
ABLE TO GO ANYWHERE,
EVEN IF THERE'S A
FORK IN THE ROAD.
GET IT?
OH, AND TAKE A
LOOK AT THIS.
TO MAKE SURE THE FRONT WHEELS
GLIDE ALONG SMOOTHLY,
I FOUND A GREAT USE
FOR THOSE OLD TOBOGGANS.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
LOTS OF CRAZY STUFF HAPPENING
ON THE ROADS THESE DAYS.
I MEAN, YOU SEE
THE ADS ON TV,
WHERE THEY GOT SOME YUPPIE,
WEENIE IN A HIGH-PRICED
STATUS-MOBILE
SLIDING INTO A CORNER IN A
FOUR-WHEEL DRIFT,
GOING ABOUT 130.
YOU THINK TO YOURSELF,
NOW, WHO WOULD BE STUPID
ENOUGH TO TRY THAT?
YOU GO OUT ON THE HIGHWAY,
THERE'S YOUR ANSWER.
I MEAN, THESE GUYS, THEY'RE
DIPSY-DOODLING THROUGH
THE TRAFFIC
DOING TWICE THE
SPEED OF SENSE,
TURNING YOUR RELAXING DRIVE
INTO A TEETH GRINDER.
YOU KNOW WHAT THESE GOOFS ARE
SAYING MORE OR LESS IS,
HEY, OUT OF THE WAY, SUCKER.
MAKE ROOM FOR
THE BIG FISH, HUH?
I KNOW THE NORMAL REACTION
IS TO TEACH THEM A LESSON
BY DRIVING LIKE
AN IDIOT YOURSELF.
BUT YOU MIGHT WANNA
THINK THAT ONE OVER.
YOU KNOW, AT THAT SPEED,
THE ROAD'LL BE GOING
BY PRETTY FAST
WHEN YOU LOOK DOWN THROUGH
THE BOARDS OF YOUR K-CAR.
SO INSTEAD, I SAY,
JUST SLOW DOWN.
THINK ABOUT THE TRUTH.
THAT GUY THAT
JUST BLEW PAST YOU
IS TRYING TO MAKE PAYMENTS
ON A $60,000 CAR.
AND HE'S GOT TO GET TO WORK
EARLY SO HE CAN GET
A PROMOTION
SO THAT NEXT YEAR HE CAN MAKE
PAYMENTS ON AN $80,000 CAR.
I MEAN, IT'S LIKE HE'S
TREADING WATER IN A SAUCEPAN.
HE'S NOT GONNA DROWN,
BUT HE'S STILL COOKED.
WHEREAS YOU, MY FRIEND,
HAVE THE SWEET LIFE.
IF YOU'RE LATE FOR WORK
NOBODY CARES.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
RISK YOUR LIFE.
DO YOU SEE A PROMOTION
COMING YOUR WAY?
NO CHANCE!
SO YOU JUST SIT BACK,
TURN UP THE RADIO,
IF IT STILL WORKS.
DON'T THE LET THE BIG FISH IN
THE SMALL CAR BOTHER YOU.
RIGHT NOW HE'S JUST
THE ONE WHO GOT AWAY.
BUT IN THE LONG RUN, YOU'RE
THE ONE WHO GOT YOUR WAY.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
IF YOUR HOME HAS STARTED TO
SMELL LIKE A BARN
AND YOU'RE 1,000 MILES
FROM THE NEAREST FARM,
CALL BEFORE THE STINK
DOES ANY MORE HARM.
DON'T WAIT TILL IT SETS
OFF THE SMOKE ALARM.
Dalton:
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL DAY.
Red: YEAH, YOU WON'T SEE
ANOTHER ONE LIKE TODAY.
Mike:
IT'S ALMOST LIKE A DREAM,
EXCEPT FOR THE
SMELL OF THE LAKE.
Dalton:
MAYBE IT IS A DREAM.
Mike:
SAY, WHAT IS THAT
SMELL ANYWAY?
Red: WELL, IT'S
EITHER RAW SEWAGE
OR DEAD ALGAE
OR DALTON.
Dalton: YOU KNOW,
IT COULD BE A DREAM.
MAYBE I'M DREAMING
AND YOUR TWO AREN'T REAL.
Mike: OR MAYBE I'M DREAMING.
THIS COULD BE MY DREAM.
EXCEPT YOU GUYS WOULD
BE WEARING DRESSES.
Red:
WELL, IF IT WAS MY DREAM,
I'D HAVE CAUGHT
SOME FISH BY NOW,
AND I WOULDN'T
HAVE YOU TWO.
I'D HAVE HARPO MARX
AND MARCEL MARCEAU HERE.
Mike: I THINK HE WANTS
US TO BE QUIET.
Dalton: I SENSED THAT.
Mike: WHAT DO YOU
DREAM ABOUT, MR. GREEN?
Red: A PERFECT WORLD, MIKE,
WHERE NOBODY BOTHERS ME.
Dalton: AMEN.
Mike: BUT FOR NOBODY
TO BOTHER YOU,
YOU'D HAVE TO BE ALONE.
Dalton: WELL, SOMETIMES
A MAN NEEDS TO BE ALONE, MIKE.
Mike: I KNOW.
IT'S CALLED SOLITARY.
I JUST NEVER HEARD OF ANYBODY
DREAMING ABOUT IT BEFORE.
Red: WELL, NO, WE DON'T WANT
TO BE ALONE ALL THE TIME,
JUST SOME OF THE TIME.
Dalton: A LOT OF THE TIME.
MOST OF THE TIME.
Mike: NOT ME.
I LIKE TO BE WITH PEOPLE,
INTERACTING, SHARING.
Red: YOU KNOW, MIKE, WHEN
YOU STEAL A PERSON'S WATCH,
THAT'S NOT CALLED SHARING.
Mike: THAT'S BEEN
A HARSH LESSON FOR ME.
Red: YEAH.
[applause]
OKAY, SO WE GO
DOWN TO THE BANK
TO BORROW THE 5,000
AND I WAS ASKED
TO BE THERE.
THEN I WAS TOLD TO SIT
QUIETLY AND KEEP MY
MOUTH SHUT.
THAT'S WHAT YOU
TOLD ME, RIGHT?
EVERYONE IN THE
BANK TOLD YOU.
OKAY,
THAT'S FINE.
SO I'M SITTING THERE
WAITING FOR HAROLD
TRUMP HERE
TO ASK FOR THE 5,000.
YOU CAN'T JUST
BORROW MONEY.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE
A BUSINESS PLAN.
NO YOU DON'T. I'VE NEVER HAD A
BUSINESS PLAN.
YOU NEVER
RAN A BUSINESS.
WELL, THIS IS A
LODGE, HAROLD.
THIS IS FOR THE ENJOYMENT
OF PEOPLE LIKE ME.
IT'S NOT ABOUT
MAKING MONEY.
AND IT'S MY JOB
TO CHANGE THAT.
I LIKE MY JOB.
I DON'T WANNA LOSE IT
AND HAVE TO MOVE AWAY AGAIN.
THAT'S WHY I MADE
THE PROPOSAL.
OH, BOY, YOU SHOULD'VE
HEARD THIS.
HE SAYS WE WANNA MAKE ALL
KINDS OF IMPROVEMENTS
TO THE LODGE
SO IT'LL ATTRACT TOURISTS
TO COME UP FROM THE CITY.
WHO WANTS THAT?
WELL, WE HAVE A FINANCIAL
PROBLEM, UNCLE RED.
WELL, OKAY, WE HAVE A
$5,000 PROBLEM, HAROLD.
WHY CAN'T WE JUST BORROW
AGAINST THE LODGE.
IT'S GOTTA BE WORTH
AT LEAST FIVE GRAND.
WELL, I'D SAY CLOSER TO 200.
REALLY?
200,000?
NO
$200?
THAT'S THE ONE.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, HAROLD?
I MEAN, THE LAND ALONE HAS
GOT TO BE WORTH 50,000.
YOU DON'T OWN
THE LAND, THE BANK DOES.
WELL, THEN WHAT ARE
THEY WORRIED ABOUT?
THAT DOESN'T EVEN
MAKE SENSE.
UNCLE RED, THE ONLY
WAY OUT OF THIS IS
WE HAVE TO MAKE
MAJOR RENOVATIONS
AND THEN THE LODGE CAN
BECOME A PROFIT CENTRE.
OH, YEAH.
YOU SHOULD'VE
HEARD THIS ONE.
HE HITS THE BANK UP
FOR TWO MILLION BUCKS!
I MEAN, IT WAS THE MOST
INSANE THING I EVER HEARD.
AND THEN THE BANK
MANAGER TOPS HIM
BY SAYING YES.
WELL, HE KNOWS A GOOD
INVESTMENT WHEN
HE SEES ONE.
HAROLD, THAT'S NOT
A GOOD INVESTMENT;
THAT'S INSANITY.
YOU DON'T TAKE ON A
$2 MILLION DEBT
TO SOLVE A $5,000 PROBLEM.
IT'S THE WAY THE
GOVERNMENT DOES IT.
[applause]
Red: MIKE AND I HAD KIND OF
AGREED TO MEET OUT BY
THE WOODS THERE
AND JUST GO HAVE
A LITTLE PICNIC.
AND MIKE PULLED UP
IN A CAR -- WOW!
THAT IS A NICE SET
OF WHEELS.
THAT YOUR CAR, MIKE?
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, YEAH, HE SAYS.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
IT'S HIS CAR NOW, I GUESS.
I GOT A LITTLE SUSPICIOUS
WHEN HE COULDN'T FIGURE OUT
HOW TO OPEN THE TRUNK.
SO I SAID, THIS IS
ONE OF THESE FANCY --
IT'S THE REMOTE DEAL.
YOU PUSH THE LITTLE BUTTON
TO OPEN THE TRUNK.
FUNNY HE DIDN'T
KNOW THAT, EH,
WITH IT BEING HIS
CAR AND EVERYTHING?
SO HE HAD BROUGHT HIS
STUFF FOR THE PICNIC,
WHICH WAS ABOUT TEN OF THOSE
BOXES OF CANNED STEW.
I FIGURED ONE WOULD DO IT,
BUT HE WANTED
TO TAKE THEM ALL.
HE SAID HE NEEDED TO HIDE
THEM FOR A WHILE.
SO AS LONG AS HE'S CARRYING
THEM, I DIDN'T MIND.
AND HE ALSO HAD BROUGHT
A TWO-WHEEL DOLLY
THAT HAD KIND OF A
FRESH LOOK TO IT AS WELL.
BUT I DIDN'T
ASK ANY QUESTIONS.
SO, UH, AWAY WE
GO INTO THE WOODS.
THIS IS A GREAT DAY,
FANTASTIC DAY.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL,
BEAUTIFUL DAY.
AND WE GOT IN THERE,
AND I GOTTA GIVE MIKE CREDIT.
THINGS GET TOUGH,
BUT HE DOESN'T QUIT.
HE FINDS A WAY TO GET THE JOB
DONE ONE WAY OR ANOTHER.
SO WE GOT THE FIRE GOING.
I WAS MAKING A HOT DOG,
BUT MIKE HAD NO CAN OPENER.
I DIDN'T HAVE
A CAN OPENER ON ME,
SO I SAID, MAYBE YOU
SHOULD GO BACK TO THE CAR.
AND SO HE'S GOING
TO GO BACK TO THE CAR,
AND I THOUGHT, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU'RE GOING TO GO
BACK TO THE CAR,
YOU MIGHT AS WELL GO IN THE
DIRECTION THE CAR IS.
THAT COULD PROBABLY SPEED
THINGS UP SOMEWHAT.
AND SOMETHING HAPPENED HERE.
SOMETIMES YOU GET
INTO THE WOODS,
AND IF THERE'S
NOT A CLEAR TRAIL,
YOU END UP DOING
A U-TURN.
YOU KNOW, IT'S THE
KIND OF THING THAT
CAN HAPPEN TO ANYBODY,
BUT I DON'T KNOW HOW HE ENDED
UP COMING IN THE WRONG WAY.
SO I SAID, MIKE,
YOU GO THAT WAY,
AND I'LL GO THE WAY
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO GO
AND I'M SURE IT'S
GONNA WORK OUT FINE.
SO I COME DOWN
THROUGH THE WOODS,
AND LIKE I SAY,
IT COULD HAPPEN TO ANYBODY.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
I COME BACK.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'M EVER
GONNA SEE MIKE AGAIN.
BUT OH, YEAH, THERE HE
IS EATING MY HOT DOG.
SO I FIGURE OKAY, WE NEED
TO ADD SOME TECHNOLOGY
INTO THIS MYSTERY,
SO I ASKED HIM FOR HIS
ITTLE REMOTE THING THERE,
AND I FIGURING IF I CAN
HONK THE CAR HORN --
WHEN YOU LOCK 'EM,
THE HORN HONKS ON THESE.
SO WE LISTENED FOR IT.
[ HORN HONKING ]
YEAH, SO WE JUST GOTTA
WALK THE WAY IT'S COMING.
NO, THAT'S NOT GONNA --
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, IT'S ALSO GOT
THE REMOTE STARTER ON
THE BACK OF IT,
SO IF WE START HER UP,
AND IF SHE'S IN GEAR AT ALL,
SHE SHOULD START
DRIVING TOWARD US.
AND THAT WOULD BE A --
THE CAR SHOULD JUST COME --
OH, I DIDN'T SEE
THE TREE THERE.
ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S --
OKAY, THERE'S GOING TO BE
SOME DAMAGE ON YOUR NEW --
OH!
THERE'S GONNA BE SOME DAMAGE,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT
WE DO NOW.
OH, WAIT A SECOND,
IF THE CAR HIT THE TREE,
IT MEANS THAT --
WELL, THIS IS A BRILLIANT
WAY TO FIND YOUR WAY HOME.
ALL YOU KIDS OUT THERE,
JUST FOLLOW THE TREE
THAT YOUR HOUSE
KNOCKED...  OVER...
AND YOU'LL GET BACK --
ANYWAY, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT WAS AS GREAT DAY,
AND MIKE'S CAR, I'M SURE,
WILL BE COVERED BY
SOMEBODY'S INSURANCE.
[applause]
WHEN YOUR SEPTICS
NEED CLEANING
BECAUSE THEY
SMELL UNKEMPT --
IT HAPPENS TO EVERYONE,
NO ONE'S EXEMPT,
CALL YOUR FRIENDS
AT ROTHSCHILD'S.
WE HOLD NO CONTEMPT.
WE'LL SUCK OUT YOUR SEWAGE
OR DIE IN THE ATTEMPT.
YOU KNOW, TO ME THE MARK
OF A TRUE HANDYMAN
IS TO BE ABLE TO SEE
WHAT SOMETHING DOES
AND THEN USE IT IN A
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
APPLICATION.
FOR EXAMPLE, THEY HAVE
THIS BUBBLY MEDICINE
FOR STOMACH ACHES
OR HEADACHES
OR DRY HEAVES
OR WHATEVER.
SEE THAT?
GOES NUTS WHEN
IT HITS THE WATER.
KIND OF LIKE A THREE-YEAR-OLD
AT AT WADING POOL
THAT'S POWER YOU'RE
LOOKING AT THERE.
AND I'M THINKING THERE'S
GOTTA BE A BETTER WAY OF
USING THAT POWER.
HOW ABOUT MAKING A
POWER CANOE?
JUST ATTACH A PIECE OF
DRAIN PIPE TO THE SIDE
AND RUN IT FROM ABOVE THE
GUNNELS DOWN INTO THE WATER.
MAKE SURE YOU
ATTACH IT LOOSE
SO THAT YOU'VE GOT
FORWARD AND REVERSE.
NOW YOU JUST POUR THE
MEDICINE DOWN THE PIPE.
IT HITS THE WATER COMING UP
AND THAT STARTS MAKING
THE POWER.
NOW ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS DIRECT THAT POWER
SO IT COMES OUT THE
BOTTOM OF THE PIPE.
THAT'S WHAT THIS
CORK IS FOR.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GIVE HER A GO.
I'M JUST GONNA POUR
THE MEDICINE INTO THE HOLE.
THEN JAM THE CORK IN THERE
AND HANG ONTO THE PIPE.
OH, YEAH,
ONE MORE THING...
GO BIG OR GO HOME.
[cheers and applause]
WELL, I THINK I GOT THE
FINANCIAL PROBLEM SOLVED.
SEE, ALL WE REALLY
NEED IS $5,000.
NOW, OKAY, NONE OF THE POSSUM
LODGE MEMBERS HAVE THAT
KIND OF CASH,
BUT I FIGURED, HEY,
WHY DON'T WE POOL OUR MONEY?
OR MAYBE A BETTER
WAY TO SAY IT IS,
WHY DON'T WE PUDDLE
OUR MONEY?
SO I FIGURE IF I GET FIVE
GUYS TO EACH PUT UP 1,000 --
THAT'S TOO HIGH.
OKAY, 50,000 GUYS
AT A DIME EACH.
THAT'S GONNA TAKE FOREVER.
THEN I THINK, OKAY, 50 GUYS
AT 100 BUCKS A PIECE
AND THAT WORKS OUT TO --
WELL, CLOSE ENOUGH.
SO I GOT HER KNOCKED
RIGHT HERE.
UNCLE RED,
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME?
ABSOLUTELY HAROLD
I'VE GOT GREAT NEWS.
I'VE SOLVED
THE PROBLEM.
HERE'S A CHEQUE
FOR FIVE GRAND.
WOW!
I CAN'T ACCEPT THIS.
YOU CAN ACCEPT IT.
IT'S A LOAN.
AND TAKE YOUR TIME
PAYING IT BACK.
THAT'S WHAT WE DO.
NO, NO, IT'S NOT
A LODGE DEBT.
THIS IS A PERSONAL
PROBLEM.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME
THAT I FIND A SOLUTION.
HAROLD, WE DON'T LIKE THE
SOLUTION, OKAY?
WE DON'T WANT THE LODGE TO
CHANGE, HAROLD, OKAY?
EVERYTHING IN
LIFE CHANGES;
WE NEED THE LODGE TO
STAY EXACTLY THE
WAY IT IS.
I UNDERSTAND THAT.
YOU UNDERSTAND IT?
YOU BORROWED TWO MILLION
BUCKS TO TURN IT INTO
THE MOSQUITO HILTON.
NO, NO,
I CANCELED THAT LOAN.
GREAT!
WELL, YOU USE THE CHEQUE
SO YOU CAN KEEP YOUR JOB.
[softly]
THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT
YOU KNOW, IN YOUR OWN WAY,
YOU'RE SAYING THAT
YOU LIKE ME
AND THAT YOU WANT
ME TO STAY.
I SAID THAT?
AND THIS CHEQUE
MEANS NOTHING.
THAT MEANS
WAY MORE TO ME.
I SAID THAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT I DID?
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I DID.
I PAID THE $5,000
OUT OF MY OWN POCKET.
SO YES,
I AM STAYING.
WELL, GOOD FOR YOU,
HAROLD.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
GOOD FOR ALL OF US.
YEAH, YOU KNOW, I'D RATHER
MAKE A LOWER INCOME
IF IT MEANS I'LL
BE ABLE TO LIVE HERE.
GOOD FOR YOU.
IS THAT DUMB?
I DUNNO, BUT IT'S
HOW CANADA WAS BUILT.
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD HAROLD
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
OH, THIS IS GREAT
OKAY, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
HAROLD HAS ABANDONED HIS WHOLE
PLAN TO RENOVATE THE LODGE.
THAT'S GOTTA BE
GREAT NEWS.
AND HE ACTUALLY
PAID OFF A DEBT,
AND THAT'S ABOUT
AS MUCH RADICAL CHANGE
AS WE CAN ABSORB
AT ONE TIME.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR
STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheers and applause]
SIT DOWN, GUYS.
SIT DOWN.
THAT'S IT.
HAVE A SEAT.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, I'VE GOT
GREAT NEWS.
HAROLD HAS ACTUALLY PAID OFF
THE DEBT ALL BY HIMSELF.
SO NOW WE DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT THE BANK HONOURING
THIS CHEQUE,
EVEN THOUGH WE POST DATED IT
TEN YEARS FROM NOW.