IT’S THE NEW
RED GREEN SHOW
AND NOW HERE'S THE
HONOURING JOE WITH
THE RUSTY JACK,
YOUR HERO,
YOUR HOST,
MY UNCLE,
RED GR-E-E-E-N!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
THE POSSUM LAKE HIGH SCHOOL
MUSIC TEACHER HAS MOVED
INTO A SMALLER HOUSE
AND HAD TO GIVE UP HIS
WHOLE TUBA COLLECTION
SO, BY GOLLY, POSSUM LODGE
IS NOW THE PROUD OWNER
OF 137 TUBAS.
WHY WOULD THE MUSIC TEACHER,
LIKE, GIVE US ALL THOSE?
THAT'S 137 TUBAS.
THAT'S A LOT.
WELL, I THINK HE'S TRYING
TO IMPROVE OUR HEALTH
BECAUSE WHEN YOU
PLAY THE TUBA,
YOU'RE A LOT MORE CAREFUL
ABOUT WHAT YOU EAT.
I KNOW WHAT WE CAN DO WITH THEM.
YOU AND I, WE CAN LEARN
TO PLAY 'EM TOGETHER.
THAT WOULD BE GREAT BECAUSE,
YOU KNOW HOW YOU'RE ALWAYS
LOOKING FOR SOMETHING FOR
ME AND YOU TO DO?
I AM?
WELL, YOU KNOW, WE NEVER
DO ANYTHING TOGETHER,
SO I JUST ASSUMED YOU WERE
LOOKING FOR SOMETHING,
BUT IF YOU WEREN'T
THAT'S OKAY --
NO, NO, NO,
NOW, WAIT NOW.
LET'S DO THIS...
EVERY TIME YOU AND
I ARE TOGETHER,
WHY DON'T YOU
PLAY THE TUBA?
YES! YES! THAT'D BE SO
GREAT IF WE COULD DO THAT
BECAUSE I LOVE THAT INSTRUMENT.
IT'S JUST THIS BEAUTIFUL THING.
YOU KNOW, I'LL PRACTICE
REALLY HARD, AND I'LL LEARN
A WHOLE BUNCH OF SONGS,
AND WHEN WE'RE TOGETHER, I'LL
SHOW YOU WHAT I'VE LEARNED.
AND I'LL EVEN LEARN
SONGS THAT YOU LIKE --
THAT'LL BE GREAT --
LIKE THOSE MILITARY SONGS
THAT YOU LIKE SO MUCH.
THEY WON'T SOUND SO OBSCENE
WHEN YOU CAN'T HEAR THE WORDS.
THAT'D BE FANTASTIC --
SO MUCH FUN.
I'M REALLY LOOKING
FORWARD TO THIS.
YEAH, YEAH.
ME TOO, HAROLD,
'CAUSE WHEN YOU'RE PLAYIN'
THE TUBA, YOU CAN'T TALK.
YEAH.
[♪♪♪]
HERE'S A FEW SCENES
FROM THIS EPISODE.
NOW, I WAS GOING
TO EXPLAIN THINGS
'CAUSE I THINK I COULD
EXPLAIN THAT,
AND I MIGHT ABLE
TO EXPLAIN THIS,
BUT I'LL TELL YOU
SOMETHIN' FOLKS,
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO EXPLAIN THAT.
(REALLY BAD TUBA PLAYING)
HAROLD, YOU BETTER
PLAY A DIFFERENT TUNE.
THE BULLS OVER AT ARNIE'S
ARE GETTING KIND OF EXCITED.
LISTEN TO THIS.
(BAD TUBA PLAYING)
(COUGHING)
(MORE BAD TUBA PLAYING)
RECOGNIZE IT?
YEAH, THE DEATH SCENE
FROM "MOBY DICK."
NO!
"FLIGHT OF
THE BUMBLE BEE."
FLIGHT OF
FANTASY, HAROLD.
DON'T WORRY, WE'LL PUT YOU
RIGHT AT THE BACK OF THE PARADE.
NOBODY'LL EVEN
HEAR YOU.
WHAT PARADE?
OH, I DIDN'T
TELL YOU.
WE'RE GONNA
HAVE A PARADE...
YEAH, ALL TUBAS.
OH, YEAH,
137 TUBAS.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE KIND OF AN
ANNUAL TOURIST ATTRACTION THING,
LIKE MARDI GRAS,
ONLY MORE FUN.
WE'RE GONNA CALL
IT "PARDI GRAS."
NONE OF US PLAY
THE TUBA.
WELL, YOU SEE, ONE AT A TIME,
THAT'S A PROBLEM.
BUT YOU GET 137
PLAYING AT ONCE,
NOBODY'LL EVER KNOW.
BOY, THERE'S NOTHING MORE
FRUSTRATING THAN THE COST
OF SOMETHING AFTER
YOU'VE BOUGHT IT.
I BOUGHT THIS CAR FROM
BUSTER HADFIELD.
NOW IT'S GOT TWO
FLAT FRONT TIRES.
NOW, I CAN BUY TIRES, BUT A NEW
TIRE IS GONNA BE ABOUT 85 BUCKS.
THERE'S TWO OF 'EM,
THAT WOULD BE --
WELL OVER $100 WITH TAX.
I ONLY PAID 50 BUCKS
FOR THE WHOLE CAR.
ANYBODY WHO WOULD SPEND
100 BUCKS ON A $50 CAR
DOESN'T BELONG AT POSSUM LODGE,
THEY BELONG IN
THE GOVERNMENT.
ALL RIGHT, SO THE FIRST THING
YOU CAN DO IS CHECK THE TRUNK.
YOU MIGHT HAVE A SPARE.
THAT'LL SAVE YOU ONE TIRE.
NO.
OKAY, SO THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN
CORNER, I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO MAKE YOUR VERY OWN
INEXPENSIVE TIRES.
FIRST THING YOU WANT TO DO...
CLEAN OUT YOUR CLOSET.
ALL RIGHT, THE OBVIOUS
QUESTION IS...
WHY ARE YOU HANGING ON
TO THESE CLOTHES?
AND DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE SAVING
THEM TO WASH YOUR CAR WITH THEM.
PEOPLE WITH  CLOTHES LIKE
THIS DON'T WASH THEIR CARS.
SO THROW THEM AWAY, OR DONATE
THEM TO CLOWN COLLEGE
OR SOMETHING.
AND THAT LEAVES YOU
WITH YOUR FOOTWEAR.
YOU WANT TO HANG ON TO THESE
BECAUSE THESE PENNY LOAFERS
AND DISCO BOOTS ARE GOING
TO BECOME YOUR NEW TIRES.
ALL RIGHT, THE NEXT THING YOU
NEED IS A PRETTY LONG PIECE
OF FOUR-INCH STEEL PIPE,
WHICH YOU CAN BUY OR,
NINE TIMES OUT OF TEN,
CAN DIG UP RIGHT IN
YOUR OWN BACKYARD...
OR SOMEBODY'S BACKYARD.
NOW YOU'VE GOT TO CUT THE
PIPE INTO 18-INCH LENGTHS.
THERE IS AN EASIER WAY AROUND
MAKING THAT MANY CUTS,
BUT IT INVOLVES YOU HAVING A
STUPID FRIEND OR A SON,
AND I'M NOT THAT LUCKY.
OH, MAN.
ALL RIGHT.
TAKE YOUR PIECE OF PIPE NOW,
AND ATTACH THAT TO THE RIM.
THAT'S GONNA MAKE A
PRETTY BIG SHOE TIRE THERE.
WHAT YOU CAN DO IS SHORTEN --
NO, I'M NOT GOING TO --
NO, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN JUST CUT OUT THE FENDER
HERE A LITTLE BIT, MAKE ROOM
FOR OUR BIG SHOE TIRE.
OH, YEAH, THIS'LL --
NO PROBLEM.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ONE.
WELL, THE TIRE TOOK
A FEW HITS THERE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, YOU'VE GOT TO GET
THAT TIRE OFF THE RIM ANYWAY,
SO I MUST'VE MEANT THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, NOW YOU WANT
TO ATTACH THE PIPES TO
THE RIM THERE.
YOU CAN WELD THEM ON THERE,
BUT I'LL TELL YOU, THEY GOT
THIS NEW GLUE NOW THAT
DRIES INSTANTLY,
AND IT'S AS STRONG AS A WELD.
HAROLD, THIS STUFF'S CRAP.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, THIS IS THE
BASIC STRUCTURE OF YOUR TIRE.
ALL THAT'S MISSING
IS THE SHOES.
YOU PUT THE LEFTS ON THE LEFT
SIDE, RIGHTS ON THE RIGHT SIDE.
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
I'LL TELL YOU THE BEAUTY
OF THIS SYSTEM,
YOU CAN MATCH YOUR FOOTWEAR
TO THE WEATHER CONDITIONS.
YOU'VE GOT YOUR RUBBER BOOTS FOR
THE RAIN, KODIAKS FOR THE SNOW,
RUNNING SHOES WHEN
YOU'RE IN A HURRY.
I WOULD SAY HUSH PUPPIES
FOR NORMAL DRIVING
AND FOR SPECIAL OCCASIONS,
THOSE FLUFFY PINK SLIPPERS.
I'VE GOT A KIND
OF MIX ON THERE,
SO IT'S MORE OR LESS
AN ALL-WEATHER TIRE.
DROP HER DOWN,
AND I'M ALL SET TO GO.
AND THE BEAUTY OF IT IS,
IF I DO HAVE A FLAT TIRE,
I'M CARRYING TWO
SPARES WITH ME,
PLUS ALL THOSE EXTRA SHOES YOU
FIND ALONG THE SIDE OF THE
ROAD FOR SOME REASON.
MAYBE I'M NOT THE FIRST
ONE TO TRY THIS IDEA.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I'M PROBABLY THE FIRST ONE.
ALL RIGHT, SO REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I GOTTA MAKE TRACKS.
HIT MY SHOE HORN.
(HORN HONKING)
SHOE TIRES,
JUST DO IT.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
OLDER GUYS OUT THERE.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S
GONNA COME A DAY,
ONE OF THESE DAYS YOU'RE GONNA
GO INTO WORK, AND YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE A NEW BOSS.
AND CHANCES ARE THAT BOSS IS
GONNA BE YOUNGER THAN YOU,
MAYBE A LOT YOUNGER,
MAYBE YOUNGER THAN YOUR KIDS,
AND THAT CAN BE
KIND OF AWKWARD.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S A BIT
OF ADJUSTMENT THERE,
'CAUSE THEY GET THESE NEW YOUNG
GUYS, THEY COME OUT OF SCHOOL,
AND THEY'VE GOT SOME KIND OF
EDUCATION, AND THEY FEEL THEY
GOTTA MAKE AN IMPRESSION,
AND THEY START UPSETTING
THE ROUTINE, MOVING THE COFFEE
MACHINE, THAT KIND OF THING.
SO HERE'S WHAT TO DO.
JUST KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN;
STAY OUT OF THE WAY.
OH, YEAH. A COUPLE OF
YEARS DOWN THE ROAD,
THAT YOUNG BOSS'LL GET MARRIED,
HAVE KIDS, GET HIMSELF A HOUSE,
AND HE'LL BE AS FRUSTRATED
WITH LIFE AS YOU ARE,
AND WORK'LL GET RIGHT
BACK TO NORMAL.
SO LOOK, DON'T DO ANYTHING.
IT'S WORKED GREAT
FOR YOU SO FAR.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
OW!
(REALLY BAD TUBA PLAYING)
(BLOWING)
TRY EMPTYING THE SPIT
VALVE THERE, HAROLD.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
(LAUGHTER)
TOO BAD I'VE GOT
SUCH A LONG NAME.
MAN, IS THAT A
TUBA OR A SCUBA?
NO, NO, I LEFT IT
OUT IN THE RAIN.
SCARY.
WELL, THINGS ARE REALLY COMING
TOGETHER, THOUGH, FOR OUR PARDI
GRAS PARADE, I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, UNCLE RED,
I WAS DOING SOME READING,
AND MARDI GRAS
MEANS FAT TUESDAY,
WHICH ALREADY SOUNDS
LIKE A LODGE EVENT.
I THINK THE PARADE IS REALLY
GOING TO BE SOMETHING,
WE'RE HAVING A
NAUTICAL THEME
'CAUSE YOU DON'T HAVE TO
HAVE A FLOATING BOAT TO
MAKE A BOATING FLOAT.
AND WE GOT COSTUMES,
AND WE GOT CLOWNS,
AND WE GOT RUBBER THINGS
TO THROW AT THE CROWD.
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE YOU NEED?
YOU NEED, LIKE,
A FIGUREHEAD.
YOU KNOW, A FIGUREHEAD LIKE
SANTA CLAUS, OR THE EASTER
BUNNY OR SPIDERMAN OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
AND THEN WHAT YOU DO IS, YOU PUT
HIM RIGHT ON THE LAST FLOAT
RIGHT AT THE END.
THAT WAY THEY BECOME THE
FOCUS OF THE ENTIRE PARADE.
LIKE THE PRINCE OF
PARDI GRAS KIND OF THING?
EXCELLENT CHOICE.
OH, YEAH, YOU PUT HIM,
YOU KNOW, IN SOME KIND
OF A REALLY COOL COSTUME,
YOU KNOW, SOMEBODY WHO CAPTURES
THE SPIRIT OF PARDI GRAS
AND, OF COURSE, LOOKS
GOOD IN A SEA OF TUBAS.
HAROLD, YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'D BE GREAT AT THAT.
NO, NO WAY.
NO, I DON'T WANNA BECAUSE
IT WILL BE EMBARRASSING.
I DON'T LIKE BEING
EMBARRASSED.
OH, HAROLD,
YOU MUST.
THIS IS KIND OF A, SORT OF,
ANTIQUE ROADKILL SHOW
KIND OF A DEAL,
WHERE LODGE MEMBERS COME IN
AND SEE IF THEY'RE SITTING
ON THE FAMILY JEWELS OR
JUST A CHEAP IMITATION.
OUR EXPERT DALTON HUMPHREY IS
GONNA TELL 'EM WHICH ONE IT IS.
DALTON.
WELL, THANK YOU, RED,
AND I'M HERE WITH MIKE HAMAR
WHO IS HERE THANKS TO
THE PAROLE BOARD.
THANKS DALTON.
I GOT THIS HERE
THING TO SHOW YOU.
YEAH, MY MOM WON
THIS IN 1966
WHEN SHE WAS CROWNED
MISS NUDE AMERICA.
AND THIS WAS THE FIRST PLACE
TROPHY, WAS IT, MIKE?
YEAH.
THIS CUP WITH THE RELIGIOUS
INSCRIPTIONS ALL OVER IT?
LATIN ENGRAVING OF
THE LIFE OF
St. IGNATIUS?
YEAH, WELL, IT WAS
DONATED BY THE POPE.
OH, THE POPE.
WELL, NOT 'THE' POPE,
BUT, LIKE, A POPE,
UH-HUH.
KINDA LIKE AN
ASSISTANT POPE.
THE ARCHBISHOP?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
SEE, HE DONATED
IT TO THE CONTEST
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, HE THOUGHT
THE CONTEST WAS SINFUL,
AND HE HOPED, LIKE, A
BEAUTIFUL RELIGIOUS THING
WOULD MAKE EVERYONE REJECT SIN
AND 'PROSTATE' THEMSELVES
BEFORE THEIR MAKER
AND, YOU KNOW,
BEG FORGIVENESS,
KIND OF LIKE A HEAVENLY
PAROLE HEARING.
AND THE ARCHBISHOP THAT
DONATED THIS, DO YOU
REMEMBER HIS NAME?
AH, DAVE.
DAVE.
WELL, NOW, ARCHBISHOP DAVE
HAD EXCELLENT TASTE
BECAUSE THIS IS A LOVELY
SILVER AND GOLD PIECE,
AND IT IS EXACTLY LIKE
THE ONE IN St. MICHAEL'S
CHURCH IN PORT ASBESTOS.
NO KIDDING.
YES.
IT'S A SILVER AND GOLD CUP
THAT IS USED TO HOLD
HOLY WATER, MIKE;
A CUP THAT WAS ORIGINALLY
WORTH $2,000.
THAT WAS IN 1937,
SO THIS IS A CUP
THAT IS WORTH NOW
PERHAPS OVER $50,000.
YES, IT'S A CUP THAT
THE GOOD PARISHIONERS OF THE
CHURCH SAVED FOR MANY, MANY
YEARS TO BE ABLE TO BUY.
IT'S A CUP THAT HAS BEEN AT THAT
CHURCH AND BEEN A SOURCE OF
FAITH AND PRIDE FOR WELL
OVER HALF A CENTURY.
THIS IS A CUP THAT
THEY WOULD REALLY
LIKE TO GET BACK!
(WEEPING)
MIKE,
MIKE, YOU'RE CRYING.
YEAH.
MIKE, WHY ARE
YOU CRYING?
'CAUSE I'M
GONNA BE RICH.
I WAS A LITTLE LATE ARRIVING
FOR MY ADVENTURE WITH BILL
THIS WEEK.
ANYWAY, OKAY, HE'S GOOD.
HOW YOU DOING BILL?
WHAT'S GOING ON TODAY?
BILL'S GOT A BIT OF A
CARNIVAL PLANNED, I HEARD.
I THOUGHT ONLY WOMEN HAD
DARTS IN THEIR CLOTHES.
ALL RIGHT. I CAN THROW A DART.
OH, MY GOSH, USED TO DO
THIS DOWN AT THE OLD
SIDESHOW THERE,
MY MOM USED TO WORK THERE.
THERE YOU GO,
THREE FOR THREE.
GIVE IT A TRY BILL.
ARE THEY SHARP DARTS, BILL?
I DON'T THINK SO.
NO, TRY ANOTHER ONE.
OH, BOY! OH!
OH, MY GOSH.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT WAS.
ALL RIGHT, THE OLD
WOODEN MILK BOTTLES.
THIS IS A LOT OF FUN.
TAKE A SOFTBALL AND FIRE THEM
AT THE MILK BOTTLES, AND THEY
ALL COME CRASHING DOWN.
NOT BAD.
THAT'S HALF A PRIZE.
YOU HAVE A GO, BILL.
I GUESS THOSE WERE REAL --
WELL, WHAT ELSE WE GOT?
GOT ANY MORE
EVENTS THERE, BILL?
OH, OH, I KNOW
WHAT THIS IS.
THIS IS THE STRONG MAN
AND THE HAMMER AND --
SLEDGE HAMMER.
SEE YOU IN A MINUTE.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT BILL AND
LADDERS. I DON'T THINK HE
UNDERSTANDS THE CONCEPT.
HE'S GOT A LITTLE RING THERE.
HE'S GOT THAT WELDED ON THERE,
AND IT SITS ON THE 4X4,
AND WHEN YOU SLAM ON THE
END OF THE 4X4,
THE CHAIN RUSHES UP THE POLE...
WELL, YOU FIGURE IT OUT!
OKAY, GIVE 'ER A GO.
WANT ME TO TRY?
OH, YEAH, LOOK AT THAT.
I WANT A BIT OF THAT AGAIN.
THAT WAS FUN.
LOOK OUT, BILL.
I'M GONNA DO IT AGAIN.
I'M GOIN' AGAIN.
BILL, I'M GOIN' AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
YOU GO. YOU GO.
OKAY. OKAY. OKAY.
A-W-W-W, THAT'S TOO BAD.
HE DOESN'T HAVE THE
SORT OF ARM STRENGTH.
THAT'S A SHAME.
OH, BOY.
OH! OW! GEESH!
OKAY. NO, I'M FINE.
THAT'S FINE.
THAT'S GOOD. IT'S GOOD.
OKAY, BILL, GIVE IT A TRY.
I'LL STAND BACK A BIT.
MY GOSH, LOOK AT THIS.
HE'S GOING FOR IT.
LOOK AT THAT, AND HE'S GOT IT.
WHAT PRIZE HAVE WE
GOT FOR HIM?
OH, A MIRROR.
OH, WHAT A FUN DAY.
A-A-A-H!
(TUBA PLAYING)
(APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
(TUBA CONTINUES PLAYING)
HEY, HEY, HEY!
OW!
KIND OF AN ODD ECHO
IN THIS PART OF THE LODGE.
ANYWAY, THINGS ARE REALLY
COMIN' TOGETHER WITH OUR
PARDI GRAS PARADE THING.
WE GOT OUR FIGUREHEAD.
GOT OUR PAMPLEMOUSSE,
THE PRINCE OF THE
PARDI GRAS PARADE.
COME ON, PAMPLEMOUSSE.
COME ON IN.
Harold:  NO!
COME ON,
PAMPLEMOUSSE.
Harold:  NO!
COME ON, EVERYONE
LOVES A PAMPLEMOUSSE
COME ON.
HERE WE GO.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
GIVE 'EM THE SPEECH.
SAY IT.
I AM PROUD TO WEAR THE
CEREMONIAL COSTUME OF
THE GREAT PAMPLEMOUSSE,
PROTECTOR OF ALL
PARDI GRASSERS.
VERY GOOD.
NOW, HAROLD, THE WAY I
UNDERSTAND THE LEGEND,
TO WEAR A CEREMONIAL
GARB LIKE THAT,
YOU HAVE TO BE A VIRGIN.
YOU MAY BE OVERQUALIFIED.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'LL BE OKAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M GUESSING YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO WEAR THAT FOR THE REST
OF YOUR LIFE.
ANYWAY, I GOT MY HORN,
I GOT MY PAMPLEMOUSSE,
AND I'M READY TO ROCK.
LET'S GO, HAROLD.
I FORGOT TO GO TO THE BATHROOM
BEFORE I PUT THE COSTUME ON.
OH, HAROLD, HAROLD, HAROLD,
THERE'S 137 TUBAS,
YOU'LL THINK
OF SOMETHIN'.
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
"IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
BUZZ SHERWOOD IS HERE WITH
SOMETHING FOR US TO FIX.
WHOA!! RED,
MAN, WHOA!
YOU KNOW, BUZZ, I DIDN'T
HEAR YOUR PLANE LAND HERE.
DID YOU DRIVE TO
THE LODGE TODAY?
NO, MAN, I FLEW,
BUT I HAD TO LAND
WITHOUT THE PROPELLER
'CAUSE I RAN OUT
OF GAS, RIGHT?
YEAH, SO I HAD TO UM --
WHAT'S THAT WHEN YOU LAND THE
PLANE WITHOUT THE PROPELLER?
I DO IT ALL
THE TIME.
GLIDE?
CRASH!
SO, RIGHT, I GOT YOU
A TOASTER HERE
'CAUSE, LIKE,
IT'S STUCK.
YOU GOT SOME BREAD
STUCK IN THERE?
OH, MAN, ALL MY
BREAD'S IN THERE.
WHAT THE HECK IS
THAT IN THERE?
MY WALLET.
ALL MY BREAD'S
IN THERE, MAN.
I MEAN, I CAN'T EVEN GO
OUT AND BUY A NEW TOASTER.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
LET'S PLUG HER IN.
COOL.
HOW DID YOU GET YOUR WALLET
STUCK IN THE TOASTER, BUZZ?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES WITH THESE
OLDER TOASTERS THERE'S A LITTLE
ADJUSTMENT YOU CAN MAKE --
NO, THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S THE OTHER SIDE.
WHOA, FLASHBACKS!
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, BUZZ, SOMETIMES IN
LIFE, YOU HAVE TO MAKE A CHOICE.
SURE, SURE.
YOU CAN HAVE THE TOASTER,
OR YOU CAN HAVE THE WALLET.
YOU CAN'T HAVE BOTH.
WALLET.
GOOD CHOICE.
OH, MAN, MY WALLET.
IT'S -- IT'S --
IT'S TOAST.
ALL RIGHT. I HATE TO
BE A PARDI GRAS POOPER,
BUT THAT WAS BAD.
HOW IRONIC THAT MARDI GRAS IS
PANCAKE DAY, AND HAROLD WAS
THE ONE TO GET PANCAKED.
LET ME START BY SAYING
IT'S VERY EASY TO UNDERESTIMATE
THE STEEPNESS OF A HILL.
AND, IN FAIRNESS, FLOATS WERE
NEVER MADE TO REACH THOSE
KINDS OF SPEEDS.
NOW, LUCKILY THE IMPACT
DIDN'T HURT HAROLD
BECAUSE, OF COURSE,
HE WAS AIRBORNE BY THEN.
AND I THINK IF I HAD HAD A
LITTLE MORE TIME TO THINK,
I COULD'VE CAUGHT HIM RATHER
THAN JUST SHIELD MYSELF
WITH MY TUBA LIKE THAT.
THIS WAS ALL I COULD SAVE.
I TELL YOU, IT BROKE MY HEART
TO SEE HAROLD ALL WRAPPED
UP IN THAT TUBA,
SOMERSAULTING DOWN THE
MAIN STREET LIKE THAT.
AND I NEVER REALLY
MEANT TO HURT HIM.
THIS IS A SAD, SAD DAY.
(APPLAUSE)
I'M SO SORRY, HAROLD.
YOU?!
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I FORGIVE YOU.
REALLY?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THAT TAKES
A LOT OF BRASS.
JUST A WARNING...
DON'T OPEN MY SPIT VALVE.
HAROLD, I THINK IT'S ONLY
RIGHT THAT YOU HAVE THIS.
THANK YOU.
OKAY.
(POSSUM CALL)
WAS THAT ME?
NO, NO, NO.
IT WAS THE MEETING.
OH, IT'S
MEETING TIME?
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD. I'LL BE
DOWN IN A  MINUTE, ALL RIGHT?
OKAY.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT THERE?
WE'LL KNOW
MORE TOMORROW.
(SOUR TUBA NOTE)
THAT WAS ME.
(APPLAUSE)
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMIN' STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M GONNA BE
BRINGING HAROLD HOME.
IF WE CAN'T CURE HIM,
AT LEAST WE CAN GET HIM TUNED.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHIN'.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF, HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTER]
Harold:  OKAY, HERE HE COMES!
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
HERE HE COMES.
ALL RISE!
Everyone:
QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red:  SIT DOWN.
Harold:  OKAY, WE JUST GOT THE
ONE ANNOUNCEMENT THIS WEEK.
UM, BUSTER HADFIELD'S
DOG HAS RUN AWAY AGAIN.
IT'S THE 47th TIME THIS YEAR,
THERE'S NO
DESCRIPTION AVAILABLE.
BUSTER SAYS THE DOG'S
RUN AWAY SO MANY TIMES,
HE'S FORGOTTEN WHAT IT
LOOKS LIKE FROM THE FRONT.
IT'S FUNNY HOW PEOPLE
GET TO RESEMBLE THEIR
PETS, ISN'T IT?
OH, I THOUGHT I'D FOUND HIM.