[quirky upbeat music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> OKAY, IT'S SHOWTIME.
HANG ON TO YOUR HATS, OR FOR
THOSE OF YOU WITH SATELLITE
DISHES, YOUR TOQUES, BECAUSE
IT'S TIME FOR THE BEGINNING OF
THE START OF THE RED GREEN SHOW
WITH A LOT OF REGULARS
AND A COUPLE OF OCCASIONALS
BUT MOSTLY FEATURING A MAN WHO
SPENDS A LOT OF TIMES OUTDOORS--
WELL, WITH VERY GOOD REASON.
SO PLEASE WELCOME THE STAR OF
THE RED GREEN SHOW--
AND MY UNCLE, IF I MIGHT INJECT
A PERSONAL NOTE AT THIS TIME--
MR. RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
AND WELCOME TO THE SHOW,
ESPECIALLY THANK YOU FOR TUNING
US IN, BECAUSE WITHOUT YOU,
I'D JUST BE TALKING TO A WALL,
WHICH REMINDS ME OF A STORY.
YOU KNOW, LAST WEEKEND, UP AT
THE LODGE, STINKY PETERSON WAS
DOING EVERYTHING IN HIS POWER TO
TRY TO GET OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S
GOAT, NOT REALIZING THAT
SEDGEWICK HAD GIVEN THE GOAT
AWAY TO HELP SETTLE A CARD GAME
DISPUTE THAT INVOLVED A DECK
WITH SEVEN ACES IN IT.
>> EXCUSE ME, UNCLE RED, UM,
WELL, AS YOUR
PRODUCER/DIRECTOR/CONCERNED
NEPHEW, IT JUST BEHOOVES ME AT
THIS TIME TO MENTION THAT
THE STORY YOU ARE ARTICULATING
SOMEWHAT IS A YAWNER, ACTUALLY,
A--SIDE ISSUE OF THIS
PARTICULARLY IMPORTANT JUNCTURE
IN THE PROGRAM.
>> OH, REALLY, HAROLD?
SO WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST?
>> WELL, I JUST--I WAS WONDERING
IF ANY OF THE VIEWERS HAVE
NOTICED THIS PIECE OF EQUIPMENT
HANGING AROUND MY NECK/THROAT.
IT IS AN ELECTRONIC EFFECTS
MACHINE THAT ENABLES ME
TO DO THIS...
[keys clacking]
[chuckles]
SO I CAN GO TO A MORE
INTERESTING SEGMENT, WHICH,
YOU KNOW, HAS EVERY OPPORTUNITY
AND POSSIBILITY.
>> WELL, THIS IS MY SHOW,
HAROLD, AND WE WON'T GO TO
THE NEXT SEGMENT UNTIL I SAY SO.
>> OH, YEAH, WELL, YEAH, SURE,
RIGHT.
OH, SORRY.
I--I MISUNDERSTOOD.
[mellow strumming]
>> I'VE DATED YOUNG WOMEN
I'VE DANCED WITH OLD MEN
I'VE WATERED MY HORSE
AGAIN AND AGAIN
AND AGAIN AND AGAIN
AND AGAIN
I'VE RODE IN NEW CARS
I'VE DRIVEN OLD TRUCKS
BUT NONE CAN COMPARE
TO THE THRILL OF
SHOOTING DUCKS
SHOOTING DUCKS!
BLAST THEM OUT OF THE SKY
BLOW THEM TO MINCEMEAT
IN THE WINK OF AN EYE
OH, I LOVE SHOOTING DUCKS
FROM DEEP IN THE BLIND
BUT IF I EVER ACTUALLY
HIT ONE
I'D LIKELY CHANGE MY MIND
THIS WEEK IN HANDYMAN CORNER,
WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU SOME
IMAGINATIVE AND SOME CREATIVE
AND, EVEN TO A CERTAIN SENSE,
THOUGHTFUL THINGS YOU CAN DO
WITH A GARAGE DOOR OPENER.
NOW, A GARAGE DOOR OPENER IS
A HANDY PIECE OF EQUIPMENT,
BUT THE THING THAT IT DOES WORST
IS OPEN GARAGE DOORS.
RATHER THAN JUST TAKE IT AND
THROW IT IN THE LAKE, WHAT YOU
SHOULD DO IS USE YOUR
IMAGINATION AND THINK OF SOME
OTHER APPLICATIONS OF THE
GARAGE DOOR OPENER.
FOR EXAMPLE, HERE I'VE HOOKED UP
THE GARAGE DOOR OPENER TO
THE DOOR OF THE--I GUESS, THAT'S
A STOVE, REALLY, IS WHAT IT IS,
AND JUST IMAGINE NOW THAT I'M
SITTING IN MY LIVING ROOM
WATCHING A FOOTBALL GAME ON
TELEVISION, AND I'VE GOT
SOMETHING IN THE OVEN, SO TO
SPEAK, MAYBE A TURKEY OR A ROAST
BEEF OR A RACCOON OR SOMETHING,
AND I WANT TO CHECK ON THE
DINNER, BUT I DON'T WANT TO
MISS THE GAME.
WITH THE GARAGE DOOR OPENER,
I CAN JUST STAY BACK,
AND I'VE GOT THE BINOCULARS
TO KIND OF CHECK ON HOW
THE DINNER'S GOING, SO I'LL
JUST SHOW YOU HOW IT WORKS.
I JUST HIT THIS LIKE THIS AND--
"WELL, I WONDER
HOW THE DINNER'S DOING.
NO, IT'S NOT READY YET."
NOW ALL I GOT TO DO THEN
IS JUST TURN THE UNIT OFF,
JUST TURN THE--
JUST TURN THIS UNIT OFF.
[metal screeching]
AND YOU...
WELL, I GUESS MAYBE IT IS
DINNERTIME.
I'M--I'M GETTING HUNGRY.
TIME TO TIE ON THE OLD FEED BAG,
I GUESS.
HOW MANY OF YOU HAVE DREAMED
ABOUT HAVING YOUR OWN PERSONAL
ELEVATOR RIGHT INSIDE YOUR HOME?
YOU CAN DO IT JUST LIKE I'VE
DONE HERE, AND I MOUNTED THE
GARAGE DOOR OPENER WITH THE
CHAIN GOING UP--THAT'S SORT OF
A PULLEY SITUATION--AND THEN IT
HOOKS ONTO A ROPE AND COMES DOWN
TO MY BASKET CAGE OR ELEVATOR
ENCLOSURE--WHATEVER YOU WANT
TO CALL THAT.
SO WHEN I WANT TO GO UP, SAY,
THE SECOND FLOOR--
DO WHATEVER IT IS THAT I DO ON
THE SECOND FLOOR--ALL I HAVE
TO DO IS JUST AIM THE GARAGE
DOOR OPENER, HIT THE BUTTON,
AND, UH, I START, UH, AHEM--
I START...
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, OBVIOUSLY,
I HAVE TO BOLT THE OPENER
TO THE FLOOR, UH,
BECAUSE I GUESS I WEIGH, WELL--
OF COURSE, I WEIGH MORE THAN--
WELL, UH...
I'M SURE THAT
YOU ALL GET THE IDEA ANYWAY.
IT CAN WORK, AND A LOT OF OTHER
IDEAS--YOU'RE ONLY LIMITED BY
YOUR OWN IMAGINATION.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME, REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[machinery screeching]
DON'T GO AWAY, BECAUSE I WANT
TO TELL YOU WHAT STINKY PETERSON
DID TO OLD MAN SEDGEWICK.
>> IT'S THE SAME THING THAT
UNCLE RED'S STORIES
DO TO THE SHOW.
>> "IT IS WINTER.
THE CHRISTMAS LIGHTS ARE UP.
THEY FRAME THE HOUSE IN
TWINKLING RAINBOW COLORS FROM
LATE DECEMBER TO MID JULY."
NOW, AS I WAS SAYING,
STINKY PETERSON WAS DETERMINED
TO PLAY A PRACTICAL JOKE
ON OLD MAN SEDGEWICK,
AND OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
WAS ASLEEP BY THE WOODSTOVE.
IN FACT, HE HAD HIS LEGS WRAPPED
RIGHT AROUND IT AND HAD HIS FACE
UP AGAINST THE CHIMNEY.
SO STINKY SNEAKS IN THERE, AND
HE OPENS UP THE STOVE, AND HE
DROPS IN A BOX OF FIRECRACKERS,
AND HE PUTS THE LID BACK ON,
AND HE GOES INTO THE NEXT ROOM,
AND THEN HE WAITS, YOU KNOW,
AND THEN HE COMES BACK IN,
AND HE OPENS UP THE STOVE, AND
HE TAKES THE FIRECRACKERS OUT,
AND THEN HE STARTS A FIRE.
THEN HE PUTS THE FIRECRACKERS
IN, AND THEN HE PUTS--
AND THEN HE GOES INTO THE NEXT
ROOM, AND THEN HE WAITS.
WELL, AFTER ABOUT TEN SECONDS,
THEY ALL GO OFF AT ONCE--
BOOMS AND BANGS AND ROMAN
CANDLES ZINGING OUT THROUGH THE
CRACKS IN THE STOVE, YOU KNOW,
BUT IT DIDN'T EVEN WAKE OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK UP.
HE JUST--HE LAY THERE WITH HIS
EYES SHUT, BIG SMILE ON HIS
FACE, UNTIL IT WAS ALL OVER,
AND THEN HE SAID,
"HOW WAS IT FOR YOU?"
>> OH, NO WAY, UNCLE RED.
AS IF!
THAT COULDN'T HAPPEN--
DIDN'T HAPPEN LIKE THAT.
NOT LIKE THAT, ANYWAY.
GET OUT OF HERE.
AH, NO WAY.
>> WELL, ALL RIGHT,
I WAS EMBELLISHING FOR
THE GOOD OF THE SHOW, HAROLD.
>> OH, OH, EXCELLENT, LIKE HYPE.
OH, OKAY, YEAH, ALL RIGHT, OKAY,
I'M WITH YOU ON THAT ONE.
[chuckles]
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING THERE,
HAROLD?
>> I WAS EMBELLISHING...
FOR THE GOOD OF THE SHOW.
>> WHILE YOU AND I ARE GOING
ABOUT OUR DAILY BUSINESS,
THERE'S SOMEONE OUT LOOKING OUT
OVER THE FOREST ON OUR BEHALF
UP IN THE TIMBERLAND,
UP IN THE HINTERLAND,
AND THAT MAN IS RANGER GORD.
FROM HIS PERCH HIGH ATOP,
RIGHT THERE IN HIS PERCH,
IN HIS PERCH UP IN THE TREE,
FROM HIS PERCH, YEAH,
LOOKING OVER OUR FOREST.
HE'S DOING THE JOB FOR
YOU AND I, AND IT'S RANGER GORD.
>> WOW, ANOTHER PERSON.
>> YEAH.
>> HI.
>> HOW ARE YOU, GORD?
IT'S ME.
>> HA-HA, OH, IT'S OKAY.
BEGGARS CAN'T BE CHOOSERS, HUH?
AND YOU BROUGHT A CAMERAMAN
AND EVERYTHING.
>> OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH.
>> HI, FOLKS AT HOME.
HOW YOU BEEN?
I'M FINE.
I MISS YOU A LOT.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, ALL
RIGHT, SO, UH, WHAT'S NEW
SINCE WE WERE HERE LAST, EH?
WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON?
>> WELL, UH, I FOUND OUT
YOU CAN SEE THE FOREST
FOR THE TREES.
>> OH, FOR GOD SAKES, HUH?
THAT'S IT?
WELL, THAT'S A GOOD THING TO
FIND OUT.
>> OH, YEAH, AND I'VE BEEN
LEARNING GUITAR BY MAIL.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> I KNOW ALL THE LATEST HITS.
[clears throat]
STAYING ALIVE
WHOO, HOO, HOO, HOO
STAYING A...
LIVE
BEEN LEARNING ALL THE SONGS
I HAVE ON EIGHT-TRACK.
>> OH, THAT'S GREAT.
THAT'S GREAT.
WELL, I GUESS YOU GOT
TO DO SOMETHING, YOU KNOW,
TO KEEP YOUR MIND BUSY,
OTHERWISE...
>> OH, YEAH, YEAH, YOU GOT TO
DO SOMETHING, RIGHT?
>> SURE.
>> OTHERWISE, YOU'D, UH--
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN UP HERE FOR
13 YEARS--ALMOST 13 YEARS.
>> ALMOST 13 YEARS NOW.
>> 12 YEARS AND, UH...
>> YEAH.
>> [sobs]
>> OH, OH, WELL, UM...
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S FINE.
I UNDERSTAND THAT.
YOU KNOW, HE'S BEEN UP HERE
FOR 12 YEARS, AND...
>> I'M SORRY.
>> THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S PERFECTLY ALL RIGHT.
>> BUT, YOU KNOW, I'M NOT
COMPLETELY ALONE, RED.
>> OH, OH.
>> I HAVE SAMANTHA.
>> OH, NOW, WHO IS SAMANTHA?
IT'S NOT LIKE A BEAR OR
SOMETHING, IS IT?
>> NO, SAMANTHA IS A WOMAN, RED.
>> OH, FOR GOSH SAKE.
GOOD FOR YOU, HUH?
>> SHE HAS A CABIN WAY OVER
ON THAT NEXT HILL THERE.
SHE'S OUT MOST DAYS SUNNING
HERSELF IN HER BATHING SUIT.
>> THIS WAY?
>> OVER HERE, OVER HERE.
>> OH, THERE'S A CABIN.
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T SEE ANYBODY, THOUGH.
>> OH, HERE.
SHE'S IN THAT BIG WINDOW
OUT FRONT.
I DON'T REALLY KNOW IF HER NAME
IS SAMANTHA.
I JUST IMAGINE IT'S SAMANTHA.
>> YEAH?
>> JUST KNOWING SHE'S THERE IS
COMFORTING, THOUGH.
I WONDER WHAT HER REAL NAME IS.
WOULD IT BE TOO MUCH OF A
COINCIDENCE IF IT WAS SAMANTHA,
HUH?
>> UH, RANGER GORD,
THAT'S A LOG.
I CAN SEE THE WINDOW, AND IT
LOOKS A BIT LIKE A WOMAN, BUT,
UH, THAT'S A LOG.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
IT'S A WOMAN.
>> NO, NO, THAT'S A LOG.
TAKE A LOOK YOURSELF.
>> I'M IN LOVE WITH
A FALLEN LOG.
>> WE GOT TO GET GOING.
IT WAS REALLY GOOD TO SEE YOU
AGAIN, EH?
>> COME ON.
STICK AROUND FOR A BIT.
>> WELL, UH, MAYBE ANOTHER TIME
WE'LL STAY OVER, OKAY, BUT NOT
THIS TIME.
>> OH, COME ON, I WAS GONNA
HAVE A BIG BARBECUE.
I GOT CANNED CORN, AND I GOT
SOME BEANS FOR SPECIAL
OCCASIONS.
I WAS GONNA INVITE SAMANTHA
OVER--
I GUESS THERE'S NO POINT
IN INVITING SAMANTHA OVER NOW,
IS THERE?
>> WELL, NOT UNLESS YOU NEED
FIREWOOD.
>> SHUT UP!
[folksy guitar and spoons music plays]
>> THERE ARE MANY
FINE HOBBIES
A PERSON CAN DO
LIKE COLLECTING THINGS
YOU FIND ON YOUR SHOE
WALKING ON BEES
AND DANCING WITH SHEEP
BUT GUYS AND ME
WE LIKE TO SLEEP
SLEEP THROUGH THE NIGHT
>> SLEEP, ALL NIGHT!
>> SLEEP HALF THE DAY
LIE BACK AND SLEEP
YOUR WHOLE LIFE AWAY
UP IN THE BUNKHOUSE
SNORING AND WORSE
BUT THE BEST SLEEP OF ALL
IS A RIDE IN THE HEARSE
>> OH, UNCLE RED, PERFECT.
THIS IS GREAT.
IT'S MAIL BAG TIME, OKAY?
SO YOU CHOOSE THE GREEN CHAIR,
BECAUSE I'VE ALREADY CHOSEN
THE WHITE CHAIR, AND I HAVE
A LETTER HERE.
I'LL READ IT OUT LOUD,
AND YOU CAN ANSWER IT, RIGHT?
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT WE DO ON
EVERY SEGMENT.
WE SHOULD CONTINUE WITH THAT,
I MEAN, IF IT'S CONVENIENT
WITH YOU.
>> JUST READ THE LETTER, HAROLD,
WOULD YOU?
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHTY.
THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S A YES.
OKAY.
"DEAR RED, EVER SINCE MY HUSBAND
RETIRED, HE'S BEEN HANGING
AROUND THE HOUSE
GETTING ON MY NERVES.
HE SHUFFLES AROUND AT ODDS,
COMPLAINING AND GROUSING.
IT'S DRIVING ME NUTS.
I CAN'T TAKE MUCH MORE OF THIS.
IS THERE ANY HOPE FOR ME?"
>> WELL, HAROLD, THIS IS
SOMETHING WE'VE HEARD BEFORE,
WHERE A FELLOW RETIRES,
AND HE CAN'T FIND ENOUGH TO DO.
WHAT THIS WOMAN HAS TO DO IS TO
FIND A HOBBY FOR HER HUSBAND,
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING TO KEEP HIM
KIND OF INTERESTED AND OCCUPIED.
I SUGGEST WATCHING TELEVISION.
IT'S EDUCATIONAL, IT'S
ENTERTAINING, AND HE CAN DO IT
DAY AND NIGHT EVEN WHEN THEY
HAVE GUESTS OVER.
>> YEAH, BUT, UNCLE RED, IT'S
NOT MUCH OF A SOCIAL ACTIVITY,
REALLY, IS IT?
WATCHING TV IS OKAY EVERY NOW
AND THEN, BUT IT'S REALLY NOT
A HOBBY, NOT LIKE, YOU KNOW,
LIKE STAMP COLLECTING OR MAKING
CABINETS OR PRODUCING MUSIC
VIDEOS FOR NEW WAVE BANDS,
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING CREATIVE
LIKE THAT.
DON'T YOU THINK THAT'D BE
A BETTER SUGGESTION AT
THIS JUNCTURE IN TIME?
DON'T YOU THINK?
>> WELL, ALL RIGHT, HAROLD,
I DID HEAR OF THIS ONE FELLOW
THAT, WHEN HE RETIRED, HE DID
SOMETHING HE WANTED TO DO HIS
WHOLE LIFE, WHICH IS, UH--
WHICH IS CARVING STATUES
OUT OF WOOD WITH A CHAIN SAW.
IT GOT HIM OUTDOORS, AND HE
WOULD BE CARVING THEM OUT OF
THOSE BIG TREE TRUNKS, YOU KNOW,
SO HE WAS GETTING HIS FRESH AIR,
AND THAT WAS A CREATIVE THING,
AND PLUS, CARRYING AROUND
A 40-POUND CHAIN SAW REALLY
KEEPS THE OLD TICKER IN SHAPE.
>> 40 POUNDS?
>> WELL, YOU NEED THE SAW WITH
THE 6-FOOT BLADE ON THERE TO CUT
THROUGH THE HEAVIER WOODS.
>> YEAH, YOU CAN'T EVEN LIFT
ONE OF THOSE.
>> WELL, THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
I'M NOT RETIRED YET.
NOW, HE WOULD JUST CARVE
STRICTLY CATFISH, BUT YOU COULD
DO INSECTS OR EVEN CHILDREN
WITH THE LARGE, SAD EYES.
>> I BET YOU THERE'S A GOOD
MARKET FOR THAT TOO--
A REAL HUGE MARKET.
I BET YOU THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
I BET YOU THERE IS.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
I BET YOU.
>> WELL, THE CATFISH SOLD WELL.
THEY WERE ABOUT 10 FEET LONG,
MADE OF REDWOOD, HECK OF A LAWN
ORNAMENT.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE ACTUALLY
FEEDING RIGHT ON THE LAWN THERE.
I HEARD AN AMUSEMENT PARK IN
MISSOURI BOUGHT ABOUT 40 OF THEM
AND MADE A HUGE CATFISH
MERRY-GO-ROUND.
BUT AFTER ABOUT FIVE YEARS OF
MAKING--HE'D DONE SO WELL
WITH THESE, HE HAD ENOUGH MONEY
TO BUY HIMSELF A NEW CHAIN SAW.
>> OH, HEY, THAT'S GREAT.
I BET YOU THAT ANSWERS OUR
LADY VIEWER'S QUESTION.
>> YEAH, IT'S A GOOD HOBBY, AND
IF THE HUSBAND GETS BORED WITH
IT OR SOMETHING, AND HE'S STILL
GETTING ON HER NERVES, SHE CAN
JUST, YOU KNOW, USE THE
CHAIN SAW ON HIM.
>> OH, NO, NO, UNCLE RED, NO.
HE'S KIDDING.
TELL HER YOU'RE KIDDING,
UNCLE RED.
DON'T SAY THINGS LIKE THAT.
TELL HER YOU'RE KIDDING.
>> WELL, WHATEVER.
>> HE'S KIDDING.
>> ONE OF THE THINGS BILL
WANTED TO SHOW YOU WAS HOW
YOU CAN SURVIVE IN THE FOREST
BY FISHING.
EVEN THOUGH YOU HAVE
NO EQUIPMENT, YOU CAN JUST FIND
THINGS AROUND THAT YOU CAN USE.
THE FIRST THING HE WANTS TO SHOW
YOU IS HOW TO DO A LITTLE
SPEARFISHING.
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR IS SOME
SORT OF A BRANCH OR A TREE LIMB.
NOW, THAT ONE'S GOT TOO MUCH OF
A CURVE; YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING STRAIGHT.
AND THAT'S GOT TOO MANY
BRANCHES ON IT.
NOW, THAT LOOKS BETTER.
>> [grunts]
>> OH, BOY, OH, BOY, OH, BOY.
THAT SMARTS.
OOH.
HE'S OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
DON'T FORGET THE POLE,
ALL RIGHT.
SO NEXT THING, HE'S GOT TO
SHARPEN THE END THERE AND--
OH, FOR GOSH SAKE.
CHECK YOUR KNIFE.
ALWAYS CHECK YOUR KNIFE.
SEE HOW THE WATER REFRACTS
THINGS?
THEY LOOK BENT, AND THIS IS WHAT
YOU GOT TO BE CAREFUL OF WHEN
YOU'RE SPEARFISHING.
OH, ALL RIGHT, OKAY, WELL,
THAT ONE WASN'T--
BUT YOU GET THE IDEA.
SO NOW BILL KIND OF HAS TO ALLOW
FOR THAT ANGLE WHEN HE GOES FOR
THE FISH, AND...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT DOES
AT ALL.
HE SEEMS LIKE HE'S--
THERE, I THINK HE'S GOT
SOMETHING.
I THINK HE'S GOT ONE.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, HE'S GOOD.
WELL, BILL'S BEEN DOING THIS
A LONG TIME.
HE KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
WELL, SOMETIMES HE KNOWS WHAT
HE'S DOING.
>> OKAY.
>> SO GIVE UP ON THE
SPEARFISHING.
THEY'RE GONNA TRY TO MAKE
A FISHING POLE OUT OF THIS,
AND THE NEXT THING HE NEEDS,
HE ONLY NEEDS A LINE.
NOW, BILL HAS AN INTERESTING
APPROACH.
HE USES A THREAD RIGHT OUT OF
HIS CLOTHES.
AND WHAT HE'S GONNA DO IS,
I GUESS, PUT THIS ON...
OH, FOR GOD'S SAKE.
PUT THAT ON--UH, EASY THERE,
BILL, EASY, EASY, EASY, EASY,
EASY, EASY, EASY, EASY.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
WE'RE OKAY.
AND, OH, LOOK WHAT HE'S DOING
HERE--KIBITZING AROUND.
THAT WON'T WORK BECAUSE MY
CLOTHES ARE STAPLED TOGETHER.
AND HE'S GONNA--
OH, THAT BILL IS A REAL KIDDER.
BUT HE'S GATHERING UP
THE THREAD.
I GUESS THAT'S PROBABLY ENOUGH,
BILL, DON'T YOU THINK?
PROBABLY ENOUGH, BILL, BILL?
OH, BOY, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, HE WINDS THAT ONTO
THE ROD THERE.
AND NOW WHAT HE NEEDS TO DO IS
FIND SOME BAIT, SO HE'S LOOKING
FOR--I THINK HE'S LOOKING FOR
A WORM HERE, LOOKING UNDER ROCKS
AND...NOTHING THERE.
WHAT'S THIS?
pop!
>> OH!
>> OH...OH, MY GOD.
I DIDN'T--I WONDER HOW LONG THAT
WAS IN THERE.
OH...
>> OUCH!
>> BILL DOESN'T LIKE PUTTING
THE WORM ON THE HOOK, DOES HE?
WELL, GOD--WELL, ANYWAY, HE'S
ALL SET, AND THEN HE GOES--
THROWS THE BAIT INTO THE WATER,
AND HE'S--LOOK AT THAT.
THERE'S A MAN--OH, JEEZ.
HE'S GOT ONE.
HE'S GOT SOMETHING THERE.
HE'S GOT SOMETHING.
OH, HE'S--SEE, THERE?
WOW.
IT'S PUTTING UP A FIGHT.
THIS IS A GOOD ONE.
OH, THIS IS GREAT.
THIS IS GREAT.
I LIKE THAT LOOK WITH THE PANTS
ROLLED UP.
BE CAREFUL NOW, BILL,
BE CAREFUL--OH.
AH, HE'S ALL RIGHT.
AND HE HAULS HER IN.
THAT'S A BIG ONE.
HE'S GOT--WAIT A MINUTE.
OH, FOR GOSH SAKE.
OH...
THEN HE MAKES US EAT
WHATEVER HE CATCHES.
BUT HE'S HAPPY TO SHARE--MORE
THAN HAPPY TO SHARE, I THINK.
"EAT IT," HE SAYS.
"IT IS WINTER.
A LITTLE VOICE SAYS, 'ME, ME,
YOU'RE OUT OF WINDSHIELD WIPER
FLUID AGAIN.'"
ALL RIGHT, AT THIS POINT,
I'D LIKE TO BRING THE SHOW
TO A COMPLETE HALT
AND GIVE HAROLD A CHANCE TO SAY
A FEW WORDS.
HAROLD, THE FLOOR IS YOURS.
DON'T MESS IT UP.
>> OKAY, UM, MUSIC VIDEOS,
RIGHT?
OKAY, A LOT OF SO-CALLED
EDUCATORS AND A LOT OF SO-CALLED
EXPERTS AND A LOT OF SO-CALLED
PARENTS THINK THAT THERE'S TOO
MUCH VIOLENCE AND TOO MUCH SEX
IN MUSIC VIDEOS.
WELL, I WOULD LIKE TO SAY TO
THEM--YOU KNOW, IF I COULD SAY
TO THEM.
THEY'RE NOT HERE, BUT I'M SAYING
TO THEM--IF THEY COULD
HEAR THIS, "NO."
[mumbling indistinctly]
WELL, I AGREE--I AGREE THAT
THERE'S TOO MUCH VIOLENCE IN
VIDEOS, AND GRANTED, THAT WILL
NOT MAKE ME POPULAR WITH A LOT
OF TEENAGERS, BUT I'M NOT
POPULAR WITH THEM NOW,
SO LIKE I CARE OR SOMETHING.
YEAH, TAKE A MINUTE
OUT OF MY BUSY DAY
AND MAKE ME CARE--I DON'T.
BUT ANYWAY, AS FAR AS TOO MUCH
SEX IN VIDEOS GOES, I JUST LIKE
TO THINK THAT, WELL--THIS IS MY
OPINION, AND YOU'RE WELCOME TO
SHARE IT--THAT I THINK THERE'S
NO SUCH THING AS TOO MUCH SEX.
[chuckles]
THERE'S A TERRIBLE, TERRIBLE
THING CALLED TOO LITTLE SEX.
BELIEVE ME, I KNOW.
IT'S HORRIBLE.
BUT MUSIC IS, LIKE, ALL ABOUT
LOVE AND ROMANCE, RIGHT?
AND, WELL, LOVE AND ROMANCE IS
ALL LEADING UP TO SEX, RIGHT?
AND NOBODY OBJECTS WHEN THEY
PLAY THE SONG DON'T SIT UNDER
THE APPLE TREE.
WELL, I OBJECT.
IT'S A STUPID SONG.
I LIKE THE MESSAGE, THOUGH.
>> I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN THE STORY
ABOUT STINKY PETERSON AND OLD
MAN SEDGEWICK.
SO STAY TUNED.
>> YOU CAN SEE WHY IT'S SO HARD
FOR ME TO MAKE THIS SHOW
ENTERTAINING.
>> DAVE, WHY DON'T WE TRY
HITTING THE BALL?
I GOT A BAT HERE, AND WOULD YOU
LIKE TO--WOULD YOU LIKE TO HIT,
OR WOULD YOU LIKE
TO PITCH ON THAT?
>> COULD I HIT?
>> NO, WHAT I'M SAYING IS,
WOULD YOU LIKE TO HIT THE BALL,
OR WOULD YOU LIKE TO PITCH?
>> HIT THE BALL.
>> HAVE YOU EVER TRIED PITCHING?
IT'S A LOT OF FUN.
>> IT ISN'T.
>> YEAH, I THINK IT IS.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT WE'LL DO.
YOU KNOW, WHY DON'T WE FLIP
A COIN?
AND THEN HOWEVER THAT GOES,
WE'LL DECIDE WHO HITS AND WHO
PITCHES, OKAY?
SO YOU CALL IT IN THE AIR, OKAY?
>> HEADS.
>> NO.
ALL RIGHT, SO, YOU KNOW,
IT'S KIND OF A LESSON IN LIFE,
I THINK, FOR THE YOUNGSTERS
TO JUST SEE THAT THINGS
DON'T ALWAYS GO THE WAY
YOU WANT THEM TO GO.
GIVE AND TAKE.
BACK UP A BIT, DAVE.
I'M GONNA PITCH TO MYSELF NOW
BECAUSE OTHERWISE, HE'S NEVER
GONNA GIVE ME ANYTHING TO HIT.
ALL RIGHT, DAVE, ARE YOU READY?
NOW GET UNDER IT.
WHERE'S YOUR HELMET?
OH, NEVER MIND.
OKAY, HERE WE GO, JUST A NICE
SOFT ONE.
HEY, COME AND GET THAT, DAVE?
THE THING IS HERE THAT, WITH
THE KID, THEY GOT THE ENERGY.
THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH IT.
I SAY TO THEM, "COME ON OUT
AND PLAY WITH ME, AND THEN YOUR
ENERGY WILL GET USED.
PLAY WITH ME."
OKAY, DAVE, YOU ALL SET?
>> YEP.
>> YOU LOOK KIND OF TIRED.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, SEE, THE THING IS THAT--
GONNA GET SOME--
THEY GET SOME FRESH AIR.
THEY GET SOME EXERCISE.
THEIR LEGS ARE GETTING
MOVED AROUND.
MIND YOU, YOU KNOW, I'M GETTING
KIND OF OLD FOR THIS, BUT,
ANYWAY, I GET TO SPEND SOME TIME
WITH THE YOUNG FELLOW,
AND HE GETS TO LEARN WHAT
GROWING UP IS ALL ABOUT.
SO ANYWAY, STINKY PETERSON KEPT
PLAYING PRACTICAL JOKES ON OLD
MAN SEDGEWICK THE WHOLE EVENING,
BUT, YOU KNOW, THE OLD GUY NEVER
GOT RILED.
I MEAN, EVEN AFTER DINNER THERE,
WHERE HE WAS SCRAPING THE
SHAVING CREAM OFF OF HIS PIE,
HE SAID TO STINKY, "YOU KNOW,
STINKY, IF YOU WANT TO GROW OLD
GRACEFULLY, YOU GOT TO FIND
A WAY TO JUST ACCEPT LIFE AND
NOT GET UPSET ABOUT PRANKS,
YOU KNOW."
AND STINKY WAS STILL MULLING
THAT OVER WHEN HE WENT TO BED
AND THEN FOUND OUT THAT
HIS SHEETS AND HIS MATTRESS
HAD BEEN FRENCHED, BUT HE DIDN'T
REALLY NOTICE THAT BECAUSE HIS
PAJAMAS WERE SO FULL OF ITCHING
POWDER, YOU KNOW, AND THEN,
OF COURSE, THE BED COLLAPSED,
AND HE WENT RIGHT DOWN THROUGH
THE CUTAWAY FLOORBOARDS, BOUNCED
OFF THE NAUGAHYDE RECLINER
OUT THROUGH THE FRONT WINDOW AND
HEADFIRST INTO THE SEPTIC TANK.
AND OLD MAN SEDGEWICK YELLED
DOWN THROUGH THE SEPTIC TANK,
"OH, YEAH, REVENGE IS GOOD TOO."
YEAH, LIVE AND LEARN.
AND THE DOCTORS SAY HE WILL.
ANYWAY, UH, IF MY WIFE IS
WATCHING, I'LL BE COMING
STRAIGHT HOME, AND I'M BRINGING
ANOTHER BUNCH OF FLOWERS
TONIGHT.
UH, I DO THIS A FEW TIMES
A YEAR, BECAUSE I'M REALLY NOT
TOO SURE WHEN OUR ANNIVERSARY
IS, AND THIS WAY, EVERYBODY
WINS.
SO THANKS FOR WATCHING THE SHOW,
AND UNTIL NEXT TIME, ON BEHALF
OF MYSELF AND HAROLD OVER HERE,
UH, AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
AT THE LODGE, KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[applause]
>> SMOKE ON THE WATER
STAYING ALIVE
WHOO, HOO, HOO, HOO
NA-NA, NA, NA, NA
NA, NA, NA-NA, NA
UH, NA, NA...