IT'S THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW!
(APPLAUSE)
AND NOW, HERE'S THE JULIUS
CAESAR OF POSSUM LODGE.
HE CAME; HE SAW;
HE COCKED OUT.
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE,
RED GREEN!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE IT.
APPRECIATE IT.
WELCOME TO POSSUM LODGE.
BOY, OH, BOY.
BIG, BIG, WEEK AT THE
LODGE THIS WEEK.
GOT A REAL SPECIAL
EVENT PLANNED.
OUR VERY FIRST EVER
RUNNING OF THE BULLS.
YEAH, WE ALL GOT A TOUCH
OF THE POMPLONA.
YEAH, I HAD THAT ONE TIME.
COUPLE OF SPOON FULLS OF IMODIUM
AND KEEP YOUR RUNNING SHOES ON.
NO, UNCLE RED, POMPLONA IS A
CITY IN SPAIN WHERE THEY HAVE
THE REAL RUNNING OF THE BULLS.
OH, YEAH.
I KNOW.
BUT OURS WILL BE JUST
AS GOOD, HAROLD.
BOY, I TELL YOU, THE IDEA OF A
BUNCH OF BULLS CHASING OUR
GUYS DOWN THE MAIN STREET
HAS EVERYBODY PRETTY
REVVED UP AROUND HERE.
YOU KNOW, IT SOUNDS PRETTY
DANGEROUS TO ME.
YOU KNOW, IF ANYBODY GETS
HURT, YOUR NAME IS MUD.
HAROLD, WHEN I'M BEING CHASED BY
AN ANGRY BULL, I'LL TAKE ANY
NAME BUT GORD.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
HERE ARE A FEW CLIPS
FROM THIS EPISODE.
HAROLD TELLS ME THIS IS WHAT
THE BIG SHOWS DO NOW, YOU KNOW,
TO GET YOU TO WATCH.
KIND OF A PREVIEW, KIND OF A
TEASER KIND OF THING.
HOW DO YOU LIKE IT?
LET US KNOW.
CALL 1-800-NICE-TRY.
WELL, GOT AN HOUR TO GO UNTIL
THE TEST RUN OF THE RUNNING OF
THE BULLS.
I GUESS YOU COULD CALL THAT THE
TEST RUNNING OF THE BULLS.
UNCLE RED, HAVE YOU
THOUGHT THIS THROUGH?
HOW DO YOU MEAN?
NOTHING.
NEVER MIND.
STUPID QUESTION.
WELL, WE GOT OUR TWO BULLS, AND
THEY'RE READY TO GO.
SO ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS THROW
ON OUR RUNNING SHOES AND
START YELLING OY VEY.
I THINK YOU
MEAN OLE.
NO, THESE BULLS
ARE KOSHER.
AND, BOY, THEY'RE BIG, YOU KNOW.
AND, BOY, THEY'RE MEAN
LOOKING, HAROLD.
AND I DON'T THINK THEY'VE BEEN
ON A DATE FOR A WHILE IF YOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
AND I'M SURE YOU DO.
UNCLE RED, YOU'RE JUST GOING TO
GET SO TERRIBLY HURT.
DO YOU ACTUALLY THINK YOU CAN
OUTRUN AN ANGRY, CHARGING BULL?
I DON'T HAVE TO, HAROLD.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS OUTRUN AT
LEAST ONE LODGE MEMBER.
(APPLAUSE)
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I THINK YOU SHOULD WORRY
ABOUT OLD MAN SEDGEWICK.
OR BUSTER HATFIELD.
OH, YEAH, HE'S NO
DONOVAN BAILEY.
MORE LIKE BEETLE BAILEY.
AND FOR SURE I CAN
OUTRUN YOU.
I'M NOT PARTICIPATING.
THIS IS A POTENTIALLY
DANGEROUS EVENT.
I KNOW.
IT'S NOT AS FULFILLING AS
SITTING AT THE COMPUTER FOR SIX
HOURS ON THE INTERNET
ARGUING ABOUT WHETHER
CAPTAIN KIRK IS BETTER THAN
CAPTAIN PICKARD.
PICKARD, PICKARD,
PICKARDING.
BUT FOR THE GUYS WHO ARE
RUNNING WITH THE BULLS,
HAROLD, THIS IS A DISPLAY OF
COURAGE, MANHOOD, AND HEART.
AND HEART ATTACKS.
OH YOUR KITE GOT CAUGHT
IN A HIGH-TENSION WIRE
YOU THOUGHT YOU COULD
GET IT DOWN
SO YOU LEAN YOUR LADDER
UP AGAINST THE POLE
AND YOU HEARD A FUNNY SOUND
YOU CLIMBED AND CLIMBED,
WAY UP TO THE TOP
WHERE THE LADDER TOUCHED
THE TRANSFORMER
YOU GRABBED THE WIRE
TO FREE YOUR KITE
AND YOU NOTICED YOUR HAND
GETTING WARMER
OH, SPARKS FLEW OUT
AND AWAY YOU WENT
WITH ONE ARM NOTICEABLY
ENLARGED
NOW NORMALLY THE COPS WOULD
MAKE AN ARREST
BUT THEY COULD SEE YOU'VE
ALREADY BEEN CHARGED
GOT A REAL COMPLICATED HANDYMAN
PROJECT ON THIS WEEK'S SHOW.
AS YOU CAN SEE, THIS VEHICLE
HERE HAS HAD A LITTLE
UNSCHEDULED BODY WORK ON HER.
AND SHE'S KIND OF UNSAFE
AND UGLY RIGHT NOW,
WHICH IS A LOT MORE ACCEPTABLE
IN A PERSON THAN IT IS IN A CAR.
AND OVER HERE, IF YOU SEE,
WE HAVE ALMOST THE IDENTICAL
UNIT OVER HERE
AND DIFFERENT SIDE DONE
ON THIS ONE.
THIS IS ACTUALLY THE RESULT OF A
LITTLE TEST WE RAN UP
TO SEE IF MERCURY CREEK BRIDGE
WAS WIDE ENOUGH FOR TWO CARS.
CAN'T REALLY TALK ABOUT THAT ANY
MORE UNTIL AFTER THE INQUEST.
ANYWAY, I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
WHAT THE CREATIVE HANDYMAN DOES
WHEN HE'S GOT TWO IDENTICAL
SIDESWIPED VEHICLES.
ACTUALLY, I GOT THE IDEA
WATCHING THEM ACTION MOVIES.
I REALLY LIKE THE ACTION MOVIES
BECAUSE AT MY AGE IT'S ABOUT ALL
THE ACTION I'M GOING TO SEE.
LET ME SHOW YOU HOW
TO MAKE A HUMMER.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THE HUMMER IS?
ONE OF THOSE THINGS THEY USE,
LIKE, ON DESERT STORM.
I DON'T KNOW WHY THEY
CALL IT A HUMMER,
BUT IF YOU'VE GOT ANYTHING
THAT'S 12 FEET WIDE, IT'S A
HUMMER, BELIEVE ME.
YOU KNOW WHO HAS THEM IS THE
MILITARY AND HOLLYWOOD
CELEBRITIES.
THAT MAKES SENSE BECAUSE THOSE
ARE TWO GROUPS THAT REALLY SPEND
MONEY WISELY.
SO WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO IS
CONNECT THESE TWO CARS
TOGETHER SIDE BY SIDE.
AND, OF COURSE, FIRST THING THAT
WE'VE GOT TO DO IS GET THE
DOORS OFF OF THEM.
HALF INCH BOLT?
NO, I THINK SHE'S A 5/8TH.
KIND OF REMIND YOU OF A ROCKER,
DOESN'T IT?
THE DOORS.
THEY BROKE UP!
ALL RIGHT.
NOW ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS DRIVE
THIS CAR UP SO THE TWO CARS ARE
SIDE BY SIDE.
THERE WE GO.
NOW, YOU JUST KIND OF GOT
TO JOIN THEM TOGETHER
INTO ONE WIDE BODY,
AND, OF COURSE, JOINING THEM UP
MEANS THAT, YOU KNOW, YOU'VE
GOT TO BE WELDING
OR BETTER STILL -- OR AT LEAST
FASTER STILL, USE THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET, DUCT TAPE.
BUT DON'T SKIMP ON THE DUCT TAPE
JUST TO SAVE A BUCK OR TWO
BECAUSE AT HIGHWAY SPEEDS,
YOU'LL BE GLAD THAT YOU SPENT
THE BIG DOLLAR.
NO WONDER HUMMERS COST SO MUCH.
IT'S ALL THE DUCT TAPE!
YOU'RE PROBABLY WONDERING, HOW'S
THIS GOING TO WORK?
WELL, I'M GOING TO TELL YOU.
FIRST OF ALL, YOU START
UP THIS UNIT.
YOU LEAVE HER IN NEUTRAL.
SAVES GAS.
WHAT ABOUT STEERING YOU'RE
THINKING?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I DUCT TAPED THE FRONT
WHEELS TOGETHER.
THIS IS NOT JUST A HUMMER.
IT'S A HUMMER DINGER.
SEATS TEN, GOT TWO SEPARATE
HEATERS, TWO SEPARATE RADIOS
SO THAT YOU DON'T GET INTO THE
ARGUMENTS OVER WHICH STATIONS
YOU'RE LISTENING TO.
ANYBODY CAN HAVE A STRETCH LIMO.
WE'VE GOT A SQUAT LIMO.
I DIDN'T STRETCH THE BUDGET.
I DIDN'T PAY SQUAT!
LET'S SEE HOW SHE HANDLES.
REMEMBER, IF WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
I'LL BE BACK.
AS TO WHY RELATIONSHIPS
ARE SO DIFFICULT.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY IT'S BAD
TO GENERALIZE,
BUT IT'S SOMETHING
I REALLY ENJOY.
SO HERE'S THE THING, OKAY?
MEN ARE INTERESTED IN CARS;
WOMEN ARE INTERESTED IN
GARDENING.
YEAH.
THINK ABOUT THAT.
I MEAN, NOT ALL MEN LIKE
CARS, SOME LIKE MOTORCYCLES
AND TRUCKS.
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO ADMIT, YOU SEE
MORE MEN AT CAR SHOWS,
AND YOU SEE MORE WOMEN AT
GARDENING SHOWS, EH?
THAT'S IMPORTANT.
THAT WILL HELP YOU UNDERSTAND
WHY THEY SEE RELATIONSHIPS
DIFFERENTLY.
SEE, BECAUSE WOMEN SEE YOUR
RELATIONSHIP LIKE A GARDEN.
YOU'VE GOT TO PUT A LOT
OF WORK INTO IT.
YOU'VE GOT TO FUSS OVER IT.
YOU'VE GOT TO TURN OVER THE
GROUND, ADD MORE FLOWERS, A
LITTLE FERTILIZER;
WHEREAS MEN SEE A RELATIONSHIP
LIKE A CAR,
ONCE THEY'VE MADE A COMMITMENT
TO HAVE ONE,
THEY REALLY EXPECT IT TO GO AT
LEAST FIVE YEARS WITHOUT ANY
SERIOUS MAINTENANCE.
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
OH, YEAH!
SEE, WOMEN ENJOY WORKING
ON A RELATIONSHIP.
THEY SEE THAT AS PART
OF THE FUN.
MEN SEE THAT AS A SIGN
THAT THERE'S SOME SERIOUS
MECHANICAL PROBLEM.
AND MAYBE THAT'S WHY WHEN THERE
IS A SERIOUS PROBLEM,
WOMEN TRY TO DIG DOWN DEEPER AND
GET TO THE ROOTS;
WHEREAS, UNFORTUNATELY, A LOT OF
MEN TRY TO TRADE UP.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(APPLAUSE)
MAN, YOU TAKE A SIMPLE IDEA LIKE
A COUPLE OF BULLS CHASING PEOPLE
DOWN THE MAIN STREET,
AND YOU THINK TO YOURSELF, WHAT
COULD POSSIBLY GO WRONG?
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
YOU HAVE NO INTEREST IN
GIRLS, DO YOU, HAROLD?
I'M NOT DRESSED LIKE
THIS TO IMPRESS GIRLS.
WELL, IT'S WORKING,
BELIEVE ME.
I'M GOING TO BE OFFICIATING
THE BIG EVENT, THE RUNNING
OF THE BULLS.
NO, HAROLD, THERE WON'T BE A
RUNNING OF THE BULLS.
WE'VE HAD A FEW PROBLEMS.
WHAT KIND OF PROBLEMS?
WELL, DURING THE TEST RUN,
WE FOUND OUT THAT JUNIOR
SINGLETON'S STARTER PISTOL
IS NOT A STARTER PISTOL.
SO RIGHT AWAY WE'RE
DOWN TO ONE BULL.
A PROBLEM.
AND WE GOT HER GOING, THOUGH,
WITH THE ONE BULL,
AND IT WAS CHASING EVERYBODY
PRETTY GOOD.
AND THEN MOOSE THOMPSON
DECIDED HE WANTS TO DOUBLE
BACK FOR HIS LUCKY HAT.
HE RAN STRAIGHT INTO THE BULL?
NO, HE CUT AROUND THE
SIDE STREET THERE,
BUT HE STILL NAILED THE
BULL PRETTY GOOD.
LIKE HEAD-ON?
MORE OF A T-BONE.
ACTUALLY 40 T-BONES, A MONSTER
RUMP ROAST, AND 900 POUNDS
OF HAMBURGER.
OH, UNCLE, THAT'S AWFUL.
POOR LITTLE BIG BULL.
THAT'S AWFUL.
WELL, GOOD, THERE'S AN UPSIDE.
THERE'S AN UPSIDE.
THIS WHOLE SILLY EVENT
HAS TO BE CANCELED.
NO, NO, NO.
WE'RE NOT GOING
TO CANCEL IT.
WE'RE JUST GOING TO FIND
SOMETHING ELSE TO RUN.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE THE
RUNNING OF THE MOOSE.
I'M GOING TO GO TELL MOOSE
ABOUT IT RIGHT NOW.
HE'LL BE CONSCIOUS RIGHT NOW.
HOW CAN YOU TELL?
I'LL TELL HIM YOU
SAID THAT, HAROLD.
DON'T!
DON'T TELL HIM I SAID THAT.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THIS SHOW
WHERE WE EXAMINE THOSE THREE
LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
CROWD:  I DON'T KNOW.
EXCELLENT.
ON THIS WEEK'S PORTION OF
THE EXPERTS, WE HAVE, JOINING
MY UNCLE RED,
IS HIS BEST FRIEND IN THE WHOLE
WIDE ROOM, MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
(APPLAUSE)
HEY, THIS WEEK'S LETTER GOES
AS FOLLOWS: "DEAR EXPERTS,
"SOME PEOPLE BELIEVE IN
LIFE AFTER DEATH AND
SOME PEOPLE DON'T.
"WHO'S RIGHT?
"I'VE SEEN YOUR SHOW, AND I'M
SURE YOU GUYS MUST KNOW WHAT
HAPPENS AFTER YOU DIE."
I DON'T THINK ANYBODY IN
THEIR RIGHT MIND CAN ANSWER
THAT QUESTION.
I CAN.
YOU DIED, MR. SHAUGHNESSY?
WHEN DID THAT HAPPEN?
AT THE SEOUL OLYMPICS
IN '88.
I RAN THE MARATHON REPRESENTING
THE NATION OF SIERRA LEONE.
DURING THE MARATHON, I DIED
OF A HEART ATTACK AT THE
52-MILE MARK.
MARATHONS ARE ONLY
26 MILES.
NO ONE TOLD ME THAT.
I THOUGHT YOU HAD TO
RUN THERE AND BACK!
SO JUST AS I REACH WHAT I
THOUGHT WAS THE FINISH LINE,
WHICH TURNED OUT TO BE THE
STARTING LINE AGAIN,
I COLLAPSED OF A HEART
ATTACK AND I DIED.
WELL, I SAY WE HAVE A FUNERAL
IMMEDIATELY.
ANYWAY, MY SPIRIT OR MY SOUL
OR WHATEVER YOU WANT TO
CALL IT WAS FLOATING.
I COULD SEE I WAS LYING THERE.
OH, EVERYBODY CAN SEE YOU'RE
LYING THERE.
I REMEMBER A BEAUTIFUL
WOMAN, AND I WAS WORKING
ON SOME POTTERY.
AND I REMEMBER A DOOR AND A
PENNY SLIDING ON THE DOOR.
AND THAT'S ALL I REMEMBER ABOUT
THE AFTERLIFE.
THEN A DOCTOR REVIVED ME, AND I
WAS BACK ON EARTH IN KOREA.
I WAS SO EXCITED I TREATED
EVERYONE TO A BANQUET OF DOG.
THAT'S A KOREAN DELICACY.
TASTES A LOT LIKE WOLF.
JUST COMING BACK A LITTLE BIT TO
YOUR MEMORIES OF THE AFTERLIFE,
YOU KNOW THAT PRETTY
WOMAN WITH THE POTTERY?
OH, YEAH.
AND THEN THERE'S THAT BIT ABOUT
THE PENNY AND THE DOOR?
YEP.
THOSE ARE BOTH SCENES OUT
OF THE MOVIE "GHOST."
I WAS A TECHNICAL ADVISOR ON
THAT MOVIE
BECAUSE THEY WANTED IT --
BECAUSE THEY WANTED IT TO
BE ACCURATE.
SO IN ANSWER TO THIS LETTER, I
WOULD SAY,
YES, THERE IS AN AFTERLIFE
WAITING FOR US AND IT'S FULL!
YEAH, UNFORTUNATELY, THE
AFTERLIFE IS FULL OF THE
SAME STUFF THIS ONE IS.
A LITTLE CAMPING TRIP ON THIS
WEEK'S ADVENTURE WITH BILL.
HOW YOU DOING THERE, BILL?
OH, YOU'RE FINE.
YEAH, WE LIKE TO GET OUT IN THE
OUTDOORS, GET A LITTLE
EXERCISE.
IT'S GOOD FOR YOU.
I ENJOY THE BACKPACKING MYSELF.
ANYWAY, BILL KIND OF PICKED
OUT A SPOT THERE.
AND KIND OF THOUGHT I'D THIN
OUT THE FOREST A LITTLE BIT.
DIDN'T REALIZE, UNFORTUNATELY,
THAT I PUT THAT TREE RIGHT
BETWEEN BILL'S LEGS.
DOESN'T HAPPEN ALL THAT OFTEN
UP AT THE LODGE.
OKAY, BACK UP.
I'LL BACK HER UP.
AHHHH!
OH!
OH, HE'S FINE.
YOU KNOW, CAMPING IS A VERY
PERSONAL THING.
AND YOU CAN KNOW A LOT ABOUT
A PERSON BY WHAT THEY CARRY
IN THE BACKPACK.
I KIND OF GO LIGHT AND BILL --
WELL, HE GOES CABLE.
ANYWAY, WE GOT ALL OF OUR
STUFF OUT THERE.
AND IT'S TIME TO ROLL
OUT THE BEDROLLS.
BILL, YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO HANG
ON TO THE ONE END.
THERE YOU GO.
GO GET IT.
GO GET IT!
THERE YOU GO.
A LITTLE MORE SPEED
GOING THERE, BILL.
LOOK OUT!
THERE WE GO.
HE'S PROBABLY TIRED NOW.
WHAT THE HECK'S THIS?
THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
OH!
HMM.
LATER THAT DAY, BILL GOT INTO
BED, EVERYTHING FINE.
OH, OH, OH.
ANYWAY, WE GOT OURSELVES
ALL SETTLED IN.
LOT OF MOSQUITOES, SO BILL KIND
OF ZIPPED HIMSELF UP THERE
LIKE A SAUSAGE ROLL,
AND HE -- YOU KNOW, HE
HAD GOTTEN IN THERE A
LITTLE TOO QUICK.
AND HE FORGOTTEN TO PUT DOWN
ONE OF THE KEY COMPONENTS
IN ANY CAMPING TRIP,
A GROUNDSHEET, RIGHT, BILL?
A LITTLE SOGGY IS IT, BILL?
AND NOT FROM THE INSIDE
THIS TIME.
NOPE.
THIS IS STARTING TO --
BILL, YOU DIDN'T PUT
DOWN YOUR GROUNDSHEET.
COME ON, PUT THAT DOWN.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
SO HE DOESN'T WANT TO GET OUT
OF THE SLEEPING BAG THERE
BECAUSE OF THE MOSQUITOES
AND DECIDES HE CAN
JUST DO IT--
LOOKS LIKE ONE OF THOSE
CATERPILLARS IN THE COCOONS.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE THE
BUTTERFLY THAT COMES OUT
OF THAT ONE, I TELL YOU.
YEAH, THERE YOU GO, BILL.
AND, BILL, IF YOU NEED ANY
HELP, I'M HERE FOR YOU, BUDDY.
THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M HERE FOR YOU.
YEAH, WELL, IN MY WAY.
YOU KNOW.
THERE HE'S ALL SET.
JUMP INTO BED, BILL.
AWAY YOU GO.
GOOD NIGHT!
OH, YOU'RE FINE.
OKAY. OKAY.
SO THEY HAD THEIR TEST RUNNING
OF THE BULLS, RIGHT?
NOW, YOU'VE GOT THIS GUY
NAMED MOOSE, AND FOR
GOOD REASON, OKAY?
AND HE'S CHASING ALL THE
MEN RIGHT DOWN THE CENTRE
OF TOWN, RIGHT?
OKAY, THAT'S ALL YOU REALLY NEED
TO KNOW.
UNCLE RED, COME IN HERE.
COME ON IN HERE, UNCLE RED.
TELL THEM WHAT HAPPENED.
MOOSE DOES NOT
CORNER WELL.
THAT'S TRUE BECAUSE THEY WERE
CHUGGING ALONG PRETTY WELL
ON THE STRAIGHTAWAY.
AND THEN WE HIT THE SHARP CURVE
IN THE MIDDLE OF TOWN THERE.
RIGHT IN FRONT OF
THE YOGURT STAND.
ALL THE WAY HOME I WAS AFRAID
SOME HEALTH NUT WAS GOING TO
START LICKING ME.
WELL, THE GOOD NEWS IS,
YOU KNOW, THAT THIS CRAZY
EVENT OF YOURS
IS MERCIFULLY A LOST CAUSE.
OH, NO. NO, IT'S NOT
OVER UNTIL I QUIT.
AND I'M NOT QUITTING.
WE'RE GOING TO DO THE WHOLE
RUNNING THING AGAIN,
ONLY THIS TIME WE'RE
GOING TO USE A LION.
A LION?
A LION!
A LION, LIKE A 10-FOOT
RAZOR-FANG MAN-EATING LION?
WELL, SORT OF.
WE'LL USE THE LION FROM
FLINTY MCCLINTOCK'S AFRICAN
LION SAFARI.
FLINTY'S LION?
YES.
THAT'S A MANGY OLD ARTHRITIC,
DYSPEPTIC, SENILE, TOOTHLESS,
HALF-BLIND LION.
THAT THING IS -- ACTUALLY, I
HEARD IT WAS A DEFORMED PIG.
THAT'S WHAT I HEARD.
YOU'LL HAVE TO PUT IT ON A
SKATEBOARD AND WHEEL IT
THROUGH DOWNTOWN.
FLINTY'S NOT GOING TO
LEND IT TO YOU ANYWAY.
HE GIVES YOU THAT LION,
HIS WHOLE LION SAFARI WILL BE A
WHOLE BUNCH OF SNOW FENCES
HOLDING BACK CHICKENS.
HOW ABOUT THAT MINK RANCH
OUTSIDE OF TOWN?
OH, YEAH, THAT PLACE WITH THE
LITTLE WEE CORRALS.
HEY, WE'LL HAVE THE
RUNNING OF THE MINKS.
DOES THAT SAY CLASS TO YOU?
OH, YEAH!
THIRD!
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW
THAT WE CALL "IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
DALTON HUMPHREYS BROUGHT
SOMETHING IN FOR US TO FIX.
WHAT DID YOU BRING
US THERE, DALTON?
WELL, YOU KNOW, RED, I WAS
HOPING THAT YOU COULD FIX MY
TENNIS RACKET HERE.
JUST GOT THAT LAST WEEK.
JOHN MCENROE HAVE A
GARAGE SALE, DID HE?
NO, NO, THAT'S BRAND NEW, RED.
CAN YOU FIX IT?
BOY, I DON'T KNOW, DALTON.
YOU SEE, THIS IS A TITANIUM
GRAPHITE, AND THOSE STRINGS ARE
MADE FROM SNOW LEOPARD GUT.
YOU KNOW, IT ALMOST LOOKS
LIKE IT WAS BENT AROUND THE
POST OR SOMETHING.
NO, MY WIFE DID THAT.
DID IT RIGHT AROUND HER KNEE.
WOW.
ANN-MARIE IS A SMALLISH
WOMAN, BUT, BOY, WHEN THOSE
HORMONES KICK IN,
SHE'S JUST GOT A POWER TO HER.
SO DID SHE BREAK THE
STRINGS TOO?
NO, NO, WE DID
THAT TOGETHER.
YEAH.
MAY I?
YEAH, SURE.
IT WAS THIS KIND OF
LOOK, YOU SEE?
SHE JUST HAD AN IMPRESSIVE
OVERHEAD SMASH.
SHE JUST REALLY GOT ALL OF IT.
YEAH.
ARE YOU HAVING PROBLEMS
AT HOME OF ANY KIND?
OH, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
OH, NOTHING SERIOUS, RED.
YOU KNOW, WE RECENTLY HAD OUR
20TH WEDDING ANNIVERSARY.
ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, YEAH.
WHICH I FORGOT.
TRIED TO PASS OFF THIS TENNIS
RACKET AS AN ANNIVERSARY GIFT
AND -- APPARENTLY ANN-MARIE
ISN'T A BIG TENNIS FAN.
WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD, DALTON.
BUT CONGRATULATIONS ON
THE 20TH ANNIVERSARY.
THAT'S SILVER, ISN'T IT?
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
IT IS, BUT I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT IT'S NOT.
IT'S NOT TITANIUM GRAPHITE.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
WELL, THE RUNNING OF THE MINK
WAS NOT AN UNQUALIFIED SUCCESS.
DOZENS OF CASUALTIES!
IT WAS LIKE GUYS WERE TRAMPLED
AND STOMPED AND BITTEN.
ONE WOMAN PULLED A MUSCLE
LAUGHING SO HARD.
YEAH, HAROLD, WHAT I
COULDN'T FIGURE OUT
WAS HOW COME THE MINKS ALL
WENT UP INSIDE OF JUNIOR'S
PANTS LIKE THAT?
IT'S BECAUSE HE KEEPS FOOD IN
HIS POCKETS ALL THE TIME.
THOSE MINKS JUST WIZZED
RIGHT UP THERE.
SO DID JUNIOR.
BOY, OH, BOY, HE WENT
CRAZY, DIDN'T HE?
IT BECAME THE RUNNING
OF THE JUNIOR.
HE WAS KNOCKING THINGS OVER.
HE WAS SMASHING INTO PEOPLE
AND TRAMPLING OVER THEM.
BOY, OH, BOY, I HAD NO IDEA
JUNIOR COULD MOVE SO FAST.
WELL, HAROLD, YOU KNOW, YOU GET
A DOZEN MINK IN YOUR SHORTS,
AND YOU GET THE
ADRENALINE MOVING.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I THINK PEOPLE
GOT THEIR MONEY'S WORTH ON THAT.
YEAH, TICKETS WERE FREE,
SO I THINK SO TOO.
MINK!
IT'S THE MEETING.
JUST THE MEETING.
YEAH, WELL, I WAS JUST DOING
THAT IN CASE --
FOR YOUR OWN SAKE,
I'M GOING DOWNSTAIRS.
ALL RIGHT.
I WANT TO GET THE MINK LAUGHING.
OKAY.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND YOU KNOW YOU ALWAYS SAY YOU
WANT TO HAVE THE EXPERIENCE OF
THE FEEL OF REAL MINK?
YOU MAY WANT TO CHECK WITH
JUNIOR ON THAT.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
COMMUNICAPTION CANADA, INC.]
YOU'VE GOT TO SIT DOWN BECAUSE
HE GETS REALLY GRUMPY IF
YOU'RE STANDING.
GET THEM UP, HAROLD.
OKAY.
ALL RISE.
I'VE GOT THE FIRST ANNOUNCEMENT.
IT'S -- OH, LOOK HERE'S A
COMPUTER FOR SALE.
22 MEGABYTES WITH 25 GIGABYTE
HARD DRIVE, LOTS OF BYTES,
BIG OUTPUT,
COMPATIBLE WITH MOST MALE TO
MALE, FEMALE --
I'M SORRY, THIS IS A PERSONAL
AD.
I'M SORRY.
THAT -- I'M SORRY.