[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN
IN TODAY'S SHOW
HAROLD FORMS A BAND,
BILL SHOWS HOW TO
MAKE A CAMP BED,
AND I'M GOING TO
COOK WITH ELECTRICITY.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
>>HAROLD: AND NOW HERE'S
THE GREATEST THING TO HIT
THE TELEVISION INDUSTRY
SINCE COLOURIZATION,
THE MAN EVERYONE IS TALKING
ABOUT AND OFTENTIMES
IN COMPLIMENTARY TERMS,
THE STAR OF OUR SHOW
MR. RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
THANKS FOR TUNING US IN
I'M YOUR HOST RED GREEN
FOR THE NEXT HALF HOUR
I'LL NOT ONLY BE YOUR HOST
BUT I'LL ALSO BE YOUR
GUIDE AND YOUR TRANSLATOR
AND UP AT THE LODGE
THIS IS WHAT WE CALL A HAROLD.
AND THAT TRANSLATES AS
I'M DIRECTING THIS SHOW
BECAUSE THE STAR IS MY UNCLE.
>>HAROLD: THANK YOU.
>>RED: IT'S BEEN KIND OF
A CHALLENGING WEEK UP HERE
AT THE LODGE I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO GET A FUNDRAISER GOING
FOR A PET PROJECT OF MINE
WHICH IS NAMELY KEEPING
THE REPO MAN OFF OUR BACKS.
SO I THOUGHT I'D HAVE A
SUGGESTION BOX AND THE FIRST
SUGGESTION I GOT WAS WHY DON'T
YOU MAKE THE SUGGESTION BOX
A DONATION BOX INSTEAD.
WELL THAT TURNED OUT TO BE
PRETTY STUPID BECAUSE WHAT THEY
DID WAS THEY STARTED DONATING
SUGGESTIONS OKAY
AND THE MOST OF THEM
YOU COULD NEVER READ ON ANY
TELEVISION ANYWHERE BUT THEN
THERE WAS ONE IN THERE STRUCK
ME AS A REAL GOOD IDEA.
>>HAROLD: HEY YOU'RE
WEARING A NEW SHIRT!
>>RED: NO THAT WASN'T IT,
IT WAS SOMEBODY SUGGESTED
WE HAVE A LAS VEGAS
STYLE CASINO...
>>HAROLD: WHAT ARE YOU
WEARING A NEW SHIRT FOR?
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH
THE REGULAR YOU KNOW
RED SHIRT WHAT?
>>RED: WELL IT'S DIRTY HAROLD.
ANYWAY THIS CASINO NIGHT SEEMED
LIKE I THOUGHT MAYBE THIS
COULD REALLY...
>>HAROLD: WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH THE REGULAR SHIRT?
I MEAN WHERE'S THE OTHER SHIRT?
YOU KNOW IT'S A REGULAR SHIRT
THAT YOU WEAR NOW, NO,
WHERE IS IT, WHAT?
>>RED: WELL IT'S IN
THE LAUNDRY HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH RIGHT
OH YOU GOT A RAISE!
YOU GOT A RAISE!
OH YEAH, SINCE WHEN IS
THERE EXTRA MONEY IN
THE SHOW'S BUDGET?
>>RED: THERE ISN'T HAROLD
THERE'S EXTRA RELISH ON
MY SHIRT, THAT'S WHY
IT'S IN THE LAUNDRY.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH! OH YEAH!
OKAY YES, I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO DO BY
WEARING THIS FANCY SHMANCY
SHIRT OF YOURS, YOU'RE JUST
TRYING TO ADD ZIP TO THE SHOW
BECAUSE YOU THINK MY DIRECTION
IS SO BAD THAT'S IT, ISN'T IT?
ISN'T IT?
>>RED: NO BUT I LIKE THE SOUND
OF THAT SO THE CASINO NIGHT
IS A DEFINITE GO WE'RE GOING
TO GET EVERYTHING ORGANIZED.
>>HAROLD: I'M JUST GOING
TO LET YOU KNOW THAT I DON'T
NEED ANY OF YOUR CHEAP GIMMICKS
I HAVE EXPENSIVE GIMMICKS.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
THAT'S A LOT OF GOLF BALLS
TO PUT IN YOUR MOUTH
THEY MAKE YOU SPECIAL
AND THE ENVY OF YOUR FRIENDS
BUT THE MAIN LESSON HERE
IS DON'T FALL ASLEEP
AT THE DRIVING RANGE
>>RED: TAKE IT!
>>HAROLD: OW! OW!
>>RED: GET THAT AWAY
FROM THERE!
THIS WEEK ON 'HANDYMAN CORNER'
GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW TO
MAKE A LOW COST,
EXTREMELY EFFICIENT,
LIGHTWEIGHT, ENTIRELY PORTABLE
ELECTRIC BARBECUE
WELL AT LEAST PORTABLE IN
THE SENSE THAT YOU CAN GO
ANYWHERE THAT THEY
HAVE ELECTRICITY...
I GOT THE IDEA FROM ONE
OF THESE LITTLE UNITS
YOU EVER SEEN THESE BABIES?
THIS IS A HOT DOG COOKER
YOU GOT LIKE A NAIL CONNECTED
TO THE WIRE YOU PUT ONE END
IN EACH END OF THE WEENIE,
AND YOU PLUG HER INTO THE WALL
BY THE TIME BOB'S YOUR UNCLE
YOU GOT YOUR WIENER BURNT
BLACK AND SILVER.
AND I'M THINKING TO MYSELF
THIS COULD WORK ON ALMOST
ANYTHING BECAUSE THE POINT
IS ELECTRICITY CAN COOK MEAT
WHICH ANY OF YOU KNOW WHO HAVE
EVER STUCK YOUR FINGER
IN A WALL SOCKET.
I'M THINKING YOU KNOW
LET'S MAKE IT A LITTLE BIGGER
THAN THAT WHY CAN'T WE GET
ELECTRICITY TO SAY COOK
A ROAST OR NOT QUITE SURE
WHAT THAT IS PROBABLY A RACCOON
I GUESS AND ALL WE'D NEED MAYBE
IS TO JUST GET A LITTLE MORE
POP TO THE ELECTRICITY
NOT JUST USE YOUR STANDARD
HOUSEHOLD CURRENT BUT MAYBE
HAVE A STEP UP TRANSFORMER
AND TAKE 'ER UP FROM
120 VOLTS UP TO WELL
HOW DOES A MILLION SOUND?
AND A TRANSFORMER IS REAL
EASY TO BUILD, IT'S BASICALLY
JUST 2 COILS OF WIRE.
SO YOU TAKE A COIL OF
YOUR NORMAL 14 DASH 2 HOUSEHOLD
WIRE AS WE EXPLAINED TO YOU
IN ONE OF OUR OTHER EPISODES
AND YOU DROP A SMALLER COIL
OF WIRE INSIDE WHICH YOU
CAN GET OUT OF SAY AN OLD
ELECTRIC RAZOR, SOMETHING OF
THAT NATURE AND THESE ARE DARN
EASY TO COME BY ESPECIALLY
WHILE THE GUYS ARE OUT FISHING.
SO I JUST POP THE TOP
OFF THIS UNIT.
ALL RIGHT NOW THIS IS A GOOD
SAFETY TIP, WHENEVER YOU'RE
WORKING WITH A SCREWDRIVER
SEE THE WAY I DID THAT?
DON'T EVER PUT THE
SCREW DRIVER TOWARDS YOU.
I HOPE YOU WERE NOTICING THAT
ESPECIALLY YOU YOUNG KIDS
OUT THERE ALWAYS HAVE
THE SCREWDRIVER WORKING
AWAY FROM YOU.
I'LL JUST POP THE TOP
OFF THIS THING.
(GRUNTING)
(SIZZLE OF ELECTRICITY)
ALL RIGHT WELL I HAD
TO REPLACE THE FUSE THERE
ACTUALLY IT WAS JUST A PENNY
AND IT HAD MELTED RIGHT OUT
OF THERE SO I REPLACED IT
WITH A NICKEL, SHOULD LAST
5 TIMES AS LONG.
BUT THE GOOD NEWS IS THAT THE
WHOLE COVERING OF THE RAZOR
MELTED RIGHT OFF SO NOW
I CAN JUST LOWER THAT RIGHT
INSIDE MY OUTER COIL AND WHEN
I PLUG THIS END IN WE'RE GOING
TO GET THE MILLION VOLTS
COMING RIGHT OUT HERE.
NOW WHAT I HAVE TO DO IS USE
SOMETHING AS AN ELECTRODE
FOR THE THING SOMETHING
WHAT DO YOU CALL 'EM?
YEAH ELECTRODE
YEAH I'M THINKING,
I'M THINKING A GOLF CLUB
JUST KIND OF BREAK THIS IN
HALF HERE I WOULD SAY GO WITH
THE STEEL GOLF CLUB RATHER THAN
THE WOOD KIND BECAUSE THE
WOOD DOESN'T REALLY CONDUCT
ELECTRICITY ALL THAT WELL
ALTHOUGH IF YOU COULD GET
'ER GOING MAYBE IF YOU GOT LIKE
17 BZILLION GUH-GILLION VOLTS
IT'D GIVE YOU A NICE HICKORY
SMOKE FLAVOUR.
ACTUALLY PROBABLY A BUNCH
OF YOU GOLFERS WHO GET OVER
A 100 ALL THE TIME HAVE
A WHOLE SET THAT
LOOKS LIKE THIS.
NOW WHAT WE DO IS WE'RE GOING
TO STICK AN END OF THIS IN EACH
END OF OUR MEAT SO TO SPEAK AND
WRAP OUR WIRES AROUND THERE
AND SEAL 'ER ALL UP WITH THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE AND WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE OURSELVES A
LITTLE BEEF ROAST.
SO I'LL WORK ON THAT,
GET THAT ALL HOOKED UP THERE
AND YOU WATCH THE REST OF
THE SHOW AND WHEN I'M ALL
READY I'LL HAVE YOU COME
BACK AND WE'LL PUT THIS
RIG INTO ACTION.
>>HAROLD: THIS IS MY FAVOURITE
PART OF THE SHOW BECAUSE WE GET
TO EXPOSE THOSE 3 LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO DIFFICULT
TO SAY 'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT
ONCE AGAIN ON THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW IS MY UNCLE RED AND
HIS BEST FRIEND IN THE
WHOLE WORLD, MR. BOB STUYVESTANT
AND MR. GLEN BRAXTON.
>>HAROLD: HERE WE ARE,
'DEAR EXPERTS FOR OUR
25TH WEDDING ANNIVERSARY,
OUR SILVER ANNIVERSARY
I BOUGHT MY WIFE A BRAND NEW
SHINY SILVER SOCKET WRENCH SET
MY WIFE BURST INTO TEARS
AT FIRST I THOUGHT THEY WERE
TEARS OF JOY BUT SINCE I'VE
BEEN SLEEPING ON THE PORCH
FOR 2 WEEKS NOW I FIGURE SHE
DIDN'T LIKE THE SOCKET WRENCH.
WOMEN SAY THEY WANT TO BE
TREATED EQUALLY WITH MEN AND
I'D LOVE A SET LIKE THAT
SO WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT DO WOMEN REALLY WANT?'
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
>>GLEN: WHAT DO WOMEN WANT?
>>RED: WELL GLEN YOU'RE
MARRIED WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>>GLEN: WELL YOU'RE
MARRIED TOO RED.
>>RED: YEAH THAT'S RIGHT
YEAH BUT YOU'VE GOT ALL
THOSE DAUGHTERS,
7 DAUGHTERS THOUGH
I MEAN YOU KNOW A LOT
MORE ABOUT WOMEN THAN I DO.
>>GLEN: WELL A LOT OF THEM
ARE STILL PRETTY YOUNG THEY'RE
GIRLS SO WELL BOB YOU'VE
BEEN MARRIED 6 TIMES RIGHT?
>>BOB: 4.
>>RED: 5 BOB.
>>BOB: OH YEAH 5 RIGHT YEAH
FORE IS WHAT YOU SAY WHEN
YOU'RE PLAYING GOLF.
ACTUALLY DO YOU KNOW WHERE
YELLING FORE ORIGINATED FROM?
>>RED & GLEN: NO.
>>BOB: WELL IT'S SCOTTISH
YOU KNOW THEY USED TO
DO A LOT OF...
>>HAROLD: 'SCUSE ME YOU'RE
JUST GETTING A LITTLE OFF TOPIC
THERE YOU KNOW THE QUESTION IS
WHAT DO WOMEN REALLY WANT.
>>ALL: OH YEAH OKAY.
>>BOB: WHAT DO WOMEN WANT?
>>GLEN: WHAT DO WOMEN WANT?
>>RED: BOY.
>>GLEN: WELL ACTUALLY IN
REFERENCE TO THE GUY'S LETTER
THERE I BROKE A SOCKET WRENCH
JUST LAST WEEK.
>>RED: YOU'RE KIDDING.
>>GLEN: NO, NO.
>>RED: HOW'D THAT HAPPEN?
>>GLEN: WELL I WAS TAKING
THE REAR SUSPENSION OFF THIS
OLD BUS I BOUGHT TO TURN IT
INTO AN R.V. AND THE TORQUE
BANG, SNAPPED IT RIGHT IN HALF.
>>RED: OH MY GOD, WOW!
>>HAROLD: WHAT DO WOMEN
REALLY WANT?
>>RED: OH YEAH, YEAH.
>>GLEN: WOMEN.
>>BOB: WOMEN QUESTION.
>>RED: WHAT ABOUT WORLD PEACE?
>>BOB: OH YEAH,
I WOULD THINK SO YEAH.
>>GLEN: WORLD PEACE
IS GOOD, SURE.
>>BOB: POLITICAL THING
OH YEAH, WORLD PEACE.
>>HAROLD: SURVEY
SAYS, WORLD PEACE?
>>RED: YUP.
>>BOB: YOU KNOW ACTUALLY
I KNEW A GUY WHO BROKE
A SOCKET WRENCH ONCE TOO.
>>GLEN: GET OUT!
>>BOB: YEAH HE WAS WORKING ON
A SNOWMOBILE I DON'T THINK HE'D
EVER ACTUALLY TAKEN ONE APART.
>>GLEN: SMALL WORLD.
>>HAROLD: (YELLING) WHAT DO
WOMEN REALLY WANT!
THEY WANT SOMETHING
THOSE WOMEN, WHAT IS IT?
>>RED: OKAY WE GOT WORLD PEACE.
>>GLEN: WELL YOU KNOW ACTUALLY
AS A HUSBAND AND A FATHER OF
7 DAUGHTERS AS YOU SAID I KNOW
AROUND OUR HOUSE WHAT THE WOMEN
WANT AT MY HOUSE IS A NEW V.C.R.
>>RED: OH YEAH, OH YOU'RE
ONTO SOMETHING THERE.
>>GLEN: YEAH OURS JAMMED UP.
>>RED: MY WIFE WOULD LOVE
A NEW V.C.R. YUP, YUP.
>>BOB: WELL IT'S A FUNNY THING
THAT YOU MENTION THAT BECAUSE
MY LAST WIFE SHE HAD CUSTODY
OF THE TV AND THE V.C.R.
>>GLEN: COOL THAT'S
SOMETHING THERE.
>>RED: WE GOT IT.
>>GLEN: THAT'S SOMETHING
THERE YES SIR!
>>RED: WOMEN WANT A NEW V.C.R.
>>BOB: AND WORLD PEACE.
>>RED: RIGHT.
>>GLEN: AND NO SOCKET WRENCHES.
>>RED: THAT'S IT.
>>RED: IT IS AUTUMN
TREES SHED GREENERY
AND STAND BARREN
NERVOUS ANIMALS SCURRY ABOUT
GLANCING SKYWARD.
WARM WATERS TURN
COLD AS BLUE STEEL
MEANWHILE THE ROCKS
SIT SILENT, SOLID.
ROCKS ARE EXACTLY LIKE
MY UNCLE ROY IF THEY
HAD GAS IN THEM.
>>RED: NOW I GOT HER ALL HOOKED
UP AND READY TO RIP THERE
BLACK WIRE BRINGS ELECTRICITY IN
YOUR WHITE WIRE TAKES
THE ELECTRICITY OUT
AND I'VE GOT THE GROUND
WIRE HOOKED UP TO THE
MEAT THERMOMETER.
NOW I RAN THE EXTENSION CORD
UP FROM THE BOATHOUSE USING
WHATEVER PIECES OF WIRE
I COULD FIND BECAUSE IT'S ON
A SEPARATE CIRCUIT DOWN THERE
AND I UPGRADED FROM A NICKEL
IN THE FUSE RIGHT UP TO
A QUARTER SO I THINK WE'RE
READY TO POWER UP AND
EAT LIKE A MAN.
(ELECTRICITY BUZZING)
(LOUD EXPLODtion)
>>RED: WOW!
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL BE
HAVING CHIPPED BEEF
NOT BAD, LITTLE UNDER DONE
SHOULD HAVE USED A 6 IRON.
ANYWAY IF WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
WELL BY GOLLY THIS CASINO NIGHT
FEELS LIKE IT'S GOING TO RAKE
IN A LOT OF COIN FOR US.
EVERYBODY IS PITCHING IN
TO MAKE IT FEEL LIKE
A REAL LAS VEGAS STYLE THING
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK SAYS WE
SHOULD HAVE AN AERIAL CIRCUS
LIKE THEY DO AT THAT
CIRCUS CIRCUS CASINO
SO HE AND MOOSE THOMPSON
ARE GOING TO SIT UP IN
THE RAFTERS AND PLAY FRISBEE.
>>HAROLD: I SEE YOU'RE WEARING
YOUR NEW SHIRT THERE HUH?
>>RED: YEAH I'M WEARING
MY NEW SHIRT HAROLD
WOULD YOU RATHER BE LOOKING
AT RELISH STAINS?
THAT WOULD JUST REMIND
YOU OF YOUR COMPLEXION.
>>HAROLD: HAW HAW HAW HAW!
SO WHAT YOU'RE REALLY SAYING
THEN IS IF HAROLD WAS A BETTER
PRODUCER WE WOULDN'T HAVE
THIS WARDROBE PROBLEM
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING ISN'T IT?
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
>>HAROLD: OH I KNOW OH OKAY
ALL RIGHT THIS IS MIDLIFE CRISIS
ISN'T IT?
OKAY OH.
>>RED: I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
ANYMORE ABOUT MY SHIRT
OKAY HAROLD.
NOW WHERE WAS I?
I FORGET OH OKAY, OKAY
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE OUR CASINO
NIGHT DOWN IN THE BASEMENT
AND THE ONLY THING THAT'S
MISSING REALLY IS LAS VEGAS
SHOWGIRL TYPE THING
BUT JUNIOR SAYS HE'S GOT SOME
WATER BALLOONS LEFT OVER FROM...
>>HAROLD: 'SCUSE ME UNCLE RED
JUST ONE MORE THING THOUGHT
YOU KNOW JUST THE ONE.
>>RED: IS THIS ABOUT
MY SHIRT HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: NO, NO, NO,
IT'S IS ABOUT WELL
MEN'S WEAR IN GENERAL.
>>RED: WELL THE NEXT PERSON
THAT MENTIONS ANYTHING ABOUT
MY SHIRT IS GOING TO GET A REAL
CLOSE LOOK AT MY FOOTWEAR.
>>RED: AS I WAS SAYING THE
CASINO NIGHT IS FIRING ALONG
WE'LL BE DOWN IN THE BASEMENT
AND YOURS TRULY IS GOING TO BE
THE MAITRE D AND THE PIT BOSS.
>>HAROLD: OH THAT'S
A GREAT IDEA.
OH UNCLE RED THAT'S
SUCH A GOOD IDEA!
ISN'T THAT A GOOD IDEA
OH BOY ABOUT THIS MAITRE'D
WHAT KIND OF SHIRT ARE
YOU GOING TO BE WEARING?
>>RED: A PINK LOW CUT DRESS
WITH A FEATHER BOA
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT?
>>HAROLD: I KNEW IT,
MIDLIFE CRISIS I KNEW, I KNEW.
I'VE SEEN A
MILLION WONDERS
THROUGHOUT THIS PRETTY
WELL UNEVENTFUL LIFE
BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN NOTHING
THAT COMES CLOSE
OR EVEN REMOTELY COMPARES
IN ANY SHAPE OR FORM
TO THE STORM
WE HAD LAST WEEK
OH THE WIND COME DOWN
LIKE THUNDER
THE THUNDER COME DOWN
LIKE WIND THE RAIN COME DOWN
LIKE CHESTNUTS
AND THE CHESTNUTS COME DOWN
LIKE SQUIRRELS
OH THE HAILSTONES
RIPPED THE ROOF OFF
AND THE BARN ROLLED DOWN
THE HILL AND THAT'S
WHEN THE SHEEP HIT THE FAN
'CAUSE LIGHTNING HIT THE SILO
AND THE ENTIRE TOWN
WAS COVERED WITH POPCORN
>>RED: WELL THIS WEEK ON
'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'
I WAS MAKING SOME OF MY FAMOUS
FOREST STEW WHICH I MAKE OUT
OF THINGS I FIND ON MY SHOE
THERE'S BILL OH OH OH OH OH
OH IT'S HOT, IT'S HOT!
IT'S WET BUT IT'S HOT
THANKS BILL.
THANKS FOR COMING OUT
ANYWAY WHAT BILL WANTED TO
DO IS SHOW US ALL HOW
TO MAKE A CAMP BED
YOU KNOW WHEN YOU DON'T
HAVE A TENT OR ANY OF
THE NICETIES AND AN AIR MATTRESS
I'M GOING TO GET MYSELF
DRIED OFF.
>>GUY: HEY!
>>RED: OH SOME OF THE CREW
I GUESS THERE OR ANOTHER CAMERA
ANYWAY BILL OH, OH, OH WELL
THE FIRST THING YOU DO IS YOU
GET SOME LITTLE PIECES OF BRUSH
AND SO ON YOU WANT TO KIND
OF MAKE IT SOMETHING A LITTLE
SOFTER THAN, WHAT IS THAT?
APPARENTLY BILL KEEPS HIS
GROUND SHEET IN HIS COVERALLS
WELL I DON'T EVEN WANT TO THINK
ABOUT THIS BUT WE HAD TO GET
IT UNROLLED WE GET THAT
SPREAD OUT, BOY OH BOY
ANYWAY YOU GET THAT SPREAD OUT
OVER THE BITS OF BRUSH AND
EVERYTHING KEEP THE LEAVES
AWAY FROM YOU.
THE NEXT UNIT YOU NEED THERE
WAS THE SLEEPING BAG
THE COVER YOU JUST THROW OH!
OH BOY!
OH WELL SO BILL'S GOING
TO UNROLL HIS SLEEPING BAG
BUT THIS THING HAD BEEN
ROLLED UP SO LONG SHE HAD
A LOT OF TENSION BUILT UP
THAT'S VERY STRANGE ISN'T IT?
WELL IT TURNS OUT IT WASN'T
JUST THE TENSION THERE WAS
SOMETHING IT WAS YEAH,
IT WAS A ROCK YEAH THERE WAS
A ROCK INSIDE THE BAG
WE DON'T NEED THAT NEAR OUR BED
SO BILL UNFORTUNATELY RIGHT
OVER WHERE HE HAD AND THEN
OH, OH, OH, OH AND AGAIN WELL
BILL ALWAYS CLAIMS A SLEEPING
BAG IS KIND OF COLD WHEN
YOU FIRST GET INTO IT BUT
THIS ONE APPARENTLY WAS REAL
WARM AND BILL WAS REAL COMFY
THERE AND (SNIFFING)
KIND OF A FUNNY SMELL
OH WELL THERE'S ALWAYS
A GOOD SIDE OF EVERYTHING
NOW AT LEAST I'LL BE ABLE
TO FINISH MAKING MY STEW.
(BILL COUGHING AND HACKING)
>>RED: AND NOW HERE'S SOMETHING
THE YOUNG PEOPLE MIGHT LIKE
'CAUSE I KNOW THE OLDER
FOLKS CAN'T STAND IT.
>>HAROLD: AWESOME!
YOUNG VIEWERS AND WELCOME
TO MY BRAND NEW SHOW
STRUMS GUITAR
GIGGING TO THE MAX!
NOT JIGGING TO THE MAST
WHO PUT THAT THERE?
IT'S NOT A SHOW ABOUT DANCING
ON YOUR DAD'S SCHOONER.
SO YOU WANT TO BE
A ROCK STAR HUH?
WELL OKAY YOU HAVEN'T GOT MUCH
OF A VOICE AND YOU REALLY
CAN'T PLAY AN INSTRUMENT
'CAUSE YOUR BAND TEACHER
THREW YOU OUT OF THE CLASS.
OKAY NO PROBLEMO START
YOUR OWN BAND.
ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS HIRE
REALLY TALENTED PEOPLE TO
SURROUND YOU AND YOU STILL
TAKE ALL THE GLORY
THAT'S WHAT MY UNCLE RED
DOES ON THIS SHOW.
OKAY YOU'RE GOING TO NEED A NAME
NAME'S ARE IMPORTANT SO
SOMETHING LIKE 'THE PHLEB'
OR 'YESTERDAY'S IMPLOSION'
NO THIS IS THE ONE!
THIS IS THE ONE!
'UNDEAD BOXCARS' OH YES!
CHECK I THINK.
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO NEED PEOPLE
LIKE TO BE IN THE BAND RIGHT
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO HAVE
GUYS AND (GIGGLES) BABES
ALL RIGHT SO WHAT YOU DO
IS YOU GO TO A PLACE WHERE
THEY'RE HIRING MUSICIANS RIGHT
AND THEN YOU GRAB THE REJECTS
AND YOU PROMISE THEM FAME AND
GLORY OR AT LEAST YOU KNOW POP,
CHIPS AND DIP, FREE REHEARSAL
SPACE FREE, MUSIC LESSONS,
INSTRUMENTS...
A GUARANTEED WEEKLY SALARY
YES OF COURSE THIS IS ALL A RISK
BUT YOU HAVE TO PAY YOUR DUES
OR SHOULD I SAY I HAVE
TO PAY THEIR DUES.
STRUMS GUITAR
HOW DO THEY DO THAT?
>>RED: I WANT TO GIVE SOME
ADVICE TO YOU TEENAGERS
IF I MIGHT
BECAUSE THE ADULTS THEY DON'T
LISTEN ANYWAY AND THEY'RE
TOO OLD TO CHANGE AND EVEN IF
THEY COULD THEY'RE GOING TO BE
DEAD SOON SO WHAT'S THE POINT?
AND HOW THIS HAPPENED HAROLD
WANTED TO GO TO A MOVIE IN TOWN
AND HE COULDN'T DECIDE WHETHER
TO SEE 'BUZZ SAW BUTCHERY
ON MAIN STREET PART 9
THE EVISCERATION' OR A
NEW COMEDY THEY GOT CALLED
'TRASH MY PARENT'S HOUSE'.
SO INSTEAD I DECIDED
WE'D RENT A CLASSIC FILM
WATCH IT AT THE LODGE
IT WAS 'ACROSS THE PACIFIC'
STARRING HUMPHREY BOGART
AND MARY ASTOR, 2 GREAT ACTORS
WHO DRANK A LOT.
WHEN IT WAS OVER HAROLD SAID
HE THOUGHT IT WAS RACIST,
SEXIST, OVER ACTED,
WITH SOME REAL CORNY
MELODRAMATIC DIALOGUE AND
SOME CHEESY SPECIAL EFFECTS.
WHEREAS I THOUGHT IT WAS
JUST BORING...
SO THE NEXT TIME YOUR PARENTS
SAY TO YOU THEY DON'T MAKE
MOVIES LIKE THEY USED TO
DON'T BE UPSET ABOUT THAT.
>>RED: I THOUGHT IT WOULD
REALLY HELP OUR CASINO NIGHT
IF I INVITED RANGER GORD NOT
THAT WE WANTED HIM THERE SO
MUCH BUT WITH HIS LIFESTYLE
I FIGURE HE'S GOT A LOT
OF DISPOSABLE INCOME.
>>GORD: OH MR. GREEN
WELCOME PRETTY MUCH THE SAME
AS YESTERDAY'S REPORT
COME IN I'M JUST FINISHING
TODAY'S REPORT.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
>>GORD: LISTEN WOULD YOU MIND
TAKING THIS DOWN WITH YOU
TO HEAD OFFICE WHEN YOU GO?
>>RED: YEAH I CAN DO THAT,
SURE NO PROBLEM.
>>GORD: GREAT GREAT AND THEY'RE
SUPPOSED TO COME BY EVERY
FRIDAY BUT THEY HAVEN'T BEEN
AROUND IN A WHILE
DON'T KNOW WHY.
>>RED: I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THAT FOR YOU.
>>GORD: THANKS.
HEY SOMETHING REALLY
DIFFERENT ABOUT YOU TODAY.
>>RED: YEAH IT'S MY SHIRT.
>>GORD: NO, NO, SOMETHING ELSE
YOU'VE GAINED A LOT OF WEIGHT
AND GOTTEN ALL GREY
OR SOMETHING.
>>RED: NO IT'S JUST MY SHIRT
THAT'S THE ONLY THING
THAT'S CHANGED ABOUT ME.
YOU SEEM PRETTY WELL
THE SAME THOUGH GORD.
>>GORD: YEAH YEAH WELL
THAT'S WHAT THIS JOB DEMANDS
BEING THE SAME MAN EVERYDAY
LOOKING OUT OVER THE SAME FOREST
SAMENESS SAME, SAME, SAME
YEAH STARING AT THE SAME SUN,
LOOKING AT THE SAME CLOUDS,
TALKING TO THEM.
THEY CHANGE, THEY CHANGE
THAT'S TRUE, THANK GOODNESS
FOR THE CLOUDS A GUY COULD
GET LONELY BUT I KNOW H.Q. IS
COUNTING ON ME SO I'M NOT GOING
TO LET THEM DOWN OH DID YOU
CHECK MY MAILBOX ON THE WAY UP?
>>RED: YEAH, THERE'S NOTHING
THERE, NO.
>>GORD: THAT'S OKAY.
YOU KNOW THEY USED TO SEND
A PAYCHEQUE EVERY COUPLE
OF MONTHS BUT I KNOW HOW
HECTIC OFFICE WORK CAN GET.
NO PROBLEM IT'S NOT LIKE I
CAN SPEND IT ON ANYTHING ANYWAY.
>>RED: WELL NOW ACTUALLY IT'S
INTERESTING THAT YOU SHOULD SAY
THAT BECAUSE I WAS JUST HERE
TO INVITE YOU TO COME DOWN
TO THE LODGE TONIGHT FOR
CASINO NIGHT.
>>GORD: NO, NO.
>>RED: OH SURE COME ON.
>>GORD: NO, NO, I COULDN'T
I MEAN WHO'S GOING TO LOOK
AFTER THE FOREST HUH?
I MEAN PEOPLE ARE COUNTING ON ME
TO PROTECT THEM AND NOT JUST
WHEN IT'S CONVENIENT OR WHEN
IT CO ORDINATES WITH MY
SOCIAL CALENDAR.
NO THANK YOU, PLUS THE FACT
THAT H.Q. HAS NEVER SENT
AN INSPECTOR TO VISIT ME IN
THE 16 YEARS I'VE BEEN
A FOREST RANGER
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU?
>>RED: THAT THEY
FORGOT ABOUT YOU?
>>GORD: NO THAT
I'M DUE, OVERDUE.
>>RED: OH ALL RIGHT.
>>GORD: TONIGHT
COULD BE THE NIGHT.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
>>GORD: TONIGHT.
>>GORD: YEAH BUT THANKS ANYWAY
COME BY AND VISIT AFTER
I'M UP ALL NIGHT.
>>RED: WELL I CAN ONLY MAKE
SUGGESTIONS TO THE FELLAS
I DON'T KNOW THEY GO...
>>GORD: GREAT BE FUN THEN
SEE YOU LATER, I CAN MAKE
LITTLE SNACKS ON TOAST.
>>RED: OH DON'T MAKE ANYTHING
UNTIL WE GET HERE GORD.
>>GORD: OH NO PROBLEM
WHAT TIME EXACTLY?
>>RED: NOT BEFORE MIDNIGHT
I WOULDN'T THINK.
>>GORD: NO PROBLEM, NO PROBLEM
UP ALL NIGHT, ALL NIGHT.
>>RED: WELL THE CASINO NIGHT...
(HAROLD CHUCKLING)
>>RED: YOU'RE A BORN
LEADER HAROLD.
CASINO NIGHT IS A DEFINITE GO
ALTHOUGH WE ALMOST HAD TO
CANCEL AT THE LAST MINUTE
BECAUSE STINKY PETERSON
MISUNDERSTOOD THE TERM
CRAPS TABLE.
DO YOU HAVE TO CHANGE WHERE
I CAN SEE YOU HAROLD?
I'LL NEVER EAT CHICKEN AGAIN.
ANYWAY THE WEATHER'S REAL GOOD
SO WE DECIDED TO MOVE THE
CASINO NIGHT OUTDOORS
WE GOT A ROULETTE WHEEL,
A ONE-ARMED BANDIT
AND A ONE-LEGGED BARTENDER
THREW ALL THE BEER INTO THE LAKE
OR AS WE CALL IT OUR WET BAR
ALL WE NEED NOW IS ORGANIZED
CRIME IT'D BE JUST
LIKE LAS VEGAS.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH IT'S
THE SOUND OF THE POSSUM
WE GOT TO LEAVE NOW.
>>RED: YEAH WELL YOU GO AHEAD
HAROLD I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
>>HAROLD: I LOOK LIKE YOU NOW.
>>RED: YEAH YEAH YOU
LOOK TERRIFIC.
IT'S A SHAME ISN'T IT?
ANYWAY WE'LL GET THE MEETING
WRAPPED UP IN A HURRY SO WE
CAN GET OUT THERE AND START
LOSING MONEY WHICH I SUPPOSE
IS THE FUN OF GAMBLING
THE ART OF THE DEAL
AS DONALD TRUMP WOULD SAY
ALTHOUGH I DON'T THINK THERE
IS ANY TRUMP IN POKER
AND YET HE OWNS A COUPLE
OF CASINOS SO GO FIGURE.
ANYWAY IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
THAT BLEACH YOU GAVE ME
TOOK THE RELISH STAINS
RIGHT OUT OF THE SHIRT AND
DIDN'T HARM THE FLANNEL AT ALL
SO EVERYBODY ELSE ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD AND THE WHOLE
GANG UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE
THANKS A LOT FOR WATCHING
AND KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>ALL: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT I'VE GOT
A COUPLE OF ANNOUNCEMENTS HERE
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK HAS ASKED FOR
ME TO ANNOUNCE THAT IF ANYONE
FINDS A BLACK AND WHITE CAT
THAT ANSWERS TO THE NAME SHRIEK
WOULD THEY PLEASE KEEP IT.