[breezy folk music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> AND NOW IT'S TIME
FOR THE GREATEST SHOW
IN THE HISTORY OF TELEVISION,
THE PROGRAM THAT HAS
RESHAPED THE MEDIUM AND IS
LEADING THE WAY IN TERMS OF
CONTENT, LOOK, AND SHEER POWER.
YES, IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW,
STARRING THE DYNAMIC
AND FORCEFUL MAN OF ACTION,
MY UNCLE
AND QUITE POSSIBLY
THE SEXIEST MAN ALIVE,
RED GREEN, GREEN, GREEN,
GREEN, GREEN!
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH, HAROLD.
THANK YOU,
AND WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
WE GOT A REAL DYNAMIC SHOW
FOR YOU TONIGHT,
A LOT OF GUESTS AND FILM CLIPS
AND WHAT HAVE YOU,
AND SO--A REAL GOOD SHOW.
GOOD SHOW.
>> DON'T DO THAT!
>> SORRY.
WE WERE UP A BIT LATE
LAST NIGHT.
WE WERE LOOKING FOR UFOs,
YOU KNOW, WEIRD THINGS
FROM OUTER SPACE.
SPEAKING OF WHICH, COME ON
OVER HERE A MINUTE, HAROLD.
HAROLD IS MY NEPHEW AND ALSO
THE PRODUCER AND THE DIRECTOR
OF THE SHOW.
HE'S A REAL
JERK-OF-ALL-TRADES.
>> PLUS I DO THIS.
THAT TAKES US INTO
A NEXT SEGMENT, YOU KNOW,
IN CASE THIS ONE'S DRAGGING
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
SO NATURALLY I, YOU KNOW,
NEED ALL THESE BUTTONS.
[laughs]
I'M BUSY.
>> YEAH, WELL, SO ANYHOW,
LIKE I SAY,
WE WERE WATCHING FOR UFOs.
WE WERE HAVING A SKINNY-DIP
AFTER DINNER,
AND WE SAW THIS HUGE THING
KIND OF GO THROUGH THE AIR.
WE THOUGHT AT FIRST THAT IT WAS
MOOSE THOMPSON, BUT THIS SEEMED
TO HAVE SOME INTELLIGENCE TO IT.
>> DID IT LOOK ANYTHING
LIKE THIS?
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
>> OH, WELL, THAT ELIMINATES
THAT.
>> THAT ELIMINATES WHAT?
>> YOU FINISHING YOUR STORY.
[folky guitar and spoons music plays]
>> WE GO OUT EVERY FRIDAY
DRINKIN' WITH THE BOYS
WE RAISE UP A RUCKUS
AND MAKE LOTS OF NOISE
>> BREAK MOST OF OUR--
>> BREAK--
>> MOST OF OUR PROMISES
>> NO.
WE BREAK ALL OUR PROMISES
AND MOST OF OUR TOYS
FRIDAY NIGHT
DRINKIN' WITH THE BOYS
>> BOYS
>> THANKS, THERE.
DRINKIN' WITH THE BOYS
200 BEERS
EACH ONE OF US DESTROYS
I LOVE TO GO DRINKIN'
DRINKIN' WITH THE BOYS
TOO BAD THEY'RE ALL DEAD NOW
THIS WEEK IN
THE HANDYMAN CORNER,
WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU HOW TO--
HOW TO REFINISH FURNITURE.
AND THIS IS KIND OF A--
KIND OF A NEW TECHNIQUE
THAT WE'RE USING HERE.
NOW, ORDINARILY WHEN I WAS GONNA
REFINISH, SAY, A BEAUTIFUL OLD
CHAIR LIKE THIS, I WOULD TAKE
JUST AN ORDINARY DINNER KNIFE
AND JUST KIND OF, YOU KNOW,
GET THAT PAINT AND WHAT HAVE YOU
OFF OF THERE.
THE PROBLEM WITH THAT IS THAT
IT DOES CREATE THE OCCASIONAL
BLEMISH ON THE FURNITURE,
AND IT MAKES DINNER TASTE FUNNY.
NOW, THE ALTERNATIVE THAT MOST
PEOPLE GO WITH IS SOME SORT
OF A CHEMICAL STRIPPER.
DON'T EVER SAY THAT AROUND
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK.
BUT WE DON'T LIKE TO USE THE
CHEMICALS UP AT THE LODGE,
BECAUSE ONE TIME,
STINKY PETERSON STRIPPED DOWN
THE TWO-HOLER,
AND HE HASN'T BEEN ABLE
TO THINK OF ANYTHING
THAT HAPPENED BETWEEN
1985 AND 1987.
SO WHAT WE LIKE TO USE--
AND I THINK THE BEST WAY
TO TAKE A FINISH
OFF OLD FURNITURE--
IS ONE OF THOSE HEAT GUNS,
WHICH WILL COST YOU ACTUALLY
UP TO ABOUT 40 BUCKS.
BUT WE HAVE A WAY AROUND THAT.
I'M SURE EVERYBODY HAS A FEW
HAIR DRYERS LYING AROUND
THE HOUSE--
YOU KNOW, ONE IN THE KIDS' ROOM,
ONE IN THE DAUGHTER'S ROOM,
ONE IN THE WIFE'S ROOM,
MAYBE ONE IN THE GRANDMOTHER'S
ROOM, AND ONE IN YOUR OWN ROOM.
MAYBE YOU USE THEM TO DRY THE
BABY'S BOTTOM OR WHATEVER.
WHAT YOU DO IS, YOU GET ABOUT
SIX OF THESE TOGETHER, AND THEN
YOU GET AN OLD BROKEN-DOWN
HOCKEY STICK LIKE THIS--
NO, THIS IS ACTUALLY
A GOOD HOCKEY STICK.
WELL, I DON'T WANT TO USE
A GOOD HOCKEY STICK FOR THIS.
THERE.
OKAY.
NOW WE GOT THE HOCKEY STICK.
AND WHAT WE DO IS, WE ATTACH
THE HAIR DRYERS TO THE STICK
USING THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON:
DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, WE GOT HER ALL
SET HERE, AND I GOT THEM ALL
KIND OF GENERALLY POINTING
THE SAME DIRECTION.
NOW, THE PROBLEM I COULD RUN
INTO IS, THESE ARE ABOUT
1,500 WATTS OF POWER EACH.
AND WE GOT SIX OF THEM.
SO THERE'S, I GUESS, OVER 7,000
OR 8,000 WATTS OF POWER THERE,
WHICH IS TOO MUCH FOR YOUR
NORMAL HOUSEHOLD CIRCUIT.
SO WHAT I DONE WAS,
I TOOK THE FUSE OUT,
AND I REPLACED IT WITH A NICKEL.
WORKS GREAT AND ONLY COSTS 5¢.
SO ANYWAY, WE'LL PICK THIS BABY
UP, AND WE'RE READY TO SHOW YOU
HOW IT WORKS ON THE CHAIR.
ALL RIGHT.
DO YOU WANT TO HIT THE POWER
THERE?
[hair dryers blowing]
THE CHAIR MAYBE DOESN'T NEED
AS MUCH AS THE WORKBENCH.
WE CAN USE IT ON THE WORKBENCH.
WELL, YOU GET THE IDEA.
SO REMEMBER, UNTIL NEXT TIME--
YOU WANT TO KILL THE POWER?
UNTIL NEXT TIME, IF YOU CAN'T
BE A HANDSOME MAN,
YOU CAN BE A HANDYMAN
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> UNCLE RED WILL BE RIGHT BACK
WITH HIS EXTRATERRESTRIALS.
>> HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
I HAVE THE SAME NUMBER OF
TERRESTRIALS AS ANYBODY ELSE.
>> YOU KNOW, HAROLD, I'VE MET
SOME PEOPLE OVER THE YEARS,
VEGETARIANS.
YOU EVER HEARD OF THEM?
>> YEAH.
THEY'RE PEOPLE WHO WON'T EAT
MEAT UNLESS IT'S, LIKE,
GROWN IN THE GROUND.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
I HOPE THIS NEVER HAPPENS
TO YOU, HAROLD.
HAVE YOU SEEN THEM?
THEY LOOK LIKE BIG GREEN BEANS.
>> THEY'RE A LITTLE PALE.
>> THEY'RE NOT PALE.
THEY'RE GREEN.
>> GREEN.
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, I GUESS THERE'S
A GREEN PALE, SO IN THAT WAY,
YOU COULD SAY THEY'RE PALE.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
I DON'T GET THAT.
>> OKAY.
BUT THE THING IS, YOU ARE
WHAT YOU EAT, RIGHT?
>> UH-OH.
>> WHY DO YOU THINK WE NEVER
HAVE RUMP ROAST?
>> THAT EXPLAINS A LOT.
>> WELL, YEAH.
THE VEGETARIAN THING TO ME IS,
THAT'S AN ANIMAL THING.
RABBIT?
>> LOOK OUT!
BE VERY CALM.
THEY CAN SMELL FEAR.
>> [sniffs] SO CAN I.
>> THAT'S ME.
I'M SORRY.
I WAS A LITTLE MORE AFRAID
THAN HE WAS.
>> SEE, IF YOU WERE A
VEGETARIAN, WE MAY NOT HAVE
HAD THAT PROBLEM.
>> WELL, IF I WAS A VEGETARIAN,
I WOULD'VE ATE HIM.
THERE'S NO MEAT ON A BUG
LIKE THAT.
>> "IT IS WINTER,
A TIME TO PAUSE.
THE DRIVEWAY IS HALF
SHOVELED OUT,
BUT I LAY DOWN THE SHOVEL,
AND I PAUSE TO ENJOY
THIS MOMENT.
AFTER ALL, THIS IS MY FIRST
HEART ATTACK."
SO ANYWAY, LIKE I WAS SAYING
ABOUT UFO SIGHTINGS,
THE BUNCH OF US WERE HAVING
A LATE-NIGHT SKINNY-DIP LAST
NIGHT, AND THIS UFO COME DOWN
ABOUT TREETOP LEVEL, HOVERED
THERE FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
THEN IT TOOK OFF ABOUT
A TRILLION MILES AN HOUR,
AND IT COMES ROLLING BACK DOWN,
SCREECHES TO A HALT
BUT WITH A SCREECH.
>> NO WAY, UNCLE RED.
THESE THINGS ALWAYS TURN OUT TO
BE, LIKE, SWAMP GAS OR WEATHER
BALLOONS OR CAFETERIA FOOD.
>> THERE ARE ALIENS,
AND THEY EXIST, HAROLD.
AND THEY'RE WATCHING US.
IT'S JUST THAT THE GOVERNMENT
IS KEEPING THE WHOLE THING
A BIG SECRET.
>> WELL, SO AM I.
>> THIS HERE IS THE FIRST BOOK
I EVER READ.
IT'S THREE OR FOUR
YEARS AGO NOW.
IT'S THE WIND IN THE WILLOWS
BY KENNETH GRAHAME.
"THERE'S NOTHING QUITE AS GOOD
AS MESSING IN BOATS."
I'M KIND OF PARAPHRASING.
EITHER MESSING IN 'EM OR MESSING
OUT OF THEM, JUST MESSING
AROUND WITH BOATS.
THAT'S WHAT KENNETH GRAHAME
SAID.
MY FRIEND JIMMY MCVEIGH,
HE'S A POSTAL WORKER,
AND HE'S BEEN MESSING AROUND
WITH THIS BOAT FOR A WHILE.
AND ACTUALLY, HE'S MADE QUITE
A MESS OF IT, HASN'T HE?
OH, HERE COMES JIMMY NOW.
HOW YOU DOING, JIM?
>> BLOODY HELL.
LOOK AT THIS.
LOOK AT THAT, RED.
>> GOD.
>> ANOTHER BLOODY PAIR OF PANTS
RUINED.
>> OH, BOY.
>> I TAKE MY LIFE IN MY HANDS
EVERY TIME I GO OUT
ON THIS CAREER.
I MEAN, I RISK MY LIFE
FOR PEOPLE LIKE ED MCMAHON.
BLOODY JUNK MAIL.
I COULD GET RABIES, YOU KNOW.
>> BOY, DOGS HATE POSTIES,
DON'T THEY, JIM?
>> DOGS?
THAT WAS NO DOG DID THAT.
A MAN BIT ME!
BLOODY LUNATIC, JUST BECAUSE
I WAS A COUPLE OF WEEKS LATE
DELIVERING HIS PENSION CHECK.
>> IT WAS AN OLD MAN?
>> IT WAS.
YEAH, THE SENIOR CITIZENS,
THEY GO OFF THEIR NUT, YOU KNOW.
THEY DO.
THEY'RE BONKERS JUST BECAUSE
THEY DIDN'T GET A LETTER
FROM HOME OR FROM THE
GRANDCHILDREN.
WHY CAN'T THEY PICK UP
THE BLOODY TELEPHONE?
>> WELL, LET'S FORGET THAT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE BOAT.
THAT'S A DIFFERENT THING.
>> NOW YOU'RE TALKING
MY LANGUAGE.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> I MEAN, LOOK AT THAT.
MY SALVA--
THIS BOAT IS MY SALVATION.
>> YEAH.
>> THIS IS MY RELIEF IN LIFE.
>> MY DARLING.
MY BEAUTY.
>> YEAH.
>> I LOVE HER.
THIS BOAT'S LIKE A WIFE FOR YOU,
ISN'T IT, JIM?
>> RED, THIS BOAT IS NOT
LIKE A WIFE.
THIS BOAT IS HERE WHEN
I COME HOME EVERY AFTERNOON.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I MEAN, THIS BOAT DID NOT
TAKE OFF WITH THE TV
AND THE VC-BLOODY-R.
>> NO.
>> OH, HO, HO. NO, NO.
THIS BOAT IS MY FRIEND.
>> YOU KNOW, JIMMY,
KENNETH GRAHAME SAID
THERE'S NOTHING MORE IMPORTANT
THAN MESSING ABOUT IN BOATS,
AND, WELL, THIS IS FOR YOU.
>> JEEZ, THANKS VERY MUCH, RED.
>> NO PROBLEM.
>> I THINK I COULD MAKE
GOOD USE OF THIS.
>> UH-HUH.
>> I NEED A 3/4 INCH SHIM
FOR THAT MOTOR IN THERE.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, JIMMY.
THIS IS AN ORIGINAL AUTOGRAPHED
EDITION, YOU KNOW,
BY THE AUTHOR.
>> OH, I SEE.
WELL, I ONLY NEED
TO TAKE IT DOWN TO 3/4.
>> JIMMY, JIMMY, JIMMY.
THIS BOOK'S WORTH $270.
>> WELL, THAT BLOODY MOTOR IN
THERE IS WORTH $2,000, SO YOU
TELL ME WHAT'S MORE IMPORTANT.
HERE'S 60 BUCKS' WORTH.
[folksy guitar and spoons music plays]
>> I'M UP PAST THE TUNDRA
WHERE THE POLAR BEARS DANCE
>> DANCE
>> I GOT SNOW IN MY FACE
AND ICE IN MY PANTS
I'M FISHING THE ARCTIC
AND I JUST HAD TO PHONE YA
'CAUSE I CAUGHT
SOMETHING BIG
>> DOUBLE PNEUMONIA
[laughs]
OH, UNCLE RED,
THAT IS SO WEIRD.
I WAS JUST GONNA READ FROM THE
VIEWER MAIL, AND EVERY TIME,
YOU WALK IN.
>> FOR HEAVEN'S SAKE.
>> THAT'S WEIRD, EH?
THAT'S WEIRD.
THAT'S SO WEIRD.
ANYWAY, HERE'S A LETTER, OKAY?
IT SAYS, "DEAR RED, I'VE BEEN
WATCHING YOUR SHOW FOR A SHORT
TIME NOW, BUT IT SEEMS LONGER.
I REALLY LIKE WHEN YOU DO
FEATURES ON WINTER ACTIVITIES.
HAVE YOU EVER DONE ANYTHING
ON SNOWMOBILES?"
>> OH, YOU KNOW THAT, HAROLD.
I CERTAINLY HAVE.
I'VE RIDDEN ON THEM.
I'VE STOOD UP ON THEM.
I WENT INTO A COUPLE OF TREES
ON THEM.
I REMEMBER ONE TIME, I--
>> NO, NO, UNCLE RED,
I THINK HE MEANS ON THE SHOW.
LIKE, HAVE YOU EVER DONE
A SEGMENT ON SNOWMOBILES?
>> OH.
OH, WELL, YES.
YES, WE HAVE.
JUST LAST YEAR THERE,
I WAS OUT FISHING FOR WALLEYE,
AND I HOOKED INTO A SNOWMOBILE
WHICH HAD GONE THROUGH THE ICE
THE PREVIOUS WINTER.
AND I PULLED HER RIGHT UP
INTO THE BOAT.
>> OH, YOU MUST HAVE, WHAT, HAD,
LIKE, 1,000-POUND-TEST LINE?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW ME.
AND IF ANY OF THE VIEWERS AT
HOME WANTED TO TRY FISHING FOR
SNOWMOBILES, WHAT YOU DO IS,
YOU RUN YOUR LINE VERY DEEP,
BIG HOOK, NO BAIT, AND DO YOUR
FISHING OUT IN THE CENTER
OF THE LAKE WHERE THE ICE
IS THE THINNEST IN THE WINTER.
AND THOSE THINGS'LL GIVE YOU
A HECK OF A FIGHT, A LOT MORE
THAN, SAY, A CAR TIRE
OR EVEN AN OUTBOARD MOTOR.
>> YEAH?
OH, JEEPERS.
NOW, THAT'S FISHING.
>> WELL, WE HAD A HECK OF A TIME
LANDING THAT, THOUGH.
YOU KNOW, WE USED A NINE-FOOT
DIP NET, LOTS OF ROPE, AND I BET
THE BOAT CAPSIZED 300, 400,
MAYBE 500 TIMES BEFORE WE
ACTUALLY GOT THE UNIT IN THERE.
>> BOY, THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
>> WELL, IT'S NOT.
>> WELL, LET'S GO
TO OUR NEXT SEGMENT.
>> I HAD MORE TO SAY
ABOUT SNOWMOBILES.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> YOU KNOW, ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT YOU NEED TO LEARN TO DO
WHEN YOU'RE A WOODSMAN
IS TO SET A FIRE.
IT'S A SOURCE OF HEAT,
IT'S A SOURCE OF A COOKING,
AND IT'S A SOURCE
OF ENTERTAINMENT.
SO BILL IS GONNA SHOW US HOW TO
BUILD A FIRE OUT IN THE WOODS.
GOT SOME PAPER THERE.
ACTUALLY GOT QUITE
A BIT OF STUFF
IN THE OLD COVERALLS THERE.
YOU CAN GET A HECK OF A LOT
INTO THOSE COVERALLS.
GOT THE BIB THERE.
MY GOD, WHAT IS THAT?
OH, HE GRABBED MY WALLET THERE,
HE'S QUITE A KIBITZER,
THAT BILL.
HE'S GOT--ACTUALLY GOT MORE
STUFF IN THE COVERALLS THAN I
EVEN THOUGHT HE--BUT YOU GET--
THAT'S--YOU GET THE--
WELL, YOU'RE PRETTY WELL READY
TO LIGHT IT NOW, I THINK.
THAT'S ENOUGH, BILL, ISN'T IT?
BILL?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I GUESS HE'S PLANNING TO DO
SOME COOKING ON THIS.
SO ANYWAY, ONCE HE'S GOT HIS
FIRE ALL SET, IT'S A QUESTION
OF WHAT DO YOU USE TO START IT,
YOU KNOW?
AND THOSE ARE MATCHES THERE.
THAT'S NORMAL.
OR WE COULD USE A--
I BELIEVE THAT'S A LIGHTER.
MAGNIFYING GLASS.
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW,
WITH THE SUN
AND FOCUS THAT IN ON THERE
AND...
WELL, HE HAS A CANDLE
THERE AND...
YOU KNOW, I GOT TO WONDER
WHAT BILL'S UNDERWEAR
IS MADE OUT OF THERE.
OH, THIS IS INTERESTING.
HE HAS A CIGARETTE LIGHT--
CIGARETTE LIGHTER
OUT OF THE CAR.
WE'RE KIND OF KIBITZING.
IT WENT DOWN INTO THE--
OH, MY GOD.
OH.
YOU KNOW, BILL CAN REALLY MOVE
WHEN HE'S MOTIVATED.
HE WAS ROCKETIN'
THROUGH THE TREES.
OH.
NOW, HERE'S SOMETHING YOU
WOULDN'T NORMALLY THINK OF:
USING JUMPER CABLES
TO START YOUR FIRE.
WHAT YOU DO FIRST OF ALL IS
HOOK IT UP TO THE BATTERY
OF YOUR VEHICLE.
[explosion]
>> AAH!
>> YOU NEED TO BE CAREFUL
WITH THAT.
ANYWAY, ONCE THEY'RE HOOKED UP
AT THAT END, YOU JUST HOOK
THE CABLES RIGHT INTO THE FIRE.
AND I GUESS THE SPARK,
THE IDEA IS, THE SPARK
WILL START THIS THING UP.
[engine turning over]
WELL, THERE SHE GOES.
THIS IS A GUN THAT BILL HAD.
YOU CAN ACTUALLY USE A GUN
TO START A FIRE.
[gunshot]
[air whistling]
AND THERE'S DINNER.
SO ALL IN ALL,
IT WAS A HECK OF A DAY.
SUPER TIME.
"IT IS WINTER.
IN THE SNOW,
THE TRACKS OF A RABBIT,
THE TRACKS OF THE PHEASANT,
THE TRACKS OF THE DEER,
THE TRACKS OF THE FOX.
AND THEY ALL STOP
AT THE SAME SPOT:
WHERE THEY WERE RUN OVER BY
THE TRACKS OF THE SNOWMOBILE."
IF ANY OF YOU VIEWERS
WOULD LIKE TO MAKE A COMMENT
OR HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
ABOUT WHAT'S ABOUT TO HAPPEN,
PLEASE CALL HAROLD AT HOME,
NOT ME AND NOT THE STATION.
HAROLD.
>> OKAY.
WAR.
OKAY?
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
LITTLE BOYS AND GIRLS,
DOGS, CATS, AND FISH.
[laughs]
THAT'S EVERYBODY.
WAR.
WHAT IS IT GOOD FOR?
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
HA.
WAR.
WHAT IS IT GOOD FOR?
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
SAY IT AGAIN.
HA.
[laughs]
THAT'S COOL.
WELL, I GOT TO TELL YOU.
WAR ISN'T GOOD.
RIGHT?
IT'S NOT.
IT ONLY BLOWS THINGS UP.
AND WAR, IT'S NOT LIKE
A JOHN WAYNE MOVIE OR SOMETHING,
'CAUSE IT'S IN COLOR.
THAT'S TRUE.
YOU KNOW, A GREAT MAN ONCE SAID,
"WAR SUCKS SCISSORS."
AND, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
BOYS AND GIRLS,
DOGS, CATS, AND FISH,
THAT GREAT MAN WAS ME.
[laughs]
WAR.
>> I KNOW THAT A LOT OF YOU
TEENAGERS ARE PRETTY CONFUSED
ABOUT LIFE THESE DAYS,
DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY
OR WHAT TO DO.
THIS IS BECAUSE OF ONE THING:
YOUR GLANDS.
RIGHT NOW, YOU SEE, YOUR GLANDS
ARE TRYING TO TAKE OVER
YOUR BODY.
IN SOME CASES, YOUR GLANDS ARE
TRYING TO TAKE OVER THE BODY OF
THE PERSON STANDING BESIDE YOU.
AND EVERY ONE OF YOUR GLANDS
IS TRYING TO TELL YOU TO DO
SOMETHING DIFFERENT, YOU KNOW,
AND YOU GOT TO BE CAREFUL WHICH
GLAND YOU LISTEN TO, BECAUSE YOU
CAN ALWAYS TELL WHICH GLAND IS
DOMINATING A PERSON'S BEHAVIOR.
LIKE, WITH MOOSE THOMPSON,
IT'S HIS STOMACH.
STINKY PETERSON--
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SO NOW THERE YOU ARE GETTING
ALL PANICKY, THINKING,
"SO MANY GLANDS,
SO LITTLE TIME."
AND I'M TELLING YOU,
JUST BE PATIENT.
EVERY GLAND WILL GET ITS TURN
EVENTUALLY.
WHY BE IN A HURRY FOR A TRUS?
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH THE
EXCITING CONCLUSION OF
THE STORY ABOUT THE ALIENS.
>> I'LL RECALIBRATE MY PHASER,
JUST TO BE ON THE SAFE SIDE.
>> HAROLD, I WANT YOU TO THINK
ABOUT TRYING SOMETHING
THIS YEAR IN THE WINTER:
CAMPING.
HUH? WE GO OUT.
WE JUST GET A TENT THERE,
AND WE GO OUT
IN 50, 60 BELOW ZERO.
>> BUT DON'T THE PEGS FALL DOWN
IN THE SNOW?
>> NO, YOU DON'T NEED PEGS.
>> NO?
>> NO, THE TENT, YOU PUT THE
TENT UP, AND IT JUST FREEZES
THE WAY IT IS.
>> OH, IT'S CERTAINLY
AN INTERESTING INVITATION.
>> WELL, HAROLD, IT'S AN
EXPERIENCE YOU WON'T BELIEVE.
>> HAVE YOU DONE THIS
EVER BEFORE?
>> WELL, YEAH, YEAH,
I'VE SEEN IT.
>> YOU'VE SEEN IT?
>> YEAH.
I SAW IT.
>> LIKE THE IGLOOS?
'CAUSE I WOULD GO IN AN IGLOO,
BUT...
>> NO.
NO, YOU DON'T WANT TO GO
IN AN IGLOO.
'CAUSE THEN YOU WAKE UP
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
YOU START CHEWING BLUBBER.
>> OH, THAT'D BE HORRIBLE,
'CAUSE I COULD BARELY REACH
MY STOMACH.
>> OH, IT'S CLOSER
THAN YOU THINK.
>> IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
A TWO-MAN TENT, DOES IT?
>> NO, IT'S BETTER
IF IT'S A ONE-MAN TENT.
>> FOR THE BOTH OF US?
>> YEAH.
WELL, I MEAN, TO KEEP
THE HEAT IN.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'LL REALLY HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT THIS.
>> WELL, I'D LIKE YOU
JUST TO THINK ABOUT IT.
I'M NOT ASKING FOR A COMMITMENT.
I'M JUST SAYING THAT, YOU KNOW,
PICTURE YOURSELF, MID-JANUARY.
>> I'M A MAN OF THE '90s.
COMMITMENT'S HARD.
>> OH.
JACK!
JACK, COME ON UP HERE.
I KNOW YOU'RE DOWN THERE, JACK.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
IF YOU'RE FIGURING ON TRYING
TO TAKE AWAY MY CAVE AND ALL MY
SUPPLIES, WELL, THINK AGAIN,
BECAUSE IT'S MINE.
I HAVE A RECEIPT.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S JUST THE GUYS AT THE LODGE
WERE, YOU KNOW,
WORRIED ABOUT YOU, AND
YOUR WIFE IS WORRIED ABOUT YOU,
AND YOUR FRIENDS.
WELL, NO, BUT AT LEAST YOUR WIFE
IS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME, RED.
I'M LIKE A WILDCAT, YOU KNOW?
I HAVE A--A FIFTH SENSE.
AND I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING.
POLLUTION, TERRORISM, LAWYERS,
IT'S ALL BREAKING DOWN, RED.
OH, YEAH.
AND WHILE THE REST OF THE WORLD
IS SINKING IN ITS OWN FILTH AND
DECAY, I'M GONNA BE RIGHT HERE
IN THIS CAVE.
AND I--
[screams]
>> JACK!
YOU OKAY?
>> [sighs]
OH, MY BACK.
STUPID BANANA PEELS.
>> JACK!
YOU HURT YOURSELF?
YOU OKAY DOWN THERE?
>> I'M FINE.
SO DON'T MESS WITH ME,
OR I'LL MESS WITH YOU.
[yells]
OH!
>> JACK!
JACK, YOU OKAY?
>> NO PROBLEM.
OH!
I'M FINE.
SO, RED, WHAT'S NEW?
>> WELL, THE GUYS AT THE LODGE
ARE, YOU KNOW, WORRIED THAT YOU
WERE GETTING ENOUGH TO EAT.
THAT'S ALL.
>> WELL, MY--
MY SEEDS CAME, RED.
AND MY CANNED FOOD ARRIVED.
OH, OH!
I HAVE ENOUGH CANNED FOOD HERE
TO SURVIVE FOR YEARS,
STACKS AND STACKS.
BUT YOU CAN'T HAVE ANY!
IT'S ALL FOR ME.
AND WHEN I WANT
SOMETHING TO EAT,
I JUST REACH OVER
TO MY BIG STACK OF CANS
AND PULL OUT SOME CANNED
GOOSEBERRIES LIKE THIS
OR--OR SOME FRUIT COCKTAIL
HERE--
[loud crash]
[yells]
>> JACK, YOU OKAY?
>> OW, OW, OW.
AND THEN I EAT IT.
WELL, RED, I'D LOVE TO VISIT,
BUT--
[groans]
I HAVE TO PRACTICE MY YOGA.
>> YEAH, WELL, OKAY, MAYBE WE'LL
COME BACK LATER WHEN YOU'RE
FEELING BETTER, YOU KNOW.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
I'M--I'M FINE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I FEEL WARM, AND EVERYTHING
IS PEACEFUL AND TINGLY.
>> WELL, I DON'T WANT TO BOTHER
YOU WHILE YOU'RE MEDITATING,
YOU KNOW.
>> [groans]
>> SO ANYWAY, THE BUNCH OF US,
AS I SAY, WERE SKINNY-DIPPING.
AND WE SAW THIS UFO THING.
AND IT CAME DOWN, AND IT WAS
JUST LIKE OUT OF THE MOVIE
E.T., EXCEPT IT WAS SMALLER
AND IT DIDN'T HAVE
THAT GREAT SONG.
BUT IT LANDED IN THE WOODS
JUST BEHIND THE LODGE.
SO WE JUST WENT
RIGHT OVER THERE.
WE DIDN'T EVEN STOP TO,
YOU KNOW,
GET DRESSED OR ANYTHING,
'CAUSE WE THOUGHT, WELL,
YOU KNOW, MAYBE THEY WOULD BE
INTIMIDATED BY CLOTHING
OR POSSIBLY ALLERGIC TO IT.
SO ANYWAY, WE JUST--BUCK NAKED,
THE BUNCH OF US, JUST WHIPPED
OVER THERE, YOU KNOW?
AND WE ALSO TOOK A GIFT:
BEER.
AND WE SHOWED THEM
HOW TO DRINK IT.
AND THEN THEY JUST STARTED
TO LEAVE.
THEY GOT UP, AND EVERYTHING--
AND WE FOLLOWED THEM.
WE CHASED THEM
ALL THROUGH THE FOREST
AND EVEN ACTUALLY UP
ONTO THE MAIN HIGHWAY.
AND WE'RE RUNNING DOWN THERE.
AND THE FEET ON THE ASPHALT
IS NOT A FUN THING.
AND JUST AS WE GOT CLOSE
TO THEM, THEY KIND OF
SHIMMERED OUT OF EXISTENCE.
AND THE SPACESHIP JUST ROSE
SILENTLY INTO THE NIGHT SKY.
AND THAT'S HOW COME
THE SIX OF US ENDED UP DRUNK
AND STARK NAKED IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE MAIN HIGHWAY.
AND YOU ASK ANY ONE OF THE BUNCH
OF US, AND YOU'LL GET EXACTLY
THE SAME STORY, WORD FOR WORD.
ANYWAY, MY WIFE IS WATCHING.
I'LL BE HOME JUST AS SOON
AS I FINISH
TALKING TO MY LAWYER.
SO HEY, ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND MY NEPHEW OVER THERE...
>> HAROLD.
>> HAROLD--I KNEW THAT--
AND THE WHOLE BUNCH OF US
UP HERE AT THE LODGE,
UNTIL NEXT TIME,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]