I’M NOT A HISTORY BUFF
IN FACT, I'M NOT
ANY KIND OF BUFF,
WHICH IS WHY I TRY
TO STAY OUT OF THE BUFF.
BUT I DO LIKE
TO TAKE OLD THINGS,
FIGURE OUT HOW THEY WORK
AND THEN MAKE
MY OWN MODERN VERSION.
FOR EXAMPLE, THIS ANTIQUE
FLINTLOCK MUSKET.
I'VE MADE A MODERN VERSION
OUT OF THIS PIECE OF
EAVESTROUGH DOWNSPOUT.
SEE, MY HAMMER
IS THIS TACK HAMMER.
AND MY TRIGGERING MECHANISM
IS THIS FISHING REEL.
WHEN I HIT THE RELEASE,
THE POINT OF THE HAMMER
WILL SLAM DOWN THROUGH
THE WINDOW
AND DETONATE MY AMMO.
OKAY, SO WHAT ARE
WE GONNA USE FOR AMMO?
WELL, IF YOU'RE
FIGHTING THE ENEMY
AND YOU WANNA WHIP 'EM,
YOU WANNA CREAM 'EM,
HOW ABOUT WHIPPED CREAM?
AND OF COURSE YOU
WANNA JAM THAT IN THERE.
PACK HER DOWN,
JUST LIKE DAVEY CROCKET --
OR BETTY CROCKET.
AND OUR PROJECTILE,
WE'RE GONNA USE AN EGGPLANT.
NOT REALLY A BULLET,
BUT IT'LL GO THROUGH
YOU LIKE ONE.
OKAY, LET'S SEE
IF WE'RE READY.
YEP.
WITH ANY LUCK
I'LL HIT A VEGETARIAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY...
DON'T SHOOT UNTIL YOU SEE
THE WHITES OF THEIR EGGS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
YOU KNOW, OUR NEXT DOOR
NEIGHBOUR UP HERE IS
A PAIN IN THE NECK.
MIND YOU, THEY COULD PROBABLY
SAY THE SAME THING.
THEY GOT NO FENCES AND
THEY GROW ALL THESE GRAPES,
WHICH IS FINE,
BUT THEY TASTE AWFUL.
THERE'S NOTHING WORSE THAN
STEALING SOMETHING THAT
HAS NO VALUE.
IT'S LIKE HOT
WIRING A K-CAR.
UNCLE RED!
I WAS JUST --
HAVE YOU BEEN
STEALING GRAPES AGAIN?
YEAH, BUT I'M
NOT ENJOYING THEM.
I MEAN, THEY'RE
REAL SOUR, HAROLD.
WELL, THEY'RE NOT FOR EATING.
THOSE ARE WINE GRAPES.
SO WHEN SOMETHING'S
NOT GOOD ENOUGH TO EAT
YOU DRINK IT?
ONTARIO GRAPES
MAKE SOME OF THE
FINEST WINE IN THE WORLD.
HOW COME YOU KNOW
EVERYTHING, HAROLD?
IT'S JUST AN UNCONSCIOUS
REACTION TO SEEING
WHAT CAN HAPPEN
WHEN YOU'RE THE
EXACT OPPOSITE.
WAS THAT
AN INSULT?
NOT IF YOU
HAVE TO ASK, NO.
[ APPLAUSE AND LAUGHTER ]
OKAY, SO,
YOU'RE SAYING
EVEN IF THESE GRAPES
TASTE LIKE AN ARMPIT
THEY MAKE GREAT WINE?
YEAH, THINGS IN LIFE ARE
OFTEN MUCH DIFFERENT
THAN THEY APPEAR.
THAT'S GOTTA BE
GOOD NEWS FOR YOU.
SO I'M THINKING WE
COULD MAKE OUR OWN WINE.
BY STEALING THE
NEIGHBOURS' GRAPES?
IT'S NOT STEALING IF
THE GRAPES ARE ON OUR
PROPERTY, HAROLD.
THEY'VE GOT NO FENCE AND
A LOT OF THE VINES ARE
OVER THE LOT LINE --
OR AT LEAST THEY WILL
BE ONCE I TUG ON 'EM
A LITTLE.
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT MAKING WINE!
I DON'T BASE MY LIFE ON
KNOWLEDGE, HAROLD.
I BASE IT ON
COURAGE AND CUNNING.
AND SOCIALIZED MEDICINE.
YOU KNOW WHAT,
I'LL MAKE THE WINE
WITHOUT YOU.
AND THAT'S
SOUR GRAPES.
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FROM MR. GUIDO'S
BARBERSHOP
AND CRAFT EMPORIUM.
"YOU'LL LOVE OUR
HOMEMADE MITTENS
"MADE ENTIRELY
FROM NOSE HAIR!
"COME ON IN
AND PICK YOURS TODAY."
OKAY, GLEN,
COVER YOUR EARS.
OKAY, RED,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET GLEN BRAXTON
TO SAY THIS WORD...
AND... GO!
OKAY, GLEN, THIS IS SOMETHING
PEOPLE DO FOR MOST
OF THEIR LIVES.
AGE.
NO, NO, OTHER THAN SLEEP,
PEOPLE DO THIS A LOT.
NAP.
NO, OKAY, YOU FINISH
YOUR BREAKFAST,
YOU SAY,
SEE YOU LATER, HONEY,
I'M GOING TO...
LIE DOWN.
NO, I MEAN, LIKE, TO HAVE
MONEY TO PUT FOOD ON THE TABLE
YOU GO TO...
THE WIFE'S PURSE.
OKAY, GLEN, IF YOU WERE, SAY,
A MECHANIC OR A CARPENTER,
YOU'D MAKE SURE YOU
HAD A SOMETHING BENCH.
COMFORTABLE.
NO, THIS IS SOMETHING
HAPPY PEOPLE DO.
WHISTLE WHILE YOU...
RED, UH, ALMOST
OUTTA TIME.
YEAH. OKAY.
OKAY, GLEN,
YOU'RE RETIRED NOW,
BUT WHAT DID YOU
USED TO DO EVERY WEEK,
MONDAY TO FRIDAY?
PHONE IN SICK.
NO, NO, GLEN, YOU'RE NOT
THINKING ABOUT THIS.
THIS IS A WORD FOR JOB,
WHERE YOU GO IN EVERY DAY,
PUT IN YOUR TIME,
AND AT THE END OF
THE WEEK YOU GET PAID.
I HEARD ABOUT THIS, RED.
I COULD JUST NEVER
MAKE IT WORK FOR ME.
THERE WE GO!
WHERE HAS ALL
THE FUN GONE?
WHERE HAS
ALL THE JOY GONE?
RIGHT HERE AT
HAROLD'S HOBBY HOUSE!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
AND JOINING ME TODAY
AT HAROLD'S HOBBY HOUSE
IS MR. DALTON HUMPHREY
OF THE HUMPHREY'S
EVERYTHING STORE.
AND WE CALL IT THAT
BECAUSE THAT STORE
HAS EVERYTHING.
WELL, NOT EVERYTHING,
BUT IT CERTAINLY
HAS A LOT.
SO, DALTON, WHY DON'T
YOU TELL US ABOUT
YOUR HOBBY?
WELL, YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
IT'S SOMETHING I'VE BEEN
DOING FOR MANY YEARS.
COIN COLLECTING.
AH! THIS IS
FASCINATING.
NOW, IN THESE CONTAINERS
ARE COINS I'VE COLLECTED.
PENNIES, NICKELS,
DIMES,
QUARTERS, LOONIES,
TOONIES.
IT'S A COMPLETE SET.
WELL, I CAN
CERTAINLY SEE THAT.
NOW, WHICH IS THE MOST
VALUABLE COIN YOU HAVE?
THE TOONIES!
THOSE ARE
WORTH TWO BUCKS.
BUT I'M ALWAYS ON THE
LOOKOUT FOR WHAT'S
VALUABLE.
NOW, HAROLD,
FOR EXAMPLE,
DO YOU HAVE ANY COINS
IN YOUR POCKET RIGHT NOW?
WHY YES, I DO.
AHA! AHA!
GREAT. GREAT.
37 CENTS!
OKAY, THIS IS GREAT
BECAUSE NOW I CAN SHOW YOU
HOW THIS COIN COLLECTION
REALLY WORKS.
OKAY, THIS IS GOOD.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, WE JUST
SIMPLY DIVIDE THEM INTO
THE DENOMINATIONS
AND PLACE THEM...
IN THE CORRECT JARS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
NOW, IN THIS WAY,
I HAVE INCREASED THE
VALUE OF THIS COLLECTION
BY 37 CENTS!
37 CENTS.
VERY GOOD.
YOU KNOW, THERE ARE LOTS OF
THINGS THAT MEN ENJOY,
BUT THE TWO MAIN ONES
ARE BOATS AND BEDS.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE'RE OFTEN
DISAPPOINTED IN OUR BOATS.
THERE'S NO DISAPPOINTMENT
IN BED --
AT LEAST NOT FOR ME.
I CAN SLEEP
ANYWHERE AT ANY TIME,
WHICH SHOULD EXPLAIN WHAT
HAPPENED TO THIS BOAT.
BUT RATHER THAN DWELL ON THE
NEGATIVE ASPECTS
OF PROPERTY DAMAGE
AND PENDING LEGAL ACTION,
INSTEAD I'M GONNA DO A PROJECT
THAT COMBINES TWO OF MY
FAVOURITE THINGS.
MEN LIKE DOING
STUFF LIKE THAT,
TAKING TWO ENJOYABLE
ACTIVITIES AND COMBINING THEM.
LIKE FRENCH FRIES
AND GRAVY
OR BEER AND FOOTBALL
OR BEER
AND WOMEN WRESTLING.
OKAY, THAT'S THREE.
ANYWAY, I'M GONNA
JOIN UP A BED AND A BOAT
AND MAKE A BED BOAT.
OR A BOAT BED.
I'LL DECIDE WHAT
TO CALL IT LATER.
NOW, THE FIRST STEP IN MAKING
YOUR OWN BOAT BED
IS TO GET YOURSELF
A BED FRAME.
I PREFER THE
WOODEN BOATS.
MORE CHARACTER,
MORE HISTORY,
AND THEY CAN SURVIVE
THE BIGGEST OCEAN SWELLS.
I BET THIS BABY
HAS SEEN SOME DANDY SWELLS.
YOU WANNA USE AIR
MATTRESSES FOR THIS JOB.
REGULAR MATTRESSES DON'T WORK
TOO WELL WHEN THEY'RE WET.
JUST ASK HAROLD.
NOW WITH THE HELP OF THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
THE BED FRAME BECOMES
YOUR BOAT'S KEEL,
AND THE MATTRESSES
BECOME YOUR HULL.
AND THERE'S
YOUR BOAT BED --
OR BUNK BOAT.
I'LL WORRY ABOUT
WHAT TO CALL IT LATER.
THIS DESIGN WAS ORIGINATED
BY A EUROPEAN BOAT
BUILDING COMPANY.
WINKEN, BLINKEN AND NOD.
I ADAPTED HER A LITTLE,
YOU KNOW, WITH THE
AIR MATTRESS TECHNOLOGY.
AND I HACKED UP A GARDEN HOSE,
CONNECTED THEM TOGETHER
SO I CAN BLOW UP ALL THE
AIR MATTRESSES AT ONCE.
I MEAN, THE BAD NEWS IS THAT
I WRECKED THE GARDEN HOSE,
BUT HEY,
I HATE GARDENING.
OKAY, LET'S BLOW UP
OUR BUNK BOAT,
OR OUR WATER BED
OR WATER-BORNE BED.
I'LL FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO CALL IT LATER.
OKAY, THAT WAS A BIT
OF A LOGIC TEST THERE.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF ALL THOSE AIR MATTRESSES
AND THEN MEASURE THAT
AGAINST MY LUNG CAPACITY,
THAT WAS JUST A LACK OF
CONSCIOUSNESS WAITING
TO HAPPEN.
NEVER SEND A MAN
ON A MACHINE'S JOB.
OKAY, WE'RE GOOD
TO GO HERE.
SEE THE WAY THIS MATTRESS GOES
RIGHT AROUND THE MOTOR?
KINDA MAKES IT
LIKE AN INBOARD.
PURE CLASS.
OH, AND YOU MIGHT WANNA GO WITH
A SMALL PROP ON THE MOTOR TOO;
OTHERWISE, YOU'RE GONNA BE
PUTTING NOTCHES INTO
THE BEDPOST,
AND IF YOU'RE A MARRIED GUY,
THAT'S DANGEROUS.
SO LET'S GO CRUISIN'
IN OUR BOAT BED --
OR BED --
OKAY, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M GONNA CALL IT.
BUT I DO KNOW, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[ MOTOR RUMBLING ]
[ MOTOR SPUTTERING ]
OKAY, YOU MAY NOT WANNA
PUT A MATTRESS,
YOU KNOW, THAT CLOSE
TO THE PROP.
AND DON'T LINK ALL THE
MATTRESSES TOGETHER TO INFLATE
BECAUSE THEY'RE STILL LINKED
TOGETHER TO DEFLATE.
OKAY, I THINK I MAY HAVE
A NAME FOR THIS THING,
BUT I'M GONNA WAIT UNTIL THE
CAMERA'S NOT RUNNING.
[ FOGHORN BLASTS ]
THE OTHER DAY MY WIFE SENT
ME OUT TO BUY A NEW
SHOWER CURTAIN.
BUT WHEN I GOT HOME
SHE TOLD ME IT WAS ALL WRONG.
HOW COULD A SHOWER CURTAIN
BE ALL WRONG?
OKAY, IF I BROUGHT HOME
A GAS POWERED WEED WHACKER
THAT WOULD BE --
IT'S LIKE THE TIME I BOUGHT
THE WRONG PAPER CLIPS,
THE WRONG TEA COZY,
OR THE WRONG THYROID MEDIC --
OKAY, THAT ONE...
OKAY, THAT WAS A MISTAKE.
BUT YOU SEE
WHERE I'M GOING HERE.
AND LATER I REALISED
IT'S ALL ABOUT EXPECTATIONS.
WOMEN ACTUALLY HAVE THEM.
WOMEN HAVE BEEN PLANNING THE
EXACT LOOK AND COLOUR SCHEME
OF THEIR LIVES
SINCE THEY WERE KIDS.
THERE ARE PLANS IN THEIR HEADS
THAT ARE MORE DETAILED
THAN THOSE SPACE FLIGHT
SIMULATORS NASA USES.
WOMEN SPEND HOURS ON THEIR
BUYING DECISIONS.
MEN DON'T PLAN;
THEY HAGGLE.
IF THAT SHOWER CURTAIN
IS 5% OFF,
BECAUSE IT'S GOT PAINT
SPLATTERS ON IT
AND IT'S MADE OF ASBESTOS,
THAT'S OUR NEW SHOWER CURTAIN.
ANYWAY, MY WIFE RETURNED
THE "ALL-WRONG" CURTAIN
AND GOT THE
COMPLETELY PERFECT ONE.
AND YES, IT IS
SLIGHTLY BLUER.
OH, SURE, I COULD SIT AROUND
AND COMPLAIN THAT MY WIFE
IS PICKY,
BUT THE WAY I SEE IT,
SHE'S ALREADY SETTLED FOR A
PRETTY BIG TICKET ITEM
THAT DOESN'T LOOK ANYTHING
LIKE WHAT SHE HAD IN MIND.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU,
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ GRUNTING ]
OKAY, WE'VE GOT
THE GRAPES ALL STOMPED.
I KNEW WE'D USE THAT BATHTUB
FOR SOMETHING EVENTUALLY.
I TELL YOU, IT'S GONNA
BE A GREAT YEAR FOR WINE,
IN TERMS OF QUANTITY.
YEAH, WE MADE
1,000 GALLONS.
WELL, THERE'S 50 OF US.
AND IF IT'S ANY GOOD,
WELL, WE'LL MAKE MORE.
UNCLE RED! UNCLE RED!
LOOK, LOOK.
I FOUND THIS BOOK
ABOUT WINE MAKING.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT
MAYBE YOU MIGHT WANNA
TAKE A LOOK AT IT
OR PERHAPS READ IT
OR HAVE SOMEONE
READ IT TO YOU.
HAROLD, THERE ARE
TWO KINDS OF PEOPLE.
THE KIND THAT
MAKE THINGS HAPPEN,
AND THE KIND THAT READ
ABOUT THINGS THAT HAPPEN.
YES, IN TOMORROW'S
NEWSPAPER.
SO TO AVOID YET ANOTHER
EMBARRASSMENT,
IT MIGHT BEHOOVE YOU
TO EDUCATE YOURSELF
A LITTLE.
A LOT OF IRRITATING THINGS IN
THAT STATEMENT, HAROLD,
STARTING WITH
THE WORD "BEHOOVE."
UNCLE RED, DO YOU
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
BOTTLING WINE?
I KNOW YOU SHOULD PUT
A CORK IN IT, HAROLD.
I'M TELLING YOU,
NOT JUST ANY IDIOT
CAN MAKE WINE.
WELL, I'M GONNA
PROVE YOU WRONG.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
HAROLD, IT'S A
SIMPLE PROCESS.
YOU SQUASH THE GRAPES;
YOU THROW IN SOME SUGAR,
A LITTLE BIT OF YEAST;
YOU LET IT STAND IN A
JUG AT ROOM TEMPERATURE
WITH A CORK
IN THE TOP.
WHAT?!
NO! NO! NO!
NO, NOT A CORK.
NOT A CORK.
IT IS A
FERMENTATION TRAP.
SAME DIFF.
NO, NOT SAME DIFF!
BIG DIFF!
A FERMENTATION TRAP
ALLOWS THE GASSES
TO ESCAPE SAFELY.
WE SHOULD MAKE LODGE
MEMBERS WEAR THEM.
JUST RELAX,
HAROLD, OKAY.
IT'S NOT
ROCKET SCIENCE.
OKAY, MAYBE IT IS
Red: NEVER BEEN EXACTLY SURE
WHAT REPOINTING IS.
WE WERE REPLACING
THE WHOLE --
WELL, THAT'S AN INUKSHUK,
I KNOW THAT.
IT'S ACTUALLY
MORE SHOOK THAN INUK.
AND WALTER'S
TASTING THE MORTAR.
HOW IS IT?
NEED SALT?
NO, IT'S GOOD.
SO WE HAD BUILT A RAMP TO
BRING THE MORTAR UP
TO THE, UH --
UP TO THE CHIMNEY.
WE HAD TO REPLACE
THE WHOLE THING,
LINER AND EVERYTHING,
AND, UH, I WAS JUST
KNOCKING THE OLD BRICKS DOWN.
I DIDN'T SEE BILL THERE.
MAYBE I SHOULD'VE LOOKED.
SORRY. SORRY.
BUT BRINGING THE UNIT UP
WAS PRETTY HEAVY,
SO I LET WALTER
DO IT ON HIS OWN.
AND UH -- OH!
OKAY, MAYBE THAT'S
REPOINTING, I DUNNO.
ANYWAY, WE GET THE
BRICKS UP THERE,
AND I'M STILL TAKING THE OLD
LINER OUT AND SO FORTH.
BILL'S COMING UP THE --
SORRY, DIDN'T
SEE YOU THERE.
THEN THE LINER
IS THESE TUBES --
UNFORTUNATELY
THEY GOT ROLLING,
AND SUDDENLY YOU
GOT SUPER MARIO BROTHERS.
PRETTY GOOD -- OH, YOU
MADE IT TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
NOW, BILL HAD HIS
TROWEL IN HIS PANTS.
DON'T ASK.
AND -- BUT IT BROKE OFF.
SO HE JUST GRABS
WALTER'S TROWEL.
WALTER'S NOT
HAPPY WITH THAT,
SO HE TRIES
TO GRAB IT BACK
AND THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW
HE'S COVERED IN MORTAR,
AND BILL FINDS THAT
FUNNY FOR A SECOND.
[ chuckles ]
AND I FIND THAT
FUNNY FOR A SECOND.
WELL, IT SPIRALS
DOWNHILL FROM THERE,
AND EVENTUALLY
RIGHT DOWN THE RAMP.
THIS IS -- I DON'T RECOMMEND
YOU TRY THIS AT HOME --
OR ANYBODY'S HOME REALLY.
HE GETS DOWN, AND HE THOUGHT
HE COULD GRAB THE --
BUT THERE'S THE CEMENT
AND THE WATER.
THEN WE THOUGHT IF WE THREW
THE SKID IT WOULD BREAK --
THE BRAKE STOPPED
PART OF HIT.
SO WE COME DOWN TO
MAKE SURE WALTER'S OKAY,
AND NOT ONLY IS HE OKAY,
HE'S -- WHERE'S HE GOING?
HEY, HEY, WAIT A SECOND!
IT SHOULD BE OUR TURN!
[ APPLAUSE ]
THERE HAVE BEEN A LOT OF
DISTURBING TRENDS OVER
THE YEARS,
FROM FOUR-CYLINDER CARS
TO VEGETARIAN PIZZA.
BUT ONE OF THE WORST HAS GOTTA
BE "ONE SIZE FITS ALL."
ANYONE WHO BELIEVES THAT HAS
NEVER SEEN WRESTLING...
OR WRESTLING FANS.
ONE SIZE FITS ALL IS REALLY
THE MANUFACTURER SAYING,
ONE SIZE SUITS US.
EVEN WITH ICE CUBES.
THEY'RE TOO BIG
FOR THE SISSY DRINKS,
OKAY FOR YOUR REGULAR,
BUT WAY TOO SMALL TO GET
THE JOB DONE ON A
MAN-SIZED THIRST
OR A
WRESTLING-FAN-SIZED THIRST.
SEE, THE PROBLEM IS
THE ICE CUBE TRAY.
THE COMPARTMENTS ARE
ALL STANDARDIZED.
ONE SIZE FITS ALL.
THAT'S WHY I DON'T
USE ICE CUBE TRAYS,
NOT WHEN I HAVE
ANOTHER KIND OF TRAY
THAT HAS PLENTY OF DIFFERENT
SIZED COMPARTMENTS.
CAN YOU SAY TACKLE BOX?
[ CHUCKLING ]
NOW I HAVE ICE
FOR ANY SIZE DRINK
OR ANY SIZE BRUISE.
[ CHUCKLING ]
YEAH, THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
SEE, KIDS, YOU CAN
LOOK COOL AND BE COOL
AT THE SAME TIME.
OH! OW! OW!
WELL, WE'RE ALL SET FOR THE
FIRST TASTING OF OUR
HOMEMADE WINE.
THREW IN SOME
CHARCOAL BRIQUETTES
AND SOME
POSSUM LAKE WATER.
DON'T KNOW IF IT'S A
"CARBONNAY" OR "BEAUJOLAKE."
UNCLE RED, I MADE
YOU A SURPRISE.
OH, WHAT'S THAT?
I MADE YOU A SIGN.
OH, HAROLD,
I LIKE THAT.
AND I USED
MAGNETIC LETTERS.
THAT WAY WE CAN REUSE IT WHEN
YOU GO OUT OF BUSINESS.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
I THINK $2.50 A BOTTLE
IS A LITTLE LOW.
WELL, LET'S WAIT TILL
SOMEBODY TASTES IT.
YOU WANTED
TO SEE ME, RED?
OH, YEAH, YEAH,
DALTON, GREAT.
WE NEED YOU TO
TEST OUR WINE,
BECAUSE YOU'RE
THE ONLY GUY WITH
MEDICAL INSURANCE.
OFFER HIM A PIECE
OF CHEESE THERE,
HAROLD.
WINE AND CHEESE,
VERY POPULAR WITH
OUR TARGET DEMOGRAPHIC.
YOU WANT ME TO SNIFF
THE CORK THERE, RED?
NAH, IT DISSOLVED
FOR SOME REASON.
IS THIS RED OR
WHITE WINE?
I DUNNO.
KIND OF A BLUE.
YOU KNOW, IT LOOKS
A LITTLE CLOUDY.
YEAH, IT'S SUPPOSED
TO CLEAR UP THIS
AFTERNOON.
IS IT GOOD?
IS IT THE CHEESE?
THAT CAN'T
BE GOOD.
NO, NO, WINE TASTERS
ALWAYS SPIT OUT THE WINE.
NOT VIOLENTLY.
HEY, RED,
LOOK AT THIS!
THE WINE CLEANED THE GLASS.
HERE, HAROLD,
TRY IT ON YOUR
GLASSES.
TAKE 'EM OFF FIRST!
NO, DON'T IT IN YOUR EYE!
OKAY!
HOLY MAN!
THIS IS AMAZING.
YOU HAVE A BEARD?
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW WHAT WE NEED?
A LITTLE MARKETING
EXPERTISE.
JUST BECAUSE WE CAN'T
SELL IT AS WINE
DOESN'T MEAN WE
CAN'T SELL IT.
I'M AHEAD OF YOU,
UNCLE RED.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GUYS
GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN
WITH THE GOOD NEWS.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I'M HOPING YOU'RE GONNA BE
IN A ROMANTIC MOOD
FOR A ROMANTIC EVENING.
YOU PUT OUT THE CANDLES,
I'LL SUPPLY THE WINE,
AND WE'LL CLEAN ALL
THE MIRRORS IN THE BEDROOM.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR
STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
OKAY, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
AFTER CAREFUL CONSIDERATION
AND ONE MOUTHFUL,
WE'VE DECIDED TO MARKET
OUR WINE AS WINDOW WASHER.
SO WE'LL HAVE A LOT
FEWER DRUNK DRIVERS
AND THEY'LL HAVE
CLEAN WINDSHIELDS.