[quirky upbeat music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> IF YOU GO OUT IN THE WOODS
TONIGHT, YOU'RE IN FOR A BIG
SURPRISE.
IF YOU GO OUT IN THE WOODS
TONIGHT, YOU WON'T BELIEVE
YOUR EYES, BECAUSE YOU'LL SEE
THE RED GREEN SHOW,
STARRING CANADA'S FAVORITE
OUTDOORSMAN, RED GREEN,
OBVIOUSLY.
AND NOW HERE'S THE HOST
AND, BY HAPPY CIRCUMSTANCE,
WELL, YOU KNOW, AT LEAST FOR ME,
MY UNCLE.
AND HERE HE IS, RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH, HAROLD.
THANK YOU.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
WE GOT A REAL GOOD SHOW
FOR YOU TONIGHT--
NOT LIKE LAST WEEK'S SHOW.
I'M NOT BLAMING ANYONE.
>> THAT WASN'T MY FAULT!
>> THIS IS HAROLD.
HE'S PRODUCER AND DIRECTOR
OF THE SHOW.
>> WHICH MEANS
I DO A LOT OF THIS.
[keys clacking]
>> THAT'S IN LIEU OF CONTENT.
>> UNCLE RED, I DON'T THINK
YOU SHOULD BLAME ME FOR WHAT
HAPPENED.
>> WELL, HAROLD, YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO DECIDED IT WOULD BE FUN
AND OUTDOORSY TO HAVE A TRAINED
ELEPHANT ON THE SHOW.
FOLKS, THAT ELEPHANT
WAS NOT TRAINED.
>> THE LODGE LOOKS GOOD AS NEW.
>> HOW ABOUT THE SMELL, HAROLD?
WHEN DOES THAT GO AWAY?
>> I THINK WE SHOULD DISCUSS
SOMETHING ELSE.
LET'S GO TO ANOTHER SEGMENT.
DO AN INTRO.
GO.
>> HERE'S SOMETHING ELSE THAT
HAROLD IS RESPONSIBLE FOR.
LET'S SEE HOW IT SMELLS.
>> ONE MISTAKE, ONE LITTLE
MISTAKE.
>> THERE WAS MORE THAN ONE,
HAROLD, AND THEY WEREN'T LITTLE.
[strums acoustic guitar]
IN THE COOL OF THE EVENING
WHEN THE SUN GOES DOWN
THAT'S WHEN A BUNCH OF US
CAN BE FOUND
DOWN BY THE CAMPFIRE
LIKE SO MANY ELVES
SITTING HERE, STANDING THERE
SCRATCHING OURSELVES
SCRATCHING OURSELVES!
ALONE OR ALL IN A BUNCH
SCRATCHING OURSELVES
BE SURE AND WASH YOUR HANDS
BEFORE LUNCH
THIS WEEK IN THE HANDYMAN
CORNER, WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW TO SOLVE THE OIL CRISIS.
A GOOD START IS TO GO
WITH A LIGHTWEIGHT VEHICLE
SUCH AS THIS ONE MADE ENTIRELY
OF WOOD, SO SHE'S NOT GONNA
RUST OUT ON YOU.
AND IT'S LIGHTWEIGHT, PRACTICAL,
SIMPLE--IT'S EASY TO PARK,
EXCELLENT VISIBILITY.
PLUS IT ONLY TAKES ONE PERSON,
WHICH SHOULD SAVE
A FEW MARRIAGES.
WITH THIS UNIT, YOU STEER IT
WITH YOUR FEET, WHICH LEAVES
YOUR HANDS FREE TO USE AS
BRAKES.
NOW, OF COURSE, THE NEXT STEP
ON THIS ONE WAS TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT KIND OF A FUEL-EFFICIENT
ENGINE I COULD USE ON THIS UNIT,
AND MY FIRST THOUGHT WAS THE
JETEX CUBES, THOSE LITTLE CUBES.
I USED TO USE THEM ON MY MODEL
CARS AND MY MODEL BOATS
AND WHAT HAVE YOU, AND--
BUT I PHONED THE JETEX PEOPLE,
AND THEY WOULDN'T SELL IT TO ME
IN A 200-POUND BLOCK.
SO I HAD TO COME UP WITH
THE NEXT BEST THING...
A FIRE EXTINGUISHER.
SO WHAT I DO HERE IS,
I CAN SQUEEZE THE TRIGGER;
THAT FIRES THE EXTINGUISHER,
AND I'M HOLDING THE NOZZLE
OUT THE BACK, AND AWAY I GO.
I SHOULD BE ABLE TO HIT 30 OR 40
MILE AN HOUR ON A FLAT ROAD,
PUTTING OUT FIRES AS I GO.
BUT AS THEY SAY, THE PROOF IS
IN THE PUDDING; IT'S USUALLY
WRITTEN ON THE LABEL.
SO LET'S GIVE HER A TRY.
[hissing]
[laughter]
WELL, EITHER I'M GONNA HAVE
TO LOSE SOME WEIGHT,
OR WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO UP
THE HORSEPOWER OF THE ENGINE.
SO WHAT I'VE DONE IS, I'VE
ATTACHED FOUR FIRE EXTINGUISHERS
TO THE UNIT, AND I'VE USED
THE HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON HERE,
DUCT TAPE, TO POSITION
EVERYTHING, AND I'VE PUT A SCARF
ON AS WELL BECAUSE THIS CO2 GETS
PRETTY COLD, AND I WOULDN'T WANT
TO BE DRIVING DOWN THE HIGHWAY
70, 80 MILE AN HOUR WITH
A FROZEN HEAD.
ANYWAY, I THINK WE'RE ALL SET.
AND I THINK I'LL BE SAYING
GOOD-BYE NOW JUST IN CASE.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME, REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[exhales]
THREE, TWO, ONE.
[hissing]
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE
OF THE RED GREEN SHOW,
UNLESS, OF COURSE, HAROLD
HAS BOOKED ANOTHER RAMPAGING
ELEPHANT THIS WEEK.
>> I'LL HAVE TO CHECK.
KIDDING.
>> "IT IS WINTER.
WHAT IS THAT BLOWING SOUND,
BLOWING LONG AND HARD
FOR MONTHS ON END?
IS IT THE CRUEL NORTH WIND?
NO, IT'S YOUR KID'S NOSE."
ANYWAY, AS I WAS SAYING,
IF YOU MISSED LAST WEEK'S SHOW,
WELL, YOU'RE A VERY
FORTUNATE PERSON.
HAD THAT ELEPHANT ON.
YEAH, THAT WAS FUN, WASN'T IT?
I MEAN, MIND YOU, WE WERE
PLANNING TO RENOVATE THE LODGE
ANYWAY; WE JUST DIDN'T FIGURE
WE'D HAVE TO REBUILD IT
FROM THE GROUND UP.
THIS SHOW IS ABOUT LIFE
HERE AT THE LODGE,
YOU KNOW, WITH OUR REGULAR
GUESTS AND WHAT HAVE YOU.
AND HOW WE EVER ENDED UP
BLINDFOLDED AND WALKING
AN ELEPHANT IS BEYOND ME.
>> IT WAS A SEEING-EYE ELEPHANT.
>> I'M SORRY.
I MISSED THAT.
>> A SEEING-EYE ELEPHANT,
LIKE A SEEING-EYE DOG
FOR BLIND PEOPLE,
ONLY, THIS WAS A SEEING-EYE
ELEPHANT.
HE'S THE ONLY ONE IN
THE WHOLE WIDE WORLD.
HE'S AN ENDANGERED SPECIES.
>> YOU SHOULD TALK.
>> LET'S GO TO ANOTHER CLIP.
TV VIEWERS DON'T LIKE TO WATCH
PEOPLE TALKING.
THEY LIKE CLIPS
AND MULTIPLE IMAGES
AND THINGS LIKE THAT.
INTRODUCE THE NEXT SEGMENT,
UNCLE RED.
>> ALL RIGHT, HERE'S ONE OF MY
FAVORITE GUESTS ON THE SHOW.
HE'S NOT GRAY, HE DOESN'T HAVE
A TRUNK, AND HE KNOWS WHAT
A BATHROOM IS FOR.
>> YOU'LL NEVER FORGIVE ME,
WILL YOU?
>> I'LL FORGIVE YOU WHEN
THE SMELL DISAPPEARS.
>> YOU'LL NEVER FORGIVE ME,
WILL YOU?
>> WELL, I'M OUT HERE ON
LOCATION AGAIN WITH DOUGIE
FRANKLIN--MY GOOD BUDDY--AND HIS
MONSTER TRUCK, AND, DOUGIE, THIS
IS ONE BIG, BEAUTIFUL MACHINE.
>> WELL, I'LL TELL YOU, RED,
IT'S GOT TO BE BIG, YOU KNOW,
FOR COMPETITION.
IF YOU'RE GONNA CRUSH CARS,
YOU NEED A BIG TRUCK.
BUT IT'S A SPORT.
IT'S LIKE ANY OTHER SPORT,
LIKE TENNIS, LIKE JAI ALAI,
BASEBALL, DEMOLITION DERBIES.
YOU KNOW, I'M A FINELY TUNED
ATHLETE, AS IS MY MACHINE,
AND SHE'S GOT TO BE BIG.
AND YOU NEVER--THE THRILL
OF COMPETITION IS WONDERFUL,
YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, YOU'RE JUST WONDERING
HOW MANY CARS YOU'RE GONNA CRUSH
ON A GIVEN DAY.
IT'S A FABULOUS FEELING.
IT'S VERY NOW.
IT'S VERY THE '90s, ACTUALLY.
>> YEAH, AND I THINK WE SHOULD
POINT OUT HERE, DOUGIE, THAT WE
ARE NOT TALKING ABOUT A BUNCH
OF LUNATICS TEARING AROUND
A SHOPPING MALL PARKING LOT
FLATTENING FAMILY SEDANS HERE.
>> OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU'D HAVE A HARD TIME GETTING
INSURANCE FOR THAT KIND OF
THING, RED, AND, YOU KNOW,
A LOT OF FAMILIES LEAVE THEIR
PETS IN THEIR VEHICLES WHEN
THEY GO IN TO SHOP.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
>> AND IT'S A SAD THING WHEN
YOU SEE A KITTY STUCK IN THE
BACK WINDOW OF ONE OF THEM
YUPPIE VOLVO WAGONS, YOU KNOW,
JUST SWEATING ON A HOT DAY.
>> YEAH.
>> WE DON'T WANT NONE OF THAT.
NOW, ALSO, IT'D BE VERY
DIFFICULT CHARGING ADMISSION
FOR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> YEAH, I CAN SEE THAT.
>> NOW, IT'S BECAUSE OF THESE--
THIS--I'M GLAD YOU BROUGHT
THIS POINT UP, RED,
BECAUSE THE INTERNATIONAL TRUCK
AND TRACTOR ASSOCIATION,
IN COOPERATION WITH YOUR
FIRE DEPARTMENT--AND I BELIEVE
THE SPCA WAS IN THERE--
THEY CAME UP WITH
A SET OF RULES.
>> WELL, THAT'S A GOOD IDEA,
SURE, YEAH.
>> I GOT A COPY OF IT...
>> THAT MAKES SENSE.
>> RIGHT HERE.
>> YOU GOT THE RULES RIGHT HERE.
>> I DO.
THERE THEY ARE THERE.
NOW...
>> THAT'S IT, DOUG?
>> WELL, YEAH.
>> THESE ARE ALL THE RULES?
>> WELL, YEAH, AND THEN ON
THE BACK THERE, WE GOT MISS
TRUCK AND TRACTOR PULL 1991
WITH AN ENTIRE LIST OF ALL
THE EVENTS FOR THE YEAR.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YEP, THERE'S A LOT OF EVENTS.
>> DOESN'T SEEM LIKE MANY RULES.
>> WELL, I MEAN, I DO HAVE
THE RULES MEMORIZED IF YOU WANT
TO GO INTO THIS INTERVIEW
A LITTLE MORE IN DEPTH.
WOULD YOU CARE TO DO THAT?
>> ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL,
RULE NUMBER ONE...
RED, THERE'S YOUR RULE
NUMBER ONE.
EVERYBODY IN THIS SPORT--
GOT TO WEAR A HELMET.
WE'RE TALKING THE DRIVERS.
WE'RE TALKING THE MECHANICS.
AND ACTUALLY, WE DISTRIBUTE
HELMETS TO THE AUDIENCE.
THE ENTIRE AUDIENCE ARE
ALL COMPLETELY HELMETED.
NOW, WE ALSO ENCOURAGE THE USE
OF HELMETS AT HOME FOR
THE VIEWERS AS WELL.
NOW, RULE NUMBER TWO,
A VERY IMPORTANT RULE, ACTUALLY,
IS: NO RUNNING OVER THE PEOPLE
IN THE AUDIENCE.
IF YOU ABUSE THAT RULE,
THEN PEOPLE WILL QUIT COMING.
>> ACTUALLY, THAT SOUNDS KIND
OF VAGUE, YOU KNOW.
THAT'S MORE OF A GUIDELINE
TO ME.
>> WELL, RED, IT HAS TO BE ABLE
TO ENCOMPASS MONSTER TRUCKS.
THEY'RE NOT EXACT TOOLS IN
THE SENSE OF THAT MEANING,
BECAUSE WHEN ONE OF THESE BABIES
GOES OVER A BIG LINE OF 1964
STRATO CHIEFS, YOU NEVER KNOW
HOW ONE OF THESE GUYS
IS GONNA FALL.
SHE COULD TILT OFF TO THE SIDE.
>> SURE. YEAH.
>> SHE COULD FLIP RIGHT OVER,
WHICH IS WHY YOU GOT THESE
SUCKERS HERE OVER YOUR HEAD.
>> YEAH.
>> AND--OR SHE COULD JUST, LIKE,
ROLL UP NEAR SOME PEOPLE AND
JUST BLOW UP INTO A MILLION
PIECES, AND I'LL TELL YOU, IF
SOMETHING LIKE THAT HAPPENED...
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'D BE MIGHTY GLAD YOU WAS
WEARING YOUR HELMET, YEAH.
>> OH, YEAH.
SO YOU JUST HAVE THE TWO RULES?
>> OH, NO, THERE'S RULE NUMBER
THREE, ACTUALLY, WHICH IS,
IF YOU KILL ANYBODY, YOU GOT TO
STICK AROUND UNTIL THE POLICE
SHOW UP.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> AND THERE'S A BIG STORY
BEHIND THAT ONE, I'LL TELL YOU,
RED.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH.
>> BUT, YOU KNOW, IF I COULD BE
SERIOUS JUST FOR A MINUTE,
RED, SINCE I'VE BEEN IN THIS
SPORT, I HAVE MET PROBABLY
SOME OF THE FINEST HUMAN BEINGS
I'VE EVER COME ACROSS, AND SOME
OF THEIR TRUCKS ARE EVEN BETTER.
[laughter]
YEAH.
>> I THINK YOU--MAYBE YOU
MONSTER TRUCKERS HAVE GOT IT
MADE, EH, DOUG?
>> I'LL TELL YOU, RIGHT OFF
THE BAT, RED, I CAN'T THINK OF
ANYTHING THAT WOULD BE MORE FUN.
>> WELL, YOU'RE A BACHELOR,
AREN'T YOU, DOUG?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, WELL, THAT'S DOUGIE
FRANKLIN AND HIS MONSTER TRUCK,
PROVING THAT SIZE DOES MATTER
TO SOME GUYS ANYWAY.
>> WHAT ABOUT THAT BACHELOR
BUSINESS?
>> NO, NO.
[lively strumming]
>> WHOO-OOH!
>> I REMEMBER THE DAY
WHEN THE RAILROAD WAS KING
THE BIG WHEELS MAY ROLL
AND THUNDER
WE WERE TREATED LIKE FREIGHT
ARRIVING SEVEN HOURS LATE
I'M PERSONALLY GLAD
THEY'RE ALL GOING UNDER
>> OH, UNCLE RED, HOW EXCELLENT.
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO TELL THE
VIEWERS THAT YOU WERE GONNA
ANSWER THEIR MAIL IN YOUR OWN
INIMITABLE WAY.
>> MY WHAT?
>> YOUR OWN INIMITABLE WAY.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
YOU'VE NEVER HEARD OF THE WORD
INIMITABLE?
YOU NEVER HEARD THAT BEFORE?
>> WELL, I'VE HEARD IT BEFORE.
I JUST NEVER KNEW WHAT IT MEANT.
>> WEREN'T YOU AT ALL CURIOUS
WHAT IT MEANT?
DIDN'T YOU THINK TO GO LOOK IT
UP IN A DICTIONARY?
>> YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT IT MEANS
EITHER, DO YOU?
>> YES, I DO.
I LOOKED IT UP.
IT MEANS...
RECHERCHE.
OKAY?
OUR FIRST LETTER TODAY ASKS FOR
SOME ADVICE FROM YOU, UNCLE RED.
IT SAYS, "DEAR RED, I'M IN
THE MARKET FOR A NEW CAR--
OR NEW TO ME.
I LIKE USED CARS.
I GUESS I'M A BIT OF
A 'FISHY AUTO.'"
"FISHY AUTO"?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> IT MEANS YOU CAN'T AFFORD
A NEW CAR.
>> OH, WELL, HOW RECHERCHE.
"ANY TIPS FOR THE POTENTIAL
CAR BUYER?"
>> ALL RIGHT, THAT'S A GOOD ONE,
HAROLD.
I THINK WHEN YOU'RE BUYING
A USED CAR, INTIMIDATION IS
THE KEY.
DON'T JUST WALK AROUND THE CAR
KICKING THE TIRES, OKAY?
KICK THE FENDERS.
KICK THE DOOR PANELS.
KICK THE HEADLIGHTS IN.
KICK THE DASHBOARD--
>> WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING WHEN
YOU DO THAT?
>> WELL, YOU'RE TRYING TO GET
THE COST OF THE CAR DOWN,
AND A CAR WITH KICK MARKS ALL
OVER IT HAS GOT TO BE
A LOWER PRICE.
>> OH, SO I GUESS WE CAN ASSUME,
THEN, THE PROPER FOOTWEAR
IS REQUIRED.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AND I'D SAY THAT PROPER FOOTWEAR
IS THE KEY, AS THE
INTIMIDATION IS.
AND ANOTHER THING IS, YOU WANT
TO ASK 'EM IF YOU CAN TAKE IT
FOR A TEST-DRIVE.
IF THEY SAY NO, THEN I'D
WONDER ABOUT THAT.
AND THEY HAVE TRICKS, HAROLD.
I KNOW WHEN I BOUGHT MY TRUCK,
THEY HAD SCOTCH-TAPED A COUPLE
OF EXTRA SPARK PLUGS ONTO
THE ENGINE TO TRY TO CONVINCE ME
THAT THE V6 WAS A V8.
I CAUGHT ON TO IT.
>> OH, YEAH?
HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
>> WELL, THEY FELL OFF WHEN I
KICKED THE ENGINE.
>> OH, SO KICKING IS IMPORTANT?
>> WELL, IT SHOWS THAT YOU KNOW
CARS, YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, EVEN KICK THE SALESMAN
IF YOU HAVE TO.
>> ON, NO, NO, NO.
WAIT A SECOND, UNCLE RED.
I THINK YOU'VE GONE OVER THE TOP
ON THAT ONE.
WE DO NOT WANT TO ADVOCATE
VIOLENCE.
>> WELL, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
THEN DON'T KICK THE SALESMAN.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW, BUT YOU MIGHT WANT
TO CHECK THE INSTRUMENT PANEL.
IF YOU LOOK AT THE ODOMETER
AND YOU SEE A BUNCH OF MARKS
FROM A CLAW HAMMER AND IT'S
A TEN-YEAR-OLD CAR WITH, SAY,
19 MILES ON IT,
I'D QUESTION THAT.
>> YEAH, THAT'S REALLY GOOD
ADVICE.
THAT'S SOMETHING TO REMEMBER.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, UNCLE RED, I WAS--
IS, LIKE, THERE, LIKE, A GOOD
TIME OR A BAD TIME TO BUY A CAR?
>> YEAH, NEVER BUY A CAR AT
3:00 IN THE MORNING.
>> ALL RIGHT, THAT'S--
AND HOW ABOUT, LIKE,
NORTH AMERICAN CARS
VERSUS DOMESTIC CARS?
NO, I MEAN, NO--
[chuckles]
I MEAN, LIKE JAPANESE CARS
VERSUS IMPORTED--
NO, THAT'S NOT RIGHT EITHER.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
I UNDERSTAND.
I GOT IT.
WITH THE JAPANESE CARS, YOU GET
MORE FEATURES, BUT WITH THE
AMERICAN CARS, YOU GET MORE
METAL.
AND WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
YOU KNOW, WE'RE ALL GONNA HAVE
HEAD-ON COLLISIONS NOW AND THEN,
SO YOU'RE BETTER TO GIVE UP
THE POWER SUNROOF AND GO WITH
A LITTLE MORE MOMENTUM.
>> I HOPE THAT ANSWERS ALL OUR
VIEWER'S QUESTIONS.
>> YEAH, AND DON'T FORGET TO
KICK EVERYTHING.
WE HAVE OUR OUTDOOR EXPERT,
BILL, WITH US THIS WEEK ON
A--OH!
GONNA TEACH US ABOUT--I THINK
HE'S JUST FOOLING AROUND THERE.
GONNA TEACH US ABOUT CANOEING
AND THE VARIOUS TECHNIQUES TO
USE FOR THE BEGINNING CANOER.
'CAUSE YOU KNOW IN THESE DAYS,
WHEN THE CAST--COST OF GAS
AND EVERY--AND THE CAST OF GOSS
AND ALL THAT STUFF IS SO HIGH--
NOW, THIS IS A PADDLE
MEASUREMENT TECHNIQUE.
YOU WANT TO--YOU WANT THE PADDLE
TO COME UP TO ABOUT YOUR CHIN.
SO ONE'S TOO SHORT,
AND ONE'S TOO TALL.
SO BILL COMES UP WITH A SOLUTION
TO THAT PROBLEM.
MAYBE NOT THE IDEAL SOLUTION
BUT A SOLUTION NONETHELESS.
AND THAT ONE WAS FINE ANYWAY.
SO ANYWAY, IT ALL WORKED OUT.
YOU KNOW, WE HAVE LOTS OF
PADDLES.
AND NOW HE'S GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW TO GET INTO A CANOE.
NOW, I THINK A LOT OF WHAT BILL
DOES IS, HE SHOWS YOU, YOU KNOW,
THE WRONG...
WRONG WAY TO DO THINGS.
I THINK HE KNEW THAT WAS COMING,
BUT HE'S OKAY.
NO PROBLEM.
AND THEN WHAT HE WANTS TO SHOW--
NOW HE'S SHOWING YOU HOW TO
GET IN FROM THE SIDE.
THAT WAS THE END SHOT.
THIS IS THE SIDE SHOT.
BUT HERE AGAIN, I DON'T--I THINK
BILL--YEAH, YEAH, I'M PRETTY
SURE HE MEANT TO DO THAT.
HE JUST LOOKED LIKE HE WAS
PANICKING.
THAT'S ALL THERE.
IT'S JUST ALL FOR EFFECT,
I THINK.
AND NOW BILL'S GONNA SHOW YOU
AN INTERESTING WAY TO GET IN,
WHICH IS THE RUNNING START,
KIND OF REMINISCENT OF
WILD BILL HICKOK, YOU KNOW.
AND THAT WAY, YOU'RE ON YOUR
WAY--UNFORTUNATELY, HE FORGOT
TO TAKE A PADDLE, BUT, YOU KNOW,
I'M THERE.
I CAN--WELL, I MEAN, I WAS--
YOU KNOW, I WAS DOING MY BEST.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT'S HARD TO
ESTIMATE 'CAUSE HE'S MOVING.
YOU KNOW, IT'S TOUGH.
AND I GOT A BIT CLOSER
WITH THIS ONE.
OH!
OH, MY GOSH.
ANYWAY, HE BRINGS THE CANOE
BACK IN, AND WE NOW HAVE A
WEEK'S SUPPLY OF DRINKING WATER.
AND WE'LL CLEAN THAT UP
LATER ON.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
SO NOW BILL'S GONNA SHOW US
THE VARIOUS PADDLING TECHNIQUES.
NOW, WHAT YOU WANT TO DO, YOU
STICK YOUR RIGHT ARM OUT THERE
AND THEN GRIP IT RIGHT
WHERE IT GETS FAT, YOU KNOW.
IT REMINDS ME OF A DATE I WAS
ON ONE TIME.
BUT ANYWAY, AND THEN PUT
THE OTHER HAND OVER THE END,
AND--NO, NO, NO, THERE'S
SOMETHING WRONG HERE.
THAT DOESN'T LOOK--NO, THAT
DOESN'T LOOK RIGHT EITHER.
OH...[muttering]
AND NOW HE'S JUST USING THE DOCK
TO SHOW YOU JUST A--
crack!
OH!
OH, MY GOSH.
WE GO--WE DO GO THROUGH A LOT
OF PADDLES IN A SEASON, BUT
EVENTUALLY, IT GETS TO THE POINT
WHERE THE STUDENT, YOU KNOW, HAS
TO HAVE HIS FIRST SOLO FLIGHT,
AND I WAS PRETTY EXCITED
ABOUT THIS, AND I THINK
I WAS DOING A HECK OF A JOB.
I DIDN'T HIT THE DOCK,
AND I GOT MOVING PRETTY GOOD
THERE, YOU KNOW.
AND I WAS QUITE PROUD.
OH! OH! OH! OH!
OH, OH...
YOU KNOW, IN RETROSPECT, I THINK
BILL SHOULD HAVE TAUGHT ME HOW
TO TURN THIS THING AROUND TOO.
OH, WELL, HE'S FINE.
"IT IS WINTER.
YOUR BREATH FORMS HUGE CLOUDS
THAT BILLOW OUT
AND BLOCK YOUR FACE.
HOT AIR, THICK AND SWIRLING.
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR EATING SKUNK."
EVERY WEEK WE HAVE HAROLD HERE
COME UP WITH A VIEWPOINT TO GIVE
YOU SOME INSIGHT ON WHAT THE
YOUNG PEOPLE OF TODAY ARE
THINKING ABOUT, AND, AH, IT'S
PROBABLY NOT THE WORST THING
YOU'LL EVER SEE ON TELEVISION.
>> OKAY, OKAY, PIXY STIX.
I REMEMBER ONE TIME WHEN I WAS
A LITTLE BOY, RIGHT, I READ IN
THE BACK OF A COMIC BOOK,
YOU COULD ORDER, LIKE,
ALL THESE PIXY STIX.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY ARE, RIGHT?
THEY'RE LIKE--OKAY, PIXY STIX
ARE LIKE STRAWS, RIGHT,
AND THEY'RE CLOSED AT BOTH ENDS,
BUT THEY'RE FILLED WITH,
LIKE, POWDERED SUGAR
AND FLAVOR CRYSTALS,
AND YOU JUST GO...[slurps]
YOU SUCK ALL THE POWDER OUT
OF THEM, RIGHT?
THEY'RE EXCELLENT.
THEY REALLY ARE.
THEY'RE REALLY GOOD.
AND I READ IN A BOOK THAT
YOU COULD ORDER, LIKE, 1,000 OF
THEM FOR 10 BUCKS.
GREAT DEAL, RIGHT?
SO I GET MY BEST FRIEND--
WELL, OKAY, I GET MY ONLY
FRIEND, LARRY GORMAN.
SO HIM AND I, WE GET TOGETHER,
RIGHT, AND WE FIGURE, "HEY, WHAT
A PERFECT CAUSE TO DEDICATE OUR
LIVES TO WHILE WAITING TO
MATURE," RIGHT?
SO WE DO THIS.
AND THEN WE SAVE ALL OUR MONEY,
AND WE SAID--WAIT, NO, WE HAD
MONEY.
WE JUST ORDERED THEM.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, WE JUST ORDERED THEM.
AND ABOUT A MONTH LATER, WE GOT
THIS BOX FROM RACINE, WISCONSIN.
WE OPEN IT UP--
1,000 PIXY STIX!
UGH!
BONUS DAY OR WHAT, RIGHT?
SO WE START EATING ALL THESE
THINGS.
WE'RE SUCKING ALL THE SUGAR
OUT OF THEM.
LIKE, OUR FACES ARE ALL PUCKERED
AND EVERYTHING.
IT WAS GREAT.
WE KEPT DOING THIS UNTIL I GOT
SICK, AND HE HYPERVENTILATED AN
ENTIRE LUNG OF POWDERED SUGAR.
WHAT A GREAT DAY.
WELL, THERE'S NO REAL POINT
TO THE STORY.
I JUST WANTED TO RELATE THAT
TO YOU.
I PROBABLY SHOULD HAVE SUNG
OR SOMETHING, EH?
>> DUMBO AND I WILL BE
RIGHT BACK.
>> HE ONLY CALLS ME THAT
'CAUSE I WORK FOR PEANUTS.
[chuckles]
LIGHTEN UP.
>> YOU KNOW, I GOT THE OUTBOARD
OVERHAULED THE OTHER DAY,
AND WHEN I WENT TO PICK IT UP,
A FELLA--A YOUNG FELLA THERE
HAD AN EARRING.
>> OH, YEAH, I KNOW HIM.
>> KIND OF A LITTLE STUD
OR A JEWEL OR SOMETHING.
NO, I DON'T MEAN HIM;
I MEAN THE EARRING.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT IS IT WITH THAT?
>> THAT'S FASHION.
THAT'S THE BEST.
>> IS THAT A SEXUAL ORIENTATION
THING OR...
>> I THINK NOT.
IT JUST SAYS YOU'RE REALLY COOL
AND ABOVE STEREOTYPING.
IT'S WONDERFUL.
PIRATES USED TO WEAR THEM,
AND WOULD YOU CONFRONT A PIRATE
IN A DARK ALLEY?
>> PIRATES HAD EARRINGS?
>> OH, YES, SOME OF THEM,
BUT MOST OF THEM WERE CLIP-ONS,
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU
HAVE TO GO OUT ON THE WEEKEND,
YOU DON'T WANT EVERYBODY TO SEE
THE HOLE IN YOUR EAR.
>> WELL, THERE--THAT'S IT, THEN.
LIKE, WHAT DO YOU DO, YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU HAVE TO GO TO A FAMILY
EVENT LIKE A FUNERAL OR
SOMETHING?
>> WELL, YOU CAN PUT
A FANCY ONE IN.
YOU WOULDN'T WEAR JUST, LIKE,
ANYTHING.
YOU'D HAVE TO WEAR LIKE
DIAMONDS TO GO WITH A SUIT
OR A PEARL OR--
>> YOU MEAN YOU'RE TELLING ME
THAT AN EARRING IS NOT
A FEMALE, UH...
>> NOT NECESSARILY, NO.
I WAS THINKING OF GETTING ONE.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH, I WAS PLAYING WITH
YOUR STUD SETTER THE OTHER DAY.
AND I PIERCED MY FINGER,
AND I THOUGHT, "WELL, WOULDN'T
THAT LOOK SILLY, AN EARRING ON
MY FINGER?"
>> WELL, YOU SURE DON'T NEED
ANOTHER HOLE IN YOUR HEAD.
WELL, ANYWAY, I REALLY HATE TO
DRAG FAMILY ARGUMENTS INTO MY
TELEVISION SHOW, BUT I'M SORRY;
WE JUST HAVE SOMEBODY HERE WHO
HAS TO BE TAUGHT A LESSON.
HAROLD, COME ON OVER HERE.
NOW, HAROLD, I KNOW THAT YOU
THINK I'M MAKING A REAL BIG
TO-DO OUT OF THIS ELEPHANT THING
AND THAT YOU THINK I'M MEAN
AND I'M JUST DOING IT TO
RIDICULE YOU AND MAKE YOU CRY ON
TELEVISION, THAT KIND OF THING.
AND I KNOW YOU THINK I SHOULD
JUST LIGHTEN UP, AND MAYBE--
I MEAN, MAYBE WHAT YOU DID
WRONG--AND BELIEVE ME, THERE WAS
PLENTY OF IT--MAYBE YOU THOUGHT
YOU WERE DOING THE BEST THING
FOR THE SHOW.
MAYBE WHAT YOU DID WAS OUT OF
MAYBE CARING ABOUT YOUR WORK.
AND I KNOW THAT YOU LIKE ME.
I KNOW YOU'RE VERY FOND OF ME,
HAROLD, AND I KNOW THAT YOU
LOOK UP TO ME, AND YOU REALLY
RESPECT MY JUDGMENT.
SO I'VE DECIDED TO KIND OF
JUST LET IT GO AS A WARNING
AT THIS POINT, HAROLD.
BUT I WANT YOU TO REMEMBER
WHAT HAPPENED HERE.
AND FROM NOW ON, I WANT YOU TO
COME TO ME BEFORE YOU MAKE
THESE BIG DECISIONS, ALL RIGHT?
>> I WILL.
YEAH, THANKS VERY MUCH,
UNCLE RED.
>> OKAY, NOW, I'M ONLY DOING
THIS BECAUSE YOU PROMISED ME
THAT YOU WEREN'T THE ONES WHO
GAVE THE LAXATIVES TO
THE ELEPHANT, RIGHT?
>> THAT'S RIGHT!
THAT'S RIGHT!
WASN'T ME.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO IF MY WIFE IS
WATCHING, THANK YOU FOR TAPING
THE SHOW TONIGHT, AND WHEN
I COME HOME, I'M GONNA STAY UP
A BIT LATE, AND I'M GONNA WATCH
THIS PART BACK.
AND IF I SEE HAROLD LAUGHING
BEHIND ME, HE IS DEAD MEAT.
SO ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND WHAT
IS PROBABLY HAROLD'S LAST SHOW
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE AT
THE LODGE, UNTIL NEXT TIME,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.