EVERYONE HAS THEIR
OWN SPECIAL THING
THAT MAKE IT CHRISTMAS.
FOR SOME IT'S
THE SPIRIT OF GIVING
AND SHARING A SPECIAL
TIME WITH LOVED ONES.
FOR ME IT'S THE TINSEL.
AND I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING,
THE TINSEL MANUFACTURERS
ARE AWARE OF GUYS LIKE ME.
THEY MAKE US PAY
THROUGH THE NOSE.
WELL, THAT DOESN'T STRIKE
ME AS A VERY CHRISTMASY
ATTITUDE.
SO I'VE COME UP WITH A WAY TO
SHAFT THOSE GUYS BIG TIME.
BORROW A PAPER
SHREDDER FROM WORK.
YOU KNOW, I FIND
THE CHRISTMAS PARTY
IS A GREAT TIME TO SNEAK
STUFF OUT THE BACK DOOR --
YOU KNOW, OFFICE SUPPLIES
OR COMPUTERS OR WHATEVER.
HEY, IT'S CHRISTMAS, HUH?
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY,
THE LORD HELPS THOSE
WHO HELP THEMSELVES.
BUT WE'RE NOT GONNA
SHRED PAPER, OH, NO!
WE'RE GOING TO SHRED A BUNCH
OF THESE FOIL POTATO
CHIP BAGS.
MAKE SURE THEY'RE
COMPLETELY EMPTY FIRST,
BUT IF YOU'RE LIKE ME,
AND I'M PRETTY SURE YOU ARE,
THAT SHOULDN'T
BE A PROBLEM.
ALL RIGHT, FIRST JUST
TURN ON YOUR PAPER SHREDDER,
AND IT'S BEGINNING TO
LOOK A LOT LIKE CHRISTMAS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
THAT'S GREAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT...
I FEEL THE SAME WAY MYSELF.
WE'RE ALL PRETTY EXCITED
HERE AT THE LODGE TOO,
BECAUSE TODAY IS
OUR SANTA CLAUS PARADE,
AND MEN JUST LOVE
BEING IN PARADES.
YOU KNOW, YOU GET TO
DRIVE A WEIRD VEHICLE;
YOU'RE THE CENTRE
OF ATTENTION;
AND YOU NEVER HAVE TO STOP
AND ASK FOR DIRECTIONS.
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME, RED?
[ APPLAUSE ]
YEAH, WE GOT THE SLEIGH
ALL READY TO GO.
NOW WE JUST NEED YOU TO
RUSTLE UP SOME REINDEER
TO PULL IT.
SO HOW MANY DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED?
WELL, WHO GETS TO
BE SANTA THIS YEAR?
MOOSE THOMPSON.
OH, MOOSE IS A
PRETTY WIDE LOAD.
YEAH, WE'LL NEED
ABOUT 20 REINDEER.
YEAH, WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE HIDE MOOSE FROM
THE REINDEER,
BECAUSE, MAN, THEY'RE,
LIKE, SKITTISH, YOU KNOW.
WELL, YOU WOULD KNOW, ED.
OKAY, I'LL BE BACK
IN AN HOUR WITH
THE REINDEER.
OH, AND I'LL NEED
ABOUT 100 GUYS
TO HELP ME GET 'EM OUT
OF THE BACK OF THE TRUCK.
A HUNDRED GUYS?
THAT'S A LITTLE
OVERKILL, ISN'T IT?
RED, IN THE ANIMAL
CONTROL BUSINESS,
THERE IS NO SUCH
THING AS OVERKILL!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WELL, I HEARD YOU
WANTED TO SEE ME.
NO, I DIDN'T.
NEVER SAID THAT.
NO? OH.
I JUST THOUGHT I COULD HELP
WITH THE PLANNING OF THE
PARADE OR SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE GOT IT COVERED.
OH.
WE'RE FINE.
OH, GOOD.
GOOD. GOOD.
YEP, WE'RE GOOD.
SO WHAT SORT OF THINGS
ARE SANTA THROWING
OUT TO THE KIDS?
WELL, HIS HAND.
HE'S GONNA WAVE.
NO, IT'S A PARADE!
SANTA HAS TO TOSS TREATS
OR SOMETHING OUT TO THE KIDS.
WELL, OKAY, WE'LL DIG UP
SOME OLD FISHING LURES.
NO, I DON'T THINK SO, NO!
WELL, OKAY,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
GO SEE DALTON.
MAYBE HE'S GOT
SOMETHING IN HIS STORE
HE COULD GIVE YOU
TO THROW TO THE KIDS.
MR. HUMPHREY?
I SURE HOPE HE'S IN
THE CHRISTMAS SPIRIT.
OH, SURE HE
WILL BE.
JUST MAKE SURE YOU TELL
HIM IT'S A TAX WRITE-OFF.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TONIGHT'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FOR 150 BOTOX INJECTIONS.
THIS CHRISTMAS KISS
YOUR WRINKLES GOOD-BYE --
IF YOU CAN STILL
USE YOUR LIPS.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
EARS, DALTON.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON HUMPHREY
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, DALTON, THIS IS AN
OLD-FASHIONED WORD
FOR CHRISTMAS.
HUMBUG.
OKAY, THINK ABOUT THIS...
SOMETHING TIDE.
LEMON FRESH?
OKAY, OKAY, REMEMBER THAT BALD
GUY WHO WAS IN THE MOVIES?
HE WAS A REALLY
GREAT ACTOR.
ELMER FUDD.
OKAY, THIS IS A KIND
OF LOG THAT PEOPLE
USE AT CHRISTMAS.
CATALOGUE?
NO, THIS IS
SOMETHING PEOPLE BURN.
UH, MONEY.
YOU GUYS ARE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME.
WHY DO YOU HAVE SUCH
A NEGATIVE ATTITUDE
TOWARD THE FESTIVE
SEASON, DALTON?
WELL, GEE, YOU SHOULD COME BY
MY HOUSE CHRISTMAS MORNING.
THEN YOU'LL SEE.
THERE YOU GO!
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP
PART OF THE SHOW
WE CALL, IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING.
AND JOINING ME TONIGHT IS
EXPLOSIVES ENTHUSIAST
EDGAR MONTROSE.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
FOR US, EDGAR?
ONLY ONE TIME WITH
A PITCHFORK, RED.
NO, WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
FOR THE REPAIR SHOP?
OH, NOTHING TO REPAIR.
NO, I'M JUST LOOKING FOR
SOME ADVICE ON WHICH ONE
OF THESE GIFTS
I SHOULD GIVE MY
EIGHT-YEAR-OLD NEPHEW.
WELL,
THE STUFFED ANIMAL.
ON THE ONE HAND I COULD
GIVE HIM THIS BORING
STUFFED TOY.
YEAH, THAT'S THE ONE,
THE STUFFED ANIMAL.
OR I COULD GIVE
HIM THIS CUSTOMIZED
EDGAR K. B. MONTROSE
JACK-IN-THE-BOX.
ANY EXPLOSIVES INVOLVED
IN THERE, EDGAR?
HOPEFULLY.
AND WHAT KIND OF A MESSAGE
IS THAT SAYING TO THE
KIDS OUT THERE?
WELL, IT TEACHES THEM
THAT LIFE IS FULL OF
SURPRISES,
THAT YOU JUST CAN'T MAKE
YOUR PROBLEMS GO AWAY.
BUT YOU CAN MAKE ABANDONED
VEHICLES GO AWAY!
NO, EDGAR, GO WITH
THE STUFFED ANIMAL.
OH, ALL RIGHT, I'LL GIVE
HIM THE STUFFED ANIMAL.
BUT LET ME SHOW YOU
THE JACK-IN-THE-BOX.
(hesitates)
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
YOU LIKE
SURPRISES, RED?
NOT SINCE THAT TIME
I CHANGED A DIAPER, NO.
[ music box playing ]
I LOVE THIS.
[ music continues ]
NO! NO! NO!
[ APPLAUSE ]
MERRY CHRISTMAS, RED.
OH, MAN.
[ playing badly ]
YOU KNOW, EVERYBODY LIKES
MUSIC AROUND CHRISTMAS,
ESPECIALLY IF IT COMES
FROM SOMETHING QUAINT,
LIKE THIS OLD PIPE ORGAN.
KIND OF TAKES YOU
BACK TO THE OLDEN DAYS
WHEN YOUR ANCESTORS
WOULD MAYBE SING CAROLS
SITTING AROUND A COLD FIRE,
FREEZING THEIR BUTTS OFF.
BUT ONE THING THAT HASN'T
CHANGED OVER THE YEARS
IS THE TIRESOME JOB OF HANDING
OUT THE CHRISTMAS PRESENTS.
SO TODAY ON HANDYMAN CORNER
I'M GOING TO COMBINE THOSE
TWO FUNCTIONS
INTO A KIND OF A
YULETIDE GIFT-DISPENSING
PIPE ORGAN THING,
BECAUSE ANY TIME YOU CAN
BUILD A DEVICE THAT DOES
TWO JOBS AT ONCE
THERE'S A CHANCE YOU
WON'T HAVE TO DO ANYTHING.
NOW, THE ONLY
CONDITION YOU NEED
IS THAT EVERYTHING
HAS TO BE WRAPPED IN
A CYLINDRICAL SHAPE.
YOU KNOW, LIKE THIS
WINE BOTTLE
OR A SLEEVE
OF TENNIS BALLS
OR EVEN A ROLLING PIN.
AND EVEN IF IT'S
NOT THE RIGHT SHAPE,
AS LONG AS IT WILL FIT INSIDE,
SAY, ONE OF THESE
SHIPPING TUBES,
IT'S FINE.
NOW YOU JUST WRAP
EVERYTHING UP GOOD AND SNUG.
SMOOTH DOWN THE
OUTSIDE OF HER THERE.
MAKE SURE
THEY'RE AIRTIGHT,
KIND OF LIKE YOUR SLEEPING BAG
ON MEXICAN NIGHT.
OKAY, NOW, THE PIPE
ORGAN RUNS ON AIR,
SO YOU PUMP ON THE
PEDALS AND THE AIR GOES
THROUGH THE PIPES.
AND THAT'S PLENTY OF
AIR FOR MAKING MUSIC,
BUT FOR OUR PURPOSES,
WE'RE GOING TO NEED SOMETHING
WITH A LITTLE MORE OOMPH.
SO I'VE REPLACED THE PEDALS
WITH THIS HIGH-VOLUME
INDUSTRIAL AIR COMPRESSOR.
OKAY, I'M NOT TOO SURE
HOW MUCH PRESSURE I NEED,
SO I'M JUST GONNA
OPEN HER UP FULL.
THEN I'LL JUST BACK IT OFF
IF SOMETHING BREAKS.
NOW ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS
MATCH OUR VARIOUS SIZED GIFTS
WITH OUR VARIOUS
SIZED PIPES.
THEN WHEN YOU
PRESS DOWN ON A KEY,
SEE, THE COMPRESSOR
WILL PLAY A NOTE
AND FIRE THE GIFT
OUT TO THE RECIPIENT.
[ hits note ]
[ glass breaking ]
OKAY, UH, YOU MIGHT WANNA
GIVE THEM A BASEBALL GLOVE
OR A PILLOW CASE
TO CATCH IT IN.
AND MAKE SURE
GRANDPA'S AWAKE,
OR HE WON'T BE.
AND NOW, OF COURSE,
YOU'RE GOING TO BE ABLE
TO GET THE MUSIC
AND THE GIFT GIVING OVER
AS QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
AND ISN'T THAT WHAT
CHRISTMAS IS ALL ABOUT?
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HAND --
WELL, BY THE WAY, MAKE SURE
YOU PICK A PIECE OF MUSIC
THAT HITS ALL
THE RIGHT NOTES.
HERE WE ARE: IT'S BEGINNING
TO LOOK A LOT LIKE CHRISTMAS.
[ knuckles cracking ]
[ playing haltingly ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
OH, HI THERE,
BOYS AND GIRLS.
YOU KNOW, I HOPE THEY'RE
STILL CALLING YOU THAT,
BECAUSE I'VE SEEN SOME OF
YOUR PICTURES IN THOSE
TEEN MAGAZINES,
AND -- WELL, I'M JUST
NOT SURE ANYMORE.
[ whistle ]
WOW!
ANYWAY, AT THIS
JOYOUS TIME OF YEAR,
I'D LIKE YOU TO START
THINKING ABOUT THOSE
WHO ARE LESS FORTUNATE
THAN YOURSELVES...
ME.
WHILE YOU'RE AT HOME
ALL SNUGGLED IN YOUR BED,
WAITING FOR SANTA TO
COME DOWN THE CHIMNEY,
I'M UP HERE IN MY
FIRE WATCH TOWER
MAKING SURE THERE ARE
NO FOREST FIRES.
WELL, BOYS AND GIRLS,
IT'S 40° BELOW ZERO.
I'D KILL FOR A
FREAKIN' FOREST FIRE.
BUT, OH, NO.
AND THERE YOU ARE AT HOME
ALL SNUGLY AND WARM AND COZY
SINGING CHRISTMAS CAROLS
AND EATING FIGGY PUDDING.
NOT ME.
I HAVE VERY LITTLE PUDDING
AND ABSOLUTELY NO FIGGY.
ON CHRISTMAS MORNING
YOU'LL WAKE UP TO GIFTS
UNDERNEATH THE TREE.
OH, SURE, THE ANIMALS LEAVE
GIFTS FOR ME UNDERNEATH
THE TREES.
BUT THEY'RE VERY, VERY
SELDOM WRAPPED,
AND THEY'RE NEVER
THE RIGHT SIZE.
NOW, DON'T GET ME WRONG,
I'M NOT LOOKING
FOR YOUR PITY.
I'M JUST KIDDING.
I AM LOOKING FOR YOUR PITY.
AND I'LL TEL YOU WHY...
BECAUSE EVERY
ONCE IN A WHILE,
YOU HAVE TO STOP THINKING
ABOUT YOURSELVES AND REALISE
THAT THERE ARE PEOPLE OUT
THERE THAT CARE ABOUT YOU,
THAT ARE DOING THEIR LEVEL
BEST TO TAKE CARE OF YOU.
SO HAVE A WONDERFUL
HOLIDAY SEASON,
BUT REMEMBER:
IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU.
IT'S ABOUT ME.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
O'ER THE HILLS WE GO
( voice cracking )
LAUGHING ALL THE WAY
I WAS JUST OVER AT MOOSE
THOMPSON'S HOUSE,
HELPING HIM GET INTO
HIS SANTA OUTFIT.
BY GOLLY,
HE IS A LARGE MAN.
YOU KNOW, IT'S
A STRETCHY MATERIAL,
SO WE COULD ACTUALLY GET
IT ON OVER HIS BUTT,
BUT WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO GREASE THE INSIDE
OF THE SLEIGH,
OR HE'LL HAVE TO STAND
FOR THE WHOLE PARADE.
UNCLE RED!
WOULD YOU TELL MR. HUMPHREY
THAT HIS OFFERING
IS NO GOOD?
YOU WANT ME TO GIVE YOU
SOMETHING FREE
SO THAT SANTA CAN
TOSS TREATS TO THE KIDS,
AND RED, THERE IS A
LIMIT TO WHAT I CAN DO.
Red:
AND WHAT IS THAT
LIMIT, DALTON?
SEVEN CASES
OF PRUNES.
YEAH, BUT THEY'RE
PITTED PRUNES,
SO NO ONE'S GONNA
LOSE AN EYE OR ANYTHING.
WELL, DON'T YOU HAVE LITTLE
AIRPLANES OR STUFFED TOYS
TO TOSS OUT
TO THE KIDS?
WELL, YES, I DO.
I SELL THEM.
THAT'S HOW I
SUPPORT MYSELF.
AND THAT'S HOW I'M ABLE
TO GIVE THINGS AWAY
FOR FREE,
LIKE SEVEN CASES
OF PRUNES.
OF COURSE,
IF YOU DON'T WANT THEM...
NO, NO, NO,
WE'LL TAKE 'EM.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL LEAVE
'EM BESIDE THE SHED.
GOOD.
PRUNES?
GET OVER IT,
HAROLD, ALL RIGHT?
I GOT SOME BAD
NEWS, RED.
I COULD ONLY GET
FOUR REINDEER.
WELL, NO, THAT'S FINE.
THAT'LL GET THE JOB DONE.
FOUR IS FINE.
NOT WITH MOOSE THOMPSON
IN THE SLEIGH.
IN FACT, I WON'T
ALLOW IT.
NO, NO, THERE'S NOTHING
MEANER THAN REINDEER
WITH A HERNIA.
WELL, WHAT DO WE
DO NOW, GUYS?
WELL, OBVIOUSLY WE HAVE TO
FIND SOMEBODY SMALLER
THAN MOOSE THOMPSON
BUT WHO STILL LOOKS
LIKE SANTA CLAUS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
Red (voice over):
NOW, ONE OF THE PARTS OF
OUR SANTA CLAUS PARADE FLOAT
WAS GOING TO BE OUR FROSTY
THE SNOWMAN DISPLAY.
SO WE ARE KEEPING
IT IN THE ARENA,
WE DIDN'T
HAVE A LOT OF SNOW.
WALTER'S NOT GOOD ON ICE.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM WITH --
OH, AND HE --
BUT HE SEEMS TO LIKE TO
TAKE WINSTON WITH HIM
WHEREVER HE GOES.
SO, UH, WINSTON DOES NOT HAVE
THE SENSE OF HUMOUR THAT
HE REALLY NEEDS.
THIS IS GOING
TO TAKE A WHILE.
ALL WE'RE TRYING TO DO
IS GET FROSTY --
NO, NO, NO.
WELL, GREAT. OKAY.
SO NOW WE GOT
A HEADLESS FROSTY
WHICH MEANS WE NEED
SOME FRESH SNOW.
SO THEY GOT
THE ZAMBONI THERE.
I KNOW THESE THINGS,
WHAT THEY DO IS THEY
SCRAPE THE ICE,
AND ALL THE SNOW GOES
UP INTO A HOPPER,
AND I FIGURED WE COULD USE
THAT AS OUR SNOW SUPPLY,
AND THEN WE COULD MAKE
OURSELVES A NEW HEAD
FOR FROSTY ON THERE.
GRAB A HANDFUL OF SNOW.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE
A NEW HEAD FOR FROSTY.
C'MON GET SOME SNOW THERE.
WATCH YOURSELF
THERE, WALTER.
WALTER'S A LITTLE SHAKY.
BUT WINSTON'S STILL CARRYING
THE GRUDGE ON WALTER.
OF COURSE --
THAT'S NOT SO GOOD.
WINSTON FINDS
THAT VERY FUNNY,
AND I'M THINKING YOU KNOW,
TRY A LITTLE OF YOUR OWN --
THERE WE GO.
I FEEL SO MUCH BETTER,
AND WALTER'S ENJOYING THAT.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO WITH
WALTER IS THREATEN HIM
AND DOWN HE GOES.
BUT THE BROOM FLIES
THROUGH THE AIR,
AND WOULDN'T YOU KNOW IT,
HITS  THE CONTROLS
ON THE ZAMBONI,
AND SHE STARTS
HEADING TOWARDS US.
AT THIS POINT IT'S
EVERY MAN FOR HIMSELF.
WALTER'S KIND OF FLAILING
AWAY ON THE ICE.
OH, BOY, THIS IS NOT --
OH, BOY. OH, MAN.
HAVE A NICE
CHRISTMAS, WALTER.
NOW SHE GRINDS TO HALT,
AND I DON'T KNOW
WHERE HE IS IN THIS.
FIRST THING WE SHOULD DO
IS JUST OPEN HER UP
AND SEE IN --
OH, HE'S FINE.
SO WE GET WALTER OUT OF THERE
AND MEANWHILE WINSTON IS
BACK WITH THE SNOW,
AND HE'S MADE HIMSELF
A BRAND NEW HEAD
AND PUT FROSTY RIGHT BACK
THE WAY HE SHOULD BE.
BUT WINSTON FIGURED THAT
TO PROTECT FROSTY,
APPARENTLY IF YOU PUT
A LITTLE COATING OF WATER,
IT'LL FREEZE IT.
PUT A NICE COATING
ON IT AND IT WON'T BE
SUSCEPTIBLE TO DAMAGES.
SO HE'S JUST
GONNA DO THAT.
AND I'M SAYING IT'S NOT AS
SMART AS IT LOOKS, WINSTON.
I BELIEVE THEY USE THE HOT
WATER IN THOSE ZAMBONIS,
AND, TO ME, HOT WATER
AND SNOW, IT'S NOT
REALLY A GOOD --
NO, NO, HE KNOWS.
HE'S A PROFESSIONAL.
HE'S GOOD WITH A HOSE.
HE KNOWS WHAT HE'S --
NOW THE END COMES OFF.
HE'S GOT HOT WATER
GOING EVERYWHERE.
AND I GOT HER TURNED OFF,
BUT THERE'S FROSTY AND --
LUCKILY I HAD A SIGN HANDY
THAT WAS JUST PERFECT
FOR THE OCCASION.
AND IT WAS A GREAT DAY.
YOU OKAY?
OH, MAN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WE ALL KNOW THAT CHRISTMAS
IS RIGHT AROUND THE CORNER,
WHICH IS A TIME FOR GIFTS AND
JOY AND WARM FAMILY MOMENTS.
AND THEY ALSO EXPECT YOU
TO DECORATE YOUR HOUSE
WITH LIGHTS
AND MISTLETOE AND WREATHS.
WELL, HERE'S A QUICK EASY WAY
TO DO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO
AND STILL SAVE A FEW BUCKS.
GET YOURSELF ALL THE OLD BOWS
THAT YOUR WIFE HAS SAVED
OVER THE YEARS.
AND THEN SPRINKLE THEM
INTO A WINDOW BOX.
MY WIFE'S OLD BEAUS ARE
SPRINKLED ALL OVER THE COUNTY.
AND IN THE SECOND BOX YOU WANT
TO POUR DOWN A THIN LAYER
OF LIQUID GLUE.
GOT TO BE SOMETHING WITH A
FAIR AMOUNT OF ADHESIVE
POWER TO IT.
[ grunting ]
THIS SEEMS PERFECT.
[ glass breaking ]
GUESS I MIGHT AS WELL
USE ALL OF THIS.
I'M GOING TO HAVE A REAL
PROBLEM GETTING THE TOP
BACK ON THERE.
OKAY.
NOW YOU TAKE
A SPARE TIRE --
EVERYBODY HAS A SPARE
TIRE THIS TIME OF YEAR,
AND YOU ROLL THAT THROUGH
YOUR GLUE BATH, EH?
DON'T WORRY IF
IT'S AN OLD TIRE
BECAUSE YOU WANT TO PICK UP
AS MUCH GLUE AS YOU CAN,
AND THE LESS
TREAD THE BETTER.
BALD IS BEAUTIFUL.
NOW YOU JUST THROW YOUR
GLUED UP TIRE THROUGH
YOUR BOX OF BOWS.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU
THINK ABOUT IT,
YOU'RE RUNNING OVER YOUR
WIFE'S OLD BEAUS.
THAT'S GOTTA BE FUN, HUH?
WHOEVER THOUGHT I'D GET
TWO JOKES OUT OF THAT?
MAYBE I DIDN'T.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THERE YOU GO.
GOT OURSELVES A PRETTY
HANDSOME CHRISTMAS WREATH.
I GOT AN IDEA.
HAVE YOURSELF A
MURRAY CHRYSLER
AND A HYUNDAI NEW YEAR.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THIS IS THE
PORTION OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE EXAMINE THOSE THREE
LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S TRUE, EH?
OKAY, TODAY'S LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS --"
LA LA LA.
"AND ALL MY FRIENDS SAY THAT
SANTA CLAUS DOES NOT EXIST.
"IS THIS TRUE OR DOES
HE ACTUALLY EXIST?"
OH, BOY,
THAT'S A TOUGH ONE.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'VE EVER
SEEN THE REAL SANTA CLAUS.
I MEAN, A JOLLY, OBESE GUY
WITH A WHITE BEARD
PRETTY MUCH DESCRIBES
EVERY LODGE MEMBER.
WELL, SANTA'S NOT
REALLY OBESE, RED.
HE'S JUST
OVERWEIGHT.
THEY EAT A LOT OF BLUBBER UP
THERE AT THE NORTH POLE,
AND IT'S NOT JUST LOADED
WITH UNSATURATED FAT,
IT IS UNSATURATED FAT.
YOU'VE ACTUALLY
MET SANTA CLAUS,
MR. SHAUGHNESSY?
WELL, NO,
TO SAY I'VE MET HIM
WOULD BE PUSHING IT.
AND WHEN HAP
STARTS PUSHING IT,
WE END UP SHOVELLING IT.
THIS VIEWER HAS ASKED
A SPECIFIC QUESTION,
AND IF WE CAN
ANSWER IT, WE SHOULD.
WELL, HAROLD, YOU KNOW
I DON'T LIKE TO EXAGGERATE,
BUT MY RUN-IN WITH SANTA
SAVED THE WORLD FROM
NUCLEAR ANNIHILATION.
YOU ASKED FOR THIS.
IT WAS CHRISTMAS EVE, 1963.
WE WERE HOLDING AT
OUR FAIL-SAFE POINTS
WHEN WORD CAME
FROM THE PENTAGON
THAT AN UNIDENTIFIED
AIRCRAFT WAS APPROACHING
FROM THE NORTH.
THEY FIGURED IT WAS
THE LEADING EDGE OF A
MASSIVE RUSSIAN ATTACK,
AND WE PROCEEDED TOWARDS
OUR TARGETS INSIDE THE
SOVIET UNION,
WHILE N.O.R.A.D.
GOT READY TO SHOOT
THEIR PLANE DOWN.
WELL, WHEN WE OPENED
OUR BOMB BAY DOORS
WE COULD SEE THAT IT WAS
ACTUALLY SANTA IN HIS SLEIGH.
ANY ALCOHOL SERVED
ON THAT FLIGHT?
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, A LOT OF
THIS STUFF IS CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION.
I MAY HAVE SAID
TOO MUCH ALREADY.
OH, FOR SURE.
OKAY, WELL, UM, I WOULD
SAY TO THIS VIEWER
THAT, UM, SOMETIMES YOU
JUST HAVE TO BELIEVE,
EVEN THOUGH THAT
MAY BE DIFFICULT.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU THIS MUCH,
I BELIEVE IT SANTA CLAUSE.
I BELIEVE IN
SANTA.
I BELIEVE IN SANTA MORE
THAN I BELIEVE IN HAP.
[ APPLAUSE ]
BOY, THE SNOW IS REALLY
COMING DOWN OUT THERE.
NOW, WE'RE HAVING THE SANTA
CLAUSE PARADE RIGHT AFTER
THE LODGE MEETING.
I'M HOPING THE REINDEER CAN
FIND THERE WAY OUT THERE
THROUGH THAT BLIZZARD.
YOU KNOW, I THINK IT'S
A GOOD THING YOU BEING SANTA.
MAYBE IT'LL RUB OFF.
YOU KNOW,
YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT.
I'M ALREADY THINKING OF
JAMMING SOMETHING DOWN
YOUR STOCKING.
RED! RED!
WE GOT A SERIOUS PROBLEM!
WHAT? DID YOU SEE
A MOUSE OF SOMETHING?
NO! THE REINDEER
ATE ALL THE PRUNES.
WELL, ED! ED!
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
MOVE MY CAR!
THAT WAS SEVEN
CASES OF PRUNES.
THERE'S NO WAY I'M STANDING
IN A SLEIGH BEHIND THEM.
MAYBE YOU COULD STAND IN
THE BACK OF THE POSSUM VAN.
WE'LL OPEN THE SIDE DOOR,
AND YOU COULD STILL WAVE
AT THE KIDS.
YEAH. OKAY.
BUT I NEED A CHAUFFEUR.
OH, RIGHT.
WHO ARE WE GONNA GET?
WELL, HAROLD, IF YOU'RE
SO DOGGONE BRIGHT,
WON'T YOU DRIVE
MY VAN TONIGHT?
AND I'LL GO
DOWN IN HISTORY
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME, SANTA.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD,
RUDOLPH.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
GOOD LUCK
WITH THAT NOSE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I WONDER IF YOU
COULD DO ME A FAVOUR,
CLEAN OUT THE FIREPLACE.
I'M DRESSED AS SANTA,
HAROLD'S DRIVING THE VAN,
PRETTY GOOD CHANCE I'M
GOING TO END UP ON THE
ROOF SOMEWHERE.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF, HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
HAVE YOURSELF
A GREAT CHRISTMAS,
AND KEEP YOUR
STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
C'MON, YOU GUYS. LET'S GO.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
MEETING'S COMING TO ORDER.
SIT DOWN, PLEASE. SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red:
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF A HAVE TO, I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, LISTEN.
WE'VE GOT A PRETTY GOOD
BLIZZARD GOIN' ON OUT THERE.
AND THE REINDEER HAVE EATEN
A FAIR WHACK OF PRUNES.
SO YOU REALLY
WANT TO BE CAREFUL
THERE'S LOTS
OF THINGS TO SLIP ON.
OH, YEAH,
AND MERRY CHRISTMAS, GUYS.
C'MON, HAROLD.