IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE MAN WHO WAS VOTED
HEAD OF POSSUM LODGE, 'CAUSE
THE OTHER BODY PARTS
WERE SPOKEN FOR,
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
GOT SOME BAD NEWS,
UNFORTUNATELY.
A BIT OF A DISASTER
THIS WEEK AT THE LODGE.
BUSTER HADFIELD'S HOUSE
WAS BURNED DOWN BY HIS BUDGIE.
OH NO.
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
PLAYING WITH MATCHES.
BUSTER LETS THE LITTLE GUY
FLY AROUND.
HE EATS BITS OF POTATO CHIPS
FROM BETWEEN
THE COUCH CUSHIONS.
HE GOT POKING AROUND
WHERE HE SHOULDN'T HAVE,
AND HE PLUGGED HIMSELF INTO
AN ELECTRICAL OUTLET.
OH, THAT'S AWFUL.
HE WENT UP JUST LIKE A FLARE,
HAROLD.
DIDN'T EVEN BLOW A FUSE
ON THAT ONE.
THE HOUSE BURNED TO THE GROUND.
THAT'S HARDLY AN ACCIDENT.
YOU GUYS DON'T HAVE
SMOKE DETECTORS, ALARMS.
YOUR FIRE EXTINGUISHERS
ARE NEVER CHARGED UP.
IT'S A WONDER
THERE'S NOT MORE FIRES.
DIDN'T EVEN BLOW A FUSE.
THAT WAS A DEAD SHORT.
WRECKLESS, IRRESPONSIBLE
NEGLIGENCE, UNCLE RED.
BUSTER HAS NO HOME.
WHAT DID WE LEARN FROM
OUR MOST RECENT DISASTER?
WE LEARNED THAT EVEN
AN ADULT, FULLY-GROWN BUDGIE
DRAWS LESS THAN 15 AMPS.
(Laughing)
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MESSAGE BEING,
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
AROUND HERE, PEOPLE GET DOWN,
BUT THEY DON'T STAY DOWN.
WE'RE GONNA TURN BUSTER'S FIRE
INTO AN OPPORTUNITY.
YOU GOING INTO
THE CHARCOAL BUSINESS?
NO, HAROLD -- WE'RE GONNA DO
WHAT THE PIONEERS DID.
YOU'RE MOVING TO CALIFORNIA?! --
OH! OH! OH!
MAYBE I CAN MEET SPIELBERG.
I GOT THIS IDEA, THIS TREATMENT.
THE TREATMENT'S NOT WORKING.
(Laughing)
THINK BACK TO THE PIONEERS,
OK.
WHAT DID THEY DO
WHEN THE GUY NEXT DOOR'S HOUSE
BURNED DOWN?
MOVE AWAY?
KEEP THEIR OWN HOUSES WET.
HAROLD, THEY'D ALL PITCH IN
AND BUILD THE GUY A NEW HOUSE.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, OK,
LIKE A BARN RAISING.
EXCEPT THIS IS BUSTER'S HOUSE.
NO, YOU KNOW, I THINK
BARN RAISING IS A GOOD ANALOGY.
YOU KNOW WHO DOES THAT IS
THE AMISH AND THE MENNONITES.
INSTEAD OF A BUNCH OF
DEVOUT CRAFTSMEN,
IT'S GOING TO BE A GANG
OF DRUNKS.
WELL, I FIGURE IT WILL GO
A LOT FASTER.
LATER ON IN
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL",
WE'LL BE DOING
SOME HIGH-WIRE WALKING.
BUT I HAD HEARD --
ONE OF THE FELLAS TOLD ME
THAT BILL WAS STUCK UP
AT THE TOP OF A FLAGPOLE,
AND THEY ASKED ME
TO GO AND GET HIM.
BUT WHAT HAD HAPPENED WAS
HE WAS TRYING TO GET
THE FLAG DOWN.
COMMUNICATION IS --
THAT'S WHEN -- AND THE --
ANYWAY, BILL HAD APPARENTLY
SHINNIED --
YOU DON'T VERY OFTEN SEE
AN ADULT SHINNY.
YOU'RE STILL NOT.
BUT, OF COURSE,
I DIDN'T GET THERE TILL
HE WAS UP AT THE TOP.
HE WAS STUCK UP THERE.
I'LL GET YOU DOWN.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, JUST RELAX.
I THINK IF I GET
THE POLE VIBRATING,
HE'S GOT TO SLIDE DOWN.
RELAX --
YOU'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
OH, YOU'RE FINE, YOU'RE FINE.
BOY, OH, BOY.
SOMETIMES THE FEAR
IS SO STRONG IN THEM,
THEIR FINGERS TIGHTEN UP,
THEIR FINGERNAILS
DIG INTO THE POLE.
LUCKILY, I HAD A LITTLE
CHAIN-SAW UNIT THERE.
WHERE THERE'S A WILL
THERE'S A WAY.
(Laughing)
SORRY, BILL.
DON'T THANK ME.
THAT'S FINE, THAT'S FINE.
OH, SOMETIMES
I GET TO THINKIN'
'BOUT ALL THE MISTAKES
I'VE MADE
ALL THE PEOPLE
I'VE HURT
AND ALL THE BILLS
I HAVEN'T PAID
SOMETIMES
I GET TO THINKIN'
I SHOULD CHANGE
AND GET ON THE BALL
BUT THEN I TURN ON
THE OLD T.V.
AND I DON'T GET TO THINKIN'
AT ALL
OK, FOR
A FREE CHIROPRACTIC ADJUSTMENT
AT ARNIE'S AUTOBODY SHOP,
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. HUMPHREY
TO SAY THIS WORD,
"WOLVES".
OOOOH, GO!
OK, DALTON, THESE ARE
LIKE DOGS, ONLY BIGGER.
MY WIFE'S SIDE OF THE FAMILY.
NO.
THESE ARE ANIMALS, DALTON.
THEY TRAVEL IN PACKS.
YEAH, THAT'S MY WIFE'S SIDE
OF THE FAMILY.
COME ON, COME ON.
THESE ARE LIKE A FOX,
ONLY BIGGER.
BIGGER TEETH.
MY WIFE'S SIDE OF THE FAMILY.
WHY DO YOU KEEP SAYING THAT?
JUST FEELS GOOD, THAT'S ALL!
NO, NO, STOP IT.
THESE ARE WILD ANIMALS.
THEY HOWL AT THE MOON,
EAT RATS, TRAVEL IN GROUPS,
AND HUNT OUT
THE WEAK AND THE SICK.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO GO WITH
MY ORIGINAL ANSWER ON THIS.
THESE ANIMALS
HARDLY EVER HURT HUMANS.
OH.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO GIVE ME
ANOTHER CLUE ON THAT ONE.
DESCRIBE YOUR WIFE'S SIDE
OF THE FAMILY EATING.
WOLVES.
THAT WAS
IT!
THIS WEEK ON
"HANDYMAN CORNER",
WE'RE GONNA DO ONE OF
THE MOST COMMON,
AND YET, ONE OF THE MOST
DIFFICULT HANDYMAN PROJECTS.
WE'RE GONNA HANG A DOOR.
HERE WE HAVE
A PORTABLE WASHROOM
WHOSE DOOR HAS BEEN RIPPED OFF
DURING SOME KIND OF
A GASTRONOMICAL EMERGENCY.
AND OVER HERE, WE HAVE A DOOR.
SO WHAT WE'VE GOT TO DO
IS GET THESE TWO TOGETHER.
FIRST, MAKE SURE THAT THE DOOR
IS THE SAME SIZE AS
THE HOLE IT'S GOTTA GO IN.
NO -- A LITTLE TOO TALL.
SO, WE'LL JUST MARK HER,
AND...
NO LEAD IN MY PENCIL.
WE'VE ALL BE THERE,
HAVEN'T WE?
I'LL TELL YA,
CAR KEY WORKS JUST AS WELL.
MARK HER UP...
AND THEN CUT OFF THE EXCESS.
ALL RIGHT,
GOT OUR DOOR CUT NOW.
ALL WE GOTTA DO
IS MARK WHERE THE HINGES GO,
STICK THEM ON.
OH.
YOU SEE THE PROBLEM
WE GOT HERE.
WE'VE CUT FAR ENOUGH
INTO THE DOOR
THAT WE'RE INTO
THE HOLLOW SECTION,
THAT'S NO GOOD,
'CAUSE WE'LL GET RAIN AND
SHINGLES AND HORNET'S NESTS,
ANYTHING THAT FALLS OFF --
BUT, YOU KNOW,
THERE'S A REAL SIMPLE SOLUTION.
FLIP HER OVER.
JUST MARK WHERE THE HINGES GO,
AND STICK 'EM ON THERE.
I'VE GOT THE HINGES MARKED.
I GOT TO CUT THESE OUT.
ORDINARILY,
I WOULD USE A CHISEL,
BUT, I DON'T HAVE A CHISEL.
I DID HAVE A CHISEL, BUT
I HAD IT FOR MORE THAN A WEEK,
SO IT'S MORE OF A SCREWDRIVER.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
YOU USE THEM AS A HAMMER.
I'M GOING TO USE
THE HINGE ITSELF.
THAT WAY I KNOW
I'LL HAVE A PERFECT FIT.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO HAVE A COUPLE
OF EXTRA HINGES, JUST IN CASE.
WE'RE ALL SET.
JUST... ATTACH OUR HINGES
TO OUR DOOR JAMB,
JUST LIKE THIS.
SEE WHAT YOU'VE DONE HERE?
YOU'VE MOUNTED THE HINGES
ON THE WRONG SIDE.
NOW THE DOOR IS GOING TO
OPEN IN.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO WORK.
PLUS, REAL DANGEROUS IN A FIRE.
AND AROUND THE LODGE
WE HAVE PLENTY OF THOSE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
DEAD EASY TO FIX.
NOT THAT EASY.
I FIND IT A LOT EASIER TO PUT
THE SCREWS IN WITH A HAMMER
THAN IT IS GETTING
ALL THOSE BLISTERS
FROM A SCREWDRIVER --
OH, NO, THAT'S A CHISEL.
SO JUST TAKE HER OVER NOW,
AND MOUNT HER
ON THE SIDE THERE.
AND JUST... HORSE HER IN.
AND SHE'S JUST THAT EASY.
ISN'T THAT A BEAUTIFUL JOB?
YOU CAN MAKE A FEW--
THERE'S ALWAYS ADJUSTMENTS.
YOU CAN CUT THAT OFF --
NO, THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
I GOT AN IDEA.
(Engine starting)
WHERE THERE'S A VAN
THERE'S A WAY.
BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL JOB.
SO REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST FIND YOU
HANDY.
THEY'LL FIND ME IN THE SHED.
(Door handle rattling)
AHH.
WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT A LOT MORE OF IT.
I WANNA TALK TO YOU OLD GUYS
ABOUT TELLING STORIES
THAT NOBODY WANTS TO HEAR.
YOU KNOW, IN HOLLYWOOD,
THEY ACTUALLY HAVE A SYSTEM
FOR TELLING STORIES.
SAY, FOR INSTANCE,
YOU HAVE A MOVIE IDEA.
I'VE GOT LOTS, BUT, ANYWAY,
A PROFESSIONAL BEGINS WITH
A CONCISE PREMISE
OF ONE OR TWO SENTENCES.
SOMETHING LIKE, A METEOROLOGIST
AND HIS EX-WIFE
CHASE TORNADOES
ACROSS THE MID-WEST
AND A BUNCH OF
SPECIAL EFFECTS HAPPEN!
IF PEOPLE LIKE THAT --
ONLY IF THEY LIKE THAT,
YOU CAN GO ON AND TELL
THE TREATMENT.
THAT'S A LITTLE BIT
LONGER VERSION.
IF THEY LIKE THAT,
YOU CAN GO INTO
THE FULL-BLOWN SCREENPLAY.
THAT'S TWO HOURS.
SO, YOU SEE HOW THEY DO THAT?
THEY TELL A LITTLE BIT
OF THE STORY
TO SEE IF PEOPLE
ARE INTERESTED.
YOU OLD GUYS,
YOU MIGHT WANNA TRY THAT.
NEXT TIME YOU
SEE A BUNCH OF TEENAGERS
TALKING ABOUT
SOMETHING REALLY INTERESTING,
LIKE THE NEW
ALANIS MORRISETTE C.D.,
AND IT REMINDS YOU OF
ONE OF YOUR AMUSING STORIES,
DON'T LAUNCH RIGHT INTO
THE TWO-HOUR VERSION.
SEE IF YOU CAN GET
THEIR ATTENTION
WITH SOMETHING LIKE,
"ONE TIME I, UH,
"I HAD TO CHANGE A TIRE
IN THE RAIN
"ON THE WAY TO A WEDDING."
(Laughing)
IF YOU'RE MET WITH COLD STARES,
DON'T TELL THE STORY.
PITCH OUT ANOTHER IDEA.
"DID I TELL YOU ABOUT THE TIME
I STEPPED IN A BIRTHDAY CAKE?"
IF THEY'RE INTERESTED,
ONLY IF THEY'RE INTERESTED,
GO ON WITH A LONGER VERSION.
BUT, AS FAR AS THE TWO-HOUR
VERSION IS CONCERNED,
TRUST ME, WE'RE WILLING TO WAIT
FOR THE VIDEO.
REMEMBER, YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
DON'T PUSH IT.
(Sighing)
(Audience laughing)
TWO HOURS AGO, BUSTER'S HOUSE
WAS A SMOULDERING RUIN.
NOW HIS NEW PLACE IS READY
TO MOVE IN.
WHEN THE LODGE MEMBERS
COME TOGETHER,
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN'T DO.
BIG WHOOP!
PUTTING UP A HOUSE -- WAAAHH!
IT WAS A PRE-FAB HOME.
IT ARRIVED IN A TRUCK,
TAKEN OFF BY A CRANE.
ALL THEY DID WAS SIT AROUND
IN LAWN CHAIRS
AND HECKLE
THE POOR CRANE OPERATOR.
GUY GOT SO NERVOUS,
HE DIDN'T PUT IT
ON BUSTER'S PROPERTY.
(Audience laughing)
HAROLD, WHEN SOMEBODY
SAYS "SHUT UP",
IT'S NOT ADVICE
YOU CAN TAKE OR LEAVE.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO DO IT.
I GIVE YOU ADVICE
AND YOU DON'T TAKE IT.
WE'RE NOT
EQUALS, HAROLD.
I KNOW, BUT I DON'T HOLD THAT
OVER YOU.
(Laughing)
BUSTER'S HOUSE IS WHERE
IT SHOULD BE, THANKS TO US.
WE CHIPPED IN
AND BUSTER GOT A GREAT DEAL.
A HOME, HUH?
IT'S A HOUSEBOAT.
HEY, HEY, COME ON!
BUSTER'S KIDS GOT A ROOF
OVER THEIR HEAD,
A BACK PORCH BIG ENOUGH
TO TAKE AN OUTBOARD MOTOR,
AND A BASEMENT
THAT WILL NEVER FLOOD.
IT'S THE UGLIEST THING
I'VE EVER SEEN.
SHOW SOME RESPECT --
THAT'S BUSTER'S HOUSE.
IT'S MORE LIKE
BUSTER'S ARK.
WELL, IF IT IS, HAROLD,
YOU CAN'T GET ON IT
'CAUSE WE'LL NEVER FIND
TWO LIKE YOU.
(Audience laughing)
UM... HI, MY NAME'S BUZZ.
I'M A MAN.
(Harold):
HEY, BUZZ!
HI, BUZZ.
UM... I ACTED LIKE A GUY
YESTERDAY.
(Red): OH, BOY.
I REALLY COULDN'T
HELP MYSELF, RIGHT?
SHE'S GOT THIS FOOD PROCESSOR
AND IT BROKE.
IT WAS STUCK ON "MINCE".
SHE SAID, "I'LL TAKE THAT
TO THE REPAIR SHOP."
I SAID, "WHOA! LET ME FIX IT!"
SHE SAID, "NO! THANK YOU.
"REMEMBER WHAT YOU DID
TO MY T.V.?
TO MY BLOW-DRYER?
"REMEMBER WHAT YOU DID TO MY
TYPEWRITER AND YOGURT-MAKER?"
I SAID, "WHAT'S THE POINT?"
SHE SAID, "SO..."
I SAID, "I WON'T TOUCH IT."
SHE LEFT IT ON THE COUNTER,
A BROKEN FOOD PROCESSOR.
HOW CAN WOMEN DO THAT?
YOU GOTTA TAKE IT APART
AND SEE WHAT'S WRONG!
YOU GOTTA!
I DIDN'T TOUCH IT.
ALL WEEK, I WALKED BY.
IT'S TAUNTING ME,
TALKING TO ME.
IT'S SAYING, "I'M BROKEN --
YOU CAN'T TOUCH ME.
"YOU CAN'T FIX ME."
I WANTED TO TAKE-- I DIDN'T.
ONE NIGHT, I SNAPPED.
SHE WENT OUT TO BINGO
AND I GOT MY TOOLS OUT.
I TOOK THAT FOOD PROCESSOR
AND I RIPPED 'ER WIDE OPEN!
I-I-I COULDN'T FIX IT,
YOU KNOW.
(Audience laughing)
BUT I PUT IT BACK TOGETHER
AND IT LOOKED ALMOST EXACTLY
THE SAME AS IT USED TO.
YOU KNOW... SHE CAME HOME.
SHE TOOK ONE LOOK AT ME.
SHE LOOKED AT THE BLENDER.
SHE SAID, "YOU TRIED
TO FIX IT, DIDN'T YOU?"
(Harold): AWW!
WHAT GAVE YOU AWAY?
THE DUCT TAPE.
(Audience laughing)
"A POEM BY ALFRED,
LORD TENNYSON... GREEN.
"HALF A LEAGUE, HALF A LEAGUE,
HALF A LEAGUE ONWARD,
"ALL IN THE VALLEY OF DEATH
RODE THE 600,
"THEIRS NOT TO MAKE REPLY,
THEIRS NOT TO REASON WHY,
"THEIRS BUT TO DO AND DIE.
"INTO THE JAWS OF DEATH,
"INTO THE MOUTH OF HELL,
RODE THE 600.
"BOY, THAT WAS THE BEST EVER
PAY-PER-VIEW 'WRESTLEMANIA.'"
(Audience laughing)
(Red): WELL, TIME FOR
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL".
GONNA DO THE HIGH-WIRE THING.
EARLIER, WE FREED UP
THE FLAGPOLE
SO HE CAN ACTUALLY USE THAT.
THAT'S THE WAY
HE USES FLAGPOLES.
THAT'S THE TROUBLE WITH BILL.
HE'S GONNA USE THAT TO--
YOU KNOW THEY HAVE
THE BALANCE BAR THAT THEY USE.
WELL, THAT'S-- OHHH!
BILL'S A DANGEROUS MAN.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET HIM
ON THE HIGH-WIRE.
I'LL TAKE ONE END OF THE ROPE.
I'M GONNA HOOK THAT
ONTO ONE OF OUR BIGGER TREES,
AND BILL'S GOT
THE CONCRETE BLOCK,
AND I'LL WHIP THAT AROUND
AND TIE THAT ON
IN, I THINK, A REEF HITCH.
AND THEN BILL'S GONNA WEDGE
THAT BLOCK INTO THE TREE
AND THEN WE'LL TIGHTEN THE ROPE
BETWEEN THE BLOCK AND--
LOOK AT THAT,
LOOK AT THAT, HUH?
THERE HE IS!
HE'S LIKE A WALLENDA.
YOU EVER HEARD
OF THE WALLENDAS?
THEY'RE A FAMOUS CIRCUS FAMILY.
IF THERE EVER WAS
A CIRCUS FAMILY,
IT'S BILL'S, I'M FIGURING.
LOOK AT THAT --
OF COURSE, WITH BILL,
SOON AS HE GETS ANYWHERE CLOSE
TO DOING SOMETHING RIGHT,
HE FEELS LIKE
HE'S ON TOP OF IT.
HE CAN-- HE'S COCKY.
THERE YOU GO --
YOU DON'T NEED THAT, DO YA?
WITH THE WALLENDAS, THOUGH --
WAIT A MINUTE.
WEREN'T THEY
"THE FLYING WALLENDAS"?
WHY WERE THEY CALLED
OHHHH!
OH, I SEE.
SO WHAT WE DID WAS
WE ADDED MORE WEIGHT.
I HAD TO ADD MORE BLOCKS
SO THERE WAS
MORE WEIGHT ON THE THING,
AND WE HAD A LADDER.
WE TOOK A KID'S BIKE,
TOOK THE TIRES OFF.
WITH THE TIRES OFF,
THE RIMS WILL SIT ON THE ROPE
AND, LIKE I SAY, WITH BILL,
ONCE HE GETS CLOSE
TO SOMETHING,
HE TRIES TO MAKE IT SO HARD
THAT HE CAN'T DO IT.
KINDA LIKE THE PETER PRINCIPLE
OF ADVENTURES.
THIS COULD BE
THE PETER ADVENTURES,
ADVENTURES WITH PETER.
PETER... PETER...
PETER... UH...
NO, IT WON'T WORK.
SO HE GETS ON THE BIKE.
GET ON THERE, AWAY YOU GO.
ON YOU GET, ON YOU GET.
AWAY YOU GO, ON YOU GET.
AWAY, ON, ON, ON,
ON, ON, ON, ON, ON.
THERE, AND BY GOLLY, I THINK
THE FLAGPOLE IS THE SECRET.
AND JUST, YOU KNOW,
A WORD OF SAFETY --
DON'T STAND CLOSE TO BILL.
HE COULD BE CROSSING
NIAGARA FALLS, COULDN'T HE,
ON HIS BIKE, AND EVERYTHING.
AND THEN, YOU KNOW
WHAT HAPPENS, HE THINKS,
"WOULDN'T IT BE FUN TO BOUNCE?"
WHICH HE OFTEN SAYS
AT PARTIES AND
HE GETS GOING TOO MUCH
THERE GOES THE POLE AND
THE BLOCKS FALL AND HE GOES
LIKE A SLINGSHOT.
AWAY YOU GO, BILL!
OH, OH, OH! OH, BOY!
OHHH!
BY GOLLY, NOW,
THAT HAS GOTTA HURT.
THAT'S WHY, AT THE CIRCUS,
YOU PAY UP-FRONT.
ALL RIGHT, THERE, BILL?
OHHH...
HE'LL BE ON HIS BIKE AWHILE,
I'D SAY.
HERE'S THE POSSUM LODGE OATH,
ALL DONE IN NEEDLEPOINT,
SENT BY A VIEWER.
I SAID THAT WASN'T
BUSTER'S PROPERTY.
I SAID, "YOU'RE BUILDING
ON THE WRONG LAND.
"BUSTER'S ENDS AT THE FENCE."
I TOLD YOU!
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
WHEN THE CRANE WAS HERE
AND WE COULD MOVE THE HOUSE?
I TOLD YOU WHEN
YOU PICKED THE SPOT!
I SAID, "BUSTER'S PROPERTY ENDS
AT THE FENCE."
WHY DIDN'T YOU SAY IT LOUDER?
I DID SAY IT LOUDER
AND I SAID IT SEVERAL TIMES.
YOU TOLD ME TO SHUT UP.
WHY DIDN'T YOU PERSIST?
YOU CAN'T STOP DOING SOMETHING
JUST 'CAUSE SOMEBODY TELLS YOU
TO SHUT UP.
IF I PERSIST--
OH, SHUT UP, HAROLD.
WELL, ANYWAY,
WE GOT BUSTER'S HOUSE NOW
50 FEET OFF HIS PROPERTY.
WE WANTED TO PICK A GOOD SITE
WITH A NICE VIEW
AND A WAYS UP FROM THE SMOKING
RUIN OF HIS OLD PLACE.
NOW WE GOTTA MOVE HIS HOUSE,
DO THE OLD CHANGE-OF-ADDRESS
THING.
YOU'RE GONNA DRAG
THAT HOUSEBOAT
OVER 50 FEET OF ROCKY,
WELL-TREED LAND?
WE'RE NOT STUPID, HAROLD.
(Audience laughing)
JUNIOR SINGLETON SAYS
IF WE GREASE THE HILL,
WE CAN SLIDE 'ER DOWN.
(Audience laughing)
(Laughing)
WANNA TELL YOU TEENAGERS
YOU'RE NOT FOOLING ANYBODY.
YOUR PARENTS KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YOU THINK THEY DON'T KNOW
WHERE YOU'RE GOING,
WHAT YOU'RE UP TO, THE PEOPLE
YOU'RE HANGING OUT WITH?
NOT THAT LONG AGO, THEY WERE
DOING THE SAME THINGS.
THEY DON'T WANT YOU TO KNOW.
OTHERWISE, YOU'D THINK
LESS OF THEM.
BELIEVE ME, THEY KNOW.
ARE YOU WITH A PARENT NOW?
YOU SEE THAT GRIN?
THEY MAY SAY THEY DON'T KNOW
BUT THEY KNOW,
AND NOW YOU KNOW
THAT THEY KNOW.
IF THEY WON'T ADMIT
YOU KNOW THEY KNOW
THAT THEY KNOW YOU KNOW,
ASK YOUR GRANDPARENTS,
'CAUSE THEY
REALLY
KNOW.
IF THEY SAY
THEY DON'T REMEMBER,
THAT MEANS YOUR PARENTS
BOUGHT 'EM OFF
OR THERE'S A COURT ORDER
AND NO ONE CAN TALK.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
YOUR PARENTS WERE BIG-TIME
PROBLEM TEENAGERS.
THAT INCREASES THE SLACK
ON YOUR LEASH BY 100 MILES!
BELIEVE ME, I KNOW!
(Audience laughing)
IT'S "MALE CALL"!
OK.
OUR FIRST LETTER IS FROM
MR. PEA CHES IN ATLANTA.
WHO?
MR. PEA CHES
IN ATLANTA.
PEACHES? IS THAT THE NAME?
YEAH, PEA CHES -- HOO-HOO!
"DEAR RED, MY BROTHER MAT CHES
AND I ARE FANS OF YOUR SHOW."
MATCHES? HER BROTHER'S NAME
IS MATCHES?
WHO?
PEACHES.
PEA CHES IS A HE.
A BOY NAMED PEACHES?!
WHAT PARENTS NAME THEIR BOYS
PEACHES AND MATCHES?
WELL... WELL, LET'S SEE.
THEIR PARENTS' NAMES
ARE RET CHES AND BEL CHES.
RETCHES
AND BELCHES?
WHERE DO THESE
NAMES COME FROM?
THEY'RE SOUTHERN PEOPLE --
THEY INCLUDED A FAMILY PHOTO.
THAT'S THE WHOLE CHES FAMILY.
THERE'S RET AND BEL,
PEA AND MAT.
PEACHES, MATCHES,
RETCHES, AND BELCHES.
SOUNDS LIKE A LAW FIRM.
MAKES YOU WANT TO
SETTLE OUT OF COURT.
WELL, GOOD NEWS.
WE SOLVED THE PROBLEM OF
BUSTER'S NEW HOUSE BEING BUILT
ON SOMEBODY ELSE'S PROPERTY.
WITH A LITTLE INGENUITY,
WE GOT HIS HOUSE
ON THE RIGHT SIDE
OF THE BOUNDARY LINE.
YOU MOVED THAT HOUSEBOAT
OVER 50 FEET?
NO, WE MOVED THE FENCE
OVER 50 FEET.
NO, UNCLE RED,
YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
THAT'S SOMEONE
ELSE'S PROPERTY.
IT'S FLINTY McCLINTOCK'S
PROPERTY -- HE DIDN'T MIND.
HE MOVED HIS FAR FENCE
45 FEET ONTO MOOSE THOMPSON'S.
THEN MOOSE MOVED HIS FENCE
OVER 40 FEET
AND BOB STUYVESANT'S 35
AND SO ON,
ALL THE WAY DOWN THE LINE.
EVERYBODY GAVE UP FIVE FEET
AND GOT THEIR FENCE REPAIRED.
THAT'S WHAT NEIGHBOURS ARE FOR.
WOW, THAT'S NEAT,
UNCLE RED.
THAT'S A REAL
PIONEER SPIRIT.
I AM VERY
IMPRESSED.
YOU MAY NOT BE.
THE LAST FIVE FEET WAS ONTO
YOUR PARENTS' PROPERTY
AND YOUR BEDROOM
WAS RIGHT ON THE LINE
SO YOUR BEDROOM IS NOW
ON SOMEONE ELSE'S LAND
AND YOU ARE
OLD MAN SEDGWICK'S SON.
(Audience laughing)
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME.
ARE YOU STILL
MY UNCLE?
YOU GO DOWN
AND SAY HELLO TO DAD.
OHHHH!
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'VE HAD QUITE A DAY.
I PUT OUT A BURNING HOUSE,
BURIED A BUDGIE,
REPLACED A HOUSE
WITH A HOUSEBOAT,
AND RE-DREW THE BOUNDARY LINES
ACROSS THE WHOLE COMMUNITY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DESERVE A REWARD.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD SEDGWICK
AND THE GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): STAND UP!
RISE AND SHINE!
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND,
HAROLD?
(Harold): YOU KNOW
THAT COMMERCIAL, IT SAYS
FOUR OUT OF FIVE DENTISTS,
RECOMMEND SUGARLESS GUM?
THAT 5th DENTIST IS MOVING HERE
SO YOU CAN EAT
WHATEVER YOU WANT.