IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
A DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
MEN AND WOMEN,
WATCH HOW THEY REACT TO
THEIR CAR STARTING
TO RUST.
MOST MEN GO NUTS,
MOST WOMEN GO SHOPPING,
BUT NOT FOR A NEW CAR.
WOMEN DON'T GET
SO EXCITED ABOUT RUST.
WITH MEN IT'S PERSONAL.
IT'S THE AUTOMOTIVE
EQUIVALENT OF GREY HAIR.
IT'S A KILLER TO
REALIZE THAT YOUR
CAR IS MIDDLE AGED.
AND IT GETS WORSE
WHEN BODY PARTS
START FALLING OFF
OR FLUIDS START LEAKING.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF
THE THINGS THAT
MAKES US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red Green:
ON TODAY'S SHOW, GLEN
IS GOING TO SHOW US
A LITTLE MORE HOW TO RUN
A BUSINESS WITHOUT WORKING,
DOUGIE AND I TALK ABOUT
WHAT TO DO WHEN YOUR DOG
LEAVES A BIT OF
HIMSELF ON THE CARPET,
BILL AND I ARE GOING TO
TAKE TURNS BEING
QUARTERBACK,
AND I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW TO MAKE A
SELF-WASHING CAR.
AND NOW HERE
IS THE REASON
THE GREAT OUTDOORS IS
STILL A DANGEROUS
PLACE,
MY UNCLE RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU.
AND HERE IS THE REASON
THE INDOORS IS A
DANGEROUS PLACE,
MY NEPHEW HAROLD.
BOY, OH, BOY.
BIG CHALLENGE UP
THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
MOOSE THOMPSON TOOK
HIS TRUCK IN TO
BE REPAINTED.
NOW USUALLY WE JUST
PAINT THE VEHICLES
OURSELVES
BUT APPARENTLY THE
LAST TIME WE DID IT,
WE DIDN'T CLEAN UP
TOO WELL AND ALL.
THE PAINT ROLLERS
WERE STUCK IN THE
TREE STILL.
UNCLE RED, NOTHING
PERSONAL, YOU KNOW,
BUT PAINTING VEHICLES
IS A PROFESSIONAL TRADE.
YOU GUYS
LEAVE FINGERPRINTS
ALL OVER THE PLACE,
YOU PAINT THE WINDOWS,
YOU PAINT THE MIRRORS.
YOU JUST CAN'T
DO IT RIGHT.
WELL, HAROLD DO RIGHT,
A PROFESSIONAL PAINT
JOB COSTS 500 BUCKS,
WE CAN DO
IT FOR 30,
THAT MEANS WE CAN PAINT
OUR VEHICLES EVERY
SEASON
AND STILL COME
OUT AHEAD.
HOW DO YOU PAINT
A VEHICLE FOR $30?
THE PAINT COSTS
MORE THAN THAT.
THE 30 BUCKS IS
FOR THE BEER.
WE STEAL THE PAINT.
I KNEW THERE WAS
A REASON ALL THE
VEHICLES AROUND HERE
WERE THE SAME COLOUR
AS THE FIRE HALL.
ANYWAY, WHEN MOOSE
WENT TO SEE THE
PROFESSIONALS,
THEY FOUND A LOT
OF RUST IN HIS TRUCK.
THE GUY WITH THE GRINDER,
WHEN HE STARTED
WORKING ON IT,
HE FELL IN THROUGH
THE FRONT WHEEL WELL
AND COME OUT
THROUGH THE TAILGATE.
THAT'S BECAUSE OF ALL
THE SALT THEY PUT ON
THE HIGHWAYS
UP HERE
IN THE WINTER.
YEAH.
AND IF TABLE SALT COULD
DO THAT TO A TRUCK,
CAN YOU IMAGINE WHAT
IT DOES TO YOUR BODY,
A HUMAN BODY OR
EVEN THAT BODY?
THAT'S SODIUM CHLORIDE.
HIGHWAY CREWS USE
CALCIUM CHLORIDE
WHICH IS ANHYDROUS
AND CREATES A
LIQUID BASE
THAT ACTUALLY HAS A
FREEZING POINT LESS
THAN THAT OF WATER.
WELL, HAROLD, WE DON'T
CARE WHAT'S CAUSING
THE PROBLEM,
WE JUST WANT
A SOLUTION.
OH, WELL, THAT WOULD
BE AN AQUEOUS SOLUTION.
IS THERE A RETROACTIVE
ABORTION AVAILABLE
ANYWHERE?
ANYWAY, THE BUNCH OF US
ARE GOING TO PUT OUR
HEADS TOGETHER
AND FIGURE OUT SOME
WAY WE CAN RUSTPROOF
ALL OUR VEHICLES
FOR UNDER 50 BUCKS.
WELL, I THINK I'LL JUST
STAY OUT OF THE WAY.
THAT OUGHT TO GIVE
US A GOOD START.
IT'S NOT OFTEN YOU'LL
FIND THIS KIND OF SHOW
AT THESE KIND
OF PRICES.
AND THERE'S A
REASON FOR THAT.
THERE'S NO EXCUSE,
BUT HERE COMES MOOSE
AND HE HASN'T GOT
HIS SHIRT ON
LIKE A KODIAK
WITH HIS HAIRY BACK
AND A WEEK AND A
HALF OF DIRT ON
OH THERE'S A BIG
ROLL OF FAT
HOLDS HIS SMOKES
AND THAT
IT'S SURE NOT A
SIGHT TO PLEASE
I'M ALSO TOLD THAT
ONE OF HIS ROLLS
HOLDS HIS WALLET AND
HIS SNOWMOBILE KEYS
OH, THERE'S ALL HIS
TATTOOS OUT THERE TO VIEW
SOME OF THEM ARE
REALLY GROOVY
AND IT'S REALLY NEAT
WHEN HE WALKS DOWN
THE STREET
IT'S LIKE BEING AT
A DRIVE-IN MOVIE
WELL, SHE WARNED
YOU ABOUT THAT DOG,
BUT YOU TOLD HER
TIME AND TIME AGAIN,
HONEY, RELAX, THE
DOG IS HOUSE BROKEN.
AND NOW THERE'S A
SOFT, STEAMING TREAT
LYING ON HER
FAVOURITE ANTIQUE RUG
THAT WOULD TEND TO
CONTRADICT THAT
STATEMENT.
MAN, THAT'S
FUNNY, YOU KNOW.
THEM DOGS ALWAYS FIND
THE MOST EXPENSIVE
BIT OF FLOORING
TO DO THEIR
BUSINESS ON.
I THINK IT'S JUST
LIKE BIRDS FLYING
SOUTH,
IT'S PURE
INSTINCT.
ABSOLUTELY.
ALL RIGHT, THE FIRST STEP,
YOU GOT TO TAKE THE
MODUS OPERANDI,
THE DOG, GET
THAT OUTSIDE,
OPEN UP ALL THE
WINDOWS AND IF YOU
CAN SALVAGE THE RUG.
ABSOLUTELY.
NOW, IF YOU
CAN'T SALVAGE THE RUG,
REARRANGE THE
FURNITURE A
LITTLE BIT
AND TRY TO COVER
THAT TRAGEDY UP.
AND DON'T SKIMP
ON THE AIR FRESHENER.
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
NOW, IF, HOWEVER,
SHE KNOWS WHAT'S
GOING ON,
WELL JUST TELL HER,
HONEY, THE DOG IS
OUT IN THE TRUCK.
I COULD NOT FORGIVE
FIDO FOR DOING THAT
UNFORGIVABLE THING
ON YOUR FAVOURITE
CARPET,
SO I HAVE NO ALTERNATIVE
BUT TO DRIVE HIM
DOWN MYSELF
AND HAVE HIM
PUT TO SLEEP.
NOW, THIS IS A TACTIC THAT
SHOULD ONLY BE USED
BY A PROFESSIONAL.
WE CALL THIS PUPPY
POKER, ALL RIGHT?
OF COURSE YOU'RE
BLUFFING BUT YOU
GOT TO PLAY THE HAND.
AND IF YOU REALLY WANT
TO UP THE ANTE,
TELL THE KIDS.
NOW, THIS MIGHT SEEM
LIKE EMOTIONAL BLACKMAIL
BUT WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
A DOG HERE, MAN'S
BEST FRIEND.
THE STAKES ARE AS
HIGH AS YOU CAN GET.
HOPEFULLY SHE'LL FOLD,
SHE'LL THROW HER
ARMS AROUND FIDO,
PULL HIM OFF OF DEATH ROW.
BUT IF SHE
CALLS YOUR BLUFF,
YOU STAND A CHANCE
TO LOSE YOUR
SELF-RESPECT
AND YOUR FAVOURITE
FRISBEE FETCHER.
WELL, THIS IS WHERE
PLAN B KICKS IN.
YOU ZIP INTO TOWN,
BUY HER A DOG,
ONE OF THEM SOFT
CUDDLY ONES THAT
LOOKS LIKE A MOP,
YOU KNOW THE ONES.
LIKE A CAT
IN A DOG SUIT?
THOSE ARE THE GUYS.
LET HER EXPERIENCE
THE JOY OF OWNING
HER OWN PET,
THE UNBRIDLED
COMPANIONSHIP,
THE UNDENIABLE
AFFECTION.
YEAH, AND HOPEFULLY
WHEN THERE'S ANOTHER
MESS IN THE HOUSE,
THERE'S A 50 PERCENT
CHANCE HER DOG DONE IT.
WELL, WITH EVERYBODY
PAINTING THEIR CAR
UP AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK,
I THOUGHT I WOULD
TAKE HANDYMAN CORNER
AND SHOW YOU HOW YOU
CAN PREVENT YOUR CAR
FROM AGING, WEATHERING,
RUSTING AND GENERALLY
LOOKING FILTHY
ALL THE TIME
BY SHOWING YOU
HOW TO BUILD
A SELF-CONTAINED
AUTOMATIC POWER WASHER
THAT'LL KEEP YOUR CAR
CONTINUOUSLY CLEAN.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, THE FIRST THING
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
TO MAKE THIS UNIT
ARE SOME SPRINKLERS.
I WOULD RECOMMEND
YOU USE SPRINKLERS.
AND, YOU KNOW, YOU
CAN GET SPRINKLERS
PRETTY CHEAP
FROM YOUR NEIGHBOUR'S
LAWN WHILE THEY'RE IN BED.
NOW WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS TO MOUNT THESE VARIOUS
SPRINKLERS
RIGHT ON TO
THE VEHICLE.
YOU CAN USE RIVETS FOR
THAT OR YOU COULD WELD
THEM ON THERE
OR IF YOU WORK
FOR THE GOVERNMENT,
YOU PROBABLY HAVE
TIME TO SIT AND
MAGNETIZE THEM.
BUT I'M GOING TO USE
THE HANDYMAN SECRET
WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
NOW YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED A SOURCE
OF WATER,
ONE THAT MOVES ALONG
WITH THE CAR,
BECAUSE IT IS A
MOBILE WASH, ISN'T IT?
AND YOU KNOW WE HAVE
A SOURCE JUST LIKE
THAT RIGHT HERE,
THE WATER PUMP
AND RADIATOR.
NOW, IF WE CAN JUST
THINK OF A WAY TO
TAP INTO THEM.
THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GIVE OUR MOBILE
CAR WASH A TRY.
ALL RIGHT.
SEE, OKAY, OKAY.
[ ENGING REVVING ]
WE DON'T HAVE AN
UNLIMITED SUPPLY
OF WATER HERE.
YOU DIDN'T THINK
OF THAT, DID YOU?
SO WHAT WE HAVE TO
DO IS WE HAVE
TO OF COURSE
RECYCLE THE WATER IN
THE SYSTEM BY RECYCLING.
AND HERE IS WHAT YOU
HAVE TO DO TO SOLVE
THAT ONE.
YOU GOT TO MEASURE THE
EXACT PERIMETER OF
THE WHOLE CAR
AND THEN YOU GET
EXACTLY THAT SAME
LENGTH IN EAVESTROUGHING.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5....
26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32.
PERFECT.
I'M REAL
GLAD I DIDN'T
USE RIVETS OR BOLTS
WHEN I PUT THIS
UP LAST YEAR.
WE'LL GET THIS DOWN
AND WE'LL HOOK THIS
ALL UP TO THE CAR
RIGHT AROUND THE
WHOLE OUTSIDE OF HER
USING RIVETS
OR BOLTS OR --
THAT'S RIGHT, NOTHING
LASTS FOREVER EXCEPT
AN ITALIAN WEDDING.
NOW, THIS MIGHT TAKE
ME A WHILE TO GET
HER ALL DOWN
AND HOOKED UP,
SO WHY DON'T WE
GET BACK TO THE SHOW
AND I WILL COME
AND FIND YOU WHEN
I GOT HER ALL DONE.
Red Green:
STAY TUNED.
I GOT SOME ADVICE
FOR YOU MIDDLE AGED
GUYS ABOUT PLAYING CARDS
AND THEN BILL IS
GOING TO GO LONG,
PROBABLY TOO LONG.
I WANT TO TALK TO
YOU MIDDLE AGED GUYS
ABOUT SOMETHING THAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN
TO YOU.
NOW YOU MAY TRY
DENIAL FOR A WHILE,
YOU KNOW, BUYING A
TOUPEE OR TWO-SIDED TAPE
OR A TWO-SEATER CAR.
NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO,
SOONER OR LATER IT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN.
AND WHEN IT DOES, YOU'LL
KNOW YOU'RE OVER
THE HILL.
NOW, IT MAY HAPPEN
NEXT WEEK OR
NEXT MONTH,
BUT EVENTUALLY, THAT'S
RIGHT, SOMEONE
IS GOING
TO INVITE YOU
OVER TO PLAY BRIDGE.
NOW, I KNOW,
DON'T BE ALARMED.
PLAYING BRIDGE IS
A NATURAL PART OF
THE AGING PROCESS.
YOUR PARENTS HAD
TO DEAL WITH IT
AND NOW THAT YOU'RE
OLD, YOU HAVE TO FACE IT.
DON'T FIGHT IT.
JUST GO WITH IT.
BRIDGE IS NOT
THAT BAD OF A GAME.
THERE'S NO LOUD MUSIC
AND YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY KIDS
WHINING AT YOU FOR
THEIR ALLOWANCE OR
THE CAR KEYS.
PLUS YOU'RE PLAYING
WITH PEOPLE YOUR OWN AGE,
SO THEY'LL BE JUST
AS BORED AS YOU ARE.
AND YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE ALONE AT OUR AGE.
BRIDGE IS A LOT
BETTER THAN SOLITAIRE.
REMEMBER, I'M
PULLING FOR YOU,
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, THE RUSTPROOFING
SCHEME IS MORE OR LESS
MOVING FORWARD.
YOU KNOW, WE ALWAYS
TURN TO NATURE
WHEN WE'RE LOOKING
FOR INSPIRATION
AND OLD MAN SEDGWICK
POINTED OUT THAT
BEEHIVES DON'T RUST,
SO WE'VE ALL COVERED
OUR VEHICLES WITH HONEY.
UM, EXCUSE ME,
UNCLE RED,
THERE'S NO METAL
IN BEEHIVES THAT'S
WHY THEY DON'T RUST.
WELL, WHERE
WERE YOU HAROLD?
THAT COULD HAVE
MADE A DIFFERENCE.
UNCLE RED, ARE YOU
TELLING ME THAT
THE POSSUM VAN
IS COVERED
IN HONEY NOW?
NO, IT'S COVERED
IN FLIES NOW.
OH, WELL, THAT
SHOULD MAKE FOR
AN INTERESTING LOOK.
USUALLY THEY'RE JUST
ALL OVER THE GRILL.
WELL, CONSIDER THIS,
YOU'RE NO LONGER JUST
LEADER OF THE POSSUM
LODGE, YOU'RE LORD
OF THE FLIES.
YEAH.
WELL, HAROLD, YOU'RE
LORD OF THE FLAWS.
GIVE ME A HAND
HERE, WILL YOU?
SO HOW YOU GOING TO
GET ALL THE HONEY
OFF THE VAN?
WELL, I THOUGHT I'D
JUST DRIVE IT OUT
INTO THE WOODS
AND LET THE BEARS
LICK IT OFF
BUT THEN MOOSE THOMPSON
OFFERED TO DO IT FOR ME.
THE DRIVING
OR THE LICKING?
WELL, HE DIDN'T
ASK FOR THE KEYS.
AND I GOT OUR WHOLE MOBILE
CAR WASH UNIT ALL
HOOKED UP HERE.
IT LOOKS PRETTY
GOOD I THINK.
GOT THE EAVESTROUGH
RUNNING RIGHT AROUND
THE WHOLE
OUTSIDE OF THE CAR
WHICH COLLECTS ALL THE WATER
AND THEN I GOT THIS
PIPE HERE TO
SUCK HER UP
AND TAKE HER BACK
INTO THE WATER PUMP.
SO SHE IS NOW 100
PERCENT SELF-CONTAINED.
AND HERE IS ANOTHER
LITTLE RIG I ADDED
ALL ON MY OWN.
THIS HOSE RUNNING UP
OVER THE TOP HERE,
GOT SOME HOLES
CUT IN THERE,
'CAUSE I'M SAYING
TO MYSELF, HECK,
IF YOU'RE WASHING
YOUR CAR ANYWAY,
WHY NOT GIVE
HER A HOT WAX.
GOT THE HOT EXHAUST
COMING OUT OF
THE PIPE HERE
INTO THE JAR OF CAR WAX
AND THEN SHE'S SUCKED
UP THIS PIPE,
GOES UP OVER THE CAR,
COMES OUT THE LITTLE
HOLES IN A FINE MIST
ALL OVER THE CAR
PROTECTING THE FINISH.
[ CAR REVVING ]
ALL RIGHT.
SPRINKLERS OFF.
HOT WAX ON.
SO REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
HERE'S THIS WEEK'S
BOATING TIP WITH
GLEN BRACKSTON.
THANK YOU, RED.
FIRST OF ALL, I WOULD
LIKE TO SAY HI
TO EVERYBODY
DOWN AT THE
CARDIAC CARE UNIT.
IT'S BEEN 17 DAYS
AND NO PROBLEMS.
WOW, YOU HAD A HEART
ATTACK 17 DAYS AGO?
OH, NO, RED, NO.
17 DAYS AGO I ATE
A DOZEN BURITTOS
AND HAD CHEST PAINS
FOR A COUPLE OF WEEKS
AND THEN BOOM
THEY WERE GONE.
IT WAS KIND OF
A HISTORICAL MOMENT.
YEAH.
ANYWAY, THAT BRINGS
ME TO TODAY'S
BOATING TIP,
WHICH IS IN FACT SOME
BOATING HISTORY, RED.
UH-HUH.
WHAT'S INSIDE
THE BUCKET?
WATER.
WELL, POSSUM LAKE
WATER WHICH COMES CLOSE.
AND?
AND THERE'S A GOLF
BALL IN THERE.
SEE DOWN AT THE
POSSUM SKI AND
COUNTRY CLUB
THEY HAVE WATER TRAPS
AND THE WATER TRAPS
ARE FULL OF PERFECTLY
PRESERVED GOLF BALLS.
WELL, THERE'S A
GREAT BOATING TIP.
THANK YOU, GLEN.
NO, RED.
THE WATER PROTECTS
THEM FROM THE ELEMENTS.
THE WATER PRESERVES
THE GOLF BALLS.
IT KEEPS THEM PERFECT
UNDER THE WATER.
THAT'S WHAT THE SAILORS
USED TO DO IN HUDSON
BAY IN THE WINTER.
WENT GOLFING?
NO, THEY'D SINK
THEIR BOATS
AND THEN THEY WOULD
REFLOAT THEM IN
THE SPRING
AND WHEN THEY CAME
UP THEY WERE IN
BETTER SHAPE
THAN THEY WERE IF
THEY HAD BEEN EXPOSED
TO THE ELEMENTS ALL WINTER.
OH, SO YOU'RE SAYING
WE SHOULD ALL SINK
OUR BOATS
TO STOP THEM
FROM GETTING WRECKED.
NO, RED.
IF YOUR BOAT
GETS WRECKED, RIGHT,
AND IT SINKS.
YEAH.
CHANCES ARE YOU'RE
GOING TO FIND A
BETTER ONE
IN BETTER
SHAPE FREE AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE LAKE.
OH, NOW THAT IS
AN EXCELLENT
BOATING TIP.
THANK YOU,
GLEN BRACKSTON.
YOU KNOW MAYBE
WE SHOULD DO THAT
WITH OUR VEHICLES,
DROP THEM TO THE
BOTTOM OF THE LAKE
AND STOP THEM
FROM RUSTING, HUH?
YEAH, GO AHEAD.
JUST DON'T PUT
THEM NEAR THE
MARINA.
NO, PEOPLE WOULDN'T BE
ABLE TO TELL THEM
FROM YOUR BOATS.
Red Green: ANOTHER BIT OF
A FOOTBALL FEATURE ON
THE SHOW THIS WEEK,
BILL IS GOING TO --
SOMEONE TOLD ME BILL
DIDN'T HAVE THE BALLS
TO PLAY FOOTBALL BUT
THAT IS OBVIOUSLY
NOT CORRECT.
AND THIS WEEK HE THOUGHT
HE'D CONCENTRATE
ON THE
QUARTERBACKING,
THE THROWING.
SO WHAT HE'S DONE
THERE IS HE'S HUNG
A TIRE FROM THE GOAL POST
AND THE IDEA IS TO
STEP BACK A FEW FEET
AND TRY TO THROW
THE BALL THROUGH
THE HOLE IN THE TIRE.
AND IT SOUNDS
A LOT EASIER THAN...
HMMMM.
NOW YOU KNOW ONE
OF THE BIGGEST COMMODITIES
YOU HAVE IN YOUR LIFE
IS OF COURSE IS
YOUR TIME.
YOU KNOW THEY SAY THAT
ONE YEAR IN A DOG'S LIFE
IS EQUIVALENT TO,
I BELIEVE,
SEVEN YEARS IN
THE LIFE OF A HUMAN.
WELL, I CAN TELL YOU,
ONE HOUR WITH BILL
IS LIKE SEVEN YEARS
OF A DOG'S LIFE.
SO I'M STANDING THERE
WATCHING MY LIFE GO BY
WHILE MY DOGS
ARE KILLING ME.
BILL HAS NO CHANCE OF
DOING WHAT'S RIGHT.
HE'S GETTING CLOSER.
MAYBE I SHOULD
GIVE THIS A TRY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, BILL?
NO?
NO.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO DO A
BIT OF A PASS PLAY HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, BILL?
WHAT IS THAT?
OH IT'S A TOWEL, A TOWEL.
OH MY GOSH, HE'S
SEEN THOSE GAMES
WHERE THEY HAVE ALL THE --
THE CENTRE AS THAT
TOWEL SO HE CAN WIPE --
OH, BILL, BILL, BILL, BILL.
CAN WE GO BILL?
CAN WE GO NOW?
GIVE ME THAT.
YOUR HANDS ARE FINE.
ALL RIGHT.
SNAP THE BALL UP TO
BILL AND HEAD OUT
OF MY PATTERN --
OH, SORRY, BILL.
SNAP AGAIN.
OH.
BILL, YOU GOT TO --
YOU GOT TO --
BILL.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
TWO MINUTE WARNING.
I'M ON THE PASS --
COME ON, BILL,
TOSS IT.
I'M WIDE OPEN.
I SMELL TOUCHDOWN.
YOU GOING TO GRAB
THE BALL BILL?
SOFT HANDS.
YOU GOT SOFT HANDS.
SOFT SOMETHING.
OH, FOR GOSH SAKE.
TOO LATE, BILL.
TOO LATE.
FORGET IT.
I'M BACK.
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO NOW?
NO, NO, NOT
A HAND OFF.
ALL RIGHT, BILL,
YOU CROUCH DOWN.
MY TURN.
I'LL BE THE QUARTERBACK.
I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW IT'S DONE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T NEED
THE STUPID TOWEL.
SOMETHING ELSE I'D
WIPE MY HANDS ON.
THERE WE GO.
GET TOUGH.
COME ON, BILL.
THERE WE GO.
YOUR HANDS ARE ALL
KIND OF MOIST NOW
AND OUT HE GOES.
GO DEEP.
THAT'S A SITE TO
BE SEEN, ISN'T IT?
YOU LOOK GOOD
IN A SKIRT, BILL.
THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S BETTER.
TURN AROUND.
LET ME DRILL IT
OUT TO YOU.
I GOT A GOOD ARM.
HERE IS COMES.
LIKE A BULLET.
LIKE A SHOTGUN.
LIKE A RIFLE.
OH, MY GOSH.
WELL, HE DUCKED.
ALL RIGHT.
A LITTLE WEDGY ADJUSTMENT
AND I THINK WE'LL GET
BILL BACK TO AS
NORMAL AS HE GETS.
THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S MY MAN.
Red Green: COMING UP,
I CAN PROVE THAT IF YOU
EAT ENOUGH SALT
YOU WILL
ACTUALLY RUST
AND DALTON TRIES
TO KEEP A STRAIGHT
FACE GIVING YOU A PRICE.
WELL, THIS SUBMERGING
THE VEHICLES FOR
THE WINTER THING
I DON'T THINK IS GOING
TO WORK OUT SO WELL.
YOU KNOW, UNCLE RED,
YOU DO NOT HAVE TO TAKE
EVERY SUGGESTION
SOMEBODY GIVES YOU.
YOU CAN SAY NO, TOO.
HAROLD, IF I TOOK
EVERY SUGGESTION,
YOU WOULDN'T BE
HERE, BELIEVE ME.
ANYWAY, WE TRIED
THE SINKING THING WITH
STINKY PETERSON'S TRABANT.
WE GOT HER DOWN THERE
AND A LOT OF THE STUFF
FLOATED OUT FROM UNDER
THE SEATS AND MADE OUR
EYES WATER
AND KILLED A HALF
A DOZEN ROCK BASS.
YOU CANNOT LEAVE
HIS CAR DOWN THERE.
IT'S AN
ENVIRONMENTAL HAZARD.
WHEREAS YOU'RE
JUST A MENTAL HAZARD.
WE'RE GOING TO GET THE
CAR OUT OF THERE.
THAT'S WHAT THE
JUMPER CABLES ARE FOR.
UNCLE RED, IT'S NOT
GOING TO START
UNDER WATER.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
PULL IT OUT WITH
A CHAIN?
DID YOU ALSO
CONSIDER, YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN LIGHTEN
THE CAR'S LOAD IF YOU
WIND UP ALL THE WINDOWS
AND FILL IT FULL OF AIR
FROM A BICYCLE PUMP?
YEAH, THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT WE'RE DOING, HAROLD.
IT WON'T WORK.
'CAUSE STINKY'S
SUNROOF IS STUCK OPEN.
YOU DO NOT
TAKE ENOUGH TIME TO
THINK THINGS THROUGH.
YOU'RE RIGHT, HAROLD.
I'M GOING TO TAKE
TWO HOURS RIGHT NOW
AND I'M GOING
TO PLAN EVERY
DETAIL ON THIS.
EXCELLENT.
I'LL BE LYING
ON YOUR BED.
Red Green: YOU KNOW
THEY SAY THERE'S A
PLACE FOR EVERYTHING
AND EVERYTHING
IN ITS PLACE.
AND HERE WE ARE OUT
BY THE MAIN HIGHWAY
AT THE
EVERYTHING PLACE,
DALTON HUMPHREY'S STORE.
DALTON, PEOPLE
MIGHT DRIVE BY
THIS PLACE
AND ASSUME THAT
IT WAS A JUNK YARD.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
RED, ONE MAN'S JUNK
IS ANOTHER MAN'S OBJET D'ART.
NOW, WHAT DO YOU
THINK THIS IS, HUH?
I WOULD CALL
THAT SCRAP METAL.
YEAH.
TO YOU AND ME MAYBE.
BUT TO SOMEONE FROM
THE CITY, THAT'S A
PRECIOUS LITTLE
DECORATOR ACCENT THAT
JUST OOZES CHARM
AND HISTORY.
30 BUCKS WORTH OF
CHARM AND HISTORY.
NO KIDDING.
IMAGINE WHAT YOU'D GET
IF YOU FIXED IT AND
PAINTED HER?
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU
DROP THIS BY THE
LODGE LATER ON,
WE'LL SLAP A COAT OF
PAINT ON THAT WHILE
WE'RE DOING OUR CARS.
THAT'S A LOT OF
WORK THERE, YOU KNOW.
YOU JUST CAN'T
PAINT METAL.
YOU GOT TO SCRAPE
ALL THE RUST OFF.
YOU'LL WANT TO DO
THAT WITH YOUR
CARS, TOO,
OTHERWISE THE RUST
JUST COMES RIGHT
THROUGH.
OH MAN, THAT'S
A LOT OF WORK.
WELL, SEE, I'M NOT GOING
TO DO IT TO THAT PIECE
BECAUSE THAT WOULD
RUIN ITS VALUE.
IT HAS TO BE IN
UNRESTORED CONDITION.
THIS IS HOW DALTON
GETS PEOPLE FROM
THE CITY
TO COME UP HERE AND
GIVE HIM ALL KINDS
OF MONEY FOR JUNK.
I KNOW EVERY ITEM
IN MY INVENTORY.
I KNOW WHAT IT COSTS.
I KNOW WHERE IT IS.
IF A CUSTOMER ASKS,
I KNOW WHAT TO SHOW THEM,
WHAT TO CHARGE FOR THEM
AND HOW TO KEEP A
STRAIGHT FACE.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE TRYING
TO SELL A GUY A BROKEN
SHOVEL FOR 60 BUCKS,
YOU TRY NOT TO LAUGH.
PICK SOMETHING OUT
OUTSIDE, I'LL
SHOW YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE WE GO.
THERE.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
WELL, SIR, YOU CERTAINLY
HAVE AN EYE FOR QUALITY.
THIS IS AN ANTIQUE
HANDMADE WOODEN
SLED,
RED ROCKET, MADE IN
STOKE-ON-TRENT, ENGLAND
IN 1890-91, AND IMPORTED
BY THE SMITHER B. TOY
COMPANY OF WINNIPEG.
THIS IS THE DELUXE
MODEL, I BELIEVE,
VERY RARE
AND MUCH ADMIRED
BY THE COGNISENTI.
WELL, WHERE ARE
THE RUNNERS?
WHERE'S THE HANDLE?
WHERE'S THE BACK?
WHERE'S THE SLED?
THIS IS IN ORIGINAL,
UNRESTORED CONDITION,
AND AT AN AUCTION THIS
WILL FETCH UPWARDS
OF $5,000.
I'M WILLING TO LET
IT GO FOR YOU
FOR THREE.
3,000?
YEAH.
I SHOULD HAVE SAID --
I'M LAUGHING.
LET ME TRY THIS AGAIN.
LET ME TRY AGAIN.
[ METAL CREAKING SOUNDS ]
SEE WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
YOU TRY TO DO
THINGS RIGHT?
A BUNCH OF US GOT OUT
THE STEEL BRUSHES AND
THE SANDPAPER THERE
AND TRIED TO GET
THE RUST OFF OF
STINKY'S CAR.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU GOT MOST OF IT.
WE GOT ALL
OF IT, HAROLD.
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS,
WHEN THE RUST DUST
CLEARED
THERE WAS NOTHING
THERE BUT A WINDSHIELD,
FOUR TIRES
AND A FAN BELT.
YOU SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
THAT STINKY'S CAR WAS
PRETTY FAR GONE.
REMEMBER THAT TIME
HE TOOK IT THROUGH THE
AIRPORT METAL DETECTOR?
IT DIDN'T EVEN BEEP.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO DO
WITH IT.
I MEAN EVEN STINKY
TOOK THE TRABANT THERE,
GOT AN IDEA OF PUTTING
IT IN ONE OF THEM GIANT
GARBAGE BAGS,
THE GARBAGE MEN
TOOK IT AWAY.
THAT'S WHEN IT HIT US,
WE'RE SPENDING A
HUNDRED BUCKS TO
RUSTPROOF A CAR WORTH 50,
SO TO HECK
WITH IT.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD,
HAROLD, I'VE GOT TO
GET ALL THIS STUFF OFF.
I NEED A MAGNET
OR SOMETHING
I THINK.
AND IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING
AND I'M HOPING TO FIND
YOU IN AN ROMANTIC MOOD
AS I'M SURE I'LL BE
ONCE I GET THE RUST OFF.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GA UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
UNTIL NEXT TIME,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Red: C'MON, HAROLD,
GET 'EM UP.
Harold: OKAY, ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.