I know they call
it a pasta maker
but at the spaghetti setting
it makes a dandy
paper shredder.
This is handy for stuff
you don't want other
people to read.
Like say that speeding ticket
your wife was unaware of.
The possum van still got it.
But wait, there's more.
Take an ordinary pair
of plain, boring pants.
Adjust the rollers from
spaghetti to rigatoni,
that way the blades don't
cut all the way through
so you can
turn these babies
into stylish corduroy pants.
But wait, there's more.
Every woman loves curly hair
except for women
who have curly hair.
So here's what you do,
dial from rigatoni
to fusilli
and crank yourself
out a curly hairdo.
For women who
like to get kinky.
But here's the best part,
if you get ambitious
or just hungry,
you can actually use the
machine to make lasagna.
[ MACHINE CRANKING ]
Waiter, there's a fly
in my lasagna.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
No, no, no.
No, no, thank you.
All right.
I appreciate it.
Boy, I really do.
This is a huge day
up here at the lodge.
This show that
you're watching,
at least until you
can find the remote --
This show is our
300th episode.
How about that?
[ CHEERING ]
You told them
the big news, huh?
What?
You told them
the big news?
Yup, I just did.
I'm a little bit
nervous, actually.
I can't believe
I'm nervous.
You shouldn't
be, Harold.
I mean you've done
this 299 times before.
No, no, I'm referring
to the fact
that this is
my wedding day.
I haven't done that
before at all.
No, no, not any part
of it, actually.
You know what, your wedding
will be fine, Harold.
I was just saying this
is our 300th episode.
Yeah, yeah, that's
cool, 300, yeah.
You know, in 10-pin bowling,
300 is a perfect game.
You know, if this was
a bowling show --
If this was
a bowling show,
you'd be like
the head pin.
Well that would make you
the pin head, I'm thinking.
You know, that's
not a very nice way
to talk to the groom.
Oh well.
You know -- I thought,
especially since
I was going to ask you
to be my best man.
Oh geez, Harold.
What does the
best man do?
Does he pay
for anything?
No, no, no.
All you have to
do is show up.
Well that sounds
like a fit.
Where is the
wedding, anyway?
It's at Bonnie's church?
The Church of the
Wholly Unnecessary.
It's in the basement
of the welding shop.
Well, you know, suddenly
I have a good feeling
about this wedding, Harold.
You know, you get married
in a welding shop
you two will be
together forever.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Yeah!
Okay, today's prize
is this coupon
for a large canister
or pure oxygen
from Possum Lake's
only oxygen bar,
To Air Is Human.
Oxygen, your grandparents
talked about it,
now experience it firsthand.
Okay, cover your
orifices, Dalton.
Okay, Mr. Green,
you've got 30 seconds
to get Dalton Humphries
to say this word:
All right, Mike.
And Go!
Okay, Dalton, what do you
call it when it's over?
Marriage.
No, no, no.
I'm talking about you're
at a symphony concert.
What do you
call the ending?
Time to wake up.
Okay, every year
at the end
of the Possum Lake
Fireworks display,
there's a huge...
Insurance claim.
Okay, okay, Dalton.
Think big and finish.
Eric The Red?
No, okay, no, no.
This is not a person.
Okay, Dalton, do you
know what a climax is?
I used to.
We're almost out of
time, Mr. Green.
Okay, okay, Dalton.
When people see the last
episode of this show,
what will they say?
Oh, finally!
Close enough.
[ BELL RINGING ]
You know, the creation of
the perpetual motion machine
has been the most
baffling mystery
the world's great scientists
have ever faced.
But then they don't have
to fill out their own taxes.
You look at the famous
authors in these physics books:
Galileo, Isaac Newton,
Dionne Warwick...
Oh no, sorry, that's
a psychics book.
And why has their never been
a perpetual motion machine?
Because the great scientists
said it couldn't be done.
But then they also said
a school bus can't be made
amphibious and
flight-worthy.
Okay, that was
a lucky guess.
But this time, I'm going
to prove them wrong.
See, I'm not prejudiced
by previous, so called,
knowledge.
I don't have
a college degree.
I don't even have
a high school diploma.
Heck, if you only add up
the times I was listening,
I may not have any
education at all.
But I got a good imagination
and I know how things work
and I have a wife
who doesn't mind
if I'm out in the
backyard all day.
So all you need is stuff you
probably have lying around.
A gas lawn mower, a downspout,
a car alternator,
45-gallon drum, ceiling fan,
chunk of garden hose
and some corn stalks.
Now you're probably
saying, geez Red,
you're using everything
but the kitchen sink.
Well you're wrong.
Okay, I've always
thought I was smart
but this is a whole
different thing.
I'll try to go slow enough
for you to follow it.
I'm pretty excited here.
I replace the blade
of the lawn mower
with a pulley
and I've strung
this drivebelt
over to the pulley
on the alternator.
So when the lawn mower
starts up,
the alternator will generate
enough electricity
to run both the ceiling fan
and the garbage disposal.
Now the ceiling fan
is mounted like this
so when the corn gets as
high as an elephant's eye,
the fan'll poke it's eye
out by lopping off an ear.
Which will make it
fly through the air
and land in the
kitchen sink.
That'll kick on the
garbage disposal
which mulches the corn
and drops it into
our oil drum
where it decomposes and
ferments into ethanol.
Which is better
than gasoline
because it makes your
exhaust smell like popcorn.
Now, obviously, the ethanol
gets siphoned down through
our garden hose
back into the fuel
tank of the lawn mower
and completes
the circle of life.
Now I now most of you
are in total awe
but there's some skeptic
out there wondering,
Hey, what about the
downspout, Mr. Brainiac?
Well don't forget, this is
a perpetual motion machine
which means, well I
believe the word perpetual
means a long, long time.
You married folks know
what I'm talking about.
The downspout recycles
some of the corn seeds
back into the ground.
And those of you who've
watched this show
for a while
already know this...
the corn just
keeps on coming.
So, there you have it,
the perpetual motion machine,
the ultimate project.
I smell a Nobel
which is way different
than smelling a no onions.
The corn just
keeps on coming.
But I can retire happy now.
So remember, if the women
don't find you stunningly
handsome...
They should at least find
you geographically handy.
[ ENGINE FAILING TO START ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
You know, my wife
says I'm a person
who has a hard time
saying goodbye.
But that depends...
I know people, as soon
as they walk up to me,
I'm itching to say goodbye.
And I don't mean
au revoir, I mean adios.
But the truth is,
when people are friends,
they never really
say goodbye,
they stay in each
other's minds
and every time they
think about them,
they're together again.
I used to think that
every good memory
knocked a hair
out of your head.
So when you see
an old bald guy,
you know he's had
a pretty good life.
I guess the main point
I'm trying to make here
is that the
pattern of life
is such that nothing
lasts forever.
You're not supposed to get
pregnant when you're 72
and nobody over 40 should
ever take their shirt off.
So as we go through life,
it's important that we move
from one phase to the next
and we have to say
goodbye to the one
so that we can say
hello to the next.
You know, if I
say any more,
I'll probably burst into
that song from Titanic.
Anyway, let's just leave it
that it's been a great ride
and that every time we hear
the sweet sound of a script
being torn off a
roll of duct tape,
we'll think of each other.
We might even smile.
Remember, I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I've been doing
a little research
on this 300th
episode-thing.
That makes 15 seasons for us
so I've been comparing
that to other shows,
I think we should get
a special Emmy or something.
I mean, the other shows,
they ran almost as long
but they were good.
I mean, we're useless
and we're still here.
We're like Senators.
Uncle Red?
Yeah?
Everything's gone wrong.
My life is ended!
Wow, look at the time,
I've got to go.
Oh, no!
No, you get back here
and you help me
deal with this.
Are you talking
to me like that?
Yes, I am!
I got a little
bit of a problem.
Yes, you do, Harold.
The church burned down.
The welding shop was
doing a muffler job
and a huge fire started.
That was brazen.
Even if I got that,
that wouldn't be funny.
We don't have a
place to get married.
Well get married
here at the lodge.
This has got
to be as nice
as the basement
of a welding shop.
I suppose if we
clean it up a little.
Harold, all you need
to have a wedding
is a minister,
a man and a woman.
In fact, you don't even
need the woman any more.
That's another thing, too.
The minister begged off.
With the fire at the church,
he took the insurance money
and moved to Tahiti.
Wow.
Imagine, imagine that,
a man of the cloth.
Well now he's a man
of the loin cloth.
So who's going
to marry you?
Well you know, I did
a little research
and with you
as a lodge leader,
you have the power
to marry people.
You can marry
Bonnie and I.
I got to go from
Best Man to preacher?
That doesn't feel like a
promotion to me, Harold.
Why would I want
to do that?
Well, it's a dream assignment
for you Uncle Red.
You don't have
to do anything
and you get
to be in charge.
Oh, so it's the
exact opposite
of the groom's job.
Ye --
[ APPLAUSE ]
Bill had asked me to join
him behind the lodge.
He said he had
something for me
and you know, it was
the Rolling Stones
who said, you don't
always get what you want
or something like that.
I wasn't expecting him
to also run over my foot.
I didn't quite know
what was in store for me.
A whole bunch of junk
and he started off
with a stick.
Yeah, yeah, nice to see you.
What's that, why would
I want the stick?
And he's saying,
well this is back
when we did an
adventure way back
and we were looking
for fishing rod --
make our own fishing
rod out of a twig
and he had picked one up
and didn't see that other tree
and I remembered how funny
that had been, you know
and I thought, okay.
A bread knife, I didn't
recognized that either.
Oh yeah, we were looking
for food in the woods
and he were using a butt of
the handle to crack a walnut
and wanted me to
hold the walnuts.
It ended up almost like
a safety film for others.
Again, I certainly saw
the humour in that.
That was a funny moment.
Thank you, Bill,
I do recall that.
We're sharing fond
memories, obviously today.
And he's got this rig
for climbing poles
or climbing trees
or whatever with a harness
and the little spikes
that go in your feet.
And he had climbed
a tree back in --
I think the idea is he
was going to top the tree,
go up there with an
axe or a saw or whatever.
Boy, look how
young Bill looks.
And he got up to
the top of the tree
and you know, he was getting
a little bit tired there.
And what he didn't notice
was that the tree
had already been
topped earlier
but that didn't matter
because Bill had always
been a fan of cartoons.
Away you go, Bill.
Away you go.
Well, again,
another high spot.
Very funny, very,
very, very funny.
And then this one...
Oh no, I remember this one,
it was a Sumo wrestling --
Remember the Sumo wrestling
thing you did Bill?
Yeah, yeah.
That was a... boy.
I tell you, that was a tough
ride home on the subway.
You know...
I remember this one.
Remember the skeet
thrower, Bill?
It was in the winter
and we were getting --
You were showing me how
the skeet thrower worked.
You handed me the skeet
and you told me to --
I understood it was
to go over there
and pull the string
as fast as you can.
I didn't know you meant
in a few minutes.
That was unfortunate.
Bill doesn't
have a family.
But by golly, these
memories are flooding back.
Gosh that was enjoyable.
And now, I'm into it now.
So I'm looking for
other stuff --
I remember, oh yeah,
the metal detector.
Remember the metal
detector, Bill?
You were searching for
metal in the ground
and then you swept it up
by mistake and caught
it on the van
and the noise was just --
Remember how loud that was?
Did that aff --
I'm saying, did that
affect your hearing!?
No, apparently not.
Okay and what else
have we got here.
Oh yeah, the lacrosse.
Remember we did that --
We had kind of a
lacrosse-baseball mix
where Bill had
the lacrosse suit on,
he pitched the
lacrosse balls to me
and I hit them
with a baseball bat
and as far as I remember,
nobody got hurt.
Oh no...
Now there's something
we can both laugh at.
[ RED LAUGHING ]
Oh boy, life is good.
So Bill says, okay
it's all coming back.
He's done with it.
He doesn't need any
of this stuff any more.
How come and he
starts to cry.
What's going on?
He's leaving the lodge?
Bill, what's going on?
And a car pulls up and a
beautiful girl gets out
and I realize that Bill's
not crying, he's laughing.
Bill has made a better deal.
He's fine.
He's heading off.
This is a nurse!
This is perfect, it's
a match made in heaven.
Bill's going to spend
the rest of his life
with a nurse.
And as one parting shot,
he realizes he's still
got one of the lacrosse
balls in his pocket.
I'll take that over here.
Thank you, Bill.
And Bill jumps into the car
and says goodbye to everybody
and heads off on the biggest
adventure of his life.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Okay, we're all set
for the nuptials.
Not as big a turnout
as we'd planned but --
You know, as soon
as the wedding
became part of the show,
most of the guests
decided to stay home
and watch it on T.V.
So we'll finally get
some decent ratings.
Oh boy.
You okay, Harold, huh?
I think so.
I'm okay.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I'm nervous and I'm good.
You know, I'm not as bad
as I thought I'd be
because I thought I was
going to be pretty bad
but I'm okay
actually, I'm good.
I'm good.
I'm okay.
Good, okay, okay.
Before we have an embarrassing
puddle on the floor,
let's bring the
bride in here.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ HUMMING THE WEDDING MARCH ]
All right,
all right, okay.
All right, we're
gathered here together
to celebrate a big occasion
in all of our lives.
Very rarely does
a television show
stay on the air
for 300 episodes.
No, Uncle Red, Uncle Red!
Okay, okay.
We're gathered here
to join this woman
and this, I don't know,
this man, I guess
in holy matrimony.
And holy mackerel.
Okay, who has the ring?
Oh, I do.
That's not the ring.
That's my ring.
Oh, oh sorry.
Is it any of these ones?
No, it's not --
that's our ring!
Winston's wearing
our ring.
Where'd you get that?
Someone sold
it to me.
Okay, well never mind.
Harold, you put that
ring on Bonnie's finger
and then I want you to
recite all those vows
that you two made
and Harold, try
to keep it moving.
Okay.
I'd like to
thank everyone
who helped
shape my life.
I know you
meant well.
The good news is, it
brought me to this point
where I have found
a life partner
and I look forward
to spending
the rest of my
life with her.
Ditto!
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Wait a second.
If there's any one
who knows any reason
why these two should
not get married,
he should speak up now.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
It's meeting time.
No, no, no, no.
Harold, that can wait.
All right, so, do the two
of you take each other,
We do!
We're here,
we do.
Okay, well then,
I now pronounce
you man and wife.
Harold, you may...
kiss the bride.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Okay, so, if my
wife is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting
and after doing all of
these television shows,
I think I'm ready to go
back to live performances.
And to the rest of you --
Meeting time, Uncle Red!
You shouldn't
be here, Harold.
Bonnie thought it was
the right thing to do.
I told her, even
though we're married,
I'm still going to want
to come back to the lodge
every now and then.
Well, well, well,
you've turned
into a man.
I hope that's
a compliment.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Here's your
wedding gift.
Wow, that's a big
roll of duct tape.
It is, Harold.
I figured you're going
to be married a long time.
And to the rest of you
who've been watching us
all these years,
on behalf of myself
and the married man
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge,
Keep your stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Sit down.
C'mon everybody.
Hurry up, guys, sit down.
All rise.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
Sit down.
Bow your heads for
the revised man's prayer.
I'm a man
but I changed
because I had to
oh well.
[ APPLAUSE ]
The years that followed
saw a lot of changes
to the lodge members.
Mike Hammer became the
police chief of Possum Lake.
With Mike having
a legitimate job,
the crime rate
dropped to zero.
Winston got a job investigating
government corruption.
He knew the territory.
Dalton and Anne-Marie took
a second chance at happiness
by renewing their vows.
Ed Frid became the leader of
the local animal rights group.
Hap Shaughnessy told us he'd
been appointed ambassador
to Guam.
We hoped it was true.
Edgar K.B. Montrose attempted
to make his own heated recliner
using plastic explosives.
Hasn't been heard from since.
Harold and Bonnie were slowly
taking over the community.
In fact, everybody
changed except me.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]