OF TWO OR MORE PEOPLE
USING THE SAME FRIDGE
IS THAT WHEN YOU GO TO PUT
SOMETHING INTO IT,
THERE'S NO MORE ROOM.
AND WHY?
BECAUSE OF THE VEGETABLES.
EVERY FRIDGE
HAS THESE DRAWERS
THAT ARE SUPPOSED
TO KEEP VEGETABLES FRESH.
HOW DOES THAT WORK?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT AIRTIGHT.
THERE'S NO
LASER GUN IN THERE,
KILLING THE GERMS
AND BACTERIA.
IT'S NO DIFFERENT THAN
THE REST OF THE FRIDGE.
ANYWAY, YOU CAN'T STOP
VEGETABLES FROM GOING BAD.
THEY WERE BAD TO BEGIN WITH.
BUT YOU CAN'T JUST TAKE 'EM
OUT AND THROW 'EM AWAY,
CAN YOU?
OR SOMEBODY'D
BE VERY UPSET.
SOMEBODY WHO CAN DO
THINGS TO YOU IN THE NIGHT.
AND NOT THE THINGS
YOU WERE HOPING FOR.
WELL, HERE'S A WAY TO GET
RID OF YOUR VEGETABLES
WITHOUT LAYING
A FINGER ON 'EM.
I PUNCHED A HOLE IN
THE BACK OF THE FRIDGE.
AND I RAN THIS
VACUUM CLEANER HOSE
RIGHT INTO MY
VEGETABLE DRAWER.
AND I DON'T MEAN A NORMAL
HOUSEHOLD VACUUM CLEANER.
I'M TALKIN' HEAVY INDUSTRIAL.
THAT BABY COULD SUCK A
FOOTBALL THROUGH A FIRE HOSE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
RID OF THOSE VEGETABLES.
OKAY, UH, MY MISTAKE.
I HOOKED IT UP TO THE OUTPUT
SIDE OF THE VACUUM CLEANER.
[ CHUCKLING ]
OH, BOY.
OKAY, UM, TUNE IN NEXT WEEK
WHEN I SHOW ALL
YOU CAT LOVERS
HOW TO MAKE YOUR
OWN KITTY LITTER.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YEAH, THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
BOY, WE GOT A BIG, BIG IDEA
THIS WEEK UP AT POSSUM LODGE.
INSTEAD OF HAVING
GROUNDHOG DAY
THAT PREDICTS
THE END OF WINTER,
WE'RE GONNA HAVE
POSSUM DAY, EH,
PREDICTS THE END
OF SUMMER, SEE.
SO ON SEPTEMBER 2,
THE POSSUM COMES
OUT OF HIS TREE.
AND IF HE DOESN'T
SEE HIS SHADOW,
IT MEANS FALL IT
JUST AROUND THE CORNER.
IF HE DOES SEE HIS SHADOW,
IT MEANS WE GET SIX
MORE WEEKS OF SUMMER.
AND IF HE SEES HAROLD,
HE PLAYS DEAD.
UNCLE RED!
THE POSSUM DAY CAMPAIGN
IS JUST REALLY TAKING OFF.
REALLY? GREAT.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
THE RADIO STATION IS
GOING TO PROMOTE IT.
WE'RE GETTING A BIG PUSH
IN THE DAILY MOVEMENT.
OH!
OH, YES.
SO HAVE YOU GOT A POSSUM
FOR US TO USE THERE,
HAROLD?
HAVE YOU?
WELL, IT'S JUST --
[ MAKING SUCKING SOUND ]
NO.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
WE'RE GONNA
NEED A POSSUM.
WELL, THEY'RE REALLY
HARD TO CATCH.
THEY'RE NOT HARD TO --
THEY ARE HARD TO CATCH!
THEY'RE NOT
HARD TO CATCH!
BUT YOU GOTTA
USE YOUR BRAIN.
OH, REALLY?
YEAH!
SEE, YOU GOTTA
OUTSMART HIM, SEE?
SO YOU SAY, OKAY,
WHAT DO POSSUMS DO?
UM, NOTHING.
WELL, I MEAN, THEY'RE PRETTY
MUCH USELESS AND LAZY.
WELL, SEE,
OKAY.
YOU USE THAT TO
YOUR ADVANTAGE.
WHAT DO THINGS DO
WHEN THEY'RE USELESS
AND LAZY?
THEY GET THEIR OWN
TELEVISION SHOW?
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S PRIZE IS A COUPON
FOR 10 MINUTES OF FREE
LONG DISTANCE SERVICE,
COURTESY OF THE
WORLD WRESTLING FOUNDATION.
WHY NOT REACH OUT AND
[ deep voice ] CRUSH SOMEONE?
OKAY, COVER
YOUR EARS, DALTON.
RED, YOU'VE 30 SECONDS TO GET
DALTON TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, DALTON,
WHEN YOU GO INTO THE HOUSE,
THE FIRST THING YOU SAY IS,
HI, HONEY, I'M...
SORRY.
NO. OKAY, THERE'S A SONG.
I'LL BE BLANK
FOR CHRISTMAS.
OH, BROKE!
OKAY, WHEN GUYS
MAKE THEIR OWN BEER,
WHAT KIND OF
BREW IS THAT?
SKUNKY.
OKAY, THINK OF BASEBALL.
ALL THE PLAYERS
ARE TRYING TO GO...
ON STRIKE.
OKAY, DALTON,
WHEN YOU GET OLDER,
YOU MAY HAVE
TO GO INTO A...
PINE BOX.
UH, RED,
ALMOST OUTTA TIME.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
OKAY, DALTON, AROUND HERE
WE HAVE AN EXPRESSION...
KEEP THE SOMETHING
FIRES BURNING.
OH, THE TIRE FIRES!
YEAH, IF IT WASN'T FOR
THAT PLUME OF SMOKE
ON THE HORIZON,
I'D NEVER FIND
MY WAY HOME.
THERE WE GO!
Mike: YOU GUYS EVER
LIE TO YOUR WIVES?
Dalton: WELL, THAT DEPENDS.
Mike: ON WHAT?
Dalton: ON WHETHER
WE'RE GONNA LIE TO YOU.
YOU KNOW, MIKE,
EVERYBODY LIES TO
SOMEBODY SOME TIME.
DIDN'T DEAN MARTIN
SING THAT?
Mike: WELL,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SELL
ME ON THE POSITIVE ASPECTS
OF LYING, MR. GREEN.
LYING IS WHAT GOT ME
TO WHERE I AM TODAY.
Dalton: OUT ON BAIL?
Red: YEAH, OKAY,
I KNOW LYING IS WRONG.
I ONLY LIE WHEN
I HAVE TO.
Dalton:
"I ONLY LIE WHEN I HAVE TO"?
WHO'D LIE WHEN
THEY DIDN'T HAVE TO?
Red: HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
BUT WOMEN LIE TOO.
THEY JUST DO IT
DIFFERENTLY THAN MEN.
MEN AND WOMEN LIE
DIFFERENTLY?
Red: ABSOLUTELY.
SEE, WOMEN WILL LIE TO MAKE
OTHER PEOPLE FEEL BETTER;
MEN LIE TO MAKE
THEMSELVES FEEL BETTER.
HOW DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, MEN LIE ABOUT
WINNING, YOU KNOW,
IF THEY'RE IN A FIGHT,
OF EVEN IF THEY'RE IN
AN ACCIDENT.
AND THEY LIE
ABOUT FISHING.
WHERE'D YOU
HEAR THAT?
I READ IT SOMEWHERE.
YOU'RE LYING.
WELL, SURE I AM.
SEE, YOU KNEW THAT.
YOU KNEW I WAS
LYING, SEE?
MEN EXPECT MEN
TO LIE ABOUT STUFF.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S KINDA LIKE
EXAGGERATING.
LIKE, SAY YOU HIT YOUR
THUMB WITH A HAMMER.
WELL, IT WINDS UP,
BY THE TIME YOU'RE
FINISHED
THAT YOU'VE DUCT TAPED
YOUR ARM BACK ON
AFTER A BAND SAW
ACCIDENT, YOU KNOW?
EVERYBODY KNOWS
YOU'RE LYING,
BUT THEY STILL OH AND AH
JUST THE SAME, RIGHT.
IT'S A MASCULINE TRAIT.
MEN LIE TO EACH OTHER.
OKAY, I KNOW THAT.
BUT WHAT I'M ASKIN' IS DO
MEN LIE TO THEIR WIVES?
Dalton: WELL, I SUPPOSE
IT HAS HAPPENED.
I MEAN, HOW CAN YOU
BUILD A RELATIONSHIP
IF YOU'RE LYING
TO EACH OTHER?
Red:
OH, NO, NO, MIKE.
ONE YOU GET MARRIED,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING TO
BUILD A RELATIONSHIP.
Dalton:
YOU'RE IN SURVIVAL MODE.
OH, YEAH, SO WHEN SHE ASKS
YOU IF THAT DRESS LOOKS
TOO SMALL ON HER,
YOU LIE.
BUT THAT'S
PERJURY!
LYING IS
AGAINST THE LAW.
NOT WHEN IT'S DONE
IN SELF-DEFENCE!
AMEN.
HEY, I GOT GREAT NEWS.
ALL-WHEEL DRIVE AND
FOUR-WHEEL STEERING
IS NOT JUST FOR
THE SUPER RICH ANYMORE.
NOW THE SUPER POOR
CAN HAVE IT TOO,
THANKS TO TODAY'S PROJECT
ON HANDYMAN CORNER.
SO I FIGURED BETWEEN
THESE TWO K-CARS,
WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO MAKE
ALMOST ONE DRIVABLE VEHICLE.
THAT'S BECAUSE THE K-CAR HAS
NO REAL FRAME TO SPEAK OF,
AND THEY'RE
FRONT-WHEEL DRIVE.
YOU COULD SAY
IT'S SPINELESS
WITH A LOT OF DEAD WEIGHT
AT THE BACK END.
IT'S REALLY THE DALTON
HUMPHREY OF AUTOMOBILES.
FIRST THING WE GOTTA DO IS
DOWNSIZE EACH OF THESE BABIES.
IT'S THE EXACT OPPOSITE OF
THE WAY THEY DOWNSIZE
THE GOVERNMENT.
WE'RE GONNA KEEP
THE PART THAT WORKS.
DON'T BE SHY WITH THE
DUCT TAPE ON THIS JOB.
IT'S THE ONLY THING
HOLDING THE UNIT TOGETHER.
AND THERE'S NOTHING WORSE
THAN NAILING A SPEED BUMP,
ONLY TO HAVE YOUR BACK END
BREAK OFF AND START
CHASIN' YOU.
AND THERE WE HAVE THE MAKINGS
OF OUR FOUR-WHEEL-DRIVE,
ALL-WHEEL-STEERING VEHICLE.
AND HERE'S AN
ADDED BONUS...
STICK THE BACK ENDS
TOGETHER,
YOU GOT YOURSELF A DANDY
PORTABLE GARDEN SHED.
OKAY, THE BIG JOBS
ARE ALL DONE.
NOW WE JUST HAVE
THE MINOR DETAILS
OF CONNECTING THE
TWO SETS OF CONTROLS.
OKAY, NOW, THIS TOOK
A BIT OF BRAIN WORK,
BUT I THINK
I'M OKAY NOW.
SEE, FOR BOTH CARS
TO WORK TOGETHER,
YOU'VE GOT TO GET THE ONE
DOING THE EXACT OPPOSITE
OF WHAT THE OTHER
ONE IS DOING.
KIND OF LIKE A MARRIAGE.
I'VE GOT THE STEERING WHEELS
HOOKED TOGETHER
SO THAT WHEN I TURN
THIS ONE TO THE LEFT,
THE OTHER ONE GOES
TO THE RIGHT.
[ CREAKING ]
THIS BABY
TURNS SO SHARP,
YOU GOTTA BACK OFF
ON THE GAS,
OR YOU'LL RUN INTO YOURSELF.
SAME THING WITH
THE TURN SIGNALS.
I SIGNAL RIGHT
ON MY END...
BUT THE REAL TRICK
IS THE GEAR SHIFT.
I HOOKED THEM UP SO WHEN
I GO INTO DRIVE AT MY END
IT GOES INTO REVERSE
AT THE OTHER END.
OH, SURE I GOT
A COUPLE OF PROBLEMS,
LIKE, I GOT NO TRUNK,
NO BRAKE LIGHTS
AND NO EXHAUST PIPE,
BUT THAT'S A
SMALL PRICE TO PAY
TO BE DRIVING WITH
CUTTING EDGE TECHNOLOGY.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE
WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU...
[ COUGHING ]
KIDS ALWAYS NEED MONEY
FROM THEIR PARENTS.
THAT'S FINE.
AND GENERALLY, PARENTS WILL
ALWAYS OPEN THEIR WALLETS
FOR THEIR OFFSPRING
FOR ANY REQUEST
THAT DOESN'T CONTAIN
THE WORD "BAIL."
BUT YOU MAY BE
AT THE POINT
WHERE THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT
A DIFFERENT KIND OF MONEY.
I MEAN THE INHERITANCE.
THE BIG POST-DATED CHEQUE.
WELL, THIS IS WHERE
I DRAW THE LINE,
ONE OF THE FEW TIMES
WHERE MY ADVICE IS...
SHOOT THE WORKS, BABY!
I'M SAYIN', SPEND IT.
IF YOU CAN'T TAKE IT WITH
YOU, WHY PACK IT?
THAT LEATHER CHAIR
THAT MASSAGES YOUR BACK
WHILE IT PLAYS
"IN A GADDA DA VIDDA,"
YOU GO FOR THAT!
THAT PICK-UP TRUCK
THAT SITS UP SO HIGH
YOU CAN SEE WHERE YOU'RE GOIN'
HALF AN HOUR BEFORE YOU
GET THERE,
RING 'ER UP!
AND MAYBE IT'S TIME TO
PUT IN THAT WET BAR
BESIDE THE POOL;
AND WHEN THAT'S DONE,
PUT IN THE POOL
BESIDE THE WET BAR.
THE POINT IS
WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T FEEL GUILTY ABOUT IT.
YOU RAISED THOSE KIDS,
AND YOU PAID FOR THEM.
WHATEVER MONEY
YOU HAVE NOW IS YOURS.
AND A LEFTOVER'S
NEVER TASTED SO SWEET.
REMEMBER I'M
PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, WE
INTERRUPT "THE RED GREEN SHOW"
SO THAT I MAY BRING YOU
THE FOLLOWING IMPORTANT
ENVIRONMENTAL MESSAGE.
GREETINGS, CAMPERS.
RANGER GORD HERE WITH ANOTHER
ONE OF MY PATENTED....
Gord: HEY NOW, HERE'S
A PLEASANT SCENE...
A COUPLE OF BACKWOODS
DOUGHNUT BRAINS
HAVING SOME FUN ON
THE DIVING BOARD.
HOWEVER, WHAT THEY
MIGHT NOT UNDERSTAND
IS THAT DANGER IN
THIS SPORT OF "DIVING,"
IF TAKEN TO ITS
EXTREME LEVEL --
I AM OF COURSE TALKING
ABOUT THE TERRIFYING
OVERLOOKED SPORT
OF CLIFF DIVING.
NOW, BEFORE ANY DIVE IS
ATTEMPTED FROM A HEIGHT
OF THIS MAGNITUDE,
ONE MUST FIRST DISCERN WHETHER
THERE ARE ANY ROCKS OR
OTHER DEBRIS
IN THE LANDING AREA.
WELL, HO-HO, IT'S A
GOOD THING HAROLD
POINTED OUT THE DANGER DOWN
THERE FOR US, HEY, RED?
THAT'S ANOTHER DIVING TIP,
ALWAYS GO WITH A BUDDY.
NOW, COME ON, RED.
LET'S FIND A SAFER SPOT.
UH, GORD, UH --
UH, THIS IS PRETTY HIGH.
UH, I MEAN A GUY
COULD GET HURT
ON A JUMP LIKE THIS.
Gord: OH, COME ON, RED.
DON'T BE SUCH A WUSS.
FOLKS, IT'S A PROVEN FACT
THAT IF YOU PLAY A
SPORT AFRAID,
YOU ARE MORE LIKELY
TO GET INJURED.
AND YOU DON'T WANNA GET
INJURED, DO YOU, LITTLE RED?
UH, NO, NOT REALLY.
HA! HA! GOOD.
[ SCREAMING ]
SO REMEMBER, KIDS,
NEVER TAKE A RIDE ON
THE WING OF A PLANE,
UNLESS PROPERLY
LICENSED TO DO SO.
IT'S JUST COMMON SENSE,
ISN'T IT?
WELL, GREAT NEWS.
WE MANAGED TO CATCH
OURSELVES A POSSUM.
ALL WE HAD TO DO WAS
SET THE TRAP UPSIDE DOWN.
SO NOW WE'RE IN BUSINESS,
AND THE POSSUM DAY THING
IS REALLY PICKING UP
A LOT OF MOMENTUM.
ACTUALLY, THE T.V. STATION
UP IN PORT ASBESTOS
SAYS THEY'RE GOING
TO SEND A CREW DOWN,
UNLESS THERE'S ANYTHING
IMPORTANT GOING ON THAT DAY.
OR ANYTHING
GOING ON THAT DAY.
OH, UNCLE RED!
OH! THERE'S BEEN A
POSSUM-NAPPING.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT
THEY DO, HAROLD.
NO. NO.
SOMEONE HAS
KIDNAPPED OUR POSSUM.
YEAH, WE THINK IT'S THE
GUYS FROM CARIBOU LODGE.
THEY'RE SO JEALOUS.
THEY'RE JEALOUS
OF US?
THAT'S HARD TO DO,
HAROLD.
WELL, DON'T YOU WORRY --
DON'T YOU WORRY,
BECAUSE MAYBE WE DON'T
HAVE A REAL POSSUM,
BUT WE STILL HAVE
OUR POSSUM MASCOT!
WHAT?
NO. NO.
YEAH. YEAH.
MIKE, WHERE IS
YOUR PRIDE?
MR. GREEN,
THIS COUNTS TOWARDS
MY 100 HOURS OF
COMMUNITY SERVICE.
THIS IS NOT GONNA
WORK, HAROLD.
OKAY, HOW 'BOUT MIKE
SNEAKS BACK INTO
CARIBOU LODGE
AND GETS
OUR POSSUM BACK?
YEAH, 'CAUSE I LOOK
JUST LIKE ONE.
WATCH.
Harold:
HAVE YOU SEEN ENOUGH?
YOU'RE TOO LATE.
Red: KIND OF AN UNUSUAL
ADVENTURE THIS TIME.
WINSTON HAD JUST
FINISHED A DAY'S WORK,
AND AS PER USUAL,
HE WAS CHECKING HIS CASH,
AND THERE WAS A SMALL
CRIME WAVE AT THAT MOMENT.
A GUN COMES IN -- THIS NEVER
HAPPENS AROUND HERE, BUT...
AS IT TURNS OUT,
JUST A WATER GUN FROM WALTER.
OH, NOW WINSTON GRABS THAT
AND TAKES AFTER HIM.
THIS IS HOW THINGS START.
AND THIS IS A REAL LESSON
OF HOW THE WORLD WORKS
WITH THE ARMS RACE
AND SO ON.
WINSTON HAS THE LITTLE GUN.
HE'S SNEAKING UP ON WALTER.
A LITTLE PAYBACK TIME,
BUT WALTER TURNS AROUND
AND HE HAS A
MUCH BIGGER GUN,
AND HE UNLOADS THAT ON HIM.
SO NOW WINSTON
GRABS THAT ONE.
NOW HE'S ESCALATED
HER A BIT,
SO WALTER'S GOING TO TAKE
IT UP TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
WINSTON COMES AROUND THERE.
I DON'T THINK HE'S
IN THE WOOD PILE.
AND I DON'T THINK HE'S
IN THAT EMPTY TRAILER EITHER.
I DON'T THINK HE'S
THERE OR THERE.
HERE HE COMES, AND,
YOU KNOW, I'M THINKIN'
HE MAY HAVE
SOMETHING FOR YOU,
BUT WINSTON FIRST
OF ALL FIRES THE --
WINSTON'S OUTTA WATER.
DON'T WORRY.
HERE'S SOME.
SO NOW WE'RE UP
ANOTHER LEVEL.
SO NOW IT'S GUNFIGHT
AT THE OK CORRAL.
VERY GOOD TURN OUT
FOR A TUESDAY.
OH, WALTER'S TAKIN'
IT TO ANOTHER LEVEL.
WINSTON... HMM.
WE'VE ALL HAD DAYS
LIKE THAT, HAVEN'T WE?
OH, BOY.
SO NOW WINSTON GOES
DOWN TO THE STORE
AND GETS SOMETHING
REAL SUPER DUPER.
PUMPS THAT UP.
OH, YEAH, BABY.
HE'S READY TO GO.
HE'S GOIN' NUCLEAR.
WHAT HE DIDN'T REALIZE WAS
THAT WALTER HAD BEEN TO
THE SAME STORE
JUST BEFORE WINSTON AND HAD
GONE WITH THE DOUBLE
EXTRA LARGE.
LOTTA WATER IN THAT THING
AS WINSTON'S PANTS
WERE ABOUT TO FIND OUT.
SO NOW WALTER'S GOING
TO THE MAXIMUM HERE.
HE'S GOT THE BACKPACK
TANKS ON THERE,
AT THE SUPER-HOWITZER LEVEL.
WINSTON JUST
HAS A LITTLE GUN,
BUT HE DOESN'T SEEM
TO BE WORRIED.
HE'S ACTUALLY
WAVING WALTER OVER.
HE'S READY TO TAKE HIM ON.
WALTER CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU'RE GONNA TAKE ME ON
WITH THAT LITTLE THING?
LOOK AT THIS BABY.
I GOT LIKE A BAZOOKA.
I MEAN, YOU ARE
GONNA DROWN.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA DROWN.
WINSTON SAYS,
NO, NO, WAIT A SEC.
IT'S NOT THE SIZE
OF THE GUN, YOU KNOW.
CHECK THE HOSE.
TAKE A LOOK.
SEE THAT? YUP.
YEAH. YEAH. YEAH.
OH, IT'S NOT PLUGGED
INTO THE CHAIR, NO.
IT'S NOT -- OH, BOY!
I THINK THIS IS WALTER'S
WAY OF SURRENDERING.
THERE YOU GO.
LET HER GO.
YOU EVER NOTICE
THAT OVER THE YEARS
YOUR DASHBOARD HAS CHANGED FROM
A BUNCH OF DIALS AND GAUGES
INTO NOTHING BUT
IDIOT LIGHTS.
THAT CAN'T BE A COMPLIMENT.
AND WHO CAN REMEMBER
WHAT THEY ALL MEAN?
WHENEVER I LOOK AT
THAT SYMBOL,
I DON'T KNOW WHETHER I'M
SUPPOSED TO ADD OIL
OR MAKE THREE WISHES.
SO I'M GONNA MAKE
A FEW ALTERATIONS.
FIRST OF ALL, I'M GONNA
PUT IN SENSIBLE SIGNS.
AND I'M ALSO GONNA HAVE A WAY
THAT I CAN ADD FLUID
WITHOUT HAVING TO
GET OUT OF THE CAR.
HECK, WITHOUT EVEN
HAVING TO STOP.
NOW, I'M GONNA DO THAT BY
SWITCHING FROM SOMETHING
NOBODY UNDERSTANDS...
THE CARS OF TODAY,
TO SOMETHING EVERYBODY
UNDERSTANDS...
BREAKFAST.
OKAY, FIRST THING YOU
WANNA DO IS TAKE YOURSELF
HALF A DOZEN OF THESE
MAPLE SYRUP DISPENSERS
THAT THEY USE IN
RESTAURANTS.
I WOULD RECOMMEND THAT YOU
GET THESE FROM ANY DIMLY
LIT 24-HOUR DINER.
THE KEY COMPONENT HERE, SEE,
IS THE SPRING LOADED NOZZLE
THEY GOT ON THE
TOP OF HER THERE.
JUST ADD A WIRE
TO THIS BABY,
FILL IT WITH THE
APPROPRIATE FLUID,
AND YOU'RE ON YOUR WAY
TO HAPPY MOTORING.
EACH OF THESE BOTTLES IS
FILLED WITH A DIFFERENT
AUTOMOTIVE FLUID.
AND I GOT THEM MOUNTED OVER
EACH OF THESE FILLER TUBES.
THEN I RAN ALL THE WIRES
THROUGH THE FIRE WALL,
AND IN KEEPING WITH
THE BREAKFAST MOTIF,
I ATTACHED A PICTURE
ONTO EACH WIRE
THAT WOULD ASSOCIATE
A FLUID DEFICIENCY
WITH A BREAKFAST FOOD.
NOW EVEN FOR YOUR CAR,
BREAKFAST IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT MEAL OF THE DAY.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
OIL HAS GOT TO BE GREASE;
GREASE, WELL,
THAT HAS TO BE BACON.
BRING HOME THE BACON.
AND IF THE RAD BOILS OVER,
WELL, THAT'S GOTTA
BE COFFEE.
IF THE TRANSMISSION
STARTS GRINDIN',
THAT'D BE SAUSAGES.
AND IF YOUR ENGINE
STARTS FRYIN',
WELL, THAT WOULD
BE THE EGGS.
THIS BABY IS TOAST.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED,
MR. GREEN!
YOU SURE HE'S
IN THERE, MIKE?
OH, YEAH.
HE'S IN THERE,
ALL RIGHT.
LET ME SEE
HIM, RED.
UNCLE RED! UNCLE RED!
THE GUYS FROM
CARIBOU LODGE,
THEY PULLED THE
OLD SWITCHEROO.
WHAT ARE TALKI''
ABOUT, HAROLD?
THE POSSUM,
IT'S NOT A POSSUM.
SURE LOOKS LIKE A
POSSUM, DOESN'T IT?
YEAH, LOOKS LIKE A POSSUM,
ACTS LIKE A POSSUM.
OF COURSE, THAT'S WHAT
YOU GET WHEN YOU SHAVE
A SKUNK!
Winston:
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
Red: DON'T YOU SMELL
ANYTHING, WINSTON?
OH, SORRY.
I CAME STRAIGHT FROM WORK.
IS THAT A NEW RUG?
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GUYS
GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO SLEEP
IN THE GARAGE TONIGHT,
EVEN THOUGH WE DIDN'T
HAVE AN ARGUMENT.
SO WAIT A SEC -- THE NEXT TIME
WE DO HAVE AN ARGUMENT,
I WANNA COUNT
THIS AS A CREDIT.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, WE'RE GONNA KEEP
THIS MEETING PRETTY SHORT,
BECAUSE A FEW OF US HAVE
TO TAKE OFF ALL OUR CLOTHES
AND BURN 'EM.
WHAT'S GOIN' ON?
WE'RE CHANGING.
WHY?
BECAUSE WE HAVE TO,
I GUESS.