IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW."
NOW, PLEASE HELP ME
WELCOME A MAN WHO
BELIEVES THAT CHARITY
SHOULD START AT HOME
BUT NOT WHEN HE'S HOME...
YOUR HOST, YOUR HERO,
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN.
(APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
KIND OF A FRUSTRATING
WEEK UP AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK.
WE GOT THIS HISTORICAL SOCIETY;
POSSUM LAKE HISTORICAL SOCIETY.
THINKS EVERYTHING SHOULD BE THE
SAME WAY IT WAS 100 YEARS AGO.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING, NEW
IS A LOT OF TIMES BETTER.
YOU KNOW, THE ADVERTISERS SAY,
"NEW AND IMPROVED."
YOU DON'T HEAR,
"OLD AND IMPROVED."
NOTHING GETS OLD AND IMPROVED...
EXCEPT YOU, BERNICE.
ACTUALLY, UNCLE RED, I THINK
WHAT THEY'RE DOING IS A
VERY GOOD IDEA.
I THINK IT'S GREAT,
PRESERVING OUR HERITAGE.
HISTORY IS  AN
EXCELLENT TEACHER.
IF YOU WANT TO CLUE
INTO THE FUTURE,
LOOK INTO THE PAST.
OH, YEAH, HAROLD, IF YOU WANT
TO CLUE INTO YOUR FUTURE,
LOOK INTO THE MIRROR.
THIS HISTORICAL SOCIETY,
THEY'VE HAVE BEEN
CALLING ME ALL WEEK.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY WANT --
PROBABLY A DONATION.
AND FOR WHAT?
THEY'RE LIKE A TELETHON
WITHOUT A DISEASE, YOU KNOW?
I'LL TELL YOU, I WOULDN'T
GIVE 'EM A DIME,
NOT ONE DIME.
OH, YOU MIGHT
CHANGE YOUR MIND.
WHAT HAVE YOU
GOT THERE, HAROLD?
THIS? OH, THIS?
O-O-H, THIS.
YES.
WELL, THIS IS JUST A LETTER
FROM THE HISTORICAL SOCIETY
WITH A PROPOSAL THAT THE
LODGE MIGHT BE DEEMED A
HISTORICAL LOCATION.
WOW, ALL RIGHT.
NOW YOU'RE TALKING.
YES, AND SO WERE YOU.
WHAT WERE YOU SAYING?
OH, AH, OH, RIGHT.
IF ANYBODY FROM THIS
HISTORICAL SOCIETY
IS WATCHING,
I CERTAINLY HOPE YOU DIDN'T
MISUNDERSTAND SOME OF MY
EARLIER COMMENTS.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU LET ME FINISH,
I WAS --
WHAT I MEANT WAS THAT
I THINK THE LODGE HERE IS A
PERFECT PLACE FOR YOU TO SPEND
YOUR RESTORATION DOLLARS.
AND IF YOU DO HAPPEN TO CHECK
YOUR VOICE MAIL LATER,
AND HEAR A MESSAGE FROM ME
THAT INCLUDES THE PHRASE
"UP YOURS WITH A WIRE BRUSH,"
THAT WAS REALLY TALKING ABOUT
A CERTAIN KIND OF WIRE BRUSH
THAT THE PIONEERS USED.
THEY OFTEN WOULD CLEAN -- THE
OLD WIRE BRUSH CLEANINGS
THEY WOULD DO ON BUILDINGS,
LIKE THE LODGE, WHICH
ARE OUR HERITAGE.
WE INHERITED THEM.
HOW CAN YOU STAND THERE AND SAY
THINGS THAT DON'T HAVE A
SHRED OF TRUTH TO THEM?
WELL, THAT'S SOMETHING THAT
MARRIED PEOPLE JUST DO, HAROLD.
EXCEPT FOR US, BERNICE.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
HERE'S A FEW SCENES FROM THIS
PARTICULAR EPISODE, AND IF YOU
HAVEN'T DECIDED WHETHER OR NOT
TO WATCH IT,
WE'RE HOPING THIS WILL KIND OF
PUSH YOU OVER THE TOP ON THAT.
WE'RE GOING TO TRY AND
ENTERTAIN YOU AS LONG
AS WE CAN.
WE EVEN GOT SOMETHING
FOR YOU TO DRINK...
A BIG BOTTLE OF COLA.
RICHARDSON'S MUSIC STORE IS
LOOKING FOR A PIANO TEACHER.
APPLICANTS MUST BE FEMALE WITH
AT LEAST 50 YEARS EXPERIENCE,
BLUE HAIR AND FUNNY
SMELLING CLOTHES.
OH.
SO I GO AGAINST
MY BETTER JUDGMENT,
I LET THEM CLASSIFY THE LODGE
AS A HISTORICAL SITE,
THEY LAY THIS ON ME.
RULES AND REGULATIONS...
WHAT I CAN DO;
WHAT I CAN'T DO;
HOW I HAVE TO MAINTAIN THE
INTEGRITY OF THE BUILDING.
WHY SHOULD THE BUILDING HAVE
INTEGRITY IF THE PEOPLE
IN IT DON'T?
YEAH, BUT, UNCLE RED, THE
HISTORICAL SOCIETY IS PAYING
FOR ALL THE WORK, AREN'T THEY?
YEAH, RIGHT.
THEY'LL COVER 1/3 OF THE
RESTORATION COST UP TO
A MAXIMUM OF $50.
THIS ROOF REPAIR ALONE
IS GOING 500 BUCKS,
AND THAT'S JUST FOR
THE DUCT TAPE.
NA, NA, NA, NA-NA, NA!
SEE WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
DON'T READ THE FINE PRINT?
YEAH, YOU END UP HAVING YOUR
NEPHEW WORK FOR YOU.
ANYWAY, I HAVE A
BETTER SOLUTION.
I GOT THE HISTORICAL SOCIETY
TO DECLASSIFY THE LODGE
AND LEAVE US ALONE.
AND WE'VE AGREED TO DONATE
OUR OLD SMOKEHOUSE
WHICH IS THE MOST
HISTORICAL THING WE HAVE.
WHAT'S SO HISTORICAL
ABOUT THE OLD SMOKEHOUSE?
WELL, HAROLD, IT WAS
BACK IN, I BELIEVE, 1856,
THE FIRST SETTLERS CAME,
AND THEY BUILT THAT OLD
SMOKEHOUSE AS KIND OF
A CRUDE CABIN
TO GET THEM THROUGH
THAT FIRST ROUGH WINTER.
AND, I BELIEVE,
WHEN THEY BUILT
A LARGER HOME,
THEY CONVERTED THAT BUILDING
INTO THE SMOKEHOUSE YOU SEE NOW.
OH, REALLY?
OH, OH.
YEAH, YEAH.
WELL, HOW COME IT'S JUST A,
LIKE, A PRE-FAB PIECE OF PLYWOOD
THAT WE USE AS A TOOLSHED NOW?
BECAUSE YOU'RE LYING,
THAT'S WHY.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, I BELIEVE IT
WAS ABRAHAM LINCOLN WHO SAID
THAT HISTORY IS TINGED WITH
TRUTHS AND HALF TRUTHS
THAT ARE AS ONE.
HE NEVER SAID THAT.
YOU'RE LYING AGAIN.
NO.
YES.
UNCLE RED IS
MAKING LIES.
NO, UNCLE RED IS
MAKING HISTORY.
(APPLAUSE)
OKAY, IT'S TIME TO PLAY THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME.
AND, THIS WEEK, WE'RE PLAYING
FOR A BEAUTY OF A PRIZE.
IF YOU OWN A MAGIC MASTER
REFRIGERATOR/FREEZER WITH
A SELF-DEFROSTING UNIT,
AND IT'S GOT THE HIGH
EFFICIENCY THERMOSTAT,
WELL, THEN, YOU'VE GOT
THE PERFECT PLACE TO STORE
THIS WEEK'S GRAND PRIZE...
A BIG BOTTLE OF COLA.
(APPLAUSE)
YES, MADE AVAILABLE FROM
RITA'S SUNDRIES AND SUCH.
OKAY. UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30
SECONDS TO GET Mr. MIKE HAMAR
TO SAY THIS WORD...
SERVE.
THIRTY SECONDS, AND GO.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE, YOU GO
INTO A STORE, THE CLERK
COMES OVER AND SAYS,
"HAVE YOU BEEN..."
SHOPLIFTING?
NO, THIS IS IN A NICE WAY,
SHE SAYS, "MAY I SOMETHING YOU"?
STRIP SEARCH?
OKAY, IT'S A RESTAURANT --
IT'S A RESTAURANT.
YOU GO IN THE RESTAURANT AND
THE WAITRESS COMES OVER TO...
HASSLE ME.
NO, MIKE, SHE'S FRIENDLY.
SHE SAYS, "CAN I SOMETHING YOU?"
WELL, HOW FRIENDLY IS SHE?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU
LIVED AT HOME, OKAY?
DINNER WAS READY; YOUR MOM
WOULD SAY, "DINNER IS..."
POURED?
ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
UNCLE RED.
OKAY, OKAY.
MIKE, THE OUTSIDE OF A POLICE
CAR, IT SAYS, "TO SOMETHING
AND PROTECT"?
I DON'T KNOW. I JUST SEE
THE HEADLIGHTS AND THEN
THE BACK SEAT.
DON'T YOU -- DON'T YOU NOTICE
ON THE OUTSIDE OF THE DOOR
AS YOU'RE GETTING IN?
NO, I'M USUALLY UNCONSCIOUS.
AND THEN I HAVE MY JACKET OVER
MY HEAD WHEN I GO TO JAIL,
AND I TRY TO KEEP IT THERE
UNTIL I'VE SERVED MY SENTENCE.
(RINGING BELL)
ALL RIGHT, A BIG
BOTTLE OF POP.
LAST SATURDAY, I WAS MOWING THE
LAWN IN A KIND OF A HURRY
BECAUSE THE AFTERNOON MOVIE
WAS "WHERE EAGLES DARE."
AND IT'S KIND OF A GUY MOVIE.
YOU KNOW:  GOOD GUYS, BAD GUYS.
AND THEY MAKE WAR
KIND OF LOOK LIKE FUN;
YOU'VE GOT TO LOVE THAT.
UNFORTUNATELY, I WAS MOWING THE
LAWN AT THE FULL SPEED, AND
ON MY LAST PASS THERE,
I SIDESWIPED BERNICE'S CEMENT
LEPRECHAUN LAWN ORNAMENT.
YOU KNOW HOW THEY SAY THAT
LEPRECHAUN'S ARE LUCKY?
I'LL TELL YOU, THIS ONE'LL
NEVER GET LUCKY AGAIN.
AND THE LAWN TRACTOR DIDN'T
FAIR MUCH BETTER.
NOW, SOME CYNICAL
PEOPLE MIGHT SAY,
"BOY, IT'S GOT TO BE MORE
THAN A COINCIDENCE THAT YOU
WRECK YOUR OLD LAWN TRACTOR
"THE DAY AFTER YOU SEE THE
NEW LAWN TRACTORS DOWN AT
MURRAY'S STORE."
BUT, BERNICE,
BELIEVE ME, I WAS UPSET.
I COULD HARDLY ENJOY
"WHERE EAGLES DARE."
BUT, YOU KNOW AT THE END
THERE, WHERE CLINT EASTWOOD,
HE RIDES OFF ON A
MOTORCYCLE SIDECAR?
BY GOLLY, LOOKED LIKE
A LOT OF FUN TO ME.
GOT TO FIGURE OUT HOW
TO GET ONE OF THOSE.
BUT, UNFORTUNATELY, I'D SPENT
SO MUCH MONEY ON THE
NEW LAWN TRACTOR
THAT I HAD TO FIND A CHEAP
WAY TO MAKE MYSELF ONE
OF THESE UNITS.
SO, BASICALLY, YOU'VE GOT
THREE COMPONENTS...
YOU'VE GOT YOUR MOTOR;
YOU GOT A CYCLE;
YOU GOT A SIDECAR.
I'VE GOT THE MOTOR.
I'VE GOT THE SIDECAR.
ALL'S I NEED IS THE CYCLE.
SO I STRUNG A ROPE ACROSS --
AT CHEST HEIGHT -- RIGHT ACROSS
THE BIKE PATH UP HERE.
(SOMEONE SCREAMS)
OH, BOY...
OH, HAROLD, YOU'RE FINE.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE IN BUSINESS NOW.
NOW, USUALLY, THE MOTOR IS
IN THE CYCLE PART.
BUT, WITH ME, I GOT THE MOTOR
IN THE SIDE CAR,
SO THE PROJECT
BECOMES REAL EASY.
ALL YOU'VE GOT TO DO IS WELD
THE CYCLE TO THE SIDECAR.
YOU KNOW, WELDING MAY LOOK
DANGEROUS BECAUSE, OF COURSE,
YOU'VE GOT A FULL TANK OF
OXYGEN AND A FULL TANK OF
EXPLOSIVE ACETYLENE.
OF COURSE, THAT'S WHY THEY GIVE
YOU THE SAFETY GOGGLES.
A'RIGHT, LET'S START BY
JUST WELDING THE BIKE
TO THE LAWN MOWER,
AND THEN, WELL, WE'RE DONE.
ALMOST DONE HERE.
ALL RIGHT, WE'VE HAD THE
TORCH A LITTLE HOT THERE.
THIS IS WHY YOU WANT TO KEEP
A GARDEN HOSE AROUND.
U-M-M, ALL RIGHT --
NO -- THAT'S -- NO.
THAT WILL BURN DOWN IN
NO TIME, YOU KNOW?
A GOOD TIME TO USE THE SAFETY
GOGGLES. THEY'RE TINTED.
SO I'M THINKING, I'M NOT EVEN
GOING TO BOTHER WELDING HER.
I'M JUST GOING TO USE THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON...
IS THIS TAPE ON FIRE?
NO.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE ALL SET TO
GO "WHERE EAGLES DARE."
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
IT STARTS.
IT RUNS.
IT GOES.
IT GOES FAST; IT TURNS...
IT DOESN'T TURN.
(CRASH)
I WANT TO TAKE A FEW MINUTES
AND TALK TO SOME OF YOU
OLDER FELLAS OUT THERE.
YOU KNOW, THERE COMES A TIME IN
EVERY MAN'S LIFE WHEN A DOCTOR
IS GOING TO PRESCRIBE FOR
YOU A LITTLE PILL;
MAYBE FOR YOUR HEART,
YOUR KNEE OR YOUR BACK.
AND LIKE IT OR NOT, YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO TAKE ONE OF THOSE
PILLS EVERY DAY
FOR THE REST OF YOUR, ALL OF A
SUDDEN, VERY SHORT LIFE.
NOW, A LOT OF YOU MAY NOT REACT
FAVOURABLY TO THIS NEW REGIMEN.
IT'S TUESDAY, SO IT MUST BE TIME
FOR MY ANTI-INFLAMMATORY.
I WANT YOU TO LOOK
AT THE BRIGHT SIDE.
THE BIGGEST PROBLEM IN YOUR
LIFE RIGHT NOW CAN BE
SOLVED WITH A PILL.
THINK BACK TO ALL OF THE
PROBLEMS YOU HAD WHEN
YOU WERE YOUNGER...
LOVE, MONEY, CHILDREN,
WORK, NEIGHBOURS.
COULDN'T SOLVE THEM
WITH A PILL, HUH?
SEE, YOU'RE NOT GETTING
OLDER, YOU'RE GETTING
BETTER MEDICATION.
SO ENJOY AND DON'T
FORGET YOUR PILLS.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
MAN, WE'RE GOING FROM THE FRYING
PAN TO THE FIRE WITH THIS
HISTORICAL SOCIETY.
I WISH THEY WERE HISTORY.
THEY DECIDED THAT THE OLD
SMOKEHOUSE IS NOT A
HISTORICAL SITE
BECAUSE SOMEBODY TOLD THEM MY
STORY ABOUT THE SETTLERS IS
A LOAD OF BALONEY.
PRETTY MUCH WHAT I THOUGHT.
ANYWAY, BEFORE THEY START
EYEBALLING THE LODGE AGAIN,
I FIGURED OUT A WAY TO MAKE THE
SMOKEHOUSE INTO A CASH DONATION.
WE'RE GOING TO SELL IT AND
THEN GIVE THEM THE MONEY.
HEY, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA,
UNCLE RED. THAT'S TERRIFIC.
AND I COULD BE
THE SALES AGENT.
I'VE SEEN THEM ON TV.
YEAH.
I'VE SEEN
THEM ON TV.
YEAH.
I COULD DO IT,
LIKE, YOU KNOW, YEAH.
LOOKING FOR CASH?
LOOKING TO GET OUT OF
TOWN IN A HURRY?
I'M HAROLD GREEN, AND I COULD
SELL YOUR HOUSE FAST.
CALL 1-800-HAROLD.
I'M A CLOSER.
(APPLAUSE)
YOU'RE A WHAT?
I'M A CLOSER.
WELL, START
WITH YOUR MOUTH.
HAROLD, I'D RATHER YOU
JUST LAY LOW ON THIS DEAL.
NOBODY IS GOING TO BUY THIS
PLACE IF THEY KNOW YOU
LIVE AROUND HERE.
SO IF ANY OF
YOU ARE LOOKING
FOR A SMOKEHOUSE,
YOU KNOW, A PLACE
YOU CAN SMOKE IN --
NOT MANY OF
THEM LEFT,
WE'VE GOT A GOOD
ONE FOR SALE.
REAL SOLID PLYWOOD.
OH, PLYWOOD IS NOT REAL SOLID.
WELL, THE KNOTS ARE SOLID.
AND, I BELIEVE, THE DOOR
IS PRETTY MUCH RUSTED
SOLID, THERE.
AND GOT THE CENTRAL
HEATING IN HER.
IT DOES?
WELL, THE WOOD STOVE
IS IN THE MIDDLE.
AND I THINK --
I BELIEVE --
I BELIEVE AT ONE TIME,
SHE HAD ELECTRICITY.
WHEN WAS THAT?
WHEN THE LIGHTNING
HIT IT.
HAROLD, DON'T BE
SO NEGATIVE, OKAY?
IN THE BIBLE, YOU KNOW,
THERE WAS A GUY WHO KILLED
THE PHILISTINES WITH THE
JAWBONE OF AN ASS?
YOU'RE GOING TO KILL
THIS SALE WITH EXACTLY
THE SAME WEAPON.
(APPLAUSE)
OKAY, IT'S ONCE AGAIN TIME FOR
THE MEETING OF MEN'S ANONYMOUS.
AND, AS ALWAYS, I WOULD LIKE
TO INTRODUCE MY UNCLE RED TO
LEAD US IN THE PLEDGE.
GO RED!
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
(APPLAUSE)
VERY NICE, OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
NOW, AT THIS TIME, IT'S MY
PLEASURE TO INTRODUCE,
Mr. DOUGIE "X"
WHO HAS SOMETHING TO
SHARE WITH THE GROUP.
Mr. FRANKLIN --
OH, DARN.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
RED, GENTLEMEN,
SOMETHING HAPPENED TO ME LAST
WEEK THAT I WOULD LIKE TO
SHARE WITH YOU.
I CAME HOME FROM WORK ONE
NIGHT AND SETTLED IN FOR
A NIGHT OF TV.
I HAD A DRINK IN THE CUP
HOLDER IN MY ARM REST;
I HAD MY LEBANESE HICKORY-SMOKED
BABAGANOUSH DIP ON MY LAP;
HAD MY CHIPS TO MY LEFT, MY BAG
OF JUJUBES TO MY RIGHT
AND MY DING DONG IN
MY TOP POCKET.
MY CHAIR WAS IN THE FULLY
RECLINED POSITION.
GENTLEMEN, I WAS IN
FOR THE DURATION.
AND, THEN, IT HAPPENED ABOUT
HALFWAY THROUGH THE OPENING
THEME OF A TV SHOW.
I REALIZED: PHANTOM PAINS,
I DID NOT HAVE MY REMOTE.
I LOOKED EVERYWHERE FOR IT...
UNDER MY ARM,
UNDER MY OTHER ARM,
DOWN IN AMONGST THE SEAT.
MY REMOTE WAS NOWHERE
TO BE FOUND.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE,
GENTLEMEN, I WATCHED AN ENTIRE
HOUR OF TELEVISION
WITHOUT CHANGING THE
CHANNEL ONCE.
(APPLAUSE)
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
EXCELLENT.
NICE.
NOT EASY TO DO.
WHAT SHOW DID YOU WATCH
FOR AN ENTIRE HOUR?
"BAYWATCH SALUTES THE THONG."
ALL RIGHT, KIND OF GETTING
BACK TO BASICS ON THIS
ADVENTURE WITH BILL --
BACK TO GOOD OL' FISHIN'.
WELL, THAT'S QUITE A LURE
YOU'VE GOT THERE.
WATCH IT, WATCH IT, WATCH IT.
GOT THE SHARP LITTLE
PRONGS ON IT.
YOU KNOW, YOU GET OUT THERE BY
THE WATER, AND YOU JUST --
OH, FEELING A BIT OF
TENSION, MAYBE.
OH, OH, OH.
CAUGHT ONE ON YOUR FIRST CAST.
I WOULD THINK THAT THAT WOULD
SMART A LITTLE BIT.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT THERE.
IT DIDN'T GO UP HIS NOSE,
SO I DON'T THINK IT
REQUIRES SURGERY.
HAROLD, TAKE THAT OFF YOURSELF.
HAROLD, DON'T LET HIM --
DON'T LET HIM DO IT.
HAROLD, HAROLD, HAROLD --
DON'T LET HIM --
HAROLD, HAROLD.
I TRIED TO WARN YOU.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY, NO,
THAT'S FINE.
THAT'S PART OF THE
BONDING EXPERIENCE.
YOU GET A MAN WITH A YOUNGER
FELLA AND THEY JUST HAVE
A FUN TIME.
SEE, THOSE BAND-AIDS,
THEY DON'T HURT YOUR
APPEARANCE AT ALL.
THOSE ARE CHICK MAGNETS,
THAT'S WHAT THOSE ARE.
DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT THAT.
ALL RIGHT, A LITTLE LESSON...
THAT'S HOW YOU CAST.
COME ON -- COME ON, BOYS.
NOW, DON'T...
I KNEW IT.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
THEY'RE ALL SET.
YOU GUYS FISHING WITH WORMS.
LOOK AT THAT.
ISN'T THAT CUTE?
COME ON, BILL,
PUT THAT ON THERE.
COME ON. YOU DON'T KNOW HIM.
OH, YOU TWO ARE PATHETIC.
OH, OH, ALL RIGHT.
IS THE HOSPITAL CLOSE BY
TO THIS FISHING SPOT?
YEAH, YOU OWN THIS ONE, HAROLD.
JUST RIP 'ER OFF THERE.
HA-HA-HA HO-HO-HO.
OH, I SHOULDN'T LAUGH.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
SO THEY GOT THEIR WORMS
ON THE HOOK.
THEY'RE HAPPY, HAPPY,
HAPPY, AREN'T THEY?
UNBELIEVABLE.
OKAY, AWAY YOU GO, BOYS.
AND, YEAH -- YEAH -- YEAH.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I THINK THE
IMPORTANT THING IS THEY'RE
SPENDING THE DAY TOGETHER.
THEY THINK THEY'VE
GOT SOMETHING.
REEL 'ER IN, HAROLD.
GIVER 'ER A GOOD YANK.
YEAH -- YEAH -- YEAH.
OKAY, IT'S A POOR FISHERMAN
THAT EATS HIS BAIT, YOU KNOW?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, HAROLD?
OH, OKAY, ALL RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY, BILL WILL GET
THAT OUT OF THERE.
JUST POP THAT OUT
OF THERE, BILL.
OH, MY GOSH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
HAROLD, WHY DON'T YOU GO OUT
AND GET A DRINK OR SOMETHING?
RINSE THAT OUT.
TAKE OFF. GET LOST.
BEAT IT.
MAN, THESE GUYS
ARE FRIGHTENING.
ALL RIGHT, BILL,
REEL 'ER IN, BILL.
THAT'S RIGHT, IT'S A TREE.
DID YOU CATCH ONE, BILL?
OH, OH, HE'S GOT A
LOVELY BASSWOOD.
HAROLD WILL HELP
YOU CLEAN THAT.
OH, OH, OH, THERE WE GO.
DON'T FORGET THE GILLS.
WELL, WE'VE DONE A TOTAL
RE-THINK ON THIS WHOLE
SMOKEHOUSE PROJECT THING.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO
BE ABLE TO SELL.
THE REAL ESTATE
MARKET IS TOO SOFT.
AND SO IS THE GROUND
UNDER THE SMOKEHOUSE,
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
SO, INSTEAD, WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE A LOTTERY.
NOBODY WANTS A SMOKEHOUSE.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO BUY
TICKETS FOR A LOTTERY IF
THAT'S THE MAIN PRIZE.
WELL, THAT'S NOT
THE MAIN PRIZE,
Mr. JUMP-TO-CONCLUSIONS.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO GIVE
THE SMOKEHOUSE AWAY,
WE'RE GOING TO BLOW IT UP.
THE WINNER GETS TO PRESS THE
BUTTON ON THE DETONATOR.
HOW MANY TICKETS CAN I SIGN
YOU UP FOR, THERE, HAROLD?
NONE!
I'M AGAINST THIS
COMPLETELY ON PRINCIPLE.
THAT'S INCREDIBLE!
COME ON.
I'VE GOT A GOOD MIND TO GO
DOWN THERE AND CHAIN MYSELF
TO THE BUILDING.
WELL, IT WOULD PROBABLY
HELP TICKET SALES.
OH, COME ON, HAROLD.
IT'S NOT DANGEROUS.
THEY'VE RIGGED THE EXPLOSIVES
SO THE BUILDING JUST KIND OF
FALLS IN ON ITSELF.
UNCLE RED, IF WE'VE LEARNED
ANYTHING FROM THIS HISTORY
I'M TRYING TO PRESERVE,
IT'S THAT SENSELESS
DESTRUCTION IS ROBBING
OUR FUTURE GENERATIONS
OF ITS BIRTHRIGHT.
OKAY, FINE.
BUT THAT SHOULDN'T INTERFERE
WITH MY RIGHT TO THE PURSUIT
OF HAPPINESS, HAROLD.
WE HAVE LAWS IN THIS COUNTRY,
AND THESE LAWS ARE MEANT
TO GUARANTEE US THE GREATEST
FREEDOM IN THE WORLD, HAROLD.
THAT'S OUR LEGACY.
THAT'S OUR
GREAT TRADITION.
AND NOW, IF YOU'LL
EXCUSE ME,
I GOTTA GO BLOW
UP A BUILDING.
(APPLAUSE)
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP PART
OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
"IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
ARNIE DOGAN IS HERE WITH
SOMETHING FOR US TO FIX.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
THERE, ARNIE?
WELL, RED, I WAS
HOPING YOU COULD
FIX MY GUITAR.
WELL, MAYBE. IT DOESN'T
LOOK TOO BAD.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH IT?
IT DOESN'T HAVE
ANY CHARACTER.
ALL THE BIG STARS, THEY'VE
GOT GUITARS WITH CHARACTER.
WILLIE NELSON,
HIS IS ALL HACKED UP.
I HEARD HE HAD IT
SPECIALLY TUNED TO
HIS VOICE, EH?
OH, YEAH.
AND THEN B.B. KING, HE NAMED HIS
GUITAR -- SPECIAL NAME -- HE
CALLS IT "LUCILLE."
WELL, THEN, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
NAME YOUR GUITAR, ARNIE.
I AM WAY AHEAD
OF YOU THERE, RED.
I CALL IT "DOUG."
YOU SEE, I WANT TO
GET AWAY FROM THAT
SEXIST THING.
YEAH.
WELL, WHAT WOULD
YOU LIKE ME TO DO TO IT?
WELL, MAYBE JUST SCUFF
IT A LITTLE BIT.
PUT SOME STICKERS ON IT.
MAKE IT LOOK LIKE I'VE BEEN
ON THE ROAD TOURING WITH IT.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, WHY DON'T
YOU HANG ON OVER THERE,
AND I'LL JUST DROP
THE BELT SANDER ON
HER A COUPLE OF TIMES.
AND HANG ON TO DOUG.
I GOT 'IM.
OH DARN, OH BOY, OH BOY...
OH, IT'S -- ARNIE...
YOU KNOW, I THINK WE'VE DONE IT.
IT SURE LOOKS LIKE
IT'S BEEN ON THE ROAD.
DO YOU THINK IT'S MORE ME NOW?
WELL, IT'S CERTAINLY
TUNED TO YOUR VOICE.
IT'S FLAT.
(APPLAUSE)
(COUGHING)
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
WELL, NOW WE KNOW WHY THEY
CALL IT A SMOKEHOUSE.
COULDA BEEN CALLED A FIREHOUSE
OR A FLYING-DEBRIS-HOUSE.
WHAT THE HECK WENT WRONG
THERE, UNCLE RED?
WELL, EDGAR SET THE
CHARGES WRONG.
YOU KNOW, WE WANTED AN
IMPLOSION; WE GOT AN EXPLOSION.
HE FIGURED IT WAS A TYPO.
I JUST FIGURED THE BUILDING
WAS GOING TO FALL OVER.
I DIDN'T EXPECT THE ENTIRE
THING TO ROCKET OUT OF
THE GROUND LIKE THAT.
YEAH, WELL, SEE, THAT'S
THAT OLD PLYWOOD. IT'S SOLID.
I MEAN, SHE REALLY
HELD TOGETHER, EH?
OH, YEAH,
BONUS THERE.
YEAH.
IT WAS WEIRD, THOUGH, SEEING
THIS ENTIRE BUILDING TUMBLING
ACROSS THE SKY.
OVER OUR HEADS WHEN
IT MADE AN ECLIPSE
IT PASSED OVER.
YEAH.
I WAS AFRAID IT WAS GOING TO
COME DOWN ON THE MAIN ROAD,
BUT, LUCKILY, SHE CAUGHT A
FAVOURABLE WIND AND
HEADED INTO TOWN.
WHAT BUILDING DID IT
ACTUALLY HIT DOWN THERE?
THE HISTORICAL SOCIETY BUILDING.
YEAH, THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT
CLOSING THE WHOLE PLACE DOWN.
THEY FIGURED IT WAS BAD FOR
THEIR IMAGE IF THE HISTORICAL
SOCIETY CAN'T PRESERVE THEIR
OWN BUILDING.
WELL, THAT'S A SHAME.
I GUESS I'LL JUST KIND OF HANG
ONTO THE CASH FROM THE TICKETS
THERE UNTIL THEY MAKE UP
THEIR MIND.
(POSSUM CALL)
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AND NOW THAT WE'VE GOT NO
HISTORICAL SOCIETY,
IF I'M THE OLD THING YOU'RE
TRYING TO PRESERVE,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO DO IT ALL ON YOUR OWN.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT THE LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
(APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTRE.]
Harold:  SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red Green:  SIT DOWN.
Harold:  OKAY THIS IS OUR
FIRST ANNOUNCEMENT...
THE ALLISTON BROTHERS HAVE BEEN
REMANDED 'TIL NEXT MONTH,
AND JIMMY GRISSLE IS
OUT ON BAIL,
AND JOEY FEATHERSTONE
GOT PROBATION,
SO THE TEAM PHOTO FOR THE
POSSUM LAKE HOCKEY LEAGUE
IS ON FOR TONIGHT.
IF WE DON'T DO IT TONIGHT, IT
MIGHT BE 3-5 BEFORE EVERYONE'S
AVAILABLE AGAIN.