YOU DON'T HAVE TO WATCH
TOO MANY NATIONAL GEOGRAPHICS
OF BULL ELEPHANTS RAMMING
THEIR HEADS TOGETHER
TO REALIZE THAT MEN ARE
KIND OF COMPETITIVE.
MEN COMPETE AT EVERYTHING,
WORK, PLAY, IN BED.
MEN EVEN TURN SHOPPING
INTO A COMPETITION.
IT'S AMAZING HOW WE'LL
OUTBID EACH OTHER
FOR SOMETHING THAT
NEITHER OF US WANTS
JUST TO PROVE WE CAN
AFFORD TO WASTE MORE MONEY.
IT'S NOT SMART OR CORRECT
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT MAKES
US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red Green:
ON TODAY'S SHOW,
BILL IS GOING TO SHOW YOU
ONE WAY TO UNROLL PIPE
DOWN THE LAKE,
I'M GOING TO VISIT
BRACKSTON'S MARINA
WHERE WE FIND GLEN
BUSY AT WORK,
I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU HOW TO MAKE
A NEAT REVOLVING
SIGN OUT OF A BED
AND MIKE IS GOING
TO REFINISH SOME
FURNITURE FOR US.
AND NOW HERE IS THE
MAN WITH THE GOLDEN FARM,
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
AS HEAD OF THE
INTERNATIONAL POSSUM
BROTHERHOOD, CHAPTER 11,
IT'S MY JOB TO EXPLAIN
THINGS AND TO MAKE SENSE
OF WHAT'S GOING
ON UP HERE,
BUT SOMETIMES THAT'S
JUST IMPOSSIBLE,
FOR EXAMPLE,
MY NEPHEW HAROLD.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK
HAD AN UNUSUAL DAY.
IT WAS GARBAGE DAY THERE
AND HE HAD HIS GARBAGE OUT.
HE HAD IT SEPARATED
INTO THE CANS AND
THE PAPER
AND THE RUBBER AND
THE BOTTLES AND THE GLASS
AND ALL THE FOUR
MAJOR FOOD GROUPS
AND HE'D ADDED TO THAT
AN OLD BROKEN DOWN
TWO LEGGED MILK STOOL
HE DIDN'T NEED ANYMORE
BECAUSE THERE ARE NO
MORE TWO LEGGED COWS.
AND THE GARBAGE MEN
WOULDN'T TAKE IT, RIGHT,
BECAUSE LIKE THEY
DON'T TAKE FURNITURE,
I KNOW THAT, BECAUSE MY
PARENTS TRIED TO THROW
OUT MY BED ONE TIME.
LET ME GUESS, WHILE YOU
WERE STILL IN IT?
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S A REALLY COOL BED
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW.
IT'S A BABY CARRIAGE
AND IT'S MADE OUT
OF PLYWOOD
AND IT HAS THESE BABY
HUEY STICKERS ON IT
BUT WHEN I
TURNED 14 THEY
THOUGHT IT MIGHT AFFECT ME.
ANYWAY, WHILE OLD MAN
SEDGWICK WAS BAWLING
OUT THE GARBAGE MEN,
A COUPLE PULLED OVER
IN ONE OF THEM CARS
FROM THE CITY.
TOURISTS, YOU KNOW.
OH NO, OLD MAN SEDGWICK
HE'S SO RUDE TO TOURISTS.
WELL, HE FIGURES THEY'RE
PROBABLY STOPPING TO
ASK FOR DIRECTIONS.
BEFORE THEY CAN SAY
ANYTHING, HE TELLS
THEM WHERE TO GO.
BUT IN THIS CASE THEY
JUST WANTED TO BUY
HIS MILK STOOL.
THEY OFFERED HIM
50 BUCKS FOR IT.
$50 FOR THAT ROTTEN
PIECE OF LITTLE CHAIR?
OH.
HE DIDN'T
TAKE IT, DID HE?
NO, GOT THEM
UP TO 75.
THAT LITTLE MILK STOOL
IT'S JUST ROTTEN AND
IT'S GARBAGE.
NO, IT ISN'T HAROLD, THE
GARBAGE MEN WOULDN'T
TAKE IT.
IF YOU SEE ANYTHING YOU
LIKE ON THIS SHOW,
MAKE ME AN OFFER.
OH, IT LOOKS LIKE
THERE'S TROUBLE BREWING
AT CAMPSITE NUMBER 10
OLD MAN SEDGWICK
IS GRILLING A FISH
AND HIS PANTS
ON FIRE AGAIN
THE COUPLE AT NUMBER 15
THEY'RE MARRIAGE
HAS GONE CAPUT.
I DON'T MIND THE
SHOUTING AND SWEARING
BUT THEIR TRAILER BOUNCED
RIGHT ON MY FOOT.
THERE'S GUNFIRE OFF
IN THE DISTANCE
AT CAMPSITE NUMBER 6
WHICH PROVES WHAT
WE KNEW ALONG,
THAT RELATIVES AND
HUNTING DON'T MIX
SO I'M PACKING UP
IN THE MORNING,
IF I STAYED I'D
BE A LUNATIC,
'CAUSE ALL THE SHOUTING,
SWEARING AND GUNFIRE
HAS MADE ME UNBELIEVABLY,
INCREDIBLY HOMESICK.
WELL, WITH OLD MAN
SEDGWICK BEEN ABLE
TO SELL THAT MILK STOOL
FOR A BUCKET FULL OF MONEY,
I THOUGHT I'D USE THIS
WEEK'S HANDYMAN CORNER
TO SHOW YOU HOW YOU
CAN MAKE A FORTUNE
FROM SOME OF THEM PRICELESS
HEIRLOOMS YOU GOT SITTING
IN YOUR CREDENZA
OR MAYBE LYING AT THE
BOTTOM OF A NEARBY RAVINE.
YOU'D BE AMAZED AT WHAT
YOU CAN DIG UP, LITERALLY.
I FOUND THIS OLD OIL
LAMP AND THIS BEAR TRAP
AND THIS OLD RED CART HERE,
ALL OF WHICH I WOULD
BE WILLING TO PART WITH
IF THE PRICE WAS RIGHT,
LIKE SAY MORE THAN ZERO.
WHAT I NEED, THOUGH,
IS SOMETHING
THAT'S GOING
TO CATCH THE EYE
OF PASSING TOURISTS,
SOMETHING THAT'S SUBTLE
AND TASTEFUL
AND CAN BE SEEN FOR MILES
AROUND, EVEN IN THE
BAD WEATHER.
SO WE'RE GOING TO BUILD
OURSELVES A REAL FANCY
CITY-STYLE ROTATING SIGN
USING THESE WINDOW BOXES
AND THIS OLD BED FRAME.
NOW, THE FIRST THING
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
IS SOME PIECES OF PIPE.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, WHAT I
HAVE ENDED UP DOING
IS ACTUALLY TAKING
THESE PIECES OF PIPE
RIGHT OUT OF THE SYSTEM.
IT DOESN'T MATTER, WE GOT
THE WATER TURNED OFF
MOST OF THE TIME OF THE
YEAR AROUND HERE ANYHOW.
YOU DON'T SUPPOSE
THESE ARE GAS PIPES.
HARD TO TELL
WITH OUR WATER.
OH, WELL, WE'LL FIND
OUT EVENTUALLY.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS DRILL A HOLE ON EACH
END OF YOUR WINDOW BOX
AND THEN YOU WANT TO
THREAD THE PIPE DOWN
THROUGH LIKE AN AXLE.
NOW, TO ATTACH YOUR
AXLE AND MAKE IT SPIN,
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED
FOUR OF THEM PULLIES
WITH A CABLE TO
RUN AROUND THEM.
NOT AS HARD TO FIND
AS YOU MIGHT THINK.
[ RED GRUNTING WITH EFFORT ]
A COUPLE OF CLOTHESLINES
AND YOU'RE THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, YOU WANT THE ATTACH
THE PULLEYS TO
YOUR PIPES
AND YOU WANT TO ATTACH
THE END OF THE PIPES
TO THE BEDFRAME.
NOW, I WOULD RECOMMEND
THAT YOU WELD THEM
ON THERE
FOR STRENGTH
AND SAFETY.
OF COURSE THE
HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE, WORKS GOOD TOO.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS PUT THE BED UP
ON ITS SIDE...
WITH THE
PULLEYS ON TOP.
I FORGOT TO PUT
THE PULLIES ON.
I'LL GET THAT LATER.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
YOU CAN DO IS CUT
PIECES OF PLYWOOD
OR CARDBOARD OR
WHAT HAVE YOU
AND ATTACH THEM ON SO YOU
CLOSE OFF THE OPEN SIDE,
THEN YOU GOT
FOUR DIFFERENT
SIGNS THAT YOU CAN MAKE.
I'M HAPPY ENOUGH WITH
THE THREE-SIDED VERSION.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT, THE
DRIVERS WILL BE
SO AMAZED,
THEY'LL VEER OFF
INTO THE DITCH
AND THEN YOU CAN CHARGE
THEM FOR A SERVICE CALL.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S PAINT OR YOU
CAN USE A FELT TIP MARKER.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT
MY PULLEYS ATTACHED,
I GOT MY CLOTHESLINE
THREADED ALL THROUGH
AND I GOT ALL MY
SIGNS PAINTED ON.
SO NOW WHEN YOU
WANT TO DISPLAY
YOUR DIFFERENT SIGNS,
YOU JUST PULL ON
THE ENDS OF THE
CLOTHESLINE.
IT'S LIKE DRAWING
FLIES TO A SHIP.
THERE'S YOUR OIL LAMP.
THERE'S YOUR BEAR TRAP.
THERE'S YOUR RED CART.
HANG ON A SECOND.
I'LL GET IT.
THERE WE GO.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
AND REMEMBER ABOUT
TRUTH IN ADVERTISING.
Red Green:
STAY TUNED.
BILL IS GOING TO COMBINE
PLUMBING WITH FINGER
EXERCISES
AND WE GOT A FEW
MORE WORDS
FROM OUR
RESIDENT DING DONG.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
TEENAGERS ABOUT THE
WAY YOU DRESS.
LET'S MAKE THIS CLEAR
PLAID SHIRTS AND
BAGGY PANTS
ARE NOT GRUNGE WEAR,
THEY'RE LODGE WEAR.
WE'VE BEEN DRESSING
LIKE THIS SINCE THE
INVENTION OF CLOTHES
AND WE'LL CONTINUE
TO DRESS LIKE THIS
LONG AFTER
YOU'VE ABANDONED IT
FOR SOME NEW FASHION FAD.
AND THIS BRINGS ME
TO MY NEXT POINT,
YOU PEOPLE ARE SUPPOSED
TO BE REBELLING AGAINST
OUR GENERATION,
NOT COPYING IT.
GO GET YOUR OWN LOOK,
TINFOIL UNDERWEAR OR
CHICKEN WIRE
OR LATEX PAINT
OR WHATEVER.
IT'S EMBARRASSING WHEN
A 40 YEAR OLD LODGE MEMBER
IS MISTAKEN FOR
A 15 YEAR OLD GIRL,
EMBARRASSING
AND DANGEROUS.
IT'S ALSO A SAD
COMMENTARY ON WHAT TODAY'S
15 YEAR OLD GIRLS
ARE LOOKING LIKE.
SO I SAY GET OUT OF
THE FLANNEL CLOTHES
AND GET INTO SOME
SHARP STUFF NOW
WHILE YOU STILL GOT YOUR
YOUTH AND YOUR LOOKS.
THERE'S NO POINT
IN DRESSING LIKE
A LAUNDRY HAMPER
UNTIL YOU GOT THE FACE
AND THE BODY TO GO WITH IT
I'LL TELL YOU,
OLD MAN SEDGWICK
GETTING 75 BUCKS FOR
THAT MILK STOOL HAS
GOT US ALL THINKING
ABOUT HOW WE'VE
UNDERVALUED OUR
POSSESSIONS.
I THINK WE
CAN SELL THEM.
YOU'RE NOT THINKING
OF SELLING THAT, ARE YOU?
WHAT THIS?
NO, NO.
I WOULDN'T PART
WITH THAT, HAROLD.
MIND YOU, IF SOMEBODY
OFFERED ME 300 BUCKS
I MIGHT CHANGE
MY MIND.
I FIGURE 850
FOR THIS UNIT
AND THIS GUY HAS GOT
TO BE WORTH AT LEAST A
1000, DON'T YOU THINK?
COME ON, THIS IS
JUST CRASS COMMERCIALISM.
YOU OUGHT TO BE ASHAMED.
AND 5 CENTS WILL
TAKE THIS OFF MY HANDS.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
YOU CAN'T TURN
THIS PLACE INTO AN
OVERPRICED TOURIST TRAP,
THAT WILL RUIN ONE OF
THE MAIN ATTRACTIONS
OF POSSUM LAKE.
AH, HAROLD, YOU'RE JUST
JEALOUS 'CAUSE YOU DON'T
HAVE ANY WORTHLESS JUNK.
ALL YOUR STUFF
IS NEW AND VALUABLE.
I'M TELLING YOU, I'M
GOING TO SELL THIS
FOR 300 BUCKS.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE
SELLING IT AT ALL.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
GIVE ME 200 I'LL
TAKE IT OFF THE MARKET.
I'LL PROBABLY HAVE
A BUSY DAY TODAY.
HERE WE ARE FOR
THIS WEEK'S BOATING TIP
WITH GLEN BRACKSTON
OF BRACKSTON'S MARINA.
THANK YOU, RED.
THIS WEEK'S BOATING TIP
WILL BE HOW TO PROPERLY
REMOVE AN OUTBOARD
MOTOR FROM A BOAT.
SO HOP IN, RED.
ALRIGHTY.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TWO GUYS IN A BOAT,
RED, NO LIFE JACKETS?
I DON'T THINK SO.
AT LEAST NOT
WITH MY HEALTH.
OKAY, NOW, THE FIRST
THING YOU GOT TO DO, RED,
IS YOU GOT TO
TURN OFF THE GAS
AND UNHOOK THE TANK.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE WE GO.
OKAY.
NOW, WHAT YOU
GOT TO DO NEXT, RED,
IS YOU GOT TO LOOSEN
OFF THOSE LITTLE
CLAMPS THERE
BUT DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THAT BECAUSE I ALREADY
DID THAT IN BETWEEN
DIZZY SPELLS.
YOU MUST BE
EXHAUSTED, GLEN.
OH, YOU GOT TO
PACE YOURSELF, RED.
THAT'S WHAT I FOUND
OUT AFTER HAVING
A HEART ATTACK.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
OKAY.
SO NOW HAUL HER
UP OUT OF THERE, RED.
YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO HELP ME?
WITH MY BACK?
I DON'T CARE
WHAT YOU USE.
QUIT YOUR WHINING, RED,
ONE GUY CAN LIFT A
MOTOR THAT SIZE.
WELL WHY DOES IT
HAVE TO BE THIS GUY?
BECAUSE YOU'RE HERE.
OH FOR PETE SAKES.
OKAY.
NOW JUST BE CAREFUL.
I TOLD YOU.
I WAS WATCHING
FOR THAT, RED.
SEE THERE'S A
SAFETY CHAIN ON THERE.
THAT'S SO IT DOESN'T
FALL IN THE WATER.
YOU GOT TO
WATCH THAT, RED.
THAT'S IT.
UNHOOK IT.
OKAY.
OKAY, NOW,
JUST LIFT HER UP.
BE CAREFUL.
BE CAREFUL, RED.
DON'T SCUFF HER.
DON'T SCUFF IT UP.
OKAY.
THAT'S GOOD.
QUIT YOUR WHINING, RED.
EXERCISE IS A GOOD
THING, NOT A BAD THING.
YOU STAND STILL I'LL
DROP THIS RIGHT
ON YOUR FOOT.
NO.
NO THANKS.
I JUST -- WHAT WE GOT
TO DO, WE GOT TO GET
IT UP TO MY PICK-UP.
WHAT?
OH, YEAH, IT'S MY
CONTRIBUTION TO
THE BIG SALE.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
GEEZ I HOPE YOU GET
LOTS OF PEOPLE
UP HERE, TOO.
MEAN LOTS OF MONEY.
WELL HOW ARE WE
GOING TO GET LOTS
OF PEOPLE UP HERE?
ADVERTISE,
RED, FLYERS.
AND ONCE YOU
GET THEM UP HERE,
YOU GOT TO
TREAT THEM
RIGHT, THAT'S THE KEY.
TREAT THEM RIGHT, RED.
SO GET GOING.
HURRY UP.
COME ON.
GET IT UP TO
THE PICK-UP.
THAT'S IT.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S NOT
THAT HEAVY, RED.
IT'S MAIL CALL.
GOT A LETTER
HERE FROM KEVIN
FROM COURTLAND, IDAHO,
AND KEVIN IS WRITING
FROM A CORRECTIONAL
FACILITY.
OH, COOL.
OKAY.
AND HE SAYS: "I HAVE HAD
TO CONVERT A LOT OF PEOPLE
"SO THAT I COULD
WATCH YOUR SHOW
"AND NOT AN EASY FEAT
FOR A FRIDAY NIGHT."
WELL, KEVIN, WE APPRECIATE
YOUR ENTHUSIASM
BUT LET ME REMIND YOU
THAT IT'S VERY DANGEROUS
TO BE FORCING
CONVICTED CRIMINALS
TO BE WATCHING OUR
PROGRAM, ALL RIGHT?
UNCLE RED,
THESE AREN'T ANIMALS.
THESE ARE JUST PEOPLE
WHO HAVE MADE MISTAKES
AND THEY'RE PAYING
THEIR DEBT TO SOCIETY.
YES, I KNOW THAT, HAROLD,
AND WE DON'T WANT TO
INTERFERE WITH THAT
BY PUTTING THESE GUYS
INTO A SITUATION
WHERE VIOLENCE
BECOMES THE
ONLY ALTERNATIVE.
YOU READ THE LETTER.
I MEAN, OUR OTHER VIEWERS
WHEN THE SHOW COMES ON
THEY HAVE CHOICES.
THEY CAN TURN IT OFF,
THEY CAN SWITCH THE CHANNEL,
THEY CAN THROW THEIR
TELEVISION SET INTO A
RAVINE IF THEY CARE TO.
THESE GUYS ARE
LOCKED IN A ROOM
WITH A TV SET AND AN ARMED
SECURITY GUARD, HAROLD.
THINK ABOUT
THIS SHOW, EH?
WE'RE ASKING FOR
TROUBLE, DON'T YOU THINK?
YEAH.
BUT I MEAN IF
THEY LIKE THE SHOW
THEY COULD CONTINUE
WATCHING IT, RIGHT?
WELL, IF THEY ADMIT
THAT IT'S GOING TO
DELAY THEIR PAROLE.
Red Green:
TIME TO INTERFERE
WITH THE LAWS OF NATURE.
TIME FOR
ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
YOU OKAY THERE, BILL?
THAT'S THE FIRST ONE.
THAT WOULD BE MOMENTUM
AND INERTIA EQUAL AN
OPPOSITE REACTION.
NOW, ONE OF THE LAWS
OF NATURE IS THAT
WATER WILL NOT GO UPHILL
AND BILL WANTS TO
WORK AGAINST THAT USING
SOME SORT OF AN
ELECTRICAL PUMP THERE
AND A PRESSURE TANK.
AND THIS IS THE INLET HOSE.
HE HAS ME HOOK THAT UP
THERE AND HE'S GOT TO TAKE
THE OTHER END
DOWN TO THE LAKE.
NOW APPARENTLY HERE IF
THE HOSE RUNS OVER A
TREE OR OVER A RIDGE
OR SOMETHING, THE WATER
DOESN'T RUN PROPERLY,
SO YOU'VE GOT TO KEEP
HER SMOOTH AND I GUESS
GET THE ROCKS
OUT OF THE WAY.
MAYBE BE A
LITTLE MORE CAREFUL OF
WHERE YOU PUT THE ROCKS.
I LET GO OF THE HOSE.
AND I HELP BILL ALL
THE WAY DOWN TO THE LAKE.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
IN THE LAKE SOON, BILL.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU'RE ON THE RIGHT TRACK.
THAT WORKED OUT REAL WELL.
THE OTHER END IS SUPPOSED
TO BE STILL HOOKED UP
TO THE PUMP.
SO WE GO BACK, WE REDO
THAT, AND I DON'T USE
ANY CLAMPS OR ANYTHING,
I USE THE HANDYMAN SECRET
WEAPON ON THAT,
MUCH TIGHTER
AND WATERPROOF.
AND BILL IS
GOING TO TIE THE FOOT
VALVE ON TO A BIG --
BILL, YOU'VE TIED
IT TO YOUR WRIST.
THAT'S GOING TO KEEP
IT ON THE BOTTOM.
SO BILL IS GOING TO BE
ON THE BOTTOM FOR
A FEW MINUTES.
SO THERE WE GO
AND NOW WE'RE --
OH.
TAKE A LITTLE BREAK
THERE FROM MY WORK.
AND WE'RE ALL SET TO
KIND OF PLUG HER IN NOW
BECAUSE WE GOT THE
OUTSIDE OF --
I JUST GOT TO --
ONCE I FINISH MY BREAK
WE'LL GET RIGHT
BACK TO WORK.
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU BILL.
CHANGE IS AS GOOD
AS THE REST I GUESS.
NOW WE'RE GOING TO --
WHEN WE PLUG THIS
THING IN, THE PUMP
WILL START
AND THE WATER WILL
COME UP FROM THE LAKE,
GO THROUGH THE
HOSE AND UP INTO THAT
BIG PRESSURE TANK THERE
AND IT GOES OUT
OF THE PRESSURE TANK
INTO THE GARDEN HOSE.
BILL IS GOING TO USE
THIS TO WATER THE
PLANTS AND SO ON
THAT WE MAY HAVE AT
SOME POINT AROUND
THE LODGE.
YEAH, BILL, OKAY,
WE UNDERSTAND IT COMES
OUT THE END OF THE HOSE.
OH MAN.
ALL RIGHT,
WE'RE ALL SET TO GO.
I JUST PLUG HER IN.
DIDN'T BOTHER WITH
A SWITCH OR ANYTHING.
WE'RE NOT MADE OF MONEY.
I WOULDN'T LOOK DOWN THERE
IF I WERE YOU, BILL.
WATER IS GOING TO COME
OUT THERE I THINK.
OH NO.
NO, I'M WRONG ABOUT THAT.
THERE'S A BIT OF HOLE
IN THE PRESSURE
TANK I GUESS.
BILL, I WOULDN'T
GO THERE, BILL.
BILL.
OH, OH, OH, WHAT
WAS I THINKING.
BY GOLLY.
OH.
SO NOW WE CHANGE
THE PLAN TOTALLY
AND TRY TO WORK WITH NATURE
RATHER THAN AGAINST IT.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO USE
ELECTRICITY OR A PUMP,
WE'RE GOING TO GET
WATER COMING OUT
THE HOSE
USING ONE OF THE ORIGINAL
FORCES OF POWER, GRAVITY.
WE DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT RUNNING NO
ELECTRICITY,
WE GOT TO WORRY ABOUT
RUNNING OUT OF GAS
Red Green:
STAY TUNED.
MIKE IS GOING TO SHOW
US A NEW USE FOR CHAINS
AND DALTON DONATES A BUNCH
OF STUFF THAT I WOULD
CALL PRICELESS.
WELL, WE'RE MOVING
AHEAD WITH THE GREAT
POSSUM LAKE SALE
OF COLLECTIBLES
AND OTHER STUFF THE
GARBAGE MEN WOULDN'T TAKE.
YOU KNOW, YOU NEVER
REALLY KNOW PEOPLE
UNTIL YOU SEE WHAT THEY'RE
WILLING TO SELL AND
FOR HOW MUCH.
AND TO WHOM.
PEOPLE FROM
THE CITY, HAROLD,
PEOPLE WITH MONEY,
PEOPLE WHO SEE VALUE IN
THE THINGS WE HAVE
UP HERE.
THERE'S BASICALLY
NOTHING BUT JUNK UP HERE.
ONE MAN'S JUNK
IS ANOTHER MAN'S
ANTIQUE, HAROLD.
AND IF SOMEONE THINKS
RUST AND DUST TURNS
TRASH INTO CASH,
WHO AM I TO ARGUE?
THESE PEOPLE ARE A
LOT SMARTER THAN WE ARE.
SO YOU MEAN THEY HAVE
A LOT MORE MONEY
THAN YOU DO.
WELL, THAT'S ABOUT
TO CHANGE, HAROLD.
WE SENT OUT 10,000
OF THESE INVITATIONS
AND WE'RE ABOUT TO HAVE
THE BIGGEST AUCTION
POSSUM LAKE
HAS EVER SEEN.
10,000 PEOPLE
ARE COMING HERE?
ALL LOADED WITH
DISPOSABLE INCOME, HAROLD,
JUST LOOKING FOR THAT
LITTLE KNICKKNACK
THAT WE PROBABLY GOT
PROPPING OPEN THE
UTHOUSE DOOR.
WITH 10,000
PEOPLE COMING HERE,
THE DOOR IS GOING
TO BE RIGHT OFF
THE OUTHOUSE.
IT WILL BE A
ONE HOUR EVENT,
GET THEM IN,
GET THE MONEY,
GET THEM OUT.
THE LOVE OF MONEY IS
THE ROOT OF ALL EVIL.
THE LACK OF MONEY IS
THE ROOT OF MOST PROBLEMS.
HOW MUCH DO YOU THINK
I WOULD GET FOR MY
BABY HUEY BED?
25 BUCKS.
REALLY?
Red: 50 IF THEY
DON'T KNOW IT'S YOURS.
WE'RE OUT HERE BY THE
MAIN HIGHWAY
AT HUMPHREY'S
EVERYTHING STORE
TO TALK TO THE MAN
WHO KNOWS EVERYTHING
THERE IS TO KNOW ABOUT
AUCTIONS, DALTON HUMPHRIES.
AND DALTON HAS KINDLY
AGREED TO DONATE
FOR THE AUCTION
A WHOLE BUSLOAD FULL
OF HIS FINEST WARES.
OH, AND A BUS.
TAKE THAT TOO.
TAKE IT ALL.
IT'S YOURS.
OH MY GOSH.
WELL, THIS WILL HAVE TO
BE OUR FEATURED ITEM
AT THE AUCTION.
IT WAS GOING TO BE
MOOSE THOMPSON'S BOX
SPRING AND MATTRESS,
BUT NOT NOW.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT,
I HATE TO GIVE AWAY
ANYTHING FOR FREE.
AND THIS WHOLE BUS
IS JUST CHALK A BLOCK
FULL OF VALUABLE ITEMS.
YOU KNOW, YOU MIGHT BE
INTERESTED IN BIDDING
ON IT YOURSELF, RED.
OH, NO THANK
YOU, DALTON,
I'M GOING TO BE SITTING
AT THE BACK OF THE ROOM
COUNTING THE MONEY.
WELL, YOU KNOW THAT
OLD BARBER CHAIR THAT
I HAD THAT YOU LIKED
AND YOU WANTED TO PUT
IT ON THE ROOF OF
YOUR VAN
BECAUSE YOU
WANTED A FLYING BRIDGE.
IS THAT IN THERE?
OH, NO, NO, BUT THERE'S
A WHOLE BOX OF CRANKS
THAT GO ON THE SIDE
HANDLE ARE IN THERE.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE --
HOLY SMOKE.
WHAT?
WELL, SEE THERE'S A
WHOLE BOX FULL OF
MUST BE
BRAND NEW PAINT CAN LIDS
IN THERE THAT I WANTED
TO HOLD ON TO
'CAUSE I THOUGHT I MIGHT
NEED SOME TIME --.
YOU WANT TO
TAKE THEM BACK?
WOULD YOU
THINK LESS OF ME?
NO.
I DON'T THINK THAT
WOULD BE POSSIBLE.
YOU KNOW, I HOPE I'M
DOING THE RIGHT THING, RED,
GIVING AWAY ALL
THESE CHERISHED ITEMS.
WELL, IF YOU'RE
WORRIED ABOUT IT, DALTON,
WHY DON'T YOU DO WHAT
THEY DO AT THE BIG
FANCY AUCTIONS?
PUT A RESERVE
BID IN ON THIS.
SO IF I DON'T GET
WHAT I THINK IT'S WORTH.
THE WHOLE BUSLOAD
COMES BACK TO YOU.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU JUST TELL ME THE
MINIMUM AMOUNT OF MONEY
YOU WOULD BE
WILLING TO TAKE
TO GET ALL THIS
STUFF OFF YOUR HANDS.
$5.00.
WELL, WE CAN TRY IT.
THIS SATURDAY THE POSSUM
LAKE NUDIST CLUB
IS HOLDING ITS
DINNER/DANCE.
DRESS IS BLACK TIE ONLY.
MUSIC -- OH, MUSIC IS
BY BUCKY AND THE
SKIN TONES.
DUE TO MISHAP LAST YEAR,
WE WILL NOT BE HAVING
THE LIMBO DANCE
OR SERVING FONDUE,
AND THE BARBECUE GRILLS
WILL BE AT CHEST HEIGHT.
AS YOU KNOW, WE'RE WELL
INTO OUR DREAM HOME
RENOVATION PROJECT
AND NOW IT'S TIME
TO START LOOKING
AT FURNITURE.
AND THAT'S WHERE
MIKE HERE COMES IN.
WELL, YOU KNOW EVERYBODY
LIKES ANTIQUES,
MR. GREEN,
RIGHT, BUT TO FILL A
HOUSE FULL OF ANTIQUES,
I MEAN YOU NEED A
MAJOR BANK ROLL, RIGHT?
YEAH.
UNLESS YOU KNOW WHERE
TO GET STUFF CHEAP.
I DON'T HANG OUT WITH
THOSE GUYS ANYMORE,
YOU KNOW?
OH NO.
IT'S A CONDITION
OF MY PAROLE.
SO TODAY WE'RE GOING
TO BE DISTRESSING
FURNITURE.
ALL RIGHT, DISTRESSING
FURNITURE,
THIS IS WHERE YOU REFINISH
ANTIQUES USING WHAT IS IT?
CHAINS, ROCKS,
HAMMERS, YOU KNOW,
ABUSING THIS FURNITURE
IS GOING TO MAKE IT LOOK
OLDER AND MORE VALUABLE.
BOY, FURNITURE UP HERE
AT THE LODGE MUST BE
WORTH A FORTUNE.
NOW, YOU TAKE
THIS TABLE HERE.
YOU SEE IF IT WAS NEW,
IT WOULD PROBABLY
COST YOU ABOUT
A HUNDRED
BUCKS, RIGHT?
THIS LOOKS LIKE YOUR
PRISON LUNCH TABLE HERE.
WELL, YES,
IT IS ACTUALLY.
BUT, YOU SEE, IT'S
ALREADY GOT CHARACTER
IN IT ALREADY, YOU SEE?
IT'S PROBABLY
BECAUSE OF THAT.
YOU SEE YOU GOT THE
SCUFF MARKS ON THE LEGS
AND YOU GOT
YOUR COFFEE
RINGS HERE AND THERE.
THERE'S A NICE
COFFEE RING, THERE.
SO LIKE PEOPLE
ARE GOING TO BE
WONDERING, YOU KNOW,
IT MAKES PEOPLE WONDER
WHO PUT THOSE MARKS
ON THERE, RIGHT?
WELL I'M
GUESSING YOU DID.
POSSIBLY.
BUT YOU SEE NOW WITH
THE CHARACTER AND
AGE AND BEAUTY
THAT IT'S ALREADY
AMASSED, IT'S PROBABLY
WORTH ABOUT 150 BUCKS
AS IS RIGHT NOW.
WOW, YOU KNOW, AND
I'LL BET THERE'S SOME
GUM UNDERNEATH THERE, TOO.
OH YEAH, ABOUT THE
SIZE OF A BEEHIVE
DOWN THERE.
BOY, YOU SURE GOT AN
EYE FOR ANTIQUES,
MR. GREEN.
NOW WE'RE GOING TO
PUT SOME MORE HISTORY
AND AGE INTO IT TO MAKE
IT REALLY WORTH SOMETHING.
LOOK OUT NOW, OKAY?
OKAY.
BOY THIS BRINGS
BACK MEMORIES.
MIKE.
TAKE IT EASY.
HUH?
OH YEAH.
WELL, IT'S PROBABLY
WORTH ABOUT 250 NOW,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
BOY, IF HE IMPROVES
IT MUCH MORE,
I'M NOT GOING TO BE ABLE
TO AFFORD THE INSURANCE.
YEAH, NOW ONE MORE BLOW
OUGHT TO MAKE IT PRICELESS.
WELL.
I'M REALLY SORRY,
MR. GREEN.
UH-HUH.
YEAH.
WHAT WOULD IT
BE WORTH NOW MIKE?
ABOUT 25 BUCKS A CORD.
SO MUCH FOR AUCTIONS.
SO HOW WAS THE TURNOUT?
IT LOOKED TO BE
LESS THAN 10,000.
IT WAS HALF OF 10,000.
OH, 5,000?
THE FIRST HALF OF 10,000.
10?
YEAH.
DISASTER, HAROLD.
DISASTER.
THE FIRST ITEM --
THE FIRST ITEM COME UP
WAS A CAST IRON
MERRY-GO-ROUND.
SOME GOOF BID 5
CENTS DELIVERED.
AND HE LIVED
IN SCOTLAND.
I HEARD JUNIOR SINGLETON
GOT IN THE SPIRIT OF
THINGS, THOUGH,
HE BID $4 ON AN OLD
RUSTY CARD TABLE
THAT HE DONATED HIMSELF.
YEAH, IT'S TRUE.
AND BUSTER HADFIELD HAD
THOSE ANTIQUE PLATES
HE WAS HOPING TO GET
5,000 FROM A COLLECTOR.
HE GOT A DIME FROM
THE SKEET SHOOTING CLUB.
THE FEATURE ITEM
SOLD WELL, THOUGH,
IT WAS A BUSLOAD OF
DALTON'S, YOU KNOW,
COLLECTIBLES.
WELL, THE BID
WAS 6 BUCKS, HAROLD,
BUT THE GUY WITHDREW
IT WHEN HE SAW
THERE WAS A SCRATCH
ON THE BACK BUMPER.
I'LL TELL YOU,
PEOPLE ARE SO CHEAP.
I THINK THEY'RE
JUST BEING CAREFUL
WITH THEIR MONEY, YOU KNOW,
A LESSON YOU COULD LEARN.
YEAH, WELL I WILL KEEP
THAT IN MIND ON YOUR
NEXT PAYDAY, HAROLD.
WELL, BASICALLY THEN YOU
DID ALL THAT WORK
AND YOU SENT OUT ALL
THOSE FLYERS AND YET
YOU SOLD NOTHING.
WELL, NO,
THAT'S NOT TRUE,
THE GUY THAT BOUGHT
THE TWO LEGGED MILK
STOOL FROM OLD MAN SEDGWICK,
HE BROUGHT IT WITH
HIM, HE GOT UP AND HE
AUCTIONED IT OFF FOR 150.
YOU SEE, THESE GUYS
FROM THE CITY,
THEY KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE DOING.
YOU CAN'T
COMPETE WITH THAT.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
IT'S MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO
AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN
IN A WHILE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING
AND I'M BRINGING
A LITTLE TREAT,
AN ANTIQUE TWO-LEGGED
MILK STOOL.
IT WAS EXPENSIVE BUT
IF PEOPLE FROM THE CITY
CAN HAVE NICE
THINGS, SO CAN WE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
UNTIL NEXT TIME, ON BEHALF
OF HAROLD AND MYSELF
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
I HAVE A
PRESENTATION FOR RED.