MY WIFE BUYS A WHOLE WHACK
OF THESE GLOSSY MAGAZINES
THEN SHE GIVES THEM
TO ME FOR SOME REASON.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
THERE'S NEVER ANY
TRUCK PICTURES
OR BOATS FOR SALE OR ANYTHING.
WHAT THEY DO HAVE IN THEM
IS A BUNCH OF ARTICLES
ABOUT BEING SENSITIVE.
I DON'T WANNA BE SENSITIVE.
IF I WAS SENSITIVE,
I'D BE INCREDIBLY DEPRESSED.
BUT THERE IS SOMETHING OF
VALUE IN THESE MAGAZINES...
THE LITTLE SCENT STRIPS
FROM ALL THE PERFUME ADS,
YOU JUST RIP THEM OUT
AND THEN WHAT YOU DO IS YOU
DUCT TAPE THEM TO THE CARDS
ON ONE OF THESE
ROLODEX UNITS HERE.
EVERY ONE OF THESE
FREE PERFUME SAMPLES
GOES INTO YOUR
ROLODEX MACHINE.
OH, YEAH, SURE, IT MEANS THAT
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE ABLE
TO PHONE ANYBODY
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO HAVE THEIR NUMBER ANYMORE,
BUT THAT'S JUST
A HAPPY SIDE EFFECT,
BECAUSE WHAT WE HAVE NOW IS
AN AUTOMATIC POWER AIR
FRESHENER.
NOW, YOU MAY WONDER WHY I
WOULD NEED AN AUTOMATIC
POWER AIR FRESHENER,
BUT THEN YOU'VE NEVER SMELLED
THE INSIDE OF THE POSSUM VAN
IN THE MIDDLE OF JULY.
[ HACKING COUGH ]
[ SUCKS IN BREATH ]
RIGHT, NOW WHAT YOU DO --
WHEW!
IS MOUNT THE UNIT OVER THE
DEFROST VENTS ON YOUR DASH.
YOU START HER UP --
NOW YOU TURN YOUR FAN
ON FULL SPEED
AND LET THE GOOD
SMELLS ROLL.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, EASY, NOW. EASY!
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WELL, BIG NEWS AT THE LODGE.
THIS IS BEAUTIFY POSSUM LAKE
CAMPAIGN WEEK.
OH, YEAH, THEY GOT
EVERYBODY PITCHING IN,
TRYING TO IMPROVE THE
APPEARANCE OF THEIR
PROPERTIES.
KIND OF A COMMUNITY
TOGETHERNESS THING.
A REAL PAIN IN THE NECK,
I'LL TELL YOU.
IF YOU DON'T DO IT YOU'RE
LOOKING AT $1,000 FINE.
YOU'VE PROBABLY
ALREADY GUESSED
WHAT BRILLIANT MIND
WAS BEHIND THIS PLAN, HUH?
UNCLE RED!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I'M HERE FOR
THE $1,000.
WHY ARE YOU DOING
THIS, HAROLD?
TO ATTRACT
TOURISTS.
IT'S ALL PART OF OUR BIG
CAMPAIGN TO DRAW PEOPLE
BACK TO THE NATURAL
BEAUTY OF THE ENVIRONMENT.
VISIT POSSUM LAKE,
AND ANSWER THE CALL
OF NATURE.
UNFORTUNATELY THE LODGE IS
VISIBLE FROM THE HIGHWAY,
SO THE COUNCIL SAYS
CLEAN IT UP OR GET FINED.
WELL, I'M WAY, WAY,
WAY AHEAD OF YOU,
HAROLD.
EXCUSES?
KNOW WHAT THESE ARE?
THEY'RE
SUNFLOWER SEEDS.
I PLANTED THEM
THIS MORNING.
I'M GONNA HIDE THE
LODGE WITH SUNFLOWERS.
UNCLE RED,
SUNFLOWER SEEDS DON'T
GROW THAT FAST OR
THAT HIGH.
WELL, THEY CAN IF YOU
GET THE RIGHT FERTILIZER.
WINSTON GAVE ME THIS
FREE SAMPLE FROM HIS
SEWAGE TRUCK.
HE GOT IT FROM THE
PORT ASBESTOS NUCLEAR
WASTE FACILITY.
IS THAT SAFE?
OH, HAROLD, NUCLEAR
POWER IS OUR FRIEND.
ANYWAY, IT'S NOT LIKE
I'M GONNA PUT A WARHEAD
ON A SUNFLOWER
OR ANYTHING.
WOW!
IT'S LIKE YOU CAN
SEE THEM GROWING.
YOU CAN!
YOU CAN SEE
THEM GROWING.
LOOK!
LOOK, UNCLE RED!
IT'S LIKE THEY TURN
THEIR FACES TOWARD
THE SUN.
IT'S LIKE THEY
HAVE A BRAIN.
NO, HAROLD, YOU DON'T
NEED A BRAIN TO STAND
IN THE SUN.
LOOK AT YOUR TAN.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER RECEIVES A
COUPON F THREE PAIRS
OF STAINLESS STEEL UNDERWEAR.
IT'S RIGHT, IT'S LIGHT,
IT DOESN'T RUST
AND IT'S VIRTUALLY
WEDGIE PROOF!
OKAY, RED, YOU GOT
30 SECONDS
TO GET WINSTON
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
DALTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, WINSTON, IF SOMETHING
IS IN VOGUE,
IT'S PROBABLY
ALSO IN...
COSMO?
OKAY, NO, BUT THOSE
ARE MAGAZINES,
AND THEY GOT
MODELS IN 'EM, OKAY?
WHAT ARE THEY
PROMOTING?
ANOREXIA.
OKAY, NO, NO.
THIS IS A SENSE.
YOU DON'T HAVE IT.
BUT A LOT OF
PEOPLE DO.
SMELL.
OKAY, THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
HELPS A PERSON CHOOSE WHAT
TO WEAR.
A WIFE.
OH, I KNOW.
EUROPEANS ARE
FAMOUS FOR IT.
IN FACT, THERE'S A FRENCH
EXPRESSION, haute couture.
ARMPIT HAIR!
TIME'S ALMOST UP, RED.
OH, COME ON,
WINSTON.
WHAT DO YOU CALL
ANY TREND IN CLOTHING?
OH, RED, I DON'T
MUCH FOLLOW TRENDS.
YOU KNOW, I'M TRUE
TO MYSELF.
I SUCK SEWAGE.
I GUESS I'M
OLD-FASHIONED THAT WAY.
THERE WE GO!
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THIS IS WHERE WE FEATURE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO
HARD TO SAY...
audience:
I DON'T KNOW!
THAT'S TRUE, BECAUSE THEY
DON'T SAY IT VERY --
ALL RIGHT, TODAY'S
LETTER READS AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS --"
LA LA LA LA LA.
"YESTERDAY WAS
MY WIFE'S BIRTHDAY.
"ORDINARILY I WOULD
HAVE GOTTEN HER
"SOME JEWELLERY OR PERFUME,
"BUT SINCE I'M AN
ENLIGHTENED HUSBAND,
"I BOUGHT HER A 12-INCH
RECIPROCATING SAW.
"SHE BURST INTO TEARS
AND LOCKED HERSELF IN
THE BATHROOM.
"WHERE DID I GO WRONG?
"SHOULD I HAVE BOUGHT
HER A BIGGER SAW?"
PROBABLY NOT.
WOMEN SOMETIMES CRY
WHEN THEY'RE HAPPY,
BUT THEY NEVER
LEAVE THE ROOM.
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE YOU BLEW
IT BIG TIME HERE, BUDDY.
I CONCUR WITH
MR. GREEN.
I'VE OFTEN GIVEN
GIFTS TO WOMEN,
BUT IF IT'S NOT
THE CORRECT GIFT,
OR PERHAPS IT WAS NOT ACQUIRED
IN A PERFECTLY LEGAL CONTEXT,
THEN THERE'S OFTEN A
CONFRONTATIONAL AFTERMATH
ASSOCIATED WITH THE
PRESENTATION OF SAID GIFT.
BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT I THINK?
I THINK WOMEN GIVE OFF LOTS
OF SIGNALS AS TO WHAT IT
IS THEY REALLY WANT.
BUT IF YOU FAIL TO
PICK UP ON THOSE SIGNALS,
IT'S REALLY YOUR
FAULT, NOT HERS.
WELL, GOOD FOR YOU,
HAROLD.
AND YOU KNOW, IF I DIDN'T
HAVE A WOMAN IN MY LIFE,
I'D HAVE LOTS OF
THEORIES TOO.
I'M JUST SAYING
THAT WOMEN SAY
WHAT THEY WANT.
I MEAN, YOU HAVE TO BE ABLE
TO LISTEN TO THOSE THINGS.
YOU GOTTA BE
HEARING PROPERLY.
SORRY, WHAT?
OKAY, IF YOU KNOW
SO MUCH,
THEN WHAT'S THE PERFECT
GIFT FOR AUNT BERNICE?
WELL, IT'S NOT
THAT EASY, HAROLD.
HA! HA!
NO, I AGREE.
I MEAN, YOU GOTTA GIVE A
GIFT THAT'S NICE ENOUGH
SO THAT SHE'LL KNOW
THAT YOU CARE FOR HER,
BUT IF YOU GIVE HER
TOO SPECIAL A GIFT,
THEN SHE'S GONNA THINK
YOU'RE COVERING UP
FOR SOMETHING YOU DID WRONG.
NO! NO! NO!
NO, I DISAGREE
WITH THAT APPROACH.
NO, IF YOU'RE IN A TRUSTING,
HONEST RELATIONSHIP,
YOU CAN BE GENEROUS
WITHOUT CONSEQUENCES.
HAROLD, HAROLD, IF
YOU'RE IN ANY KIND
OF RELATIONSHIP,
YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING
WITHOUT CONSEQUENCES.
I HATE
CONSEQUENCES.
OKAY, WELL, I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO APOLOGIZE TO
THIS MAN WHO WROTE IN,
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY WE CAN'T
AGREE ON ANYTHING.
SO MY SUGGESTION IS JUST
FOLLOW WITH YOUR OWN HEART.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU KNOW, I THINK IF I
WAS MARRIED TO YOU GUYS,
I'D KILL MYSELF.
HAROLD,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TO.
CHOOSING THE
RIGHT PARKING SPOT
IS A FINE ART, ISN'T IT?
OH, I KNOW THEY TEACH
FINE ART IN UNIVERSITY,
BUT THIS IS THE KIND
YOU CAN ACTUALLY USE.
NOW, THE MAIN ITEM YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR HERE
IS SHADE.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO KEEP YOUR
CAR AS COOL AS POSSIBLE,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU
HAVE VINYL SEATS.
EVEN MORE SO IF YOU
HAVE BLACK VINYL SEATS
AND YOU'RE WEARING
A BATHING SUIT,
BECAUSE SKIN GRAFTS
CAN BE VERY EXPENSIVE.
BUT YOU KNOW, YOU CAN'T ALWAYS
FIND A SPOT UNDER A TREE.
SO TODAY I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO PROTECT YOUR VEHICLE
WITH SOMETHING I LIKE
TO CALL PORTABLE SHADE.
OKAY, I'M GONNA START WITH A
COUPLE OF THESE RETRACTABLE
TAPE MEASURES.
OH, I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE THINKING...
HEY, IF THIS INVOLVES
ACCURATE MEASUREMENT,
COUNT ME OUT.
[ chuckling ]
ACCURATE MEASUREMENT.
I'LL HAVE TO
REMEMBER THAT ONE.
NO, NO, WE'RE ACTUALLY GOING
TO USE THESE AS SIMPLE
MOUNTING UNITS.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS TO
MOUNT YOUR TAPE MEASURES
ONTO YOUR VEHICLE
JUST ABOVE AND IN
FRONT OF THE HOOD.
AND YOU CAN USE WHATEVER
FASTENING DEVICES
BEST SUITS THE LOOK
AND STYLE OF YOUR CAR.
OKAY, NOW, I'VE ATTACHED A
COUPLE OF OLD DRAPERY RODS
TO THE TOP OF
THE TAPE MEASURES.
I LIKE USING THEM
BECAUSE THEY'RE FLEXIBLE,
BUT THEY'RE STIFF ENOUGH TO
STAY AN INCH OR SO ABOVE
THE BODY OF THE CAR.
SEE, THAT ALLOWS
FOR AIR FLOW.
WHEN YOU GET TO MY AGE,
AIR FLOW IS CRUCIAL.
BY THE WAY, DON'T LET YOUR
WIFE CATCH YOU DOING THIS
WITH HER BRAND NEW
DRAPERY RODS,
OR IT'LL BE
CURTAINS FOR YOU.
OKAY, NOW WE ATTACH THE OTHER
ENDS OF THE DRAPERY RODS
TO THIS LUGGAGE RACK.
IF YOU DON'T
HAVE A LUGGAGE RACK,
YOU CAN TAKE ONE OFF
OF ANY BRITISH CAR.
THEY USE 'EM TO
CARRY BICYCLES AROUND
BECAUSE THEY'RE
CARS ARE SO USELESS,
YOU REALLY GOTTA
HAVE A BACKUP PLAN.
OKAY, SO NOW ALL
WE NEED IS OUR SHADE.
NOW, YOU COULD GO WITH CLOTH
DRAPES OR SHEET METAL
OR ONE OF ARETHA
FRANKLIN'S DRESSES,
BUT I PREFER TO USE SOMETHING
WATERPROOF AND LESS EXPENSIVE.
THAT'S RIGHT,
SHOWER CURTAINS.
I HAD TO TRIM THESE
BABIES OFF A LITTLE BIT,
BECAUSE THEY WERE TOO LONG
FOR THE WIDTH OF THE CAR.
AND I ADDED RING HOLES
TO THE BOTTOM EDGE THERE
SO THAT BOTH SIDES OF
THE CURTAIN WILL BE
DRAWN UP EVENLY
OVER THE CAR.
I GUESS YOU COULD
CALL THIS VEHICLE
FORD OF THE RINGS.
[ NO AUDIO ]
OKAY, NOW, TO
AUTOMATE THE UNIT,
WELL, THAT'S WHERE MY TAPE
MEASURES COME BACK INTO PLAY.
I PULL OUT THE
TAPE ON BOTH SIDES,
THEN ATTACH
THE ENDS OF THE TAPES
TO THE FRONT EDGE
OF MY CURTAIN.
THEN ALL'S I GOTTA DO IS
LOCK THE RECOIL SWITCH
ON EACH OF 'EM,
AND WE'RE READY
FOR A ROAD TEST.
WHO CARES ABOUT THE SUN?
BECAUSE NOW WHEN I PARK
AND PULL ON THE HOOD RELEASE,
I GOT IT MADE IN THE SHADE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HAND --
OH, YEAH, ONE MORE THING.
IF YOU WANNA PROTECT
YOUR DOORS AS WELL,
GO BACK TO THE TUB,
GET THE BATH MAT OUT OF THERE.
NO ONLY GREAT
PROTECTION FROM THE SUN,
BUT ALSO FROM
THOSE IDIOTS
WHO DING YOU WHEN
THEY PARK TOO CLOSE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, THERE COMES A TIME
IN THE LIVES OF MOST MEN
WHEN YOU REALISE YOU'VE TAKEN
BETTER CARE OF YOUR CARS
THAN YOU HAVE OF
YOUR OWN BODY.
HECK, YOU'VE TAKEN
BETTER CARE OF RENTAL CARS
THAN YOUR OWN BODY.
AND IT'S NOT A
RENTAL, IS IT, HUH?
YOU CAN'T JUST DITCH
YOUR BODY IN THE WOODS
AND THEN REPORT IT STOLEN.
ARE YOU ONE OF THOSE GUYS?
IS THERE A CHANCE YOU HAVEN'T
KEPT YOURSELF IN SHOWROOM
CONDITION?
EASY WAY TO FIND OUT.
STAND IN FRONT OF
THE BATHROOM MIRROR.
DON'T ACTUALLY
LOOK IN THE MIRROR.
YOU AREN'T READY
FOR THAT YET.
I'M JUST SAYING OPEN UP
THE MEDICINE CABINET,
TAKE A LOOK AT
WHAT'S INSIDE THERE.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU WERE YOUNG
YOU'VE HAVE NOTHING IN THERE
EXCEPT MAYBE A TUBE
OF TOOTHPASTE,
BOTTLE OF MOUTHWASH, EH?
NOW WHAT DO YOU GOT?
ANTIHISTAMINES,
ANTI-INFLAMMATORIES,
ANTI-DIARRHEA STUFF,
ANTI-DEPRESSANTS, IN CASE
THE ANTI-DIARRHEA STUFF
DOESN'T WORK?
THERE WAS A TIME WHEN YOUR
MEDICINE CABINET WAS
PRACTICALLY EMPTY.
NOW YOU ALMOST
NEED TO BUILD ON
BECAUSE YOU GOT TUBES AND
BOTTLES ALL OVER THE
SINK COUNTER
ACROSS THE TOP
OF THE TOILET TANK,
ON EVERY HORIZONTAL SURFACE
IN THE WHOLE BATHROOM.
YOU MAY ACTUALLY NEED
A WALK-IN MEDICINE CABINET.
THAT'S BECAUSE YOUR LIFE HAS
REACHED THE HALFWAY POINT
BETWEEN PIMPLE CREAM
AND LIVER SPOT REMOVER.
SEE, THIS IS WHEN MEN NEED
THOSE MEDICINES THE MOST
BECAUSE WHEN YOU
REALLY ARE OLD,
EVERYTHING THAT THEY'RE
USED FOR IS DRIED UP,
SHRIVELED AWAY,
HARDENED, SOFTENED,
WRINKLED, CRINKLED,
BLOWN OUT OR FALLEN OFF.
SO STOP COMPLAINING,
TAKE YOUR MEDICINE LIKE A MAN,
AND REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I EMPTIED THE REST OF THE
RADIOACTIVE FERTILIZER
ONTO THE SUNFLOWERS THERE.
YOU KNOW, NOW I GUESS THIS
IS A NUCLEAR EFFICIENT LODGE.
UNCLE RED!
THE SUNFLOWER SEEDS
ARE STILL GROWING.
THEY'RE ALMOST
UP TO THE ROOF.
YEAH, I GAVE 'EM A LITTLE
BOOST THERE, HAROLD.
I THINK THE LODGE'LL BE
HIDDEN IN JUST A FEW
MINUTES NOW.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK
WILL NEVER FIND US.
OH, YEAH!
[ chuckles ]
THEY'RE PAST THE ROOF!
THAT'S FINE.
THEY'RE VERY CLOSE TO
THE POWER LINES, UNCLE RED.
VERY CLOSE!
HAROLD, YOU WORRY
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
[ mock fear ]
THEY'RE VERY CLOSE
TO THE POWER LINES.
THESE FLOWERS ARE
SO SCARY, AREN'T THEY?
WELL, I THINK SOMEONE
SHOULD TURN THE POWER
OFF TO THE LODGE!
OH, I WOULDN'T
BOTHER, HAROLD.
WELL, THEN FINE.
I'LL DO IT MYSELF.
WELL, SUIT YOURSELF.
MAYBE THE BABY SHOULD
TAKE THE THUMB OUT
OF HIS MOUTH.
OH!
[ shuddering ]
I TOLD YOU NOT
BOTHER, HAROLD.
Red (voice over):
IT WAS AN EXCITING
DAY FOR US ALL.
WALTER WAS MOVING,
AND WE WERE HELPING HIM OUT.
WINSTON SHOWED UP WITH
ONE OF THE TRUCKS OF HIS
SEWAGE FLEET THERE.
WE ASKED HIM NOT
TO BRING THE PUMPER.
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT WINSTON BRINGS,
IT'S GOT A CERTAIN
SOMETHING TO IT, YOU KNOW.
LIKE, TO ME, I WOULD'VE
TAKEN THE HOSES OUT
BEFORE I BROUGHT IT OVER,
BUT THAT'S JUST WINSTON.
SO WE GOT A FAIR
NUMBER OF BOX --
WALTER TOOK A GOOD
LOAD, I THOUGHT.
I MEAN, IT'S HIS STUFF.
SO I GOT MINE IN TO
THE TRUCK THERE,
AND I THOUGHT WALTER WOULD
JUST SLIDE HIS INTO MY LEFT,
BUT HE WENT ANOTHER
WAY WITH IT.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WALTER, IT'S REALLY --
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
NO, THAT'S FINE.
YOU'RE GOOD.
OH, AH, OH -- UH-OH!
SO WALTER THROWS
HIS UP THERE,
AND THEN -- LOOK.
HE'S VERY ATHLETIC.
LOOK AT THIS.
AND THEN HE'S INVITING
US TO DO THE SAME.
NOT GONNA HAPPEN,
I DON'T THINK.
SO WE JUST START CASUALLY
THROWING THE BOXES.
LIKE I SAY,
HE'S PRETTY ATHLETIC.
WELL, MAYBE HE'S NOT
THAT ATHLETIC.
THEN YOU ALWAYS HAVE THAT
ONE HEAVY BIT WHEN
YOU'RE MOVING.
THIS DRESSER WEIGHED A LOT.
SO WINSTON GOT THE IDEA TO
TAKE THE DRAWERS OUT OF HER,
WHICH I THOUGHT WAS GOOD,
BUT DIDN'T REALLY
UNDERSTAND THE --
I DON'T QUITE
SEE HOW THAT --
BUT WINSTON SAYS, NO, NO.
WHAT HE'S GOING TO DO IS USE
THE ROPE OFF THE FLAGPOLE.
IF I CAN JUST TIE THAT AROUND
THE DRAWERS AND DRESSER,
THEN WE CAN USE
LIKE A PENDULUM DEAL,
AND INSTEAD OF LIFTING
IT ONTO THE TRUCK,
WE'LL JUST HOIST HER UP,
AND WE'LL JUST SWING HER
ONE THERE, YOU KNOW?
BRING HER IN.
AND THEN IF WE JUST TIE
THAT OFF ON THE FLAGPOLE,
AND THEN WE CAN DO
LIKE A AN UP AND OVER
OR AN EASY GOER
OR A UNDER ROUNDER
OR WHATEVER THE
HECK THEY CALL IT.
NOW, WATCH THIS.
NOW, YOU CATCH THIS, WALTER.
HERE SHE COMES.
OH!
OKAY, JUST --
I'M SURE IT WASN'T THAT
EXPENSIVE AN HEIRLOOM.
NOW, WE'VE GOT JUST
A LITTLE BIT OF ROOM LEFT
AND WE'VE GOT ALL THIS STUFF
WE'VE GOTTA FIGURE OUT --
SO WINSTON'S GOT THE IDEA
WHAT WE GOTTA DO IS GET
EVERYTHING INTO THE ONE BOX.
SO I DUMP THIS
BOX IN THERE.
BUT TO ME THERE
SEEMS TO BE --
THIS IS LIKE PACKING A TRUNK
WHEN YOU'RE GOING AWAY
ON HOLIDAYS.
IT JUST DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
YOU CAN GET EVERYTHING IN.
YOU KNOW, SOME PEOPLE I GUESS
THEY'RE BETTER PACKERS.
LIKE I TRIED TO
GET THAT GOLF BAG IN.
IT JUST WOULD NOT GO.
BUT WINSTON GRABS HER,
AND HE HAS AN EYE.
HE JUST JUST FLIPS HER OVER
AND THERE YOU GO.
SO WE GET EVERYTHING
EXCEPT THE PULL-OUT SOFABED.
AND THAT WAS
A PITCH FORK.
WE DIDN'T REALISE
THESE THINGS SPRING OUT.
OH!
OH, YOU'RE FINE.
SO WE THINK IF
WALTER WOULD LAY ON IT,
HIS WEIGHT WOULD
HOLD THE BED DOWN.
IS THAT THE QUICKEST
WAY THERE, DO YOU THINK?
ANYWAY, HE GETS ON THERE.
NOW WE GET HER LOADED
ON TO THE BACK OF THE TRUCK.
I MEAN, WALTER
HAS TO STAY THERE,
BUT IT'S GOOD.
HE CAN SEE WHERE
HIS NEW HOUSE IS.
AND WE'RE ALL SET TO GO.
AND YOU KNOW, THAT WOULD'VE
BEEN THE END OF IT.
IT'S A PERFECT DAY.
EVERYTHING TURNED OUT GREAT.
BUT WE FORGOT ABOUT THE PIPES
THAT WINSTON HAD LEFT,
AND THEN AWAY SHE GOES.
AND -- OH!
WELL, THAT'S EVEN BETTER,
BECAUSE I WAS AFRAID WE WERE
GOING TO LEAVE A BOX BEHIND.
BUT WE GOT EVERYTHING NOW,
INCLUDING WALTER.
AND WALTER, WHAT YOU
CAN DO NOW, I GUESS,
IS STAY BACK THERE
AND HOLD THE LOAD ON.
HE WON'T ASK US TO HELP
HIM NEXT TIME, WILL HE?
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, EVERYBODY'S
BEEN BUGGING ME
THAT I SHOULD DRIVE A MORE
FUEL-EFFICIENT VEHICLE.
BUT I THINK I'VE COME UP WITH
A BETTER WAY TO DO THE SAME
DARNED THING.
NOW, I KNOW IF YOU
FOLLOW CLOSE ENOUGH BEHIND
ONE OF THESE BIG
TRACTOR TRAILER UNITS,
YOU CAN SAVE A LOT OF GAS
BECAUSE THE TRUCK IS
BLOCKING THE AIR RESISTANCE.
IN OTHER WORDS,
IT'S BREAKING THE WIND
SO YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
BUT HERE'S A WAY
TO NOT BURN ANY GAS.
I TOOK THE
PULL START MECHANISM
OFF OF A LAWN MOWER
THAT I BORROWED,
AND THEN I MOUNTED HER ONTO
THE HOOD OF MY CAR HERE.
HAD TO ADD A LITTLE
EXTRA ROPE TO HER,
BUT WHAT I END UP WITH IS A
SPRING LOADED TOE MECHANISM
THAT I HAVE COMPLETE
CONTROL OVER.
NOW, I KNOW YOU'RE THINKING,
HEY, THIS IS DANGEROUS.
I MEAN, TRUCK DRIVERS
ARE BIG STRONG GUYS.
THEY COULD EASILY
COME BACK HERE
AND TEST THE LIMITS
OF MY DENTAL PLAN.
BUT FOR THAT TO HAPPEN THEY'D
HAVE TO SEE ME FIRST,
WOULDN'T THEY?
IF THE GUY STARTS HEADING
IN SOME DIRECTION I
DON'T WANNA GO,
I JUST RELEASE THE HANDLE,
DROP HER INTO GEAR
AND HEAD FOR
THE NEXT TRUCK STOP.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ coughing ]
THERE WE GO.
WE'RE GOOD.
NO PROBLEM.
NO PROBLEM, HAROLD.
NO PROBLEM?!
WE ALMOST BURNED
THE LODGE DOWN!
AND THAT'S
NO PROBLEM?
NOW, SEE, TO ME, THE KEY
WORD THERE IS "ALMOST".
AND LOOK WHAT YOU
LEARNED TODAY.
YOU LEARNED THAT
SUNFLOWERS ARE
FLAMMABLE.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
YOU LEARNED THAT THE FIRE
DEPARTMENT DOESN'T ALWAYS
GET THERE ON TIME.
AND I LEARNED NOT
TO STAND IN WATER
DURING AN
ELECTRICAL FIRE.
WHERE'D THAT WATER
COME FROM ANYWAY?
I'D RATHER
NOT SAY.
AND YOU KNOW,
I'M THINKING
YOU LEARNED
THAT EVERY CLOUD
HAS A SILVER LINING.
WELL, NOT WHEN
IT'S A MUSHROOM CLOUD.
SEE, YOU'RE NOT LOOKING
AT THE BIG PICTURE HERE.
WE HAD TO EITHER
HIDE THE LODGE
OR PAY $1,000 FINE.
OKAY, THE SUNFLOWER
PLAN DIDN'T WORK
PERFECTLY.
NO, NO,
NOT PERFECTLY, NO!
OKAY. OKAY.
BUT NOW THE CITY'S PUTTING
UP A GREAT BIG BILLBOARD
THAT'S GONNA
BLOCK THE LODGE.
SO MISSION
ACCOMPLISHED.
UNCLE RED,
THE SIGN SAYS,
"TOXIC WASTE.
KEEP OUT"!
SEMANTICS, HAROLD.
THAT'S ALL THAT IS, EH?
I MEAN, THE JOB GOT DONE.
DIDN'T COST US ANYTHING.
WE'RE THE LUCKY ONES.
OH, REALLY?
WELL, I MIGHT NOT BE
ABLE TO HAVE CHILDREN.
WELL, THEN THEY'RE
THE LUCKY ONES.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
BE CAREFUL NOW.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I LEARNED TODAY THAT YOU
CAN'T FIX AN UGLY THING
BY HIDING IT.
BUT I'M STILL NOT
GONNA SHAVE MY BEARD OFF.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND FIREMAN HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
EVERYBODY, SIT DOWN.
MEETING TIME.
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
WHAT ARE YOU EATING
THERE, WINSTON?
OH, SUNFLOWER SEEDS.
YOU WANT SOME?