UNTIL THIS LAST CENTURY,
MAN HAS ALWAYS FOUND
A WAY TO GET ANIMALS TO
DO THE WORK FOR HIM.
OF COURSE THAT JOB
HAS NOW BEEN TAKEN
OVER BY ASSISTANT MANAGERS.
BUT THE INSTINCTS
ARE STILL THERE,
SO NOW WE GOT ANIMALS
SUPPLYING OUR ENTERTAINMENT
IN MOVIES ON TV AND
AS THE FEATURED ACT
IN THEM THEME SHOWS.
I THINK IT'S JUST MAN'S
WAY OF REAFFIRMING
HIS DOMINANCE
OVER THE ANIMAL KINGDOM.
WE'LL TAKE A KILLER
WHALE, PLOP IT INTO
A SWIMMING POOL
AND FORCE IT TO
DO BACK FLIPS
THROUGH A FIERY HOOP
JUST TO EARN A FREE LUNCH.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT MAKES
US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
RED GREEN: THE SURGEON
GENERAL HAS DECLARED
THAT SMOKING IS
HAZARDOUS TO
YOUR HEALTH,
STAY TUNED.
BILL AND I ARE GOING
TO GO FISHING IN A
RUBBER RAFT
WHICH IS NOT
COMPLETELY SUCCESSFUL,
AND OUR OLD PAL BUZZ
SHERWOOD IS GOING
TO SAY HELLO
TO HAROLD.
I ALWAYS LIKE IT
WHEN HE HURTS HAROLD.
AND NOW HERE HE IS,
THE MASTER OF ALL
HE SURVEYS
BUT ONLY BECAUSE HE'S
EXTREMELY SHORTSIGHTED,
MY UNCLE,
MR. RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
YES, IT'S TRUE,
I AM SHORTSIGHTED,
AND I CAN PROVE
THAT BY HIRING HIM TO
DIRECT AND PRODUCE MY SHOW.
I'M HAROLD AND
I'M HERE AND I'M
HIP AND I'M HAPPENIN'.
AND YOU'RE HISTORY.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
THE LAST EPISODE
OF THE RED GREEN
SHOW AS WE KNOW IT.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT, WE'RE CANCELLED?
NO, WE'RE NOT
CANCELLED, HAROLD,
IT'S JUST THAT I THINK
I'VE GOT A BETTER IDEA.
WE'RE GOING TO CHANGE
THE FORMAT A LOT.
IT'S GOING TO BE RED'S
WATER WONDERLAND MARINE
EXTRAVAGANZA.
OH, THIS BECAUSE
JUNIOR SINGLETON TOOK HIS
FAMILY TO FLORIDA, RIGHT?
OH, HAROLD, HE TELLS
ME THAT THE SEA WORLD
DOWN THERE
IS JUST RAKING
THE CASH IN.
PEOPLE LOVE TO SEE
FISH DOING TRICKS.
OF COURSE YOU'VE
PROVEN THAT.
SO WE'RE GOING TO
REPLACE YOU, HAROLD,
WITH THE KILLER WHALES
AND THE SEALS AND
THE PORPOISES
AND THE DOLPHINS
AND THE MANATEES,
AND ALL THAT
KIND OF STUFF.
WELL, HAVE YOU GOT
ANY OF THESE
ANIMALS YET?
NO, BUT WE'VE GOT
AN AQUARIUM, POSSUM LAKE.
AND WE GOT A RUSTED OUT
VAN FOR THE FISH
TO JUMP THROUGH
AND WE GOT A WHOLE
BUNCH OF STUFF TO
BALANCE ON THEIR NOSES.
YEAH, BUT YOU HAVE
TO HAVE PERFORMERS.
I MEAN, YOU CAN'T DO
A SHOW WITHOUT TALENT
IN FRONT OF THE CAMERA.
WE HAVE FOR YEARS.
DID I SAY CAN'T?
I MEANT SHOULDN'T.
OH THE FIRE IN MY EYES
COULD NOT DISGUISE
HOW I FELL FOR HEATHER
SHE HELD MY HAND
LIKE I WAS HER MAN
AND SAID ZIP OUR
SLEEPING BAGS TOGETHER
WELL, I COMPLIED
IN A HURRY
BUT SHE SAID WAIT
YOU'RE NOT WORTHY
AND ALL HOPE OF
ROMANCE WAS KILLED
MY LOVE SHE TURNED
HER BACK ON
BECAUSE MY BAG
WAS ONLY DACRON
WHEREAS HERS WAS
THE MORE EXPENSIVE
GOOSE DOWN FILLED
ALL RIGHT, SO YOU GOT
YOURSELF SPLATTERED
ACROSS THE COUCH
WATCHING TV,
GRAZING THE DIAL
WITH YOUR THUMB,
SNAPPING ON THE
REMOTE LIKE YOU'RE
SENDING MORSE CODE.
PHASE NUMBER ONE,
YOUR WIFE SAYS,
"HEY STOP FLICKING
AROUND LIKE A
RABID BANSHEE,
"YOU'RE GIVING THE
DOG A CONNIPTION, EH?
"FIND A CHANNEL
AND STICK TO IT.
AND THEN YOU ANSWER THAT
YOU CAN'T FIGURE OUT
WHAT YOU WANT TO WATCH
UNTIL YOU SEE
EVERYTHING THAT'S ON.
AND SAY ALL OF THAT
WITHOUT TAKING YOUR
EYES OFF THE TV SCREEN.
PHASE NUMBER TWO,
SHE SUGGESTS THE
TV GUIDE,
WHICH IS WHAT
IT'S FOR.
NOW YOU GOT TO TELL
HER THAT YOUR GLASSES
ARE OVER ON THE TABLE
AND THE TV GUIDE IS
UP ON THE BACK OF
THE TOILET.
PHASE NUMBER THREE,
SHE PICKS UP HER
KNITTING
OR A BOOK
OR SOMETHING.
YEAH, AND THEN YOU
FIND OUT WHAT YOU
WANT TO WATCH,
A COMEDY, SPORTING EVENT
AND ONE OF THE SHOWS WHERE
GUYS ARE SHOOTING PEOPLE.
AND YOU'RE GOING TO
WATCH ALL THREE
AT ONCE.
THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN
SOMETHING REALLY EXCITING
HAPPENS ON THE COMEDY,
LIKE HAWKEYE FINDS
A DATE FOR RADAR OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT, EH?
YEAH.
SO YOU START WATCHING
THAT FOR AWHILE
AND THEN YOUR WIFE STARTS
WATCHING IT WITH YOU.
BUT THEN THE COMMERCIALS
COME ON AND YOU START
THUMBING YOUR WAY
ON TO A
BETTER SHOW.
PHASE NUMBER FOUR,
YOUR WIFE GETS UP,
LEAVES THE ROOM, FINDS
HERSELF HER OWN TV
AND FILES
FOR DIVORCE.
BUT IT COULD HAPPEN.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, LIFE IS
ABOUT CHOICES
AND YOU CANNOT HAVE A
SUCCESSFUL MARRIAGE
AND A TV REMOTE,
SO I SAY GO FOR THE
SUCCESSFUL MARRIAGE.
WELL, UNLESS THE
PLAYOFFS ARE ON
OR IT'S SWEEPS WEEK.
WELL, WITH EVERYONE
THINKING ABOUT OUR
NEW MARINE SHOW,
I THOUGHT I WOULD TAKE
HANDYMAN CORNER AND
SHOW YOU ALL
HOW TO BUILD
AN AQUARIUM.
BECAUSE WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT IT, WHAT IS
AN AQUARIUM?
JUST A GLASS BOX
WITH A BIG PRICE TAG.
SO ALL YOU NEED IS A
COUPLE OF WINDOWS
THAT ARE MADE INTO
DIFFERENT PANES HERE.
YOU CAN USUALLY
GET THESE AT YOUR
NEIGHBOUR'S HOUSE
WHILE HE'S
AT WORK.
AND THEN WHAT YOU'VE
GOT TO DO IS SCRAPE
THE PUTTY OFF THERE
SO YOU CAN GET
THE WINDOWS OUT.
OH.
I TELL YOU WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO,
I'M GOING TO USE
MAYBE A PROPANE
TORCH OF MINE
AND JUST MELT THE
PUTTY OUT OF THERE.
WHERE'S THAT PROPANE?
OH, THERE IT IS.
ALRIGHTY.
THIS SHOULD WORK
IN NO TIME.
THERE SHOULDN'T
BE ANY PROBLEM.
WELL, I'LL JUST
GET THE FIRE --
MAYBE I WILL JUST
LET THE FLAME JUST BURN
THE PUTTY OUT OF THERE.
YEAH.
PERFECT.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT TURNED OUT
REAL GOOD THERE.
AND NOW ALL'S
YOU GOT TO DO
IS PICK UP THE GLASS
OUT OF THE RUBBLE.
OH.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU ALWAYS WANT TO LET
THAT GLASS COOL DOWN
WHEN YOU USE
THIS TECHNIQUE.
NOW HERE'S SOMETHING THAT
MIGHT BE OF INTEREST
TO YOU,
THIS IS ANOTHER HANDYMAN'S
HELPER, THIS IS CALLED
SILICONE CAULKING.
THIS STUFF IS A
PLIABLE GLUE
AND IT ALSO HOLDS OUT
WATER, SO IT'S PERFECT
FOR MAKING AN AQUARIUM.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW I'M READY TO
PUT A LITTLE BIT OF
WATER IN THAT THING.
YOU GOT TO LET THE
WATER GET IN THERE
AHEAD OF TIME
SO, YOU KNOW, IT CAN
KIND OF SIT IN THERE
AND GET ALL THE CHEMICALS
OUT OF IT BEFORE
YOU PUT THE FISH
IN THERE.
OH.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, IF YOU SHOULD HAPPEN
TO GET A LEAK OF SOME KIND,
DON'T FEEL BAD ABOUT IT,
NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED OF,
IT'S NO ONE'S FAULT,
AND THE SOLUTION
IS VERY SIMPLE,
MORE CAULKING.
THERE THAT
SHOULD DO IT.
SMELLS LIKE A
PREHISTORIC ORDER
OF FISH AND CHIPS IN HERE.
BUT I BET WE GOT
THE LEAK FIXED.
NO.
NOT QUITE.
I THINK THIS IS GOING TO
TAKE ME A LITTLE LONGER
THAN WE HAD FIGURED ON,
SO WHY DON'T WE GET
BACK TO THE SHOW AND
I'LL CALL YOU WHEN I'M DONE.
RED GREEN:
STAY TUNED.
BILL IS GOING TO SHOW
YOU WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU HAVE A LEAK
IN YOUR INNER TUBE
AND HAROLD IS GOING
TO AUDITION FOR THE
MARINE SHOW.
I WANT TO TALK TO ALL
YOU MIDDLE AGED
GUYS OUT THERE
WHO FOR WHATEVER REASON
HAVE ABANDONED YOUR DREAMS.
MAYBE YOU DREAMED OF
BEING AN ASTRONAUT
AND YOU ENDED UP
AS A SPACE CADET,
MAYBE YOU DREAMED
OF BEING AN AWARD-
WINNING STATESMAN
AND YOU ENDED UP
AS A WARD OF THE STATE
OR MAYBE YOU DREAMED OF
BEING AN AMWAY SALESMAN
AND YOU ARE.
WHATEVER THE DISAPPOINTMENT,
AT THIS POINT IN OUR LIVES
WE SHOULDN'T BE BITTER.
MAYBE WE SET OUR
GOALS TOO HIGH.
MY PERSONAL GOAL WAS
TO SET THE LAND SPEED
RECORD IN A ROCKET CAR
THAT I WOULD DESIGN,
ENGINEER AND BUILD.
BUT IN RETROSPECT,
I THINK THAT WAS A
BIT OF A LONG SHOT,
ESPECIALLY AFTER I
DROPPED OUT OF
JUNIOR HIGH.
THE LAST HALF OF
OUR LIVES,
WE GOT TO STAY
AMBITIOUS.
MAYBE WE SHOULD WE
MAKE OUR DREAMS JUST
A LITTLE MORE REALISTIC, EH?
WHY DON'T YOU VOW
TO GO TO YOUR GRAVE
WITH AT LEAST ONE
OF YOUR OWN TEETH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
OR MAYBE YOU CAN TRY
TO DO SOMETHING NICE
FOR SOMEBODY EVERY DAY,
EVEN IF IT'S NOT TELLING
THEM WHAT YOU'RE
REALLY THINKING.
I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING,
I'M GOING TO KEEP
MY DREAM
NO MATTER HOW OLD
AND RUN DOWN I GET.
EVEN IF I END UP IN
A WHEELCHAIR,
I WILL TURN IT INTO
A ROCKET-POWERED
WHEELCHAIR.
REMEMBER, I'M
PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, RED'S WATER
WONDERLAND MARINE
EXTRAVAGANZA
HAS ALREADY BOOKED
IT'S FIRST MAJOR
STAR ATTRACTION.
SOMEONE FROM THE CAST
OF BAYWATCH IN A BIKINI?
NO, HAROLD, MOOSE
THOMPSON GOT US A
REAL LIVE SEA CREATURE,
ONE THAT ALREADY HAD
HIS OWN TV SERIES.
FLIPPER?
HE GOT FLIPPER?
OH, I LOVE FLIPPER
THE DOLPHIN.
OH, HE WAS SO COOL.
HE SAVED HUNDREDS OF
LIVES IN HIS SHOW.
OH, YEAH, YEAH, I LOVE
FLIPPER THE DOLPHIN, YEAH.
NO, NO, MOOSE
GOT US FLOPPER,
THE MUSICAL MANATEE.
FLOPPER THE MANATEE?
YEAH.
HAD HIS OWN SERIES?
HE CERTAINLY
DID, HAROLD,
IT WAS FLOPPER'S RAGTIME
RIVERBOAT REVIEW.
IT WAS ON COMMUNITY
ACCESS UNTIL THE
COMMUNITY SAW IT
AND FLOPPER KINDA
WENT DOWNHILL AFTER THAT.
A BIT ASTRAY ON US.
BUT HE'S GONE TO
THE BETTY FORD AQUARIUM,
GOT HIMSELF ALL
CLEANED UP,
LOST 900 POUNDS.
HE'S COMING BACK
IN GREAT FORM.
LEARN TO DO THE BACK
FLIPS AND JUMP
THROUGH HOOPS
AND BALANCE
STUFF ON HIS NOSE.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
WELL, YOU'RE A LITTLE
HEAVY TO BALANCE
ON HIS NOSE.
NO, I MEANT LIKE WHAT
ABOUT ME AND THE
NEW SHOW?
IS THERE A PLACE
WHERE I FIT IN
TO THE NEW SHOW?
OH, SURE THERE
IS HAROLD.
WE'RE GOING TO NEED
AN AUDIENCE, AREN'T WE?
OKAY.
WE'RE BACK.
AND TO MAKE
OUR AQUARIUM WORK,
I HAD TO CALL
IN THE HANDYMAN
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
I GUESS WE ALL
KNOW SHE'S GOING TO
BE WATER TIGHT NOW, HUH?
WELL, YOU'RE WRONG.
ALL RIGHT.
SO WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO ADAPT OUR INITIAL PLAN
AND FOR THAT YOU'RE
GOING TO NEED ANOTHER
SHEET OF GLASS
AND A PIECE
OF TINFOIL.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU TAPE THE FOIL
TO THE SHEET OF GLASS
AND THEN YOU TAPE THE
GLASS ON TO THE TOP
OF THE AQUARIUM
AND THEN YOU JUST SET
THE ANGLE OF THAT
LIKE A MIRROR
SO WHEREVER YOU HAPPEN
TO BE SITTING
IN THE ROOM
BECAUSE UNFORTUNATELY
THIS IS GOING TO BE
REALLY YOUR ONLY
VIEW OF THE FISH.
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE, IT
IS SHOWING A CERTAIN
AMOUNT OF RESPECT
FOR THE PRIVACY OF THE
FISH, IS IT NOT?
SO REMEMBER, IF THE
WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OH, BOY,
THE BASIN LEAKS.
WELL, I SUPPOSE I COULD
PUT MORE CAULKING ON THAT
OR, NO, I COULD THROW
THIS WHOLE UNIT
INTO A BATHTUB
OR INTO A DUMPSTER.
HERE WE ARE WITH
OUR RESIDENT
BUSH PILOT,
BUZZ SHERWOOD.
HOW YOU DOING, BUZZ?
HEY, IT'S THE
BIG RED GUY!
HEY, HAROLD,
HOW'S DIRECTING?
SO, BUZZ, DO YOU WANT
TO DO SOME FLYING TODAY?
SURE.
AS LONG AS IT DOESN'T
BREAK ANY OF MY NEW
AIR SAFETY RULES.
LIKE RULE NUMBER ONE,
MAN, I'M NOT FLYING ANY
MORE LAWYERS UP HERE,
NO WAY, MAN.
ON THESE HUNTING TRIPS
ALL THE TIME WE'RE
AIRBORNE, RIGHT,
THEY GO BUZZ MY DOOR
WON'T CLOSE PROPERLY,
OR BUZZ IS THE WING
SUPPOSED TO WOBBLE
LIKE THAT,
OR BUZZ WE DIDN'T
SIGN A RELEASE FORM
AND THAT MAKES
YOU CULPABLE.
I SUPPOSE IF I KNEW
WHAT THAT MEANT I'D
KNOW HOW TO REACT.
BUZZ, HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT FLYING MANATEES?
MANATEES?
IS THAT LIKE THOSE
MASON OR SHRINER GUYS,
BECAUSE I FLEW A
FAT SHRINER --
NO, NO, NO, THE MANATEES
THEY'RE KIND OF LIKE
A FISHY MAMMAL.
AND THERE'S TWO OF
THEM AND THEY'RE
KIND OF BIG.
PROBABLY LOOKING AT
TWO AND A HALF
TONS THERE.
OH, THAT SHOULD
BE NO PROBLEM.
I'LL BRING THEM IN
BY THE NORTH END
OF THE LAKE
AWAY FROM
THE COTTAGERS.
BUT THERE ARE A
LOT OF TALL TREES UP
THERE, AREN'T THERE?
YEAH, BUT NOT BY
MY SECOND PASS.
HA, HA.
ALL RIGHT THEN.
I TELL YOU WHAT,
MOOSE THOMPSON WILL
GO ALONG WITH YOU TO
SUPERVISE, ALL RIGHT?
MOOSE THOMPSON,
NO WAY MAN.
TOO MUCH WEIGHT.
NOW WE'RE BENDING
THE NEEDLE.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE
CAN DO, OH, OH,
WHAT WE'LL DO IS
WE'LL GET RANGER
GORD'S FIRE BOMBER.
THE WATER BOMBER.
IT'S A BIGGER
PLANE, RIGHT?
WE'LL FILL THAT
SUCKER FULL OF WATER.
YEAH.
THEN MANATEES CAN
JUST LIKE WALLOW AS
WE CRUISE THEM IN.
IT WILL BE --
IT WILL BE GREAT.
IS THAT LEGAL?
PSSSSS.
OH, RIGHT.
JUST DON'T TELL ANYBODY.
I COULD LOSE MY PILOT'S
LICENSE, RIGHT?
BUZZ, YOU DON'T HAVE
A PILOT'S LICENSE.
OH RIGHT.
IT'S MAIL CALL.
[ RINGING BELL ]
I HAVE A LETTER
TODAY FROM DAVID
OF CALGARY, ALBERTA.
AND DAVID ASKS: HAVE
YOU EVER TRIED A
MEPP CYCLOPS?
OH, YEAH, I BELIEVE
I DRANK ONE OF THOSE
WHEN I WAS IN THE MILITARY.
FIRE DOWN ONE
OF THOSE PUPS,
IT WILL LAST YOU A
WHOLE THREE DAY PASS.
UNCLE RED, HE'S
TALKING ABOUT A
FISHING LURE.
OH YES.
OH YEAH.
THE CYCLOPS.
I KNOW THAT VERY
WELL, VERY WELL.
BUT, YOU KNOW, YOU GET
INTO ENDORSING FISHING
LURES AND SO ON,
TOUCHY AREA
THERE, HAROLD.
I MEAN, I'VE SEEN GUYS
CATCH FISH WITH A PAIR
OF PANTS ON A COAT HANGER.
WOW.
HOW DO YOU CATCH FISH
WITH A PAIR OF PANTS?
WELL, YOU GO
FLY FISHING.
BUT, YOU KNOW, THERE
ARE SO MANY FACTORS
THERE, HAROLD.
THERE'S THE TIME OF
DAY, THE TIME OF YEAR,
THERE'S THE WATER
TEMPERATURE, THE WIND,
THE AGE OF THE
FISH, YOU KNOW.
AND THE REAL TRUE
FISHERMEN LIKE MYSELF
TAKE ALL THESE FACTORS
INTO CONSIDERATION.
YEAH.
HOW MANY FISH WOULD
YOU SAY YOU CATCH
ON AVERAGE?
OH, TOO MANY TO
COUNT, HAROLD.
OH, I WORDED THAT WRONG.
I SAID HOW MANY WOULD
YOU SAY YOU CATCH.
ACTUALLY, HOW MANY WOULD
YOU REALLY CATCH,
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
IN A YEAR?
A LOT, HAROLD.
QUITE A FEW.
A WHOLE MESS OF THEM.
MORE THAN A HUNDRED?
WELL, YOU KNOW, I GET
PRETTY BUSY WITH THE
SHOW AND SO ON.
YEAH.
SO LIKE IT'S LESS
THAN A HUNDRED, BUT
IT'S MORE THAN TEN.
MORE THAN YOU, HAROLD.
I CAUGHT ONE LAST YEAR.
ALL RIGHT, WE TIED.
BILL ASKED ME TO
GO FISHING AND SAID
HE'D BRING THE BOAT.
I DON'T BELIEVE THAT'S
TECHNICALLY A BOAT, BILL.
OH, OH, OH.
NOW ALL WE GOT TO
DO IS LOAD ALL THE
STUFF INTO THE BOAT.
SO IT'S NOW
LATER THAT DAY,
WE'RE OUT FISHING.
THE FISH ARE PROBABLY
FINISHED AND ARE AT HOME
WATCHING ONE
OF THE SOAPS.
ANYWAY, FISHING YOU
GOT TO JUST KIND OF
GET INTO A MINDSET.
YOU JUST RELAX, KIND
OF WRAP YOUR LEGS AROUND
THE COOLER AND GO FOR IT.
SO I'M JUST TRYING
TO ENJOY MYSELF
AND THE WAY TO DO
THAT, OF COURSE,
IS TO IGNORE WHAT
BILL IS DOING.
OF COURSE IN THIS CASE
IT WAS A BIT OF
A MISTAKE.
BILL, YOU'RE HOOKED
INTO THE RUBBER
RAFT THERE.
LATER THAT DAY.
BY GOLLY THOSE THINGS WILL
GET HEAVY WHEN THEY'RE
FULL OF WATER,
AS DOES BILL,
AS DOES MY HAT.
WHAT DO YOU GOT THERE?
MEDICAL CUSHION.
WHAT'S THAT FOR?
WHAT IS THAT, BILL?
IT'S SOME SORT OF
A DIVERSION FROM
FISHING?
WHAT'S THE IDEA?
WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
WELL, THERE'S A BIT OF AN
EXAMPLE OF OVERPACKAGING
I WOULD SAY.
SO IS THIS SHOW.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING, BILL?
ARE YOU GOING
TO BLOW THAT UP?
WE CAN'T GET IN THERE.
THAT'S NOT BIG
ENOUGH FOR US
NO MATTER HOW MUCH YOU --
OKAY, BILL, OKAY,
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT STILL
IT'S NOWHERE NEAR --
IT'S STILL.
OH, OH, OH, OH.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
CAPTAIN, SHE'S
GONNA BLOW.
SO THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO USE AS --
I DECIDE NOT TO GO.
BILL I THINK THAT'S
MORE OF A ONE MAN FISHING --
OH, A BIT OF A NAIL COMING
OUT OF THE DOCK, THERE.
DIDN'T NOTICE THAT.
IN YOU GO.
THERE YOU ARE.
BILL, LET ME GET THE
EQUIPMENT FOR YOU,
ALL RIGHT?
LET'S GET READY.
HERE SHE COMES.
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE?
THERE'S QUITE A
SELECTION HERE.
OH.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
NOW WE'RE SAFE.
THERE WE GO.
A COUPLE OF TACKLE BOXES,
A PADDLE, ANOTHER PADDLE,
PAIL, A LITTLE BAIT
BOX, A FISHING NET,
GOT YOUR LURE IN
THERE, AND GOT
SOME SUNTAN --
OH, OH, OH, OH.
OH BOY.
HOLY COW.
BILL YOU CAN'T --
SLOW DOWN.
COME BACK, BILL.
OH, NO, NO, NO,
NOT THIS WAY.
THERE WE GO.
SO WERE THEY BITING?
DON'T YOU KNOW IT'S
BAD LUCK TO COME HOME
WEARING YOUR BOAT
THERE, BILL?
LET ME HELP YOU
OUT OF THAT STUFF.
OH, IT'S LINE DANCING
AT POSSUM LODGE.
RED GREEN:
STAY TUNED.
RANGER GORD TRIES TO
EXPLAIN ZEBRA MUSSELS
AND THE MARINE SHOW
LOSES ONE OF ITS
HEADLINERS.
MOOSE CAN FLY, BY ME.
LAST WINTER JUNIOR
SINGLETON DROVE
MY SNOWMOBILE
A RECORD 49 FEET
THROUGH THE AIR,
RIGHT OVER OUR TOOL SHED.
TODAY MOOSE THOMPSON
ANNOUNCED THAT RECORDS
ARE MADE TO BE BROKEN,
BUT WITH MOOSE EVERYTHING
IS MADE TO BE BROKEN.
VERY, VERY EXCITING
STUFF NOW.
BUZZ SHERWOOD AND
MOOSE THOMPSON
HAVE FLOWN OFF
TO BRING IN
FLOPPER.
AND EVERYTHING IS
FALLING INTO PLACE.
IT'S PRETTY
DARN EXCITING.
WE GOT A LOT
OF OTHER ACTS, TOO.
WE'RE GOING TO
START OFF WITH
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
AND HIS DANCING BASS
AND WE GOT JUNIOR
SINGLETON'S MAGICAL
MINNOWS,
THEN WE'RE HAVING
A MEDLEY OF SONGS
FROM THE LITTLE MERMAID
SUNG BY SALLY STRUTHERS.
WOW.
YOU REALLY GOT OLD MANY
SEDGEWICK'S DANCING BASS?
YES, WE DID,
HAROLD.
AND I JUST
BOOKED SMELT BOY.
THAT WOULD BE
STINKY PETERSON.
WOW.
YOU FOUND A
SMELT COSTUME.
IT WASN'T
NECESSARY, HAROLD.
ANYWAY, FLOPPER,
OF COURSE,
FLOPPER THE
MUSICAL MANATEE
IS STILL GOING TO
BE THE STAR OF
THE SHOW.
AND THEY SAID VARIETY
TELEVISION IS DEAD.
BUT, UNCLE RED, WHO
ARE YOU GOING TO GET
TO DIRECT FLOPPER?
WELL, FLAPPER.
THAT'S FLOPPER'S SISTER.
SHE'S HIS MANAGER
AND SHE DIRECTS ALL
OF HIS LIVE PERFORMANCES.
OH, OKAY.
YEAH, OKAY, LIVE, SURE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, HAS
SHE EVER DIRECTED
A NETWORK TELEVISION
SHOW BEFORE?
YEAH, I BELIEVE SHE DID
THE THIRD SEASON OF
WHO'S THE BOSS.
ANYWAY, THEY'RE ALL
ARRIVING LATER ON TODAY
AND THEY'RE GOING TO
WARM UP AT POSSUM LAKE.
OH, YEAH.
BUT, UNCLE RED,
POSSUM LAKE IS FRESHWATER.
FRESHWATER, WHAT
AM I SAYING?
BUT, NO,
IT'S UNSALTED, YOU KNOW,
AND MANATEES LIVE
IN SALT WATER SO.
WELL, THERE'S A JOB
FOR YOU ON THE SHOW.
REALLY?
YEAH, GO SALT
UP POSSUM LAKE.
OH, I LOVE
SHOW BUSINESS.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
NATURE TALK PART
OF THE SHOW.
WE'RE HERE WITH
OUR GOOD FRIEND
RANGER GORD.
HELLO CIVILIZATION.
YEAH, ANYWAY, GORD IS
GOING TO TELL US
ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT ACTUALLY COULD
PUT A KIBOSH ON OUR
WHOLE MARINE SHOW,
NAMELY ZEBRA
MUSSELS.
THANK YOU VERY
MUCH, RED.
SHOULD WE WAIT FOR
THE REST OF THE
GUYS TO SHOW UP?
NO, I WOULDN'T.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I
JUST THOUGHT THAT BEING
AT THIS FIRE WATCH TOWER
FOR THE LAST 16 YEARS
WITHOUT A DAY OFF,
THEY COULD GIVE ME
A HALF AN HOUR.
JUST TELL US ABOUT
THE ZEBRA MUSSELS,
GORD, WOULD YOU?
YEAH, THE ZEBRA IS A
MEMBER OF THE EQUINE
OR HORSE FAMILY,
AND SO THE ZEBRA'S
MUSCULATURE,
IS VERY SIMILAR
TO THAT OF A HORSE.
GORD.
NOW, THE HIND LEGS --
JUST A MINUTE,
PLEASE, RED.
THE HIND LEGS
ARE EXTREMELY
POWERFUL LIMBS
AND THEY CAN PROPEL
THE ANIMAL FOR
QUITE A DISTANCE
AT A SINGLE BOUND.
GORD, WE'RE NOT
TALKING ABOUT ZEBRAS.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
ZEBRA MUSSELS.
YOU KNOW THOSE
THINGS LIKE BARNACLES,
THEY FORM ON THE
BOTTOM OF BOATS?
WHAT?
WHEN DID THESE THINGS
SHOW UP, JUST NOW?
MID-80S.
THE GOVERNMENT WARNED
EVERYBODY TO LOOK
OUT FOR THEM.
I HAVEN'T HEARD A
THING ABOUT IT.
THE LAST I GOT
FROM HEAD OFFICE
WAS A PAMPHLET ABOUT
A NEW PROBLEM CALLED
ACID RAIN.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
WATCH OUT FOR
THAT ONE.
I HAVEN'T GOT A THING
FROM THEM SINCE, RED,
NOT EVEN A
PAY CHEQUE.
BUT, GORD, GORD,
THINK ABOUT IT
THIS WAY,
BY THE TIME THEY
PAY YOU THAT BACK
PAY THEY OWE YOU,
IT'S GOING TO TRIPLE
THE NATIONAL DEBT, HUH?
NATIONAL DEBT?
YEAH.
WHAT, THE COUNTRY
IS IN DEBT NOW?
WELL, FLOPPER AND
FLAPPER ARE NOT
GOING TO BE PART
OF RED'S WATER WONDERLAND
MARINE EXTRAVAGANZA.
BUT I JUST SALTED
UP POSSUM LAKE.
IT'S LIKE THE
DEAD SEA OUT THERE,
IN MORE WAYS THAN ONE.
AND NOW THE MANATEES
AREN'T EVEN COMING?
OH, NO, NO THEY'RE
HERE, HAROLD.
BUZZ SHERWOOD FLEW
THEM IN IN ONE OF
THEM WATER BOMBERS
HE BORROWED
FROM A FRIEND.
MOOSE THOMPSON WENT
ALONG FOR THE RIDE
AND YOU KNOW HOW MOOSE
GETS NERVOUS AROUND
BIG STARS.
FLOPPER AND FLAPPER?
YEAH.
MOOSE GOT ALL EXCITED
UP THERE AND WHILE
THEY WERE CIRCLING
HE PULLED THE WRONG LEVER,
OPENED THE BOMB BAY DOORS.
I GOT TO TELL YOU,
MANATEES ARE NOT YOUR
NATURAL BORN HIGH DIVERS.
FOUR TONS
OF BELLY FLOP.
OH, NO.
WHY IS IT THAT
BIG STARS ALWAYS GO
DOWN IN PLANE WRECKS?
WHY?
THEY'RE NOT
DEAD, HAROLD,
THEY'RE JUST --
WELL, THEY'RE A
DIFFERENT SHAPE NOW.
OH.
WELL, I BET YOU, YOU
KNOW, HE PROBABLY CAN'T
BALANCE THINGS ON
HIS NOSE ANYMORE.
OH, YOU GOT
TO BE KIDDING.
HE COULD BALANCE A
PIANO ON THERE NOW.
IT'S LIKE A
HELICOPTER PAD.
BUT FLOPPER HAS
DECIDED TO RETIRE
FROM SHOW BUSINESS,
SO I GUESS WE'RE
GOING TO GO BACK
TO THE OLD RED GREEN
SHOW THE WAY IT WAS.
OH, SO WHO'S GOING
TO LIKE, YOU KNOW,
PRODUCE/DIRECT,
UNCLE RED?
WELL, I SPOKE TO HIS
SISTER, FLAPPER, BUT
SHE WANTED TOO MUCH MONEY.
IT'S ME, ISN'T IT?
OH, YES.
IT'S ME.
YOU WILL NOT
REGRET THIS.
YES, I DO.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
CRY OF THE POSSUM.
IT'S MEETING TIME.
WAIT 'TIL THE
GUYS HEAR.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD,
I WILL BE DOWN WHEN
I GET DRIED OFF.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING
AND I'M BRINGING
A PICTURE OF A
SEACOW AUTOGRAPHED.
MAYBE YOU CAN GIVE
THAT TO YOUR SISTER,
THE RESEMBLANCE
IS UNBELIEVABLE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
UNTIL NEXT TIME, ON
BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
HAROLD: ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
WE GOT THE NEW PROP IN
FOR THE CHRISTMAS SHOW,
SCHINDLER'S
CHRISTMAS LIST.