OH.
YOU SEE THIS?
SOMETHIN' UNDER
THE WINDSHIELD WIPER HERE.
YOU SHOULD NEVER READ ANY
PAPER YOU FIND UNDER YOUR
WINDSHIELD WIPER.
SEE, THAT WAS A WASTE OF TIME.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE READ THAT.
AND I SHOULDN'T BE EXPECTED
TO HAVE TO READ THINGS
UNDER MY WIPER
JUST BECAUSE SOCIETY THINKS IT'S
A GREAT PLACE TO STICK STUFF.
SO LOOK WHAT I'VE DONE HERE.
I GOT A PAIR OF HEDGE CLIPPERS
AND TOOK 'EM APART.
ON THE BOTTOM OF THE
WINDSHIELD I STUCK ONE BLADE,
SHARP SIDE UP.
THE OTHER BLADE I PUT RIGHT
ON THE WIPER ITSELF,
SHARP SIDE DOWN.
NOW I'M ALL SET FOR ANY KIND
OF ADVERTISING FLYER
OR SAVE THE WHALES PAMPHLET
OR PARKING INFRACTION
THAT HAPPENS TO FIND ITS
WAY ONTO MY WINDSHIELD.
I DON'T HAVE TO LOOK AT IT;
I DON'T HAVE TO READ IT;
I DON'T EVEN HAVE TO TOUCH IT
TO GET RID OF IT.
I JUST DISPOSE OF IT BY
CLEANING MY WINDSHIELD
THE NORMAL WAY.
[cheering and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
WELL, WE'VE HAD A MAJOR
WIMPING OUT
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
EVERY YEAR AT THIS TIME,
WE CHALLENGE THE GUYS AT
CARIBOU LODGE
TO A BIG TUG OF WAR.
BUT THEY BACKED OUT.
THEY SAID THERE'S TOO MUCH OF
A HEALTH RISK.
BECAUSE AFTER LAST YEAR'S
TUG OF WAR,
IT ENDED UP IN A DRAW AFTER
FIVE HOURS OF STRAINING
ON BOTH SIDES.
THE ONLY REAL WINNER WAS
THE LOCAL HERNIA CLINIC.
SO NOW WE MISSED THE
THRILL OF COMPETITION
AND THE FUN OF BEATING THE CRAP
OUT OF ANOTHER LODGE.
WELL, DALTON,
I SEE YOU FINALLY GOT
THAT SUIT BACK FROM
THE CLEANERS.
I GOT A GREAT IDEA HOW TO
REPLACE THE TUG OF WAR
WITH CARIBOU LODGE.
YOU'RE GOING TO PERFORM
THE NUTCRACKER?
NO, NO, RED.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF THOSE
GROUPS THAT RECREATE BATTLES?
OH, YEAH.
NO, NO.
WE DON'T NEED TO RECREATE --
THE WORLD HAS ENOUGH
FRESH BATTLES.
NO, THESE ARE
HISTORIC BATTLES, RED.
THEY REENACT HISTORIC BATTLES.
WELL, SURE, BUT THERE'S
BEEN NO HISTORIC BATTLE
AROUND HERE,
OTHER THAN THAT TIME JUNIOR
SINGLETON'S WIFE FOUND OUT
HE BOUGHT A HOVERCRAFT.
NO, SEE, WE'RE GONNA
MAKE UP OUR OWN BATTLE.
AS LONG AS IT'S THE CARIBOU
LODGE VERSUS US, WHO CARES?
WE GET TO WEAR
THE NEAT CLOTHES.
WE GET TO SHOOT
THE MUSKETS.
DO WE GET TO BE SHOT
AND KILLED OURSELVES?
'CAUSE THAT WOULD KINDA TAKE
THE FUN OUT OF IT FOR ME.
NO, NO, NO.
HERE LET ME SHOW YOU.
HERE HOLD THIS.
OKAY, NOW, SEE,
WHAT WE'RE SHOOTING --
OOP --
ARE THESE
LITTLE FLAGS, RED.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
SEE, WE SHOOT
THE RED FLAGS,
THEY SHOOT THE
GREEN FLAGS.
PUT A LITTLE PIECE OF DUCT TAPE
ON HERE SO IT'LL STICK TO A
GUY WHEN HE GETS HIT.
DUCT TAPE, THE MUSKETEER'S
SECRET WEAPON.
OH, BOY.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU KIND OF WON ME
OVER WITH THAT PART,
BUT, BOY, I REALLY DON'T
WANNA WEAR THE COSTUME.
MAYBE I COULD BE AN
UNDERCOVER MUSKETEER.
NO, RED, YOU CAN'T!
WHAT?
NO, YOU GOTTA WEAR THE
COSTUME, OR IT'LL WRECK IT.
OH, ALL RIGHT,
I'LL WEAR THE COSTUME.
BUT I'M NOT
WEARING THE TIGHTS.
AH, YOU GOTTA WEAR THE
TIGHTS, OR IT'LL --
I'LL WEAR THE TIGHTS!
MAN.
[applause]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheering and applause]
AND TODAY'S PRIZE --
WELL, LET ME JUST SAY,
YOU'RE GONNA NEED THIS
WHERE YOU'RE GOING.
ARIZONA!
NOPE.
TWO FREE LINE DANCING LESSONS AT
THE MERCURY CREEK DANCE ACADEMY.
UH, Mr GREEN,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET Mr ROTHSCHILD
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND GO!
OKAY, WINSTON, YOUR JOB
DOESN'T PAY ENOUGH, SO YOU --
WORK HARD FOR A RAISE.
NO, SEE,
YOU'RE WAY OFF.
YOU HATE THIS JOB, OKAY.
THINK ABOUT IT,
AND WHEN YOU DO THINK ABOUT IT,
YOU'D RATHER BE DOING
ANYTHING ELSE, SO YOU --
STOP THINKING
ABOUT IT SO MUCH!
JUST DO IT TO IT, YOU KNOW.
SUCK IT UP.
THAT'S WHAT WE DO IN THE
SEWAGE BUSINESS ANYWAY.
WELL, I'M SAYING THIS JOB
IS DRIVING YOU CRAZY.
YOU'RE GETTING ALL
DEPRESSED, SO YOU --
SEEK PROFESSIONAL HELP.
GET A CHECK-UP
FROM THE NECK UP.
YOU WOULDN'T EVEN NEED TO GO
SEE A DOCTOR IF YOU DO THIS.
OH, GET ANTHONY ANTHONY'S
NEW TAPE.
YEAH, IT GIVES YOU
THE MOTIVATIONAL
BOOST YOU NEED
TO GET ON WITH YOUR LIFE
IF YOU'RE FEELING DOWN.
IF YOUR LIFE STINKS,
DON'T INHALE.
YOU'RE ALMOST OUTTA
TIME, Mr GREEN.
THIS WORD ISN'T IN
YOUR VOCABULARY.
I GIVE UP.
WHAT?
THAT'S A TERRIBLE ATTITUDE!
YOU CAN'T JUST QUIT NOW.
THERE YOU GO.
HEY, HAROLD.
OH, HEY, UNCLE RED.
NOW, DON'T TAKE
THIS THE WRONG WAY,
BUT HOW CAN YOU
STAND IT HERE?
I LOVE
WORKING HERE.
IT'S VIBRANT.
IT'S EXCITING.
IT'S CHALLENGING.
IT'S SEXY.
SEE WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE
A GIRLFRIEND, HAROLD?
WELL, AS A
MATTER OF FACT,
SEE THAT BLONDE
OVER THERE?
WHERE?
THERE.
OVER THERE!
WELL, I CAN'T SEE
WHERE YOU'RE POINTING.
WHAT'S HER NAME?
CYNTHIA.
HEY, CYNTHIA!
JUST HI,
THAT'S ALL.
SHE'S KINDA CUTE.
YOU ASKED HER OUT YET?
IN MY MIND.
YOU WANNA KNOW
WHAT YOU GOTTA DO?
YOU'RE GONNA GIVE
ME ADVICE ON DATING?
COME ON, NOW, HAROLD,
I WAS QUITE THE LADIES' MAN
BEFORE I MET YOUR
AUNT BERNICE YOU KNOW.
AND LOOK AT US NOW, HUH?
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER A
LONG, LONG, LONG TIME.
LONG, LONG...
UNCLE RED.
RIGHT, OKAY,
SO YOU GOTTA GET A
GIFT FOR CYNTHIA, OKAY?
SOMETHING SPECIAL
JUST FOR HER.
UM, MAYBE ELECTRIC SOCKS
OR A PERSONAL FLOATATION DEVICE.
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
THEN YOU GOTTA ASK
HER OUT ON A DATE.
BUT KEEP IT SUBTLE, ALL RIGHT?
YOU WANNA LEAVE SOMETHING
OF YOURS ON HER DESK.
NOTHING TOO
OBVIOUS, RIGHT.
MAYBE A PAIR OF BOOTS
OR A BUCKET, EH?
THAT'S JUST AN EXCUSE
SO YOU CAN TALK TO HER.
THEN YOU JUST
KEEP IT COOL.
YOU SAY,
HEY, CYNTHIA!
PASS ME THAT BUCKET,
WILL YOU?
AND LET'S GO OUT.
SEE?
UNCLE RED, UM, I GOTTA
GET BACK TO WORK NOW.
RIGHT.
RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
OKAY, I'LL SEE
YOU LATER, HAROLD.
BY, CYNTHIA!
Red:
IT SEEMS NO MATTER
HOW MUCH PLANNING YOU DO
OR HOW SAFETY CONSCIOUS YOU ARE,
SOMETHING ALWAYS GOES WRONG.
I HAD THIS FISHING BOAT MOUNTED
ON TOP OF MY CAR THERE,
AND SHE WAS SOLID.
I HAD PUT A ROLL AND A HALF
OF DUCT TAPE INTO THE JOB.
SO I'M DRIVING ALONG,
AND UP COMES THE WIND.
BAM! SHE'S OUTTA THERE.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
I DIDN'T ACTUALLY AIM THE
BOAT AT THAT HITCHHIKER.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
YOU SHOULD HAVE HEARD
THE STRING OF OBSCENITIES.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
A WOMAN OF THAT AGE
SHOULDN'T BE HITCHHIKING
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
BUT I'M THINKING THIS WHOLE
ROOF RACK CONCEPT NEEDS A
BIT OF REENGINEERING.
WOULDN'T IT BE A LOT SAFER
AND MORE AERODYNAMIC
IF YOU COULD PUT STUFF
UNDER THE CAR
INSTEAD OF OVER IT?
BUT AS THE FAT GUY SAID
TO THE PHONE BOOTH,
WE NEED A LITTLE MORE CLEARANCE.
[groaning]
ALL RIGHT THE NEXT
STEP'S REAL EASY.
WHAT YOU NEED IS FOUR OF THESE
GREAT BIG TRACTOR TIRES.
THEY'RE NOT THAT
HARD TO COME BY.
THERE'S ABANDONED TRACTORS
ALL OVER THIS COUNTRY,
THANKS TO THE
GOVERNMENT TRADE POLICIES
AND PEOPLE PREFERRING
TO EAT FOOD MADE FROM VINYL.
[groaning]
OKAY, WE HAVE A CHALLENGE HERE.
THE TRACTOR WHEEL ISN'T ACTUALLY
MADE TO MOUNT RIGHT ONTO
THE CAR HUB.
I GOT THE RIM OFF.
TOOK THE TIRE OFF THAT.
THE RIM FITS FINE.
I DON'T WANT THE RIM ON THERE.
I WANT THE TRACTOR
WHEEL ON THERE.
SO WHAT I NEED TO DO IS MOUNT
THE TRACTOR WHEEL ONTO THE RIM
WITH SOME KIND OF AN ADAPTOR.
NOW, IF YOU CALL UP
YOUR LOCAL AUTO SUPPLY
AND TELL 'EM YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR AN ADAPTOR TO PUT TRACTOR
WHEELS ONTO A 1990 HONDA,
WELL, THERE'S GONNA
BE SOME LAUGHTER,
PROBABLY A VISIT FROM THE COPS,
MAYBE A PSYCHIATRIC NURSE.
SO INSTEAD,
MIGHT I RECOMMEND
THE HANDYMAN'S SECRET ADAPTOR,
DUCT TAPE.
STARTING TO THE
IDEA NOW, AREN'T YOU?
NOW ALL I HAVE TO DO IS SLIDE
THE BOAT UNDERNEATH THERE,
AND I'LL BE ABLE TO CARRY IT
SAFELY AND EASILY
TO MY PREDETERMINED DESTINATION.
IT'S NOT A TRACTOR-TRAILER.
IT'S A TRACTOR
AND A TRAILER.
AND IT'S JUST THAT SIMPLE.
SO REMEMBER IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
THERE'S ANOTHER BONUS
TO THIS UNIT.
I'VE ACTUALLY ADDED PADDLES TO
THE DRIVE WHEELS ON HER.
SO IT'S NOT JUST
A BOAT CARRIER,
IT'S AN AMPHIBIOUS CAR.
THERE'S ONE QUESTION THAT
TERRIFIES ALL MEN,
EVEN MORE THAN "CAN I
HELP YOU FIND THE LINGERIE
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR, SIR?"
YOU KNOW IF YOU'RE A GUY WHO'S
LIVED WITH A WOMAN FOR ANY
LENGTH OF TIME,
SHE'S EVENTUALLY GONNA ASK
YOU THAT TERRIBLE QUESTION,
"DO I LOOK OLD?"
NOW, I KNOW SHE'S TOLD YOU
SHE ALWAYS WANTS YOU TO BE
HONEST WITH HER,
BUT SHE WASN'T BEING HONEST
WITH YOU WHEN SHE SAID THAT.
OKAY, SO YOU COULD PRETEND
YOU DIDN'T HEAR HER,
BUT SHE'LL ASK AGAIN,
BELIEVE ME.
OR YOU COULD JUST
LAUGH IT OFF, YOU KNOW.
BUT I SAY KEEP THAT LAUGH TO
EXACTLY THREE SECONDS.
A THREE-SECOND LAUGH MEANS,
NO, YOU DON'T LOOK OLD.
A TEN-SECOND LAUGH SAYS,
CAN YOU SAY METHUSELAH?
AND A 30-SECOND LAUGH IS
TECHNICALLY A SUICIDE
ATTEMPT ON YOUR PART.
NOW, THE BEST ANSWER HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH THE QUESTION
BECAUSE THE QUESTION HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH THE QUESTION.
SHE KNOWS SHE LOOKS OLD.
AND SHE KNOWS YOU KNOW
SHE LOOKS OLD.
WHAT SHE'S CONCERNED ABOUT IS
THAT YOU'RE GONNA BE UNHAPPY
BECAUSE SHE LOOKS OLD.
SO WHEN SHE SAYS,
"DO I LOOK OLD?"
GIVE HER AN ANSWER
THAT PUTS HER MIND AT EASE.
SAY, "YOU LOOK PERFECT
TO ME, HONEY."
OR, "NOT THROUGH THESE EYES."
RATHER THAN,
"DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
"I NEVER LOOK AT YOU."
UNLESS YOU WANNA BE OUT THERE
BUYING LINGERIE AGAIN.
REMEMBER I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[audience whistling]
[applause]
I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THIS.
BOY, YOU LOOK GREAT.
I GAVE YOU THE
FANCIEST UNIFORM.
I FEEL LIKE A MORON.
SEE, GETTIN' USED
TO IT ALREADY.
DOESN'T HELP.
WHAT'S THIS THING FOR?
WELL, THAT'S YOUR
BATON, RED.
YOU'RE THE COMMANDER.
THAT'S HOW YOU LEAD THE TROOPS!
WELL, SOME TROOPS.
SO FAR, YOU, MIKE, AND I ARE
THE ONLY GUYS WITH COSTUMES.
WHAT'S THAT ABOUT?
WELL, THERE'S A BIT
OF RESISTANCE TO MY
COSTUME RENTAL FEE.
BUT IT'LL WORK OUT, YOU KNOW.
ONCE THOSE GUYS
HEAR THE BATTLE CRY,
THEY'LL BE SCRAMBLING
FOR THEIR LEOTARDS.
THERE'S A VISUAL.
[whistling and applause]
I DELIVERED ALL THE FLAGS
TO THE CARIBOU LODGE.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO GIVE
THEM THE GREEN ONES,
AND THEN WE SHOOT OFF
THE RED ONES, RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
WHAT ABOUT THE
GUYS AT THE LODGE?
DID THEY HAVE
THEIR UNIFORMS ON?
YEAH, THEY'RE A
BUNCH OF CLOWNS.
WHAT DO THEIR
COSTUMES LOOK LIKE?
THEY'RE A
BUNCH OF CLOWNS.
THEY DIDN'T LIKE
Mr HUMPHREY'S PRICES,
SO THEY MADE A DEAL WITH
THE CIRCUS THAT'S IN TOWN.
WAIT A SECOND, DOESN'T
THE CIRCUS NEED THEM?
NO, THEY SHUT DOWN.
OH.
YEAH, THE ELEPHANT HAD A
GASTRO-INTESTINAL PROBLEM.
THEY HAD TO HOSE DOWN THE
FIRST FOUR ROWS OF SEATS.
THERE'S A BIG
STINK ABOUT THAT.
WELL, LET'S GET
THIS OVER WITH.
YES, LET'S FIGHT THOSE
CLOWNS ON THE BEACHES!
FIGHT THEM IN
THE MARKETPLACE!
WE WON'T REST UNTIL WE --
DALTON, DALTON.
I'M THE COMMANDER,
NOT YOU.
OH.
SORRY.
OKAY.
WE'RE GONNA FIGHT
ON THE WEEKEND.
AND, UH, WE'LL FIGHT
ON A CIVIC HOLIDAY,
IF WE HAVE TO.
THAT'LL BE DOUBLE TIME,
OF COURSE.
ALL RIGHT, NO,
DALTON, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'M KINDA OUTTA
THE MOOD NOW, RED.
LET'S GO KICK
SOME CARIBOU BT!
YEAH-H-H-H!
WELCOME TO
TALKING ANIMALS.
ANIMAL CONTROL OFFICER, ED FRID,
HAS BROUGHT US IN
SOMETHING SPECIAL TODAY,
ABOUT A
GAZILLION BEES.
COME ON
UP HERE, ED.
NO, NO,
COME ON.
IT'S JUST THAT I THOUGHT
I SAW ONE GET OUT.
I GUESS WE'RE GONNA BE OKAY.
IS IT A GOOD IDEA TO HAVE AN
ACTIVE BEEHIVE INDOORS?
I MEAN, IS THIS SAFE?
NO, NOT REALLY.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
HAVE PROTECTIVE WEAR ON.
YEAH, DEFINITELY.
BUT MY SAFETY SUIT'S GETTING
A LITTLE SNUG, RIGHT.
SO INSTEAD,
WHAT I DID
WAS I TOOK THIS INSECT NET,
AND I COVERED OVER
THE ENTIRE --
THE, UH --
HIVE. HIVE.
HIVE, YES.
OH, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
THAT'S TOO BAD
'CAUSE I WAS HOPING YOU COULD
STICK YOUR HAND IN THERE
AND GRAB A CHUNK OF HONEYCOMB
AND SHOW IT TO EVERYBODY.
YEAH, I THOUGHT YOU
MIGHT WANT THAT, YOU KNOW.
THEY ALWAYS WANNA
SEE THE HONEYCOMB.
I GUESS IT'S WORTH IT,
ME GETTING STUNG TO DEATH!
I'M KIDDIN'
YOU, RED.
I'LL GET YOU
HONEYCOMB.
THAT'S WHY I BROUGHT
THIS SMOKER.
KNOCKS THE BEES
RIGHT OUT.
ALL RIGHT.
GONNA NEED A LITTLE MORE SMOKE
THAN THAT, AREN'T YOU, ED?
YEAH, YOU WANT ME
TO MAKE 'EM MAD?
IS THAT YOUR
HELPFUL SUGGESTION?
OH, ONE GOT OUT!
WATCH OUT.
WHERE'D SHE GO?
THERE ON THE TABLE.
OKAY, RED,
HOLD THIS.
I DON'T SMOKE.
THIS IS NOT A GOOD
TIME FOR HUMOUR, RED.
WHOA!
AH-H-H-H!
OKAY, I GOTTA GO.
Red:
YOUNG WALTER AND I ARE
GONNA PUT A NEW DOCK IN.
WE'RE GONNA USE THE OIL DRUMS
FOR FLOATATION UNDER THE DOCK
AND WE HAD ALREADY BUILT IT.
WE JUST HAD TO KINDA POSITION
THEM IN THE RIGHT DISTANCE --
PUT THAT RIGHT
UNDER THERE, WALTER --
RIGHT DISTANCE APART.
AND THE DOCK WE JUST --
HEAVY, IT'S A HEAVY UNIT.
THAT DOCK, THE WATER WAS --
THE WOOD WAS PRETTY WELL --
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYIN'.
SO WE GOT THAT ON THERE AND -
OH-OH, LOOK OUT.
LOOK OUT.
OH, OH!
OH, BOY.
OH!
YOU KNOW, I DON'T REALLY
REMEMBER THIS PART.
I'M SURE WALTER DID
EVERYTHING HE COULD FOR ME.
ANYWAY, WE GOT HER UP,
AND THE IDEA WAS WE WERE
JUST GONNA ROLL HER RIGHT IN.
WE DIDN'T WANNA
GET INTO THE LAKE.
NOT REALLY SURE WHAT --
BUT THE DRUMS KINDA
BUNCHED UP ON US THERE,
AND WALTER ENDED UP ON THE --
NOW, DON'T --
WHY WOULD YOU GO UP THERE?
THAT'S NOT HELPING TO GO UP -
WALTER, THAT'S REALLY
OF NO USE.
THAT'S OF NO USE.
THAT'S OF NO VALUE
TO UP THE POLE.
YOU'RE NOT A FLAG, WALTER.
WE NEED TO GET THE DOCK
INTO THE WATER.
HE DOESN'T WANNA --
IT'S POSSUM LAKE.
OKAY, TELL YOU WHAT.
HERE YOU GO.
I'LL GET HER LEVEL.
JUST JUMP DOWN.
NOT TOO HARD!
OH-H-H-H!
OH, MAN.
WALTER'S NOT REALLY
MUCH OF A SWIMMER.
I DIDN'T HAVE A LIFE RING
OR A LIFE JACKET.
NEED TO THROW HIM SOMETHING
THAT WOULD FLOAT.
UH, OH, HERE WE GO.
INCOMING!
OH, I KNOW.
GIVE HIM SOMETHING
HE CAN KINDA STEER HIMSELF.
GET HIMSELF BACK TO SHORE.
HERE YOU GO.
PADDLE.
I BETTER GO OUT AND RESCUE HI
LIKE THE COAST GUARD WOULD.
ACTUALLY THIS GAVE ME --
I GOT OUT THERE ON THE BARRELS
AND I GOT AN IDEA.
COME ON IN.
HERE'S WHAT WE'LL DO.
OKAY, SEE THAT TRUCK?
THAT'S OUR NEW DOCK!
MOST PEOPLE DON'T REMEMBER
RODERICK FEATHERSTONE,
AND EVERYBODY ELSE
IS WORKING ON IT.
HE WAS THIS AREA'S GIFT
TO THE SILENT SCREEN.
BUT WHEN THE BRIGHT
LIGHTS OF HOLLYWOOD
TURNED THEIR BACK ON HIM
AND SHOWED HIM THE DOOR,
HE RETURNED BACK TO
SPEND OUT HIS LIFE
HERE AT POSSUM LAKE.
BORN WEB SWITZER,
APRIL 1, 1900,
HE WAS A NATURAL
THEATRICAL TYPE,
SO HE WAS FORCED TO LEAVE
TOWN AT THE AGE OF 19.
HE WENT TO HOLLYWOOD,
WHERE HE GOT SORT OF FAMOUS
AS AN ACTOR UNDER THE NAME
RODERICK FEATHERSTONE.
NOBODY EVER MENTIONED RODERICK
BY THE TIME I HIT IT BIG
IN HOLLYWOOD.
HE ALWAYS PLAYED
THE HERO'S BEST FRIEND.
HE MADE A WHOLE STRING
OF PRETTY BAD FILMS...
"VIOLET'S TENDER CONDITION,"
"MUSTARD KEENE,"
"KNEE FLAPPERS,"
AND "DON'T TELL MOMMA!"
BUT IT WASN'T UNTIL HE
DID A SOUND FILM
THAT PEOPLE REALIZED
HE WASN'T PRETENDING.
HE REALLY COULDN'T ACT.
HIS LAST FILM
LAID A BIG TIME EGG.
CAME OUT IN 1930,
A MUSICAL CALLED
"WHAT DEPRESSION?"
AFTER A FEW YEARS,
RODERICK WAS TENDING CHICKENS
BACK ON THE FAMILY FARM
NEAR POSSUM LAKE.
ACCORDING TO MOST PEOPLE,
HE WAS HAVING A LOT OF TROUBLE
ADJUSTING BACK TO OUR LIFESTYLE.
NOW, I DON'T RECALL HE CAME
INTO MY STORE VERY MUCH.
HE'D SEEN HOW
THE OTHER HALF LIVED,
AND HE STILL CARRIED
HIMSELF THAT WAY.
YOU KNOW THE KIND.
GUY WANTED TO BUY
STUFF THAT WORKED.
HE RAN THAT
AMATEUR THEATRE COMPANY,
AND HE WAS ALWAYS AFTER ME FOR
YEARS TO PLAY WILLY LOMAN
IN A PLAY CALLED
"DEATH OF A SALESMAN."
AS IF ANYONE WAS
GONNA COME SEE A PLAY
WHEN THE TITLE GAVE
AWAY THE ENDING.
I REMEMBER ON
HIS 80th BIRTHDAY
THEY GOT TOGETHER A BUNCH
OF HIS OLD FRIENDS,
AND THEY HAD THIS BIG TO-DO FOR
HIM AT THE OLD FILM HOUSE.
I WAS WORKING THERE AT THE TIME
AS A FREELANCE USHER.
SO WE HELPED Mr FEATHERSTONE
TO HIS SEAT
AND THEY STARTED SHOWING ALL
THESE JERKY BLACK AND WHITE
OLD FILMS, RIGHT.
BUT THAT FILM BROKE,
AND TOOK 'EM A LONG
TIME TO FIX IT,
SO Mr FEATHERSTONE, HE GOT UP
AND MADE THIS LITTLE SPEECH
ABOUT WHAT A GREAT LIFE HE'D
HAD BEING A MOVIE STAR
AND EVERYTHING,
BUT THAT POSSUM LAKE WAS HOME,
AND HOME'S THE
MOST IMPORTANT THING.
AND EVERYBODY WAS CRYING AND
CLAPPING AND EVERYTHING.
AND I REALIZED THAT THIS WAS MY
CHANCE TO EMPTY THE TILL.
AND THEN HE WAS GONE.
HE NEVER MARRIED.
NEVER EVEN HAD ANY KIDS.
BUT LET'S NOT FORGET
THE POSSUM LAKE LITTLE THEATRE,
THE GOVERNMENT GRANT PLAYERS,
AND THE STILL CONTROVERSIAL
NUDE SCENE IN "OUR TOWN"
WERE ALL COURTESY OF THE EFFORTS
OF RODERICK "WEB SWITZER"
FEATHERSTONE.
WE'LL NEVER SEE
ANOTHER ONE LIKE HIM,
AT LEAST THAT'S THE HOPE.
WELL, I THINK WE MAY HAVE
CHANGED THE COURSE OF
REENACTED HISTORY.
WE COULD'VE USED A LITTLE MORE
INSPIRED LEADERSHIP.
PUT A SOCK IN IT, DALTON.
IT WAS ALL YOUR IDEA.
OH, GOOD IDEA,
POORLY EXECUTED.
I'LL HAVE YOU
WE WERE THE
ONLY ONES WITH THE
COSTUMES OUT THERE.
MAN, IS IT EVER
HARD TO LEAD GUYS WHEN
YOU'RE WEARING TIGHTS!
WELL, THE GUYS AT CARIBOU LODGE
DIDN'T HAVE THAT PROBLEM.
WELL, NO,
THEY DIDN'T, DID THEY?
THOUSANDS OF THEM
DRESSED AS CLOWNS,
FIRING OFF ALL
THOSE GREEN FLAGS.
YEAH, WHEN THAT
LITTLE CAR TURNED UP,
AND ABOUT 100
REINFORCEMENTS HOPPED OUT --
HEY, WAIT A SEC.
LOOK AT ALL THE
HITS MIKE AND I TOOK.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOU?
WELL, I SPRAINED MY ANKLE
IN A GOPHER HOLE.
YEAH, WHILE YOU
WERE RUNNING AWAY.
OH.
TURN AROUND.
WELL, SO WHAT?
YOU GOT FLAGS ALL
OVER YOUR BACK TOO!
YEAH, BUT THEY'RE
FROM OUR SIDE.
[laughter and applause]
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT WHEN A
COMMANDER LED THE TROOPS
THE TROOPS WERE
SUPPOSED TO FOLLOW,
NOT STAY BEHIND AND FIRE OFF
ROUNDS FROM THE BEER TENT.
THEY WERE FIRING OFF ROUNDS
LONG AFTER THEY RAN OUTTA AMMO.
THERE'S A BIG
STINK ABOUT THAT.
[possum squealing]
OH, MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN TO
JOIN THE TROOPS LATER.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
DESPITE HOW I LOOK,
I'M GONNA GO RIGHT TO SLEEP.
I'M COVERED WITH FLAGS,
BUT THEY'RE ALL AT HALF MAST.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
OKAY, YOU GOTTA SIT DOWN NOW.
IT'S TIME TO SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY GOTTA SIT DOWN.
OKAY, GUYS, SIT DOWN, PLEASE.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, PLEASE.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
AND THE FIRST THING I'M GONNA
CHANGE ARE THESE TIGHTS.
THERE'S A BIG STINK ABOUT THAT.
OH, STOP IT.