[shuffling noises]
YOU KNOW, EVERY YEAR, I PUT
THESE DECORATIONS OUT ON THE
LAWN AT CHRISTMAS.
THIS TIME, I THOUGHT I'D BE A
LITTLE MORE AMBITIOUS.
[slide whistle]
IT'S A WONDERFUL RED GREEN
CHRISTMAS.
[cheers and applause]
[sleigh bells]
AND, NOW, HERE HE IS, THE QUIRKY
AND FUNNY GUY WHO COMES OFF YOUR
ROOF.
MY UNCLE, YOUR HARE-ROASTING
HERO, RED GREEN!
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY, VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE IT.
AND ALL THE BEST OF THE HOLIDAY
SEASON TO EACH AND EVERY ONE OF
YOU.
THIS IS OUR VERY FIRST CHRISTMAS
SPECIAL.
I'D LIKE TO APOLOGIZE, FIRST OF
ALL, FOR BEING SO CRASS AS TO
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THE WHOLE
CHRISTMAS THING.
AND I'D ALSO LIKE TO APOLOGIZE
FOR TAKING SO DARN LONG TO THINK
OF IT.
YOU KNOW, UNCLE RED, I REALLY
DON'T THINK YOU HAVE TO
APOLOGIZE FOR BEING INSENSITIVE.
PEOPLE HAVE COME TO EXPECT THAT
OF YOU BY NOW.
I'M SURE YOU KNOW MY NEPHEW,
HAROLD, OR AS HIS PARENTS CALL
HIM, THE GHOST OF CHRISTMAS
PAST.
I JUST THINK IT'S SO COOL.
IT'S SO COOL TO GET, LIKE, A
CHRISTMAS SPECIAL.
IT'S SO COOL.
NOT A LOT OF OUTDOOR SHOWS GET A
CHRISTMAS SPECIAL.
NO, THAT'S RIGHT, NO.
YOU KNOW, THE SPORTS NETWORK DID
A COUPLE.
TROLLING FOR PRESENTS.
AND THE OTHER ONE WAS FROSTY THE
COLD ONE.
THAT WAS A BIG ONE.
WELL, WE'RE NOT HERE TO TALK
ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE'S MISTAKES.
WE'VE GOT LOTS OF OUR OWN TO
SHOW.
THAT'S RIGHT, SO YOU JUST SIT
BACK AND LOWER YOUR STANDARDS.
YOU'LL HAVE A HAPPIER CHRISTMAS,
AND IT'LL MAKE THIS A BETTER
SHOW.
[cheers and applause]
[sleigh bells]
IT'S TIME TO PLAY THE POSSUM
LODGE WORD GAME, AND, TODAY
MR. MIKE HAMAR GETS TO PLAY FOR
THE OPPORTUNITY TO GO TO FRANCE.
WHOO-HOO.
YES, ALL EXPENSES ARE PAID.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS STICK OUT
YOUR THUMB.
[laughter]
OH, I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
THINKING, AND, YES, THE RETURN
TICKET IS INCLUDED.
[laughter]
ALL RIGHT, MR. HAMAR...
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. HAMAR TO SAY THIS
WORD...
"GIVING."
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, GO.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE, THIS IS
SOMETHING PEOPLE DO AT
CHRISTMAS.
ARGUE?
NO, NO, NO, THIS IS A HAPPY
THING, BUT PEOPLE DO IT TILL IT
HURTS.
OH, EAT.
NO.
OKAY, LOOK, MIKE, THIS IS BETTER
THAN JUST GETTING, OKAY?
GETTING...
AWAY?
NO, OKAY, NO.
YOU KNOW, THEY HAVE A
SAYING, "CHRISTMAS IS THE SEASON
FOR..."
LIGHTER SENTENCES.
TRUE, YEAH.
OKAY, MIKE.
YOU WRAP SOMETHING UP, AND YOU
GIVE IT TO SOMEBODY.
WHAT'S THAT CALLED?
SELLING NARCOTICS.
NO, AND IT'S ALMOST OUT OF
TIME, UNCLE RED.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
THERE'S AN EXPRESSION, OKAY?
"LOVE IS THE GIFT THAT KEEPS
ON..."
REQUIRING MEDICATION?
MY CELLMATE PROVED THAT.
HE WAS A VERY GIVING PERSON.
THERE WE--
[bell dinging frantically]
CHRISTMAS IS--AT LEAST WHERE I
COME FROM--SNOW.
APPARENTLY, THE INUIT PEOPLE,
NOW, HAD 23 DIFFERENT WORDS
FOR SNOW.
THEY'VE INVENTED NAMES FOR EVERY
KIND OF SNOW YOU GOT.
THEY GOT BUILDING SNOW, DRIFTING
SNOW, FIRST SNOW, SALTY SNOW,
WATERY SNOW, EVEN SOMETHING
CALLED BEADING SNOW.
THIS GOT ME WONDERING, HOW MANY
NAMES FOR SNOW DO I KNOW?
LET'S SEE, THERE'S PACKING SNOW,
POWDER SNOW, SLUSH, SLEET, BLACK
ICE, FLURRIES, WHITEOUTS,
DUMPED-ON, BURIED, AND, "BOY,
IT'S REALLY COMING DOWN."
THEN THERE'S, "IT'S LIKE A
SKATING RINK OUT THERE.
I DON'T THINK I BETTER HEAD OUT
IN THIS MESS.
HAVE YOU GOT A SPARE BED AND
ANOTHER EGGNOG HANDY?"
TYPE OF SNOW.
OKAY, THAT'S ONLY 11 NAMES FOR
SNOW.
I GOT PLENTY MORE, BUT I CAN'T
SAY THEM ON TELEVISION...
EVEN IN INUIT LANGUAGE.
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP PART OF
THE SHOW WE CALL "IF IT AIN'T
BROKE, YOU'RE NOT TRYING."
JOINING US TODAY, WE GOT HAP
SHAUGHNESSY.
WHAT DO YOU GOT FOR US THERE,
HAP?
THIS IS MY CHRISTMAS LIGHTS,
RED.
OH, BOY.
IS THIS AN UNTANGLE JOB, OR IS
THIS "FIND THAT ONE DARN BULB
THAT'S BURNT OUT" JOB, 'CAUSE
THERE BOTH KILLERS.
NOPE, NEITHER.
THE RAT CHEWED THE PLUG OFF.
HAP, YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO
PUT A PLUG ON A PIECE OF WIRE,
HUH?
YEAH, BUT EVERY TIME I
TRY IT, THE RAT BITES ME.
OW!
[laughter and applause]
COME ON, HAP.
HE'S STILL IN THERE.
THAT'S THE MAIN PROBLEM.
JEEZ, HE'S REALLY HANGING ON
THERE.
YOU MAY HAVE TO DO WITHOUT
CHRISTMAS LIGHTS, HAP.
NO, NO, CAN'T DO THAT.
GOT TO HANG THE LIGHTS.
I INVENTED THEM.
[laughter]
YOU INVENTED CHRISTMAS
LIGHTS?
YEAH.
I ONLY TRIED TO SAVE MY PLATOON.
ON CHRISTMAS DAY, WE WERE
SURROUNDED, OUT OF AMMO, AND OUR
SERGEANT, SERGEANT...
PEPPER...
[laughter]
HE WANTED TO SURRENDER, BUT
WE WERE HOLED UP IN A LIGHT BULB
FACTORY.
SO I GOT THIS IDEA STRINGING A
WHOLE LOT OF BULBS TOGETHER, YOU
SEE, AND THEN PLUGGING THEM IN
AND OUT REAL QUICK.
FLASH, FLASH, FLASH.
AND, FROM A DISTANCE, IT
LOOKED AS THOUGH THAT WAS THE
FLASH OF RIFLES FIRING.
WELL, I KEPT FLASHING THE
LIGHTS.
THE GERMANS STAYED AWAY.
AND THE VERY NEXT DAY, GENERAL
MONTGOMERY DECIDED TO GIVE ME
THE CONGRESSIONAL MEDAL OF
HONOR.
NOW, NOW, THAT'S INCREDIBLE,
HAP.
A CANADIAN SOLDIER GETTING AN
AMERICAN MEDAL FROM A BRITISH
GENERAL.
CHRISTMAS IS WHITE SNOW ON THE
TREES.
AND PEOPLE DECORATE THEIR STUFF
WITH CHRISTMAS THINGS.
AND YOUR BREATH IS...
WELL, YOU CAN SEE IT, YOU
KNOW, SO IT'S COLD, YOU KNOW
WHAT I--YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
LOOK, OKAY, I GUESS THIS ISN'T
VERY POETIC.
BUT SOMETIMES IT'S--YOU KNOW,
IT'S GOOD JUST TO GIVE OUT FACTS
ABOUT CHRISTMAS WITHOUT
EMBELLISHMENT.
JUST EVEN--EVEN POINT FORM
THINGS THAT ARE RELATED TO
CHRISTMAS, LIKE TREES AND
PRESENTS AND SNOWMEN.
OLDER PEOPLE NEED THIS
STRAIGHTFORWARD KIND OF APPROACH
SO THEY UNDERSTAND WHAT'S GOING
ON AROUND THEM.
IT'S ALSO GOOD FOR PEOPLE WHO
AREN'T FAMILIAR WITH CHRISTMAS,
LIKE THE AUSTRALIANS.
THEY JUST--THEY JUST WANT TO
KNOW THE FACTS.
IF YOU WANT THE FACTS, COME TO
ME.
IF YOU WANT POETRY, READ A
BUMPER STICKER.
YOU KNOW WHAT I HATE ABOUT
CHRISTMASTIME, EVEN MORE THAN
FRUITCAKE?
[laughter]
NOTHING.
I HATE FRUITCAKE.
I CAN'T...
GETS STUCK IN YOUR TEETH, YOU
KNOW.
LIKE, DOING THAT.
IT'S, LIKE, GROUNDHOG DAY OR
SOMETHING.
BUT A CLOSE SECOND, A CLOSE
SECOND WOULD BE, LIKE, WAITING
FOR CHRISTMAS DAY TO COME,
RIGHT?
'CAUSE I LOVE CHRISTMAS, AND IT
TAKES SO LONG!
LIKE, FOR INSTANCE, I WISH,
LIKE, TODAY WAS TOMORROW
BECAUSE THEN I'D BE, LIKE, ONE
DAY CLOSER TO CHRISTMAS.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT GONNA
HAPPEN 'CAUSE I GOT TO WAIT
FOR TODAY TO END, AND THAT'S
GONNA BE TOMORROW SOMETIME, SO
I'VE MISSED IT.
SO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO IS
EFFECTIVELY COME UP WITH WAYS
TO KILL TIME PRIOR TO
CHRISTMAS ACTUALLY ARRIVING.
WAH, WAH, WAH.
SO EACH YEAR, WHAT I DO IS, I
CREATE A RED AND GREEN...
RED AND GREEN, I SAID!
I DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE THAT
BEFORE.
THAT'S SO COOL.
I'M--WHAT I DO IS, I MAKE THIS--
A RED AND GREEN PAPER CHAIN
REINDEER DAYS-LEFT
WALL-MOUNTED CALENDAR.
AND ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS, EVERY
DAY THAT GETS CLOSER TO
CHRISTMAS, YOU JUST, YOU KNOW,
TEAR OFF A LINK.
LA-LA, LIKE THAT, YOU SEE?
AND NOW YOU--YOU'VE EFFECTIVELY
KILLED, LIKE, TWO SECONDS,
RIGHT?
GOSH, TWO SECONDS, WHERE DID IT
GO?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S GONE.
SO NOW ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS,
WAIT, LIKE, 23 HOURS, 59
MINUTES, AND 58 SECONDS BEFORE
I CAN TEAR OFF ANOTHER ONE,
KILL SOME MORE TIME.
JUST TEAR RIGHT OFF, LIKE THAT.
[laughter]
I--I TORE OFF TOMORROW.
I'M GONNA HAVE NOTHING TO DO
TOMORROW!
YOU KNOW WHAT, YOU KNOW WHAT,
I COULD EFFECTIVELY KILL TIME
BY PUTTING IT ALL BACK TOGETHER.
YOU SEE, THAT'S WHAT I--THAT'S
HOW I'LL EFFECTIVELY KILL TIME
FOR THE NEXT LITTLE WHILE.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT'S REALLY
INTERESTING ABOUT ALL THIS, IS,
NONE OF THIS WOULD EVEN MATTER
IF I HAD A GIRLFRIEND.
[laughter and applause]
MY MA'S IN THE KITCHEN
BUTTERING THE HOG
DADDY'S IN THE STUDY
FEEDING BRANDY TO THE DOG
[together]  DOG.
GRANDMA AND HER BOYFRIEND
ARE SLEEPING KIND OF LATE
AUNTY'S IN THE PANTRY
PUTTING ON SOME WEIGHT
[together]  WEIGHT
[all three together]  OH
I LOVE CHRISTMAS
I...
MERRY CHRISTMAS, AND
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW.
THIS IS THAT PART OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE LIKE TO EXAMINE THOSE
THREE LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN
FIND SO HARD TO SAY--
[audience together]
"I DON'T KNOW."
YEAH, IT'S--THERE THE ONES,
EXACTLY.
OKAY, JOINING ME AND UNCLE RED
IN EXPERT PORTION OF THE SHOW
TODAY ARE, WOW, TWO EXPERTS IN
THE--OKAY.
MR. MIKE HAMAR, AND MR. DALTON
HUMPHREY.
[cheers and applause]
WOW, THAT'S GREAT--THREE WHOLE
EXPERTS.
NOT QUITE THE THREE WISE MEN,
BUT...
WELL, AT LEAST WE STILL GOT
THE EXPECTANT VIRGIN.
[cheers and applause]
TODAY'S LETTER GOES AS
FOLLOWS.
"I AM EIGHT YEARS OLD, AND A
LOT OF MY FRIENDS HAVE
RECENTLY TOLD ME THERE IS SUCH
THING AS A SANTA CLAUS.
PLEASE TELL ME THE TRUTH.
IS THERE A SANTA CLAUS?"
IS THERE A SANTA CLAUS?
I MEAN, WHAT KIND OF QUESTION
IS THAT?
I MEAN, YOU MIGHT AS WELL ASK,
DOES MOOSE THOMPSON EXIST?
OR IF MR. GREEN'S WIFE,
BERNICE, EXISTS.
WELL, BERNICE BETTER EXIST.
OTHERWISE, I'VE BEEN LETTING
HER PARENTS VISIT FOR NO GOOD
REASON.
[laughter and applause]
YOU KNOW, IT'S GONNA BE A
TERRIBLE WORLD TO LIVE IN
WITHOUT SANTA CLAUS.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I THINK THIS
LETTER ADDRESSES A GOOD POINT.
I NEVER GOT ANY PRESENTS FROM
SANTA WHEN I WAS A KID.
YOU KNOW, SO MAYBE HE DOESN'T
EXIST.
WELL, MIKE, YOU WERE
A ROTTEN KID.
THAT'S WHY SANTA DIDN'T BRING
YOU ANY PRESENTS.
YOU STOLE MY BICYCLE.
WELL, HOW DO YOU KNOW
IT WAS ME?
'CAUSE YOU USED TO RIDE BACK
AND FORTH IN FRONT OF MY
HOUSE, RIDING IT AND WAVING
AND LAUGHING.
OH, YEAH.
[laughing]
WELL, TO ANSWER OUR--OUR
VIEWER THERE, I'D JUST LIKE TO
SAY THAT HAROLD HERE EXISTS,
SO SANTA CLAUS MUST EXIST,
OTHERWISE LIFE ISN'T FAIR.
[laughter]
I'LL TELL YOU, SANTA CLAUS
EXISTS AS SURELY AS POSSUM
LODGE EXISTS.
I KNOW SOMETIMES IT'S HARD TO
BELIEVE IN A CHUBBY GUY WITH A
BEARD, BUT YOU'LL GET
USED TO IT.
[laughter and applause]
CHRISTMAS IS, I GUESS,
SHARING.
GIVING SOMETHING OF YOURSELF.
SHARING A GIFT.
SHARING A MEAL.
SHARING SOME GOOD CHEER.
MAYBE EVEN SHARING SOME BAD
WINE.
NOW, THE REAL INTENTION WAS
PROBABLY TO SHARE WITH THOSE
LESS FORTUNATE THAN ME, BUT
THOSE PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS
INSULTED THAT I THINK I'M MORE
FORTUNATE THAN THEM OR
FORTUNATE AT ALL.
SO I GUESS CHRISTMAS IS THE
TIME OF YEAR WHEN WE FEED AND
INVITE INTO OUR HOMES PEOPLE
WHO REALLY DON'T NEED TO BE
FED AND HAVE HOMES OF THEIR OWN.
AT LEAST, THAT'S WHAT I DO.
I JUST FOCUS MY GENEROSITY ON
FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
THAT WAY, THERE'S A BETTER
CHANCE OF A PAYBACK, OR AS I
CALL IT, SHARING.
WELL, I DO--I DO A CHRISTMAS
COUNTDOWN THING.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME WHEN
CHRISTMAS IS, BECAUSE THE BEER
STORES ARE CLOSED.
BUT...
I DON'T LIKE THE THING THAT
HAROLD DID, THE MOOSE WITH THE
LINKS AND ALL THAT STUFF.
I'M MORE OF A HANDYMAN THAN A
CRAFTY GOOF.
I LIKE THE IDEA OF THE CHAIN
LINKS, THOUGH.
BUT I SAY...
LET'S USE A REAL CHAIN.
[laughter]
SURE, MAYBE IT'S HEAVY, AND IT'S
OILY AND DIRTY AND SO ON, BUT
YOU DON'T HAVE TO MAKE IT.
IT'S ALREADY THERE.
YOU JUST HANG THAT UP ON THE
WALL.
AND YOU GET YOUR BOLT CUTTER
AND...
EVERY TIME A DAY GOES BY, YOU
JUST--YOU JUST...
YOU JUST...
[laughter]
I'M FINISHED HAVING MY FAMILY.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, YOU GET THE
IDEA ON THAT.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU GO WITH A
HEAVIER CHAIN, MAYBE IT WOULD
BE BETTER TO JUST KIND OF LET
A FEW DAYS GO BY.
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
SO YOU LET FOUR DAYS GO BY.
NOW YOU JUST CUT THAT LINK.
AND THEN ALL THE DAYS.
THAT'S WHAT TO DO.
JUST CUT--JUST CUT EVERY FOUR
DAYS.
OR, YOU KNOW WHAT YOU COULD DO,
IS JUST HANG IT UP AND WAIT
FOR ALL THE DAYS TO GO BY.
THEN, ON CHRISTMAS MORNING,
FIRST THING YOU DO...
[chains crashing]
TAKE THE CHAIN DOWN.
THAT'S THE HANDYMAN WAY.
[cheers and applause]
'TWAS THE NIGHT BEFORE
CHRISTMAS, WHEN ALL AROUND THE
LODGE, NOT A VEHICLE WAS
STIRRING, NOT EVEN MY DODGE.
THE STOCKINGS WERE HUNG BY
THE CHIMNEY WITH CARE, IN
HOPES THAT THEY'D STINK LESS
IF THEY'D GOTTEN SOME AIR.
THE LODGE MEMBERS WERE
NESTLED, CLOTHED IN THEIR
BEDS, WHILE VISIONS OF
HANGOVERS STOMPED ON THEIR
HEADS.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU YOUNG
PEOPLE OUT THERE ABOUT ONE OF
THE MOST IMPORTANT ELEMENTS OF
CHRISTMAS: THE GIFTS.
AND I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT THE
GIFTS YOU GET.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE ONES YOU
WERE SUPPOSED TO GIVE, OKAY?
LIKE, YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE ON A
LIMITED BUDGET LIKE THE WAY I
AM, YOU KNOW HOW DIFFICULT IT
IS TO SPREAD THE AMOUNT OF
MONEY THAT YOU ACTUALLY HAVE
TO THE AMOUNT OF PEOPLE WHO
ARE ON YOUR LIST, RIGHT?
WAH, WAH?
YEAH?
THAT'S HARD.
AND PLUS, HERE'S A QUANDARY FOR
YOU: HOW MUCH--HOW ARE YOU
GONNA KNOW TO SPEND THE SAME
AMOUNT ON THE PERSON THAT JUST
BUYING FOR, THAT THEY SPENT ON
YOU?
THE ONLY WAY TO FIND OUT?
FIND OUT WHAT THEY BOUGHT YOU.
AND HOW DO YOU DO THIS, YOU
ASK YOURSELF?
WAH, WAH, WAH.
WELL, THE ANSWER IS SIMPLICITY
ITSELF.
TEAR THE HOUSE APART WHEN
EVERYBODY GOES OUT.
IT'S TRUE, OKAY?
I RECOMMEND THAT YOU START IN
THE BACK BEDROOM CLOSETS.
GET IN THERE, RIFLE AROUND,
OKAY?
IF IT'S A WOMAN WHO HID THESE
PRESENTS, YOU KNOW WHAT YOU DO
THEN?
YOU GOT TO ROOMS WHERE MEN NEVER
GO.
THAT'S WHERE THEY HIDE THEM.
THESE ROOMS BEING THE LAUNDRY
ROOM, THE PANTRY, THE
KITCHEN--THIS IS EXCLUDING THE
FRIDGE, NATURALLY.
AND IF YOU THINK YOU'RE REALLY
BRAVING UP TO IT, LOOK UNDER
THE KITCHEN SINK.
OKAY, NOW WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU
FIND A PRESENT AND IT'S
UNWRAPPED?
WHO'S IT FOR?
YOU DON'T KNOW.
WAH, WAH, WAH.
OKAY.
MAYBE IT'S A GIFT THAT YOU
KIND OF ASKED FOR.
IT MIGHT BE SOMETHING YOU WOULD
WANT.
IT'S PROBABLY YOURS.
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE ADULTS HAVE
THAT WAY OF REALLY NEVER
GRASPING THE PROPER PRESENT
THAT YOU WANTED, YOU KNOW?
LIKE, LIKE, FOR INSTANCE, LIKE,
YOU WANTED A CD PLAYER, BUT
YOU GET, LIKE, A ONE-SLICE
TOASTER.
YOU KNOW...
ADULTS, YOU KNOW.
OR A PARTICULARLY UGLY COSTUME
KIND OF THING, YOU KNOW?
LIKE A--A SHIRT THAT'S GOT,
LIKE, REALLY PUFFY SLEEVES ON
IT, YOU KNOW, OR A SWEATER WITH
NO SLEEVES.
YOU KNOW...
THAT'S YOURS.
[laughter]
NEW LEVEL PROBLEM, OKAY?
WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU FIND A GIFT, AND IT'S
WRAPPED.
WAH, WAH, WAH.
OKAY, NOW, WHAT I'VE DONE, IS
I'VE BROUGHT ALONG AN EXAMPLE.
THIS IS A GIFT THAT MY UNCLE,
RED, WILL BE GIVING ME THIS
CHRISTMAS.
SO YOU GET--WHAT YOU DO IS,
YOU GOT TO GET YOURSELF IN,
LIKE, A ZEN-LIKE STATE, RIGHT,
TO FIGURE IT OUT.
SO YOU GO...
[laughter]
HOW...
MUCH IS IT WORTH?
AND ONCE YOU'RE IN THAT STATE,
YOU ASK YOURSELF A SERIES OF
QUESTIONS.
CAN I SEE THROUGH THE PAPER?
NO.
OKAY, WILL ONE OF THE SEAMS
LIFT UP, AND I CAN JUST PEEK IN?
[paper tearing sounds]
OH, OH, WHY IS THE TAPE SO
LOOSE?
WHY DOES THIS PAPER TEAR SO
EASILY?
[car approaching]
DO I HEAR SOMEONE PULLING UP IN
THE DRIVEWAY?
[car door shutting]
AM I A DEAD MAN?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NOTHING.
DID YOU FIND...
NO.
A GIFT.
NO, I--NO.
YOU DIDN'T FIND ANY--
IT WAS WRAPPED IN THIS KIND
OF PAPER.
[gasps]
NO.
WELL, IF YOU DO FIND IT,
PUT IT BACK UNDER THE TREE,
OKAY?
IT'S FOR BERNICE.
SHE ALWAYS PEEKS AT THE STUFF
THAT I GET HER, BUT I PULLED A
LITTLE TRICK THIS YEAR.
I PUT YOUR NAME ON THE TAG.
[laughter]
CHRISTMAS IS A GREAT FAMILY
TIME, ISN'T IT?
REALLY BRINGS RELATIVES
TOGETHER.
WHAT A SHAME THAT NOBODY GETS
ON YOUR NERVES FASTER THAN
YOUR LOVED ONES.
SOMEBODY SAYS THE WRONG THING OR
LOOKS AT SOMEBODY THE WRONG
WAY, NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
EVERYBODY'S GOING HOME WITH AN
EYE SOCKET FULL OF MASHED
POTATOES.
YOU KNOW THE BEST WAY TO AVOID
THAT?
GET YOURSELF A PROJECT THAT GETS
YOU OUT OF THE HOUSE, YOU
KNOW, A HANDYMAN'S CHRISTMAS
SPECIAL.
HOW ABOUT MAKING A ONE-HORSE
OPEN SLEIGH FROM A 100-HORSE
OPEN "K"...
"K" CAR, THAT IS.
YOU KNOW, THE OPEN SLEIGH REALLY
WAS A PIONEER VERSION OF THE
CONVERTIBLE.
SO THE FIRST STEP IS TO GET THE
ROOF RIGHT OFF THE UNIT.
ACTUALLY, I DID THAT USING MY
GARAGE DOOR.
IT'S NOT REALLY AS HARD AS IT
LOOKS TO DO THAT.
WHAT YOU DO IS, YOU JUST COME
DRIVING OUT OF THE GARAGE AND
ACCIDENTALLY SIT ON THE REMOTE.
DOWN THE DOOR--IT JUST PEELS
IT RIGHT OFF, CLEAN.
BUT DON'T FORGET TO DUCK.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, WE'RE GONNA PUT
A OLD-FASHIONED, HIGH OPEN
SLEIGH DRIVER SEAT INTO THIS
UNIT.
SO WHAT I GOT TO DO IS, FIRST
OF ALL, GET THE OLD SEAT OUT
OF THERE.
[clanking]
THERE WE GO, AND...
OH, LOOKS LIKE SOME OF THE FLOOR
COME UP WITH THE SEAT THERE.
NOW, THAT--NO, THAT'S A GOOD
THING.
THAT'S A GOOD THING 'CAUSE WE
CAN SEE RIGHT DOWN THROUGH THE
FLOOR WHEN WE'RE DRIVING.
THAT'S ALWAYS HANDY.
AND, YOU KNOW, IF YOU RUN OVER
SOMEBODY, YOU GET A CHANCE TO
APOLOGIZE TO THEM AS THEY GO BY
THE HOLE.
WE DON'T ACTUALLY HAVE ANY
ANTIQUE SLEIGH SEATS, BUT WE
DO HAVE A LOT OF TALL
BARSTOOLS.
THE TRICK IS FINDING AN EMPTY
ONE, ESPECIALLY THIS
TIME OF YEAR.
SO I'M GONNA STICK THE STOOL
BEHIND THE HOLE, AND I'M GONNA
SNUG HER DOWN THERE WITH THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON, DUCT
TAPE.
I'LL TELL YOU THE PROBLEM,
THOUGH.
IN THE COLD WEATHER, THE DUCT
TAPE JUST DOESN'T STICK VERY
WELL.
BUT HERE'S A TRICK I LEARNED
FROM MY FRIENDS UP IN
YELLOWKNIFE.
WHAT YOU DO IS, YOU KEEP THE
DUCT TAPE INSIDE YOUR CLOTHES
NEXT TO YOUR SKIN.
AND YOUR BODY HEAT KEEPS IT
STICKY.
OH, YEAH, THERE WE GO.
OH, NO.
WHAT THE HECK IS THAT?
THERE, THAT'S PERFECT.
TOOK ME A LITTLE WHILE TO FIND
THE DUCT TAPE, BECAUSE I FORGOT
I HAD CHANGED MY UNDERWEAR.
YOU KNOW, THE "K" CAR WAS NEVER
ACTUALLY BUILT FOR SPEED, BUT
EVEN THIS UNIT HAS A FEW MORE
PONIES THAN WE NEED UNDER THE
HOOD FOR OUR SLEIGH.
WHAT WE WANT IS JUST TO HAVE A
ONE-HORSE UNIT.
SO I THINK I'M GONNA HAVE TO
UNHARNESS A FEW.
WE WANT A--
pop!
ONE-HORSE...
ONE-CYLINDER...
pop!
OPEN SLEIGH.
GOSH, I HOPE I'M USING ONE OF
THE CYLINDERS THAT STILL WORKS.
OF COURSE, THE KIDS ARE GONNA BE
BUGGING, YOU KNOW.
"WHERE'S THE HORSE?
WHERE'S THE HORSE?"
AND RATHER THAN MAKE UP SOME
DUMB, POLITICALLY CORRECT
STORY ABOUT SOME CHRISTMAS HORSE
THAT GOES OFF TO UNIVERSITY TO
AVOID A LIFE OF MANUAL
LABOR--INSTEAD OF THAT, WE'RE
GONNA MAKE A HORSE...
OUT OF WHAT'S LEFT OF THE ROOF.
SHOULD BE A SNAP TO CUT A HORSE
SHAPE OUT OF THAT.
BOY, THIS HAS TURNED OUT GREAT.
LOOK AT THIS THING.
OH, BABY, YEAH.
OH, MAN, THAT'S FANTASTIC.
[laughter]
YOU KNOW, IF I'D SET THE TORCH
A LITTLE HOTTER, I COULD HAVE
CUT OUT TWO HORSES.
YOU KNOW, KIDS HAVE GREAT
IMAGINATIONS, DON'T THEY?
YOU KNOW, THEY--THEY SEE CASTLES
IN CLOUDS.
THEY SEE FACES IN TURNIPS.
THEY'LL SEE A HORSE IN THAT.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, WHAT I'M GONNA
DO IS, I'M GONNA CUT A GROOVE
INTO THE HOOD OF THE "K" CAR SO
THAT I CAN MOUNT THE HORSE IN
THERE GOOD AND SOLID.
[drilling]
[hissing]
NOW, THESE ARE OBVIOUSLY THE
REINS HERE, WHICH I'M GONNA
USE TO STEER THE END.
AND I GOT THEM RUNNING THROUGH
THE STEERING WHEEL, SO WHEN I
WANT TO TURN, I JUST PULL ON
THE REIN AND THE STEERING
WHEEL WILL TURN.
WON'T BE A SHARP TURN, BUT I'M
GUESSING PEOPLE WILL GET OUT OF
THE WAY.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, WHAT I'VE DONE
IS, I'VE CRANKED THE IDLING WAY
UP ON HER THERE, SO I DON'T HAVE
TO GO NEAR THE--NEAR THE GAS
PEDAL AT ALL.
AND I'M GONNA USE A RIDING CROP
TO CHANGE GEARS.
WELL, IT'S NOT A REAL RIDING
CROP.
THIS IS A--THIS IS A RADIO
AERIAL, BUT IT'S A POWER--LOOK
AT THIS.
HUH?
IS THAT BEAUTIFUL?
[laughing]
ACTUALLY, I WANTED A REAL RIDING
CROP.
I WENT INTO THE STORE.
I SAYS TO THE GUY, "ARE THE
CROPS IN?"
WOULDN'T EVEN SERVE ME.
ALL RIGHT, SO--OH, I WANTED TO
SAY ONE OTHER FEATURE I'VE
ADDED TO THIS THING.
I ADDED A COUPLE OF THOSE FAKE
POLY-FOAM, POLYSTYRENE
PLASTIC CANDY CANES.
GOT THEM HANGING DOWN BY THE
WHEELS.
THEY LOOK LIKE RUNNERS, HUH?
OF COURSE, NOW, THOSE ARE JUST
FAKE RUNNERS, YOU KNOW.
'CAUSE RIGHT NOW WE'RE MAINLY
GOING FOR LOOKS.
AND I BET WE GET A FEW.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
ON DONNER, ON BLITZEN, ON ARES.
[banging]
AH.
[applause]
RIGHT, NOW, WE'RE COUNTING DOWN
THE DAYS UNTIL CHRISTMAS.
AND I--RANGER GORD HERE.
RANGER GORD, I UNDERSTAND THAT
WHEN YOU WERE UP IN THE FIRE
WATCHTOWER THERE FOR 18 YEARS...
MM-HM.
WE USED TO MAKE THE--THE
ADVENT CALENDARS WITH THE LITTLE
TABS AND THE CHOCOLATES INSIDE
THEM.
ABSOLUTELY.
YEAH.
WELL, NOT CHOCOLATE INSIDE,
BUT TREATS, NONETHELESS.
FOREST TREATS.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, TREATS OTHER
CREATURES HAD DROPPED IN THE
WOODS.
[laughter]
YOU KNOW, FOLKS, I DIDN'T
JUST DO THE 25 DAYS BEFORE
CHRISTMAS.
I DID THE ENTIRE YEAR--388 DAYS.
WELL--WELL, GORD, THERE'S
ONLY 365 DAYS IN A YEAR.
[laughter]
365?
YEAH.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, THAT WOULD
EXPLAIN WHY, AFTER A COUPLE OF
YEARS, IT WAS HOT AND SUNNY AT
CHRISTMAS, AND COLD AND SNOWY
IN JULY.
WELL, THAT--THAT WOULD
EXPLAIN PART OF IT.
WELL, ANYWAYS, FOLKS, NOW
THAT I'M BACK IN CIVILIZATION,
I HAVE DEVELOPED A FOOLPROOF,
EXTREMELY SIMPLE WAY OF COUNTING
DOWN THE DAYS BEFORE CHRISTMAS
THAT MAKE ALL OTHER WAYS SEEM
EXTREMELY COMPLEX BY COMPARISON.
NOW, ALL MY METHOD INVOLVES IS A
SIMPLE PERMANENT MARKER, A
SIMPLE CALENDAR, AND A SIMPLE
BOWL FILLED WITH BROKEN PIECES
OF SPAGHETTI AND METAL
SHAVINGS FILLED TO THE BRIM
WITH HOT BOILING WATER AND
STIRRED VERY RAPIDLY UNTIL IT
MAKES A STRANGE NOISE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S FORGET ABOUT THE BOWL
RIGHT NOW, BECAUSE IT'S NOT THAT
IMPORTANT.
OW, GOD.
OKAY...
ALL RIGHT, WELL, HERE'S MY
METHOD.
YOU SIMPLY TAKE THE PERMANENT
MARKER, AND YOU CROSS OUT ALL
THE DAYS BETWEEN NOW AND
CHRISTMAS, OKAY?
ARE YOU WITH ME SO FAR?
OKAY.
THEN YOU TAKE THE ERASER, AND
YOU ERASE THE DAYS AS THEY PASS.
OKAY, NOW, YOU PROBABLY HAVE
NOTICED, PERMANENT MARKER IS
EXTREMELY DIFFICULT TO GET OUT.
SO YOU HAVE TO RUB VERY
VIGOROUSLY.
[paper tearing]
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, SO--SO,
NOW, AFTER YOU'VE RIPPED THE
CALENDAR, THEN WHAT?
RIGHT, WELL, AFTER YOU'VE RIPPED
THE CALENDAR, YOU DECIDE THAT
YOU'RE GOING TO RIP OUT THE DATE
INSTEAD OF USING THE ERASER ON
THE PERMANENT MARKER.
SIMPLE, OKAY?
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, NOW THAT YOU'VE
RIPPED OUT MOST OF THE DATES
AND YOU'VE EXPOSED MOST OF
JANUARY UNDERNEATH, WHICH, YOU
KNOW, REALLY CONFUSES AND
FRUSTRATES YOU, YOU--YOU TAKE
OUT YOUR MATCHES AND SET THE
CALENDAR ON FIRE.
NO, NO, NO.
[laughter]
OKAY, WELL, YOU GET THE IDEA.
HAVE SOME FUN, OKAY?
AND REMEMBER, ONLY 422 MORE
SHOPPING DAYS TILL CHRISTMAS.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
[cheers and applause]
AND I IN MY RETAINER, AND
UNCLE RED IN HIS CAP, HAD JUST
CRASHED ON SOME COUCHES FOR A
POST-TURKEY NAP.
WHEN OUT ON THE LAWN THERE
AROSE SUCH A SMELL, I DASHED
TO THE WINDOW TO SEE WHAT THE--
HECK, HECK.
AWAY TO THE WINDOW I FLEW
LIKE A FLASH TO OPEN THE
SHUTTERS, WHICH FELL OFF AND
WENT SMASH.
SORRY.
THE MOON ON THE CREST OF THE
NEW-FALLEN SNOW COULDN'T HIDE
WHERE THE SEPTICS HAD ALL
OVERFLOWED.
WHEN WHAT TO MY WONDERING EYES
SHOULD APPEAR BUT A MINIVAN
FULL OF WOMEN AND BEER.
[laughter and applause]
WITH A DRIVER IN VINYL AND
ARTIFICIAL FLEECE, I KNEW IN A
FLASH IT WAS MY WIFE, BERNICE.
I'M GONNA TALK TO YOU OLDER GUYS
ABOUT TELLING THE TRUTH.
THE TRUTH ABOUT SANTA.
'CAUSE YOU KNOW SOME NAIVE KID
IS GONNA SAY TO YOU, "SHOULD I
BELIEVE IN SANTA?"
WELL, YOU GOT TO LOOK THEM
STRAIGHT IN THE EYE AND SAY,
"YES, HAROLD...
[laughter]
OF COURSE YOU BELIEVE IN SANTA."
WHAT'S NOT TO BELIEVE?
YOU KNOW, SANTA'S A PRETTY
AVERAGE, NORMAL GUY.
SPENDS 99% OF HIS TIME
SQUIRRELED AWAY IN HIS WORKSHOP,
MAKING STUFF THAT'S ONLY GOOD
ENOUGH TO GIVE AWAY.
I KNOW LOTS OF GUYS LIKE THAT.
HE'S GOT THESE LITTLE HELPERS
THAT DO ALL THE WORK.
WE ALL HAVE THOSE.
AND EVERY CHRISTMAS, HE LOADS UP
WAY TOO MANY GIFTS AND DRIVES
ALL OVER KINGDOM COME
DELIVERING THEM.
THAT SOUND FAMILIAR
TO YOU AT ALL?
AND EVERYWHERE HE GOES, HE
EXPECTS SOME SNACKS AND A DRINK.
SO DO I.
AND WHEN IT COMES TO THE CHOICE
OF DOING THINGS THE EASY WAY OR
THE HARD WAY, HE CHOOSES THE
HARD WAY EVERY TIME.
DOOR VS. CHIMNEY.
NEED I SAY MORE?
HE'S JUST ONE OF US, EH?
PLUS, HE'S FAT; HE'S BALDING; HE
WEARS RED LONG UNDERWEAR.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE HALF THE LODGE
TO ME.
SO WHEN A KID ASKS YOU IF
THERE'S A SANTA CLAUS, SAY,
"HECK, YEAH, THERE'S PROBABLY
A COUPLE IN YOUR OWN FAMILY."
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[cheers and applause]
JOINING ME TODAY, WE'VE GOT
EDGAR MONTROSE.
MERRY CHRISTMAS, EDGAR.
[cheers and applause]
SO WHAT DO YOU GOT FOR US TODAY?
THAT'S RIGHT, USUALLY AT THIS
TIME OF YEAR.
[laughter]
WELL, FIRST OFF, I HAVE A GIFT
FOR YOU, RED.
SURE.
IT'S A LITTLE SOMETHING I
CALL A CHRISTMAS CRACKER.
YEAH.
MY OWN IDEA.
OH...
NO, NO, NO.
EDGAR, NO OFFENSE, BUT, YOU
KNOW, LOTS OF PEOPLE HAVE HAD
CRACKERS.
YES, BUT DO THEY USE THE
MERCURY DETONATOR?
NO, THAT'S--THAT'S ALL YOU.
YEAH, YEAH.
NOW, RED, I'M HERE BECAUSE MY
SNOW CANNON ISN'T WORKING.
SNOW CANNON.
BOY, THAT SOUNDS CUTE.
HOW'S--HOW DOES THAT WORK?
WELL, NORMALLY, WHEN YOU
PUSH DOWN HERE, IT SENDS SNOW
OUT IN SPRINKLES ACROSS THE
YARD.
[sharp whooshing]
OH!
WELL, GEE, THANKS, RED.
THAT'S A GOOD REPAIR.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
I MADE A LITTLE ADJUSTMENT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT NOW.
OH.
WELL, BY GOLLY, IF THERE'S
ANYTHING I CAN DO TO RETURN THE
FAVOR...
OH, AS A MATTER OF FACT,
YEAH, YOU COULD.
I GOT TO DECORATE THE TREE HERE.
I GOT TO DECORATE THE TREE.
AND THAT'S A LONG JOB.
COULD YOU HELP ME OUT WITH THAT,
EDGAR?
WELL, YOU'RE IN LUCK, 'CAUSE
TODAY I GOT MY HOWITZER HOLIDAY
SPECIAL WITH ME.
HOWITZER HOLIDAY SPECIAL.
THAT SOUNDS INTERESTING.
BOY, THIS BABY CAN TINSEL A
TREE FASTER THAN YOU CAN
CALL 911.
[laughter]
GREAT.
YOU JUST LOAD IT UP WITH SOME
TINFOIL...
YOU TAKE AIM...
AND YOU FIRE...
boom!
[cheers and applause]
CHRISTMAS IS A YULE LOG.
WELL, IT USED TO BE, ANYWAY.
GUYS WOULD CHOP DOWN THE BIGGEST
TREE THEY COULD FIND, HAUL IT
HOME, AND BURN IT ALL THROUGH
CHRISTMAS.
THAT WAS OKAY IF YOU HAD A
FIREPLACE THE SIZE OF A BUICK,
BUT A REAL SAFETY HAZARD IF YOU
CONVERTED TO NATURAL GAS, I'LL
TELL YOU.
TODAY, OF COURSE, A YULE LOG IS
AN ICE CREAM ROLL FILLED WITH
CANDIED FRUIT.
IF YOU TAP THAT SUCKER DOWN ON
TOP OF THE FIVE POUNDS OF
TURKEY, STUFFING, POTATOES, AND
GRAVY YOU ATE, THEN YOU'LL
DEFINITELY GET A BURN THAT'LL
LAST THROUGH CHRISTMAS.
PLUS, YOU MIGHT NOT HAVE A
CHOICE ABOUT CONVERTING TO
NATURAL GAS.
JUST DON'T STAND TOO CLOSE TO
THE FIREPLACE.
OH, HELLO, BOYS AND GIRLS.
I'D LIKE TO SHARE WITH YOU,
TODAY, A BRAND-NEW CHRISTMAS
TRADITION.
NOW, THIS IS AN ANCIENT
CHRISTMAS STORY THAT I WROTE
JUST A FEW DAYS AGO.
[laughter]
NOW, YOU'VE PROBABLY NEVER BEEN
TO A FIRE WATCHTOWER LIKE I'VE
BEEN FOR THE LAST 18 YEARS, SO
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE TO
WAKE UP CHRISTMAS MORNING,
ALONE, ALL EXCITED, AND THEN RUN
DOWNSTAIRS TO UNWRAP YOUR
LAUNDRY AND FIND OUT MOST OF
IT'S NOT FOR YOU.
YEAR AFTER YEAR...
ANYWAY, HERE'S THE STORY.
ARE YOU READY?
ONCE UPON A TIME--WELL, ABOUT
246 DAYS AGO, REALLY--THERE
WAS A TALL RODENT NAMED GORD
WHO HAD A CHRISTMAS WISH NOT TO
BE HIT BY LIGHTNING.
IT HAD HAPPENED SO MANY
CHRISTMASES BEFORE.
GORD WOULD BE CELEBRATING
CHRISTMAS AND WOULD BE RIGHT IN
THE MIDDLE OF A SECOND VERSE OF
JINGLE BELL ROCK,
WHEN--ZING--LIKE A LIGHTNING
BOLT, CAME A LIGHTNING BOLT.
IT DIDN'T STAY LONG, BUT IT
ALWAYS RUINED HIS CHRISTMAS.
IT SINGED GORD'S EYELASHES AND
FORCED HIM TO SPEND BOXING DAY
WITH THE SMELL OF BURNT HAIR.
HOW GORD PRAYED THIS YEAR WOULD
BE DIFFERENT.
DAY IN AND DAY OUT, THIS SLENDER
AND IN MANY WAYS ATTRACTIVE
RODENT, GORD...
WOULD STAND ATOP HIS TOWER
EATING NOTHING BUT CANNED CREAM
CORN AND SLOW-MOVING INSECTS
AS HE WAITED FOR CHRISTMAS TO
ARRIVE.
FINALLY, RIGHT AFTER CHRISTMAS
EVE, IT ARRIVED.
THE WIND CAME UP, AND THE STORM
BEGAN.
BUT THIS TIME, LITTLE GORD WAS
NOT HIT BY LIGHTNING.
INSTEAD, HE WAS HIT BY HIS OWN
TOWER.
LIKE SO MANY OF US, HE WAS
DOWNSIZED.
HEAD FIRST TOO.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
[applause]
[together] I LOVE
CHRISTMAS
ALL RIGHT, ON THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW THIS WEEK,
JOINING US IS MR. DALTON
HUMPHREY FROM THE HUMPHREY
EVERYTHING STORE.
[cheers and applause]
OKAY, AND OUR LETTER GOES AS
FOLLOWS.
"DEAR EXPERTS"--LA, LA, LA.
"IT'S CHRISTMASTIME ONCE AGAIN.
EVERY YEAR WE HEAR ABOUT HOW
CHRISTMAS HAS BECOME TOO
COMMERCIAL AND THAT WE HAVE
LOST SIGHT OF ITS TRUE MEANING.
COULD YOU TELL ME THE BEST WAY
TO CELEBRATE CHRISTMAS IN ORDER
TO REMAIN TRUE TO WHAT IT'S
REALLY ALL ABOUT?
SIGNED, BEWILDERED."
THIS ONE'S MINE.
SORRY TO JUMP IN THERE, BUT THIS
IS SOMETHING THAT I'M ACTUALLY
QUALIFIED TO OFFER
AN OPINION ON.
WELL, BOY, HERE'S A FIRST.
YEAH, YOU HATE CHRISTMAS,
MR. HUMPHREY.
WHAT MAKES YOU AN EXPERT?
WELL, HAROLD, YOU KNOW, EVERY
YEAR, I TRY AND COME UP WITH AN
EXCUSE TO AVOID CELEBRATING THE
DARN THING, YOU KNOW.
AND I'VE LEARNED AN AWFUL LOT
ABOUT THE TRADITIONS.
MORE THAN MOST PEOPLE, YOU KNOW.
AND I'M TELL YOU, SOME OF THE
TRUTHS BEHIND THE THINGS WE DO
TO CELEBRATE CHRISTMAS--THAT
WOULD CURL YOUR HAIR, RED.
WHEREVER THAT IS, NOW.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
SO YOU'VE BEEN GOING THROUGH ALL
THE TRADITIONS OF CHRISTMAS AND
LOOKING FOR A LOOPHOLE, EH,
DALTON?
OH YEAH, YEP, YEP.
WELL, NOW, TAKE YOUR TREE, FOR
INSTANCE.
WE WILL HAVE NO TREE IN OUR
HOUSE THIS YEAR.
WOW.
AND I'VE GOT A GOOD REASON
FOR IT.
YEAH, IT'S THE SHEER WASTE OF
TREES AND THE LAND THEY'RE
GROWING ON, HUH?
OH, WORSE THAN THAT, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW, THE TRADITION OF
DECORATING THE PINE TREE DIDN'T
START IN THE BIBLE, MY NAIVE,
YOUNG FRIEND.
NO, NO.
IT WAS WITH THE ANCIENT DRUIDS.
YES.
THOSE EGG-TOTING,
STONEHENGE-BUILDING,
TREE-WORSHIPPING PAGANS!
WELL...
SO NO TREE?
NO.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE WAS NO SCOTCH PINE.
THERE WAS NO EXTRUDED ALUMINUM
TREE AT THE MANGER...
AT LEAST IN MY HOLIDAY INN
GIDEON.
WASN'T IN THERE.
SO HOW'S THIS WHOLE THEORY
SITTING WITH THE REST OF THE
HUMPHREY CLAN?
WELL, NOW, I'M EXPECTING
THERE'S GONNA BE SOME MINOR
RESISTANCE TO OVERCOME.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I BELIEVE THAT
COMMON SENSE WILL PREVAIL WHEN
I EXPLAIN TO THEM THAT I'M JUST
TRYING TO PROTECT THEM FROM
PARTICIPATING IN PRE-CHRISTIAN
VOODOO.
THERE'LL BE NO PAGAN RITUALS AT
OUR HOUSE, YOU KNOW.
THERE'LL BE NO LITTLE RED FAT
MAN IN A SUIT.
THERE'LL BE NO MUTANT REINDEERS
WITH RADIOACTIVE NOSES.
YOU KNOW, THOSE PEOPLE DIDN'T
HAVE STOCKINGS.
WE DON'T NEED STOCKING STUFFERS.
YOU KNOW, DALTON, I'M NOT A
PSYCHIATRIST, BUT I THINK YOU
FINALLY HAVE ALL FOUR WHEELS OFF
THE ROAD.
NO, NO, NO, NOW, LISTEN TO
THIS, RED.
DID YOU KNOW THAT THE TRADITION
OF HANGING MISTLETOE GOES BACK
TO THE ANCIENT DRUIDS TOO?
ARE YOU SURE, MR. HUMPHREY?
AS SURE AS I AM THAT GREAT
MUSIC STARTS FAST AND SLOWS
DOWN, THEN SPEEDS UP AGAIN.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE WILL BE CELEBRATING THE TRUE
ELEMENTS OF THE ORIGINAL
CHRISTMAS IN OUR HOUSE:
BIG TURKEY DINNER WITH ALL THE
TRIMMINGS, AND THAT'S IT.
WELL, YOU MIGHT WANT TO KEEP
SOME OF THAT MISTLETOE AROUND.
IF YOU'RE NOT CELEBRATING OR
BUYING ANYBODY GIFTS, YOU CAN
KISS YOUR MARRIAGE GOOD-BYE.
[cheers and applause]
CHRISTMAS IS NO SURPRISES.
YOU KNOW THE TOYS WILL BE OPEN
BY 7:00, CAUSING FIGHTS BY 9:00,
AND BROKEN BY 10:00.
YOU KNOW THE KIDS WILL BE CRANKY
BY NOON, THE IN-LAWS WILL ARRIVE
BY 2:00, AND YOU'LL BE HIDING IN
THE BASEMENT BY 2:30.
YOU KNOW YOU'LL GET 15 MINUTES
OF PEACE ON EARTH BEFORE YOUR
BROTHER-IN-LAW FINDS YOU SULKING
BEHIND THE FURNACE.
YOU KNOW YOU'LL HAVE DINNER AT
4:00 PM, WHEN NO ONE'S HUNGRY,
BUT THEY'LL ALL STILL EAT LIKE A
CHAIN GANG ON A DAY PASS.
AND YOU KNOW BY 10:00, YOU'LL BE
REEKING OF CHRISTMAS CHEER,
SHOUTING AT THE COPS AS YOU TRY
TO EXPLAIN THE GUNSHOT HOLES IN
YOUR NEIGHBOR'S LAWN ORNAMENTS.
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE,
FROM ROTHSCHILD SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC-SUCKING SERVICES, WHERE
OUR NEW MOTTO IS, "WHATEVER YOU
CALL IT, I'LL UP AND HAUL IT."
YEAH, THAT OFFICIALLY REPLACES
OUR OLD MOTTO: "WE DO IT ALL
SO YOU CAN TOO."
YOU KNOW, WITH THE HOLIDAYS UPON
US, I'D JUST LIKE TO TAKE SOME
TIME TO REMIND YOU THAT THE GIFT
YOU GIVE A KID IS SO IMPORTANT.
IT'S ALMOST AS IMPORTANT AS THE
STUFF OTHER PEOPLE GIVE YOU.
YOU KNOW, I'LL NEVER FORGET WHEN
I WAS SEVEN AT CHRISTMASTIME.
I GOT THREE GIFTS: A TOY RATTLE,
A TOY CAR, AND A SHOVEL.
NOW, THE RATTLE WAS GIVEN TO ME
BY MY AUNT DEIRDRE.
YOU KNOW, I'LL NEVER REALLY
UNDERSTAND WHAT A PERSON IS
DOING GIVING A RATTLE TO A
SEVEN-YEAR-OLD.
YOU KNOW, I KNOW I WAS SHORT FOR
MY AGE, BUT, I MEAN, JEEZ, I
HAD A FULL RACK OF TEETH AND I
COULD BELCH LOUDER
THAN MY DAD, EH?
BUT IN FAIRNESS TO DEIRDRE,
I MEAN, I DON'T THINK SHE REALLY
KNEW HOW OLD I WAS ANYWAY.
I KNOW SHE LIVED WAY OUT OF
TOWN, AND SHE WAS ON THIS
SPECIAL MEDICATION THAT SHE'D
MAKE FROM POTATOES.
WEIRD.
NOW, THE TOY CAR WAS GIVEN TO
ME BY MY FRIEND NEXT DOOR, EH?
AND I REALLY LIKED IT AT FIRST,
BUT AFTER A MONTH OR SO, I JUST
KIND OF STOPPED PLAYING WITH IT
AND DECIDED TO GO BACK TO
SCHOOL.
THE BEST GIFT OF ALL WAS THIS
SHOVEL MY PARENTS GAVE ME.
YEAH, I USED TO DIG AND DIG FOR
HOURS WITH THIS SHOVEL, UNTIL
FINALLY THEY KICKED ME OUT TO
THE BACKYARD, EH?
AND THAT'S WHERE I FOUND OUT
WHAT A SEPTIC SYSTEM'S ALL
ABOUT, EH?
AND WHAT HAPPENED TO OUR DOG,
LUCKY.
[laughter]
ANYWAY, I GUESS WHAT I'M SAYING
IS, WHEN YOU'RE GETTING A GIFT
FOR A KID, DON'T GET HIM
SOMETHING THAT SUITED HIM
YESTERDAY.
DON'T EVEN GET HIM SOMETHING
THAT WILL SUIT HIM TODAY.
GET HIM SOMETHING THAT'LL SUIT
HIM FOR TOMORROW.
THANKS, DAD.
'CAUSE YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
EVERY TIME I HEAR THAT FINAL--
[slurps loudly]
WHEN I'M PUMPING OUT A TANK, I
THINK OF YOU.
[laughter and applause]
[together] I LOVE
CHRISTMAS
ONE OLD LADY HAD A MOUTH
DRAWN UP LIKE A BOW, AND THE
HAIR ON HER MOLE WAS AS WHITE AS
THE SNOW.
ANOTHER WAS HAMMERED, A RIGHT
JOLLY OLD ELF, AND I LAUGHED
WHEN SHE BELCHED, IN SPITE OF
MYSELF.
THEY SPOKE A FEW WORDS AND WENT
STRAIGHT TO THE KITCHEN, WHILE
THE GUYS STARTED WAKING UP,
SCRATCHING AND ITCHING.
THEY BROUGHT TURKEY AND
SAUSAGES, KIPPERS AND TROUT.
THEY SAID, "HAVE FUN BOYS
'CAUSE TONIGHT, IT'S LADIES
NIGHT OUT."
THEY SPRANG TO THE MAGIC
WAGON TILL THE HORN GAVE A HONK.
AND AWAY THEY PUTT-PUTTERED
TO GO OUT AND GET STONKED.
AND I HEARD THEM EXCLAIM AS
THEY DROVE OUT OF SIGHT,
"HAPPY CHRISTMAS TO ALL--
[together] BE HOME EARLY
TONIGHT."
[cheers and applause]
SOMETHING A LITTLE BIT
SPECIAL FOR THIS SHOW--A
CHRISTMAS ADVENTURE WITH--OH,
YEAH, BILL, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM, HUH?
OH, HE'S GOT THE--GOT THE CAR
PARKED ON THE SNOW SHOE.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST MOVE THE CAR,
BILL?
I'LL MOVE THE CAR.
NOW, DON'T--DON'T LIFT THAT.
NO, LET'S MOVE IT.
THAT'S EASY.
LET'S JUST MOVE IT.
BILL ALWAYS WANTS TO DO THINGS
THE HARD WAY.
YEAH--YEAH, THAT'S GOOD, BILL.
AH, OH.
ALL RIGHT, WHAT WE'RE OUT TO DO
ACTUALLY IS TO GET OURSELVES A
CHRISTMAS TREE.
SO A BIG ONE, A BIG TREE FOR THE
LODGE THERE.
THESE TREES ARE--OH.
THERE, THEN, THAT'S WHAT THE
TOBOGGAN'S ALL ABOUT.
WE'RE GONNA HAUL HER HOME THERE,
AND--OH, NO, BILL THAT
ONE--NO, THAT'S TOO--BILL,
THAT'S TOO BIG.
YOU'LL NEVER GET THAT TREE
STANDING UP IN THE LODGE.
IT WOULD HAVE TO BE--OH.
ALL RIGHT, THERE, BILL.
LET'S--A LITTLE BIT--OH.
THIS IS GONNA BE A LONG DAY, I
THINK.
WHAT'S HE GOT?
OH, HE'S GOT AN AXE IN HIS
PANTS...
WHICH I GUESS IS BETTER THAN
HAVING AN ACCIDENT IN YOUR
PANTS.
HE'S GOT TWO--OH, MY GOLLY,
THAT'S NOT...
SIZE MATTERS, RIGHT, BILL?
UH-OH, UH-OH, UH-OH.
BILL, DON'T--OH, GEE, THE AXE
IS--THE AXE IS INCOMING.
MY GOSH.
YOU KNOW, THAT COULD HAVE HURT.
SO, BILL, YOU ALMOST KILLED ME,
JUST THOUGHT YOU SHOULD KNOW.
I ACCEPT YOUR APOLOGY.
OH, HE'S GOT AN IDEA,
AND SO DO I.
NO, NO, CAN'T DO THAT IN FRONT
OF THE CAMERAS.
AND JACK CLIMBED AND CLIMBED
WHILE HIS MOTHER WONDERED WHAT
HE HAD DONE WITH THE MONEY.
UP HE GOES TO SEE THE GIANT.
NO, THAT'S ANOTHER ADVENTURE.
THERE YOU GO, BILL.
RIGHT UP TO THE TOP THERE.
TRUNKS GETTING A LITTLE THIN AT
THIS POINT.
AND BILL CERTAINLY ISN'T.
THERE YOU GO.
PULL YOUR WAY UP THERE.
HANG ON.
YEAH, NOW, JUST ROCK IT, ROCK
IT.
MAYBE YOU'LL SNAP IT OFF AT THE
TRUNK OR SOMETHING, BILL.
OR JUST--JUST TAKE--OH, I SEE.
LOOK AT THIS KIDS, EH?
SEE HOW YOU CAN USE YOUR
BALANCE TO--MOVING THE WEIGHT
AND KEEPING THE TREE IN...
I DON'T THINK BILL IS ACTUALLY
ALL THAT BALANCED, NO MATTER
WHAT WE DO--OH.
OH, MY GOLLY.
HOLY SMOKE.
THE TREE CURLED RIGHT
AROUND--WHOOPS--RIGHT DOWN
THERE.
OH, THERE'S YOUR--THERE'S YOUR
TREE.
THAT WON'T TAKE LONG TO
DECORATE.
YEAH, BILL.
HAVE YOURSELF A GREAT CHRISTMAS.
BYE-BYE.
[applause]
[paper rustling]
OH...
OKAY, YEAH.
I...
I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU PARENTS
ABOUT CHRISTMAS.
THE KIDS REALLY LOOK UP TO YOU
TO MAKE CHRISTMAS A SPECIAL
TIME.
AND I MEAN THAT IN A GOOD WAY.
CHRISTMAS CAN BE UPSETTING TO
THE KIDS.
FOR EXAMPLE, YOU DADS OUT THERE,
DON'T COME HOME ON CHRISTMAS
EVE IN THE BACK OF A SQUAD CAR.
[laughter]
CHRISTMAS IS A TIME OF FAMILY
AND LOVE.
I MEAN, IF YOU CAN'T AFFORD
PRESENTS FOR THE KIDS, THEY'LL
UNDERSTAND.
DON'T GO OUT IN THE GARAGE AND
FIRE OFF A SHOTGUN AND THEN TRY
TO CONVINCE THE KIDS THAT SANTA
COMMITTED SUICIDE.
AND DON'T GIVE THEM A BIKE YOU
STOLE FROM THE KID ACROSS THE
STREET.
YOU KNOW, YOU GOT TO JUST BE
TOGETHER AT CHRISTMAS AND TRY
NOT TO GET ON EACH OTHER'S
NERVES.
MAYBE AVOID SENSITIVE TOPICS
LIKE POLITICS AND RELIGION AND
WHO OWES WHO MONEY.
AND EVEN IF YOU'RE NOT HAVING A
FANCY CHRISTMAS DINNER, YOU CAN
AT LEAST TAKE THE PIZZA OUT OF
THE BOX.
AND DRESS UP FESTIVE.
MAYBE PUT A SHIRT ON.
AND PUT SOME PANTS ON.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S A GIFT THAT
KEEPS ON GIVING.
YOU GOT TO TAKE THIS SPECIAL DAY
TO BE WITH YOUR FAMILY AND YOUR
FRIENDS AND LET THEM KNOW HOW
MUCH YOU CARE.
TALK TO THEM.
FIND OUT ABOUT THEIR LIVES.
REALLY SHARE.
I MEAN, WHAT HAVE YOU GOT TO
LOSE?
THERE'S NOTHING GOOD ON
TELEVISION TILL BOXING DAY.
THINK ABOUT IT.
CHRISTMAS IS A TIME TO SLOW
DOWN A LITTLE.
A TIME TO SIT DOWN AND THINK
BACK OVER THE YEAR AND ASSESS
YOUR ACCOMPLISHMENTS.
YOU MAY REALIZE THAT YOU'VE
ACCOMPLISHED DIDDLY-SQUAT.
AND A YEAR OF YOUR LIFE IS GONE
FOREVER, AND WHAT THE HECK WERE
YOU THINKING?
IN THAT CASE, FOCUS ON WHAT
OTHERS HAVE ACCOMPLISHED, AND
FEEL GOOD FOR THEM.
THINK ABOUT PEOPLE WHO HAVE DONE
REALLY IMPRESSIVE THINGS OVER
THE LAST YEAR.
PEOPLE WHO DIDN'T WASTE A YEAR
OF THEIR--OKAY, OKAY, YOU KNOW
WHAT?
I KNOW, I KNOW.
SIT DOWN AND WATCH A LOT OF
CHRISTMAS SPECIALS ON
TELEVISION, AND DON'T THINK AT
ALL--THE SAME ONES YOU WATCHED
LAST YEAR AND THE YEAR
BEFORE--AND BASK IN THE WARM
GLOW OF KNOWING CHARLIE BROWN
AND FROSTY THE SNOWMAN AND THE
GRINCH WHO STOLE CHRISTMAS
DIDN'T DO ANYTHING NEW EITHER.
JOINING ME TODAY, WE GOT
DALTON HUMPHREY--OR MAYBE I
SHOULD SAY, DALTON TENENBAUM.
ARE YOU HERE FOR CHRISTMAS OR
HALLOWEEN, DALTON?
WELL, YOU KNOW, RED, I
THOUGHT MAYBE TODAY WE COULD
REPAIR THESE CHRISTMAS LIGHTS.
CHRISTMAS LIGHTS?
I DIDN'T THINK YOU WERE
CELEBRATING CHRISTMAS.
DIDN'T YOU JUST TELL US IT WAS A
PAGAN RITUAL AND YOU WEREN'T
GOING TO HAVE ANY
PART OF IT, EH?
WHAT MADE YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND?
MY WIFE, ANNE-MARIE.
ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
HOW DID YOU GET ALL TANGLED UP
LIKE THIS, DALTON?
WELL, YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T WANT
TO GET OUT THE STEPLADDER FOR
JUST A LITTLE JOB LIKE THIS, SO
I GOT OUT THE KITCHEN CHAIRS AND
A COUPLE OF PHONE BOOKS, AND I
WAS UP THERE WITH A STAPLER,
PUTTING ON THE LIGHTS.
AND, OF COURSE, THEN THE YELLOW
PAGES SLIP OUT, AND I FALL OFF,
AND I ROLL OVER AND OVER AND
OVER DOWN THE HILL IN FRONT OF
MY HOUSE.
DALTON, PHONE BOOKS AND
KITCHEN CHAIRS?
I KNOW.
YOU'RE ASKING FOR TROUBLE.
IT'S GOT TO BE ENCYCLOPEDIAS AND
END TABLES.
MAN, I--I KNOW YOU SELL
ANTIQUES, BUT THESE BABIES ARE
PREHISTORIC.
WELL, COME ON, NOW, YOU ONLY
USE THESE A WEEK OUT OF THE
YEAR.
WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO SPEND
MONEY ON SOMETHING YOU HARDLY
USE?
YOU FEEL THAT WAY ABOUT
COMBS, DO YOU?
THESE LIGHTS WORK, DALTON?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
THEY--THEY--WHEN I--I TESTED
THEM BEFORE I TRIED TO HANG THEM
UP, YOU KNOW, NOTHING.
OH, MAN, YOU KNOW, THESE ARE
THE OLD KIND.
LIKE, ONE GOES OUT, NONE OF THEM
WORK.
OH?
YEAH.
WELL, YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE
SAYING IT'S IMPOSSIBLE, YEAH,
I'LL JUST TELL ANNE-MARIE, "RED
GREEN SAYS NO CHRISTMAS LIGHTS
THIS YEAR.
YEP, THE KING OF THE HANDYMEN
CAN'T SAVE A FAMILY'S
CHRISTMAS."
WHAT?
COME ON OVER HERE.
I GOT AN EXTENSION CORD.
OH...
ALL RIGHT, STAND STILL.
[electricity crackling]
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
OH--OH, JEEZ, RED.
I'M GETTING SHOCKED--THOUSANDS
OF LITTLE FINGERS TICKLING ME
ALL OVER MY BODY.
YEAH, SORRY ABOUT THAT,
DALTON.
NO, IT'S OKAY, I DON'T MIND.
WHOO!
IS THERE--IS THERE ANY PART
OF YOUR BODY THAT'S NOT
TINGLING?
THE LEFT KNEE.
MY LEFT KNEE.
WELL, THAT'LL BE THE TROUBLE
BULB.
THERE WE GO.
COME ON.
[laughing]
BOY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GETTING SOME IDEAS HERE.
I DON'T THINK WE NEED A TREE
THIS YEAR.
[laughter and applause]
YOU KNOW, AROUND CHRISTMASTIME,
PEOPLE LIKE TO PUT A DISPLAY OF
SOME KIND OUT ON THEIR LAWN.
USUALLY IT'S GOT THE COLORED
LIGHTS ON IT OR MAYBE SANTA ON
HIS SLEIGH OR SOMETHING.
BUT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I PREFER SOMETHING THAT REFLECTS
THE TRUE MEANING OF CHRISTMAS:
KEEP IT CHEAP.
I'M THINKING, GET A BUNCH OF
APPLIANCES AND MAKE YOURSELF A
NATIVITY SCENE.
STOVE HERE--WELL, THAT WOULD BE
THE VIRGIN MARY.
GET ONE FROM A PRIEST, FOR
OBVIOUS REASONS.
AND THEN THE FRIDGE, OF COURSE,
THAT'S JOSEPH.
KIND OF TALL AND QUIET AND COOL.
AND GET YOURSELF THREE
COMPUTERS.
THAT'S YOUR WISE MEN.
AND LOOK AT THIS--I EVEN GOT THE
LITTLE DRUMMER BOY.
[funky percussive music playing]
OH, HERE'S AN EXTRA BONUS:
A SHEPHERD.
WE KNOW WE GOT A LOT OF KIDS
WATCHING THIS CHRISTMAS SPECIAL
'CAUSE YOUR PARENTS ARE SITTING
RIGHT THERE, AND YOU CAN'T ZAP
OVER TO THE CRAP ON THAT ROCK
VIDEO STATION, CAN YOU?
SO HAROLD AND I THOUGHT WE WOULD
GIVE YOU KIDS A TIP.
YEAH, YEAH, YOU KNOW, LIKE,
OKAY, YOU LOOK UNDER THE
CHRISTMAS TREE, AND THERE'S
SOME EARLY PRESENTS THERE, AND
THEY GOT TAGS WITH
YOUR NAMES ON IT?
YOU CAN'T HELP BUT GRAB AND
SHAKE THEM, AND FIND OUT WHAT'S
IN THEM, RIGHT, RIGHT?
UNCLE RED, WOULD YOU GRAB ME
A GIFT?
YEAH, SURE.
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN TELL A LOT
BY THE WEIGHT OF THESE GIFTS,
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE YOU CAN FIND
OUT OF IT'S SOLID, YOU KNOW, OR
IF IT MOVES AROUND IN THE BOX.
YEAH, THIS ONE'S KIND OF, I'D
SAY, AVERAGE WEIGHT.
BUT IT'S PRETTY SOLID, SO IT'S
NOT GONNA SHAKE AROUND TOO MUCH.
AND MAINLY, IT'S NOT CLOTHES.
THAT'S THE GOOD PART.
REAL IMPORTANT TEST, THOUGH,
IS THE SHAKING TEST.
YOU GOT TO REALLY SHAKE IT.
YEAH, BECAUSE IT HELPS YOU
DECIDE WHETHER IT'S LIQUID OR
IT'S A SOLID, OR PERHAPS THERE'S
TWO GIFTS IN THERE.
WAH, WAH, WAH.
BUT DON'T BE AFRAID TO SHAKE IT.
REALLY GIVE HER A GO WHEN YOU'RE
SHAKING IT.
[glass shattering]
OH, OH, OH.
YEAH.
NOW, THAT'S HOW YOU LEARN.
[broken glass rattling]
WE KNOW NOW THAT THIS GIFT IS
MADE OF GLASS.
AND THERE'S SOME ASSEMBLY
REQUIRED.
I FORGOT TO MENTION, WHEN
SHAKING ANY GIFT, ALWAYS GET
A GRIP.
THAT WOULD BE A DREAM COME
TRUE FOR ME, HAROLD.
WELL, THIS PARTICULAR GIFT,
THE NEXT ONE, IT DOESN'T FEEL AS
HEAVY.
NO?
NO, THIS--THE EDGES SEEM
SOFT.
IT'S DEFINITELY LIQUID-FILLED.
BUT, NOW, THE SHAKE TEST.
THIS WILL DETERMINE ALL.
[rattling sound]
[dog barking]
OOH, OOH, OH.
[dog yelping]
ALL RIGHT, IMPORTANT...
[screaming]
NEVER SHAKE A GIFT THAT'S
BREATHING.
OOH, HE'S A KILLER!
HE'S A KILLER!
HE'S A KILLER, I TELL YOU.
YEAH, YEAH, HE'S A--HE'S A
KILLER.
HELLO, EVERYONE.
I'M DALTON HUMPHREY, AND RIGHT
NEXT TO ME IS RANGER GORD.
AND WE HAVE SOME ADVICE FOR THE
CHRISTMAS SEASON.
NOW, MY ADVICE WILL BE MOSTLY
FOCUSED ON SAVING MONEY, WHEREAS
GORD'S ADVICE HERE WON'T BE
LIKELY FOCUSED ON ANYTHING
AT ALL.
HI, EVERYBODY.
MY NAME IS RANGER GORD.
STANDING NEXT TO ME IS DALTON
HUMPHREY.
GORD, GORD, GORD, SEE, I'VE
ALREADY DONE THE INTRODUCTIONS.
DON'T NEED TO DO THEM TWO TIMES.
OH, GOOD IDEA.
SO--
SAVE SOME TIME.
YES, AND WE DON'T HAVE A LOT
OF TIME, SO LET'S MOVE RIGHT
ALONG.
AND WHAT WE HAVE HERE IS A--
DALTON.
YES?
YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL GO SECOND.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, GORD.
YES, WHAT WE HAVE HERE--
[laughing]
IS A TYPICAL GIFT WRAPPED IN A
TYPICAL CHRISTMAS FASHION FOR A
TYPICAL KID.
WEIRD.
NO, IT'S--IT'S--IT'S TYPICAL.
IT'S NOT WEIRD.
THERE'S NOTHING WEIRD ABOUT
THIS.
IT'S JUST--IT'S...
NO, I WAS TALKING ABOUT YOUR
HAIR.
CARRY ON.
YES, THANK YOU.
NOW THE POINT I WOULD LIKE TO
MAKE IS, I WOULD LIKE TO PORTRAY
A TYPICAL KID RIPPING INTO A
TYPICAL CHRISTMAS GIFT ON
CHRISTMAS MORNING.
AND THIS IS THE WAY IT MIGHT GO,
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
OH, BOY, IS THIS FOR ME?
IS THIS FOR ME?
I CAN'T WAIT.
I GOT TO GET THIS OPEN.
OH, BOY, LOOK WHAT SANTA BROUGHT
ME.
LOOK WHAT SANTA BROUGHT ME.
WOW, THIS IS FANTASTIC!
LOOK WHAT I GOT!
WOW!
LOOK AT THAT.
[applause]
WOW, YOU REALLY CUT LOOSE
THERE, DALTON.
BOY, YOU KNOW, COME TO THINK
OF IT, I SURE DID.
I'VE NEVER OPENED A GIFT THAT
WAY BEFORE.
BOY, IT REALLY TOOK ME BACK TO
THE WAY I USED TO FEEL AS A KID.
WELL, ACTUALLY I NEVER REALLY
DID FEEL LIKE I WAS--LIKE THAT
WHEN I WAS KID 'CAUSE MY DAD
SAID IF I DID, I'D GROW UP
FUNNY, BUT...
YEAH.
IS YOUR DAD STILL ALIVE?
EH, PROBABLY.
MY POINT IS THIS: WHAT A WASTE
OF WRAPPING PAPER.
NOW, WHAT WE HAVE TO DO IS TEACH
OUR CHILDREN HOW TO DO THIS--HOW
TO TAKE THE TAPE OFF THE PAPER
SO THAT WE SAVE IT AND BE ABLE
TO USE IT YEAR AFTER YEAR.
THIS IS THE WAY MY FATHER TAUGHT
ME.
PLACE YOUR FINGER UNDER THE LIP
OF THE GIFT.
DALTON, BEFORE YOU GO ON
THERE, LET ME JUST ADD SOMETHING
TO YOUR LAST POINT, IF I MIGHT.
FOLKS, IF YOU HAPPEN TO GET A
GOLDFISH FOR CHRISTMAS AND THE
GOLDFISH DIES, YOU CAN FLUSH IT.
BUT, IF YOU GET A POINSETTIA,
AND THE POINSETTIA DIES, DON'T
FLUSH IT, OKAY?
BAD MISTAKE.
THANK YOU.
GORD...
THAT DOESN'T ADD TO MY POINT.
THAT DOESN'T ADD TO ANY POINT.
NOW, LISTEN, SEE, IT'S NOT YOUR
TURN YET 'CAUSE I'M NOT
FINISHED.
SO WHEN IT IS YOUR TURN, THEN
YOU CAN GIVE YOUR SAFETY TIP,
OKAY?
ALL RIGHT.
NO, IT'S OKAY.
I'VE ALREADY DONE IT.
THANK YOU.
I'M DONE.
OKAY.
WELL, THAT'S ALL THE TIME WE
HAVE.
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYBODY.
NOW, WAIT, STOP!
WHAT WAS THE POINT OF ME
BRINGING THIS STUFF?
IT'S A WASTE.
IT'S A WASTE!
WELL, HERE, I'LL FLUSH IT FOR
YOU.
NO!
OH, FOR--GORD!
CHRISTMAS IS THE SOUND OF
BELLS: BELLS ON THE CHILDREN'S
MITTENS AS THEY THROW SNOWBALLS
AT SENIOR CITIZENS; BELLS IN THE
CHURCH STEEPLES THAT MAKE YOU
FEEL EVEN MORE GUILTY THAN
USUAL; BELLS ON THE LITTLE BROWN
PONY AS THEY TOW IT IN FOR
SERVICE; BELLS ON THE STREET
CORNERS FROM CHARITIES PRYING
LOOSE CHANGE OUT OF TIGHT
FISTS; BELLS ON YOUR DOOR THAT
RING WHEN UNEXPECTED GUESTS
BRING UNEXPECTED GIFTS AND
UNEXPECTED APPETITES; BELLS ON
THE POLICE DOGS AS THEY SEARCH
MY CAR; BELLS ON THE STRIPTEASE
DANCER AS SHE GIVES HAROLD A
CHRISTMAS TO REMEMBER; BELLS ON
THE AMBULANCE THAT COMES TO GET
HIM; BELLS FROM THE KITCHEN
SAYING, "COME AND GET IT."
AND "WILL I BE THERE?"
OH, YEAH, WITH BELLS ON.
YEAH, IT WAS FUN, WASN'T IT?
THAT'S--THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT
FOR OUR CHRISTMAS SPECIAL.
WE HOPE YOU ENJOYED IT, OR SOME
OF IT, OR AT LEAST DIDN'T GET
HURT, OR DIDN'T GET HURT BAD,
ANYWAY.
I ALSO WANT TO REMIND PEOPLE
THAT CHRISTMAS IS A TIME OF--OF
PEACE AND FORGIVENESS; A TIME
TO FORGET ABOUT ALL YOUR PETTY
DIFFERENCES WITH PEOPLE AND BE
KIND TO THOSE WHO ARE HURTFUL TO
YOU ALL YEAR LONG; A TIME TO
OPEN UP YOUR HEART AND EXPRESS
AN ELEMENT OF HOPE AND--THROUGH
A GESTURE OF GENEROSITY OF
SPIRIT.
AND WITH THAT IN
MIND--WAH--UNCLE RED, I'VE GOT
YOU A GIFT.
OH, WELL, THANK YOU, HAROLD.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
I APPRECIATE IT.
OKAY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I SEEM TO HAVE SOMETHING HERE IN
MY POCKET.
OH, BY GOLLY, IT'S A--IT'S A
GIFT OF SOME KIND, I THINK,
HAROLD.
I WONDER WHO THIS IS FOR?
WHAT DOES IT SAY ON THE TAG
THERE?
"NO REFUND WITHOUT SALES
SLIP."
NO, NO, THE OTHER SIDE, THE
OTHER SIDE.
WHAT DOES THAT SAY?
OH, "TO HAROLD, FROM UNCLE
RED."
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
NO PROBLEM.
BY GOLLY, THIS IS...
YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
NO.
IT'S AN ELECTRONIC ORGANIZER.
IT'S REALLY COOL.
IT'S LIKE AN ELECTRIC COMPUTER,
YOU KNOW?
YOU PUT ALL YOUR MESSAGES AND
PHONE NUMBERS AND STUFF IN
THERE, AND IT ELECTRONICALLY
REMINDS YOU.
WELL, THAT'S--THAT'S GREAT,
HAROLD.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
OH, YOU'RE WELCOME VERY MUCH.
[laughter and applause]
YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
YEAH, YEAH.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME, HAROLD.
MERRY CHRISTMAS, EVERYBODY.
MERRY CHRISTMAS, EVERYONE.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
[cheers and applause]
THERE YOU GO.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
HEY, HOW YOU DOING?
[together] I LOVE
CHRISTMAS