[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ GUNSHOTS ]
[ BIRD SQUAWKS ]
Harold:
YOU KNOW, IT'S BEEN SAID
THAT MANY ARE CALLED,
BUT FEW ARE CHOSEN.
WELL, HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
WE HAVE A SAYING, TOO --
"MANY ARE COLD,
BUT FEW ARE FROZEN."
WA-A-A!
THAT'S BECAUSE
WE'RE IN THE HINTERLANDS.
ANYWAY, BUT HERE'S
THE HINTER MAN HIMSELF --
MY UNCLE AND THE STAR
OF THE SHOW --
WOULD IT BE IMMODEST OF ME
TO SAY, THE COSTAR,
ALONG WITH YOURS TRULY,
OF "THE RED GREEN SHOW,"
MY UNCLE, MR. RED GREEN!
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
THANK YOU, AND, UH,
WELCOME TO POSSUM LODGE.
AND BY THE WAY, HAROLD,
YOU'RE NOT THE COSTAR.
YOU'RE THE COASTER.
OH.
AND A PAIN IN THE HINTERLAND.
HAROLD HERE IS MY
PRODUCER/DIRECTOR/NEPHEW
ON THE SHOW.
I'M ALSO
THE RESIDENT WHIZ.
AND WE ALL ENJOY A WHIZ,
DON'T WE?
I THINK WHAT HAROLD
IS REFERRING TO
IS THAT CONGLOMERATION
HANGING AROUND HIS NECK THERE
THAT HE USES FOR DOING
ALL HIS VISUAL DEFECTS.
LIKE THIS.
[ KEYBOARD CLACKING ]
WA-A-A!
THAT'S SO HAROLD
CAN DO TO YOUR EYES
THE SAME THING
HE DOES FOR YOUR EARS.
ANYWAY, BY GOLLY, THE HILLS ARE
ALIVE WITH THE SOUND OF SHOTGUNS
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK,
'CAUSE IT'S THE OPENING
OF HUNTING SEASON.
AND THE LADS ARE ALL OUT IN THE
BUSH, DOING WHAT THEY DO BEST --
FLATTENING FERNS
AND DRAINING WINESKINS.
YOU KNOW,
UNCLE RED, IT'S --
I FIND IT HARD TO FATHOM
THE FACT THAT,
IN THIS ENLIGHTENED AGE --
YOU KNOW, I MEAN,
THE TIMES OF ANIMAL RIGHTS
AND ANTIFUR LOBBYISTS,
GUN CONTROL -- THAT SOMEHOW
HUNTING CAN STILL SURVIVE.
WELL, HAROLD, I'M AMAZED
THAT YOU CAN SURVIVE.
SO, IN OUR WAY,
WE ALL STAND IN WONDER.
I AM AGAINST HUNTING.
THAT IS MY POSITION.
YOU'RE HERE AT THE LODGE
AS A FAVOR TO MY BROTHER.
THAT'S YOUR POSITION.
SO ANYWAY,
EVERYBODY'S PRETTY EXCITED
ABOUT THIS HUNTING THING.
SO FAR, THE BIGGEST KILLING HAS
BEEN MADE BY MURRAY AND DWAYNE
DOWN AT THEIR STORE.
I MEAN, THEY'RE SELLING
EVERYTHING.
THEY SOLD OLD MAN SEDGWICK
A REALLY POWERFUL SHOTGUN,
SO THE BUNCH OF US CHIPPED IN
AND GOT HIM SOME GLASSES.
AND, UH, STINKY PETERSON --
HE GOT HIMSELF A BOW AND ARROW
THIS YEAR.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY, WHILE HE WAS
BITING THE RUBBER SUCTION CUPS
OFF THE TIPS OF THE ARROWS,
MOOSE THOMPSON SAT
ON HIS QUIVER.
THEY'LL BOTH BE OUT
OF THE HOSPITAL THURSDAY.
BUT PROBABLY THE, GOLLY,
THE MOST EXCITED GUY
WOULD BE NOEL CHRISTMAS,
OUR SECURITY GUARD,
BECAUSE, ORDINARILY, NOEL
IS NOT ALLOWED TO CARRY A GUN,
WHICH MEANS HE HAS TO USE HIS
PERSONALITY TO DEFEND HIMSELF,
WHICH ACTUALLY STARTS
MORE FIGHTS THAN IT STOPS.
EXCUSE ME, UNCLE RED, MAYBE
WE SHOULD JUST KEEP MOVING ON,
YOU KNOW, WHILE WE STILL HAVE
A VIEWER.
OH, YEAH, HAROLD.
NO, THAT'S FINE, THAT'S FINE.
LET'S KEEP IT MOVING.
I'M, UH, KIND OF ANXIOUS
TO GET HUNTING MYSELF, SO, UH,
WE'LL TRY TO GET THIS HALF-HOUR
DONE AS QUICKLY AS WE CAN.
WELL, I SUPPOSE
ANYTHING'S POSSIBLE.
EINSTEIN DID PROVE
THAT TIME IS RELATIVE.
YEAH, I WISH HE'D PROVED
THAT YOU WEREN'T, HAROLD.
LET'S GO, LET'S GO.
YEAH, OKAY.
UH, I HAVE AN EMERGENCY
ANNOUNCEMENT.
UH, CAN I HAVE
EVERYONE'S ATTENTION, PLEASE?
THANK YOU.
UH, WE'VE HAD A SHOOTING.
OH!
[ SCOFFS ]
WELL, I'M NOT IMPRESSED
WITH THAT, NOEL.
GROWN MEN OUT IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE WOODS,
SHOOTING DEFENSELESS ANIMALS --
WHOOP-DE-DOO.
THERE'S NO ANNOUNCEMENT
TO BE MADE THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED, NOEL.
WELL, ACTUALLY, UH, YOU KNOW,
NO -- NO ONE SHOT ANY ANIMALS.
UH, I SHOT MURRAY.
OH.
WELL, THAT'S NOT SO BAD.
AND IT SEEMS BILL'S HAVING
A HARD TIME FINDING DOC RENDER.
UH, TRY THE KITCHEN.
HELLO, NOEL.
WHO'D YOU SHOOT THIS TIME?
MURRAY.
OH.
WELL, THAT'S NOT SO BAD.
UH...
OH. OH.
[ CHUCKLES ]
BRING HIM IN HERE.
DOES IT HURT?
OH, NO, HAROLD.
IT'S ONLY A BULLET!
NOEL SHOT ME!
YEAH, WE HEARD.
OH! YOW! GEEZ!
[ Sarcastically ]
THANK YOU, NURSE.
MURRAY'S BEEN SHOT
IN THE BACK!
THE LOWER BACK --
THE REALLY LOWER BACK.
BUT ABOVE HIS LEGS.
BILL'S GONE TO GET
DOC RENDER.
I DON'T NEED A DOCTOR.
I NEED A LAWYER!
HOW ABOUT A PROCTOLOGIST
WITH A MAGNET?
I'M GONNA SUE YOU FOR EVERYTHING
YOU HAVE, NOEL.
OH, YEAH,
I'M GONNA OWN YOUR CHEROKEE.
WELL, I-IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
OH, A-AND I SHOULD BE SUING YOU!
OH, YEAH, I WAS OUT
AFTER A SQUIRREL,
AND WITH THAT, YOU KNOW, BUTT OF
YOURS TAKING UP HALF THE FOREST,
WELL, MY BULLET
DIDN'T STAND A CHANCE.
WHAT IS THAT, AN INSULT?
OH, VERY CLEVER, NOEL!
YOU CAN SHOOT PEOPLE
AND GET OFF A FEW ZINGERS!
OH, I WISH I WERE YOU.
WELL, THINK OF THIS, MURRAY,
THERE'S A SILVER LINING.
YOU'LL GET A MEDAL --
YOU KNOW,
CERTAINLY NOT A PURPLE HEART,
BUT A REAL NICE,
PURPLE...
YOU KNOW, IF YOU NEED ME,
I'M JUST --
I'LL BE OUT OF YOUR WAY,
OVER HERE. HOW'S THAT?
MURRAY, IF YOU DIE,
DO I GET THE STORE?
IF I DIE, YOU DIE.
THAT'S A PACT I MADE
WITH THE DEVIL.
REALLY?
WELL, YOU SHOULD HAVE DISCUSSED
THAT WITH ME.
I SHOULD BE CONSULTED ON THINGS
THAT TERMINATE MY LIFE!
THAT'S THOUGHTLESS!
DON'T PUSH IT, DWAYNE!
WE'VE HAD ONE SHOOTING ALREADY!
OKAY, DROP YOUR DRAWERS.
THE DOCTOR'S HERE.
NOT YOU, DWAYNE.
DWAYNE, COULD I GET A LITTLE
PRIVACY HERE, HUH?
NOW, IT WAS ME WHO --
WHO SENT BILL TO GET DOC.
DON'T FORGET THAT, MURRAY.
I NEVER SAW BILL.
I JUST FIGURED YOU PROBABLY
SHOT SOMEBODY BY NOW.
THIS MIGHT STING
A TOUCH, MUR.
OH! AAH!
OH, YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR THIS,
NOEL, TRUST ME!
WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING AT?
OH, NOTHING.
OH.
SOME HEAD OF SECURITY!
OH, YOU SHOULD ARREST YOURSELF
FOR ATTEMPTED MURDER!
OH, BILL, BILL,
I THINK I SAW DOC RENDER
DOWN BY THE TROUT POND.
[ STRUMS ACOUSTIC GUITAR ]
GRANDMA'S MUSTARD PLASTER
COULD CURE MOST ANYTHING
GRANDMA'S MUSTARD PLASTER,
IT'D MAKE YOUR EYEBALLS STING
SHE USED IT ON HER WALLS
GRANDMA'S MUSTARD PLASTER
THE HOUSE LOOKED FINE,
BUT IT SMELLED KIND OF SICK
GRANDMA'S MUSTARD PLASTER
Red: THIS WEEK
ON "HANDYMAN CORNER,"
WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU SOMETHING
THAT YOU CAN DO
WITH YOUR OLD CAR HOOD.
IF YOU'RE ANYTHING LIKE ME --
I'M SURE IT HAPPENS
A LOT OF TIMES --
YOU'RE DRIVING DOWN THE HIGHWAY
AND BAM! --
YOUR HOOD JUST BLOWS RIGHT OFF.
DON'T YOU HATE THAT?
UH, OF COURSE, WITH ME, NOW,
IT'S PROBABLY MY OWN FAULT,
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN KEEPING
THE HOOD CLOSED
BY USING THE SAME PIECE OF DUCT
TAPE OVER AND OVER AND OVER.
BUT YOU KNOW, IT'S WORTH GOING
BACK AND GETTING THAT CAR HOOD,
EVEN IF YOU HAVE TO APOLOGIZE
TO THE PEOPLE AT THE BUS STOP,
BECAUSE THAT CAR HOOD
IS GONNA SAVE YOU
ABOUT 30 BUCKS COME CHRISTMAS,
BECAUSE WITH A LITTLE INGENUITY,
SOME ELBOW GREASE,
A LITTLE BIT OF USE
OF THE BRAINS HERE,
YOU CAN MAKE YOURSELF
A DANDY LITTLE TOBOGGAN.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
ALL RIGHT.
UH, NOW, FIRST THING
WE WANT TO DO IS, UH,
GET THE HOOD ORNAMENT OFF THERE.
NOW, IS THAT A -- A PHILLIPS ON
THERE OR -- OH, I SEE IT.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
NOW, NOW...
OKAY, THAT'S GOT HER.
NOW WE JUST FLIP HER OVER.
[ SIGHS ]
WE GOT A VOLKSWAGEN HOOD,
I GUESS.
NOW, YOU TAKE THIS ROPE AND, UH,
JUST STRING THE ROPE, UH,
THROUGH THE FRONT HERE,
AND THEN YOU CAN TIE IT
TO SOMETHING
OR JUST GET THE FAT KID
TO SIT ON IT.
THEN, AFTER THAT, YOU'RE --
YOU'RE PRETTY WELL READY TO GO.
BUT, UH, FOR ME, NOW, UH,
I DON'T LIKE JUST SITTING
RIGHT FLAT ON THE HOOD.
I LIKE TO BE UP A LITTLE HIGHER,
YOU KNOW,
SO I CAN SEE WHAT'S COMING,
BECAUSE THERE'S --
THERE'S NOTHING WORSE THAN,
UH, FLYING DOWN A FARMER'S FIELD
AND GETTING HIT IN THE FACE
WITH A FROZEN TRAIL TREAT.
OKAY, SO, WHAT WE'VE DONE IS --
IN MY OPINION, ANYWAY -- WE HAVE
COMBINED COMFORT AND STYLE.
AND WE'VE DONE IT QUICK
AND CHEAP,
USING THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON -- DUCT TAPE.
I GUESS THE DOWNSIDE WOULD BE
THAT WE DID PORK THE FRONT SEATS
OUT OF THE CAR, BUT, UH,
YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T
BE DRIVING IN WINTER ANYWAY.
AND DON'T FORGET --
WEAR YOUR SEAT BELTS.
SO, IF YOU'LL JUST EXCUSE ME,
I'M GONNA DO A LITTLE
TOBOGGANING.
BUT UNTIL NEXT TIME,
REMEMBER --
IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
[ GRUNTING ]
AAH!
"IT IS SPRING --
"A TIME TO ASSESS THE DEGREE
OF WINTER DAMAGE.
YOU GO TO THE BASEMENT
AND COUNT THE EMPTIES."
WOW, YOU KNOW,
NOBODY WAS VERY HAPPY ABOUT, UH,
MOOSE GETTING SHOT
IN THE BACKSIDE.
COUPLE OF INCHES OVER, IT COULD
HAVE MEANT THE LOSS OF A MEMBER.
AND EVEN IF IT HAD BEEN SERIOUS,
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'D GET A TROPHY
THAT YOU'D WANT TO STUFF
AND HANG ON YOUR KITCHEN WALL.
I'LL TELL YOU,
THIS SHOULD PUT AN END
TO THOSE SELF-RIGHTEOUS
COMPLAINERS WHO SAY
THAT HUNTING IS ONE-SIDED
IN FAVOR OF THE HUNTERS.
I DO NOT KNOW HOW YOU CAN
TRIVIALIZE SUCH A THING.
NO, I GUESS IT WON'T
SILENCE THEM.
WELL, I'M --
HOW CAN YOU BE SO FLIPPANT
ABOUT A SERIOUS HUNTING
ACCIDENT, UNCLE RED?
I FEEL YOU SHOULD JUST BE
A LITTLE MORE SENSITIVE
TOWARDS THE ISSUE.
ALL RIGHT, UH,
WE ALL FEEL BAD THAT, UH,
MURRAY GOT SHOT
IN THE BACKSIDE,
AND HE'S GOT A RIGHT
TO BE ANGRY WITH NOEL.
BUT I DON'T THINK HE NEEDS
TO TAKE IT OUT ON THE REST OF US
BY DOUBLING THE PRICE
OF EVERYTHING IN HIS STORE.
EVERYTHING?!
INCLUDING CHERRY LICORICE?!
OH, YEAH, CHERRY LICORICE,
PIXY STIX,
EVEN THE SPONGE TOFFEE,
HAROLD.
[ GULPS ]
UNCLE RED,
CAN I HAVE A RAISE?
LET ME THINK ABOUT THAT
A MINUTE.
NO.
ANYWAY, UH, YEAH,
MURRAY'S RAISED THE PRICE
OF EVERYTHING DOWN THERE.
IT'S CREATING
SOME REAL PROBLEMS.
UH, MOOSE THOMPSON SAYS
THAT THE PRICE OF AFTERSHAVE
HAS SKYROCKETED
WITH, UH, NO APPRECIABLE
IMPROVEMENT IN THE TASTE.
I ASKED STINKY PETERSON IF MAYBE
THE PRICE OF DEODORANT OR SOAP
OR TOOTHPASTE HAD GONE UP,
AND, UH, STINKY HAD NO IDEA.
BUT ONE THING
I JUST HEARD RECENTLY
IS THE PRICE OF AMMO
IS NOW AT THE POINT
WHERE A BULLET COSTS THE SAME
AS A SIDE OF BEEF,
WHICH MEANS
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO ADMIT
THAT WE HUNT JUST FOR THE FUN
OF IT, WHICH IS A NO-NO,
WHICH MEANS SOMETHING
HAS GOT TO GIVE.
UNCLE RED, INSTEAD OF MAYBE
GETTING A RAISE,
YOU THINK MAYBE I COULD JUST
GET, LIKE, PAID IN PIXY STIX?
THINK ABOUT IT.
I DON'T LIKE TO QUESTION YOUR
MEDICAL JUDGMENT, THERE, DOC,
BUT YOU THINK WE SHOULD HAVE
TAKEN MURRAY TO THE HOSPITAL?
NOW, RED, THERE'S A REASON
THEY CALL ME "DOC,"
JUST LIKE THERE'S A REASON
THEY CALL YOU "RED."
SAY, WHY THE HELL
DO THEY CALL YOU "RED" ANYWAY?
NO IDEA.
WELL, MURRAY WILL BE FINE,
TRUST ME.
YEAH,
BUT HE WAS SHOT, DOC.
RED, HE'S GOT A MINOR ABRASION
ON HIS GLUTEUS MINIMUS.
SURE, HE'S GOT SOME NASTY
POWDER BURNS ON HIS BUTT,
BUT HE'LL HAVE TO GO AT THAT ON
HIS OWN TIME WITH A SCRUB BRUSH.
IT WAS ALL I COULD STOMACH
JUST TO EMPTY THAT BOX
OF BAND-AIDS ON HIM.
HE'LL BE FINE.
YOU KNOW,
I-I ONCE SAW A MAN
GET HIT BY OVER 100 BULLETS
AND NOT BLINK.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH, WELL, DEAD MEN
DON'T BLINK, DOC.
WELL, NOW,
DO I LOOK DEAD, RED?
THERE'S NO FISH HERE --
NOT A ONE.
ARE YOU TELLING ME YOU WERE HIT
BY 100 BULLETS?
YEAH, YEAH.
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT, SOMEBODY DROP A BOX
OF THEM ON YOUR FOOT?
NO, NO, IT WAS WHEN
I WAS WORKING AS A FIREMAN.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YEAH, WE GOT A CALL
TO AN AMMUNITION FACTORY.
SHE WAS A MEGAFIRE, RED.
[ CHUCKLES ]
FLAMES SHOOTING UP INTO THE SKY
SO HIGH, THERE WERE --
THERE WERE PIGEONS FLYING OVER,
COMPLETELY COOKED. YEAH.
OH, YEAH.
AND THEN WE GOT THE WORD
THERE WERE CHILDREN
TRAPPED INSIDE THE BUILDING.
OH, YEAH, SURE, DOC.
I MEAN, WHO WOULD LET CHILDREN
INTO AN AMMUNITION FACTORY?
UH, IT WAS A SCHOOL TOUR.
OH, YEAH, YEAH?
WHAT KIND OF SCHOOL IS THIS?
UH...
MILITARY ACADEMY,
I BELIEVE.
HE'S TOO FAST FOR ME,
HAROLD.
SO, WITHOUT ANY REGARD FOR
MY PERSONAL SAFETY WHATSOEVER,
I RAN IN...
YEAH.
...DODGING THE ROCKETS'
RED GLARE,
THE BOMBS BURSTING
IN THE AIR,
AND I LED THOSE KIDS
TO SAFETY, RED.
YEAH?
WELL, THE -- THE SMILES
ON THOSE LITTLE CHERUBIC FACES
AND THE THANKS
FROM THEIR PARENTS
WERE MORE THAN AMPLE
COMPENSATION
FOR THE 100 BULLET HOLES
IN MY BODY.
HOW COME I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANY BULLET MARKS
ON YOUR BODY, THERE, DOC?
WELL, THEY'RE --
THEY'RE THERE, RED.
THEY'RE JUST -- YOU KNOW,
YOU GOT TO LOOK REAL CLOSE.
THEY'RE ALL OVER MY BACK --
ALL OVER MY BACK.
OH, YEAH.
HEY, THEY LOOK A LOT LIKE,
UH, BAD ACNE SCARS,
BUT, UH, THEY'RE
THE REAL McCOY, ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, YOU CAN'T OUTRUN A BULLET,
MY FRIEND.
[ SIGHS ]
YOU THINK YOU COULD
OUTTALK ONE?
[ SQUEAKING ]
Red: NOW IT'S TIME TO GET BACK
TO REALITY.
OH, OH, OH, OH!
OH, OH.
IT'S "ADVENTURES WITH BILL."
BILL GOT HIMSELF
A LITTLE BIKE, THERE,
HE WANTED TO FIX UP.
OH, THE KICKSTAND.
THAT'S NOT A KICKSTAND ANYWAY.
THAT'S JUST A PAIR OF PLIERS.
WHAT A NEAT IDEA -- USE
THE PLIERS AS YOUR KICKSTAND.
YOU CAN USE THE PLIERS
AND JUST --
WANT TO ADJUST
THE HANDLEBARS HERE
AND GET THEM
KIND OF STRAIGHTENED OUT.
THEY WERE KIND OF OUT OF WHACK.
AND HE DROPPED THE BELL, AND --
AND WHEN HE BENT DOWN
TO PICK IT UP,
HE HAD HIS SLEEVE CAUGHT
IN THE -- IN THE HANDLEBAR,
WHICH I POINTED OUT TO HIM,
JUST TRYING TO BE SAFE.
AND THEN...
OH, MY GOLLY.
OH! OH! OH! OH!
OH, MY GOSH.
AND NOW WE WERE OFF
TO A GOOD START.
FRONT TIRE WAS FLAT, SO BILL
FIGURED HE'D PUMP IT UP.
AND PUMP AND PUMP AND PUMP
AND PUMP, AND THEN JUST --
OH, OH, OH, OH.
A LITTLE TOO LONG OF A STROKE
THERE, I GUESS, BILL.
OH, WELL, NO PROBLEM.
[ THUD ]
OH, SORRY.
AND HE GOT ANOTHER PUMP,
AND THIS IS THE HAND-PUMP KIND
THAT YOU CAN'T REALLY EXTEND
QUITE AS MUCH.
HOOKS THAT ONTO A TIRE
AND JUST --
NOW, BILL PAYS TOO MUCH
ATTENTION TO THE CAMERA,
FOR MY MIND,
NOT ENOUGH TO THE TIRE.
HE HAD A WEAK SPOT THERE, AND
SHE'D KIND OF BEEN STARTING --
OH, MY GOSH,
SHE WAS RIGHT THERE AND --
[ EXPLOSION ]
OH! OH! OH!
KIND OF STARTED THINKING ABOUT
MY HERNIA WHEN I SAW THAT.
ANYWAY, HE GOT THAT ALL DONE,
AND NOW HE'S GONNA OIL UP
THE CHAIN.
[ HORN HONKS ]
OH, THERE GOES THE HORN.
OH, WELL.
UH, GET THAT IN A MINUTE.
OIL UP THE CHAIN -- FLIP HER
OVER AND DO HER UPSIDE DOWN.
AND, THAT WAY, YOU CAN
GET THE WHEEL SPINNING
THEN YOU GET THE CHAIN SPINNING,
AND THEN YOU CAN, UH, YOU KNOW,
JUST BY HOLDING THE OIL CAN
IN ONE POSITION,
YOU CAN OIL THE WHOLE CHAIN.
OF COURSE, WHAT WAS HAPPENING
WAS THE OIL WAS CATCHING
ON THE WHEEL
AND GETTING THROWN PRETTY WELL
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
WELL, MAYBE NOT
[ WHOOSHING ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, BILL.
WELL, HE GOT THAT DONE,
AND HE FLIPS HER OVER.
AND WHAT HE DOESN'T NOTICE,
OF COURSE,
IS THE CHAIN JUST FALLING RIGHT
OFF THE BICYCLE, WHICH...
WHOA!
THAT WOULD SLOW YOU DOWN
A LITTLE.
BUT, UH, HE'S ON IT.
HE GETS THE --
GETS THE CHAIN BACK ON THERE
AND GETS HER ALL BACK INTO SHAPE
AND, UH, PUTS THE HORN BACK ON.
I DUCT-TAPE THE BELL ON THERE,
WHICH, UH, YOU KNOW, HOLDS IT,
BUT IT MAKES IT
JUST A WEE LITTLE BIT...
[ MUFFLED RINGING ]
YEAH, A LITTLE BIT QUIETER
THAN IT WOULD BE ORDINARILY.
AND THEN HE STILL HAS
THE TWO WRENCHES, LUCKILY.
SO, NOW THEY'RE GOOD ENOUGH.
NOW LOOK AT THE STREAMERS
ON THERE.
AND HE'S GOT THE HARD HAT,
AND HE'S GOT EVERYTHING.
AWAY HE GOES,
AND, BOY, HE'S REALLY --
HE CAN REALLY MOVE
ON THAT THING.
THERE'S OIL ALL OVER IT.
AND HE'S -- HE'S WHISTLING.
WAY TO GO, BILL.
AND JUST WHIPS RIGHT BY ME.
AND THEN THE STREAMERS GOT
CAUGHT RIGHT UP IN THE TIRE.
AND IT'S ALMOST --
UP AND OVER HE GOES!
LOOK OUT!
OH! OH! OH! OOH!
OH! OH!
OH, WELL.
[ SQUEAKING ]
[ HORN HONKS, BILL GROANS ]
"IT IS SPRING --
MY FAVORITE TIME OF YEAR.
"WINTER IS ICE AND COLD
AND SHOVELING SNOW
"AND CARS THAT WON'T START.
"SUMMER IS BAKING HEAT, SUNBURN,
BUGS, AND NOISY TOURISTS.
"FALL IS COLD AND DAMP,
WITH LEAVES TO RAKE
"AND EVERYTHING DRYING
AND FREEZING UP.
"SPRING ONLY HAS BUGS AND RAIN,
"SO IT'S MY FAVORITE
TIME OF YEAR
[CLEARS THROAT] BY DEFAULT."
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
WELL, UNFORTUNATELY,
THE SITUATION BETWEEN MURRAY AND
NOEL HAS REALLY DETERIORATED.
MURRAY'S PRICES ARE SO DARN HIGH
IN THE STORE
THAT THE LODGE MEMBERS
HAVE ALL DECIDED TO BOYCOTT IT,
WHICH I PUT IN THE "DEPARTMENT
OF REDUNDANCY" DEPARTMENT.
THE ONLY GUY SHOPPING THERE,
ACTUALLY, IS DOC,
BECAUSE MURRAY LOWERED
THE PRICES ON RUBBER WORMS
AND FLUORESCENT FROGS
IN RETURN FOR DOC ACTING
AS MURRAY'S LAWYER,
WHICH PUTS THEM BOTH INTO ONE
OF THOSE LOSE-LOSE SITUATIONS
THAT MURRAY AND DOC
ARE KIND OF FAMOUS FOR.
IT SURE IS FUNNY HOW A SHOOTING
CAN SPOIL THE MOOD OF A PLACE.
OH, WELL, I'M SURE WE'LL GET IT
ALL STRAIGHTENED OUT
AT TONIGHT'S LODGE MEETING.
[ SCREECHING ]
OH, UNCLE RED,
THAT'S THE CALL OF THE MEETING.
WE HAVE TO GO NOW.
COME ON, HURRY UP, OKAY?
'CAUSE YOU KNOW HOW I LIKE
PUNCTUALITY.
YEAH, AND I LIKE
PUNCHING YOU, HAROLD.
ANYWAY, UH, WE'LL JUST GO DOWN
TO THE MEETING,
AND JUST HANG WITH US
FOR A MINUTE, HERE,
AND WE'LL JUST CLEAR THE AIR
OF ANY ANIMOSITY,
AND THEN WE CAN GET RIGHT BACK
TO HUNTING.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ SCREECHING CONTINUES ]
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
STINKY?
STINKY, GET AWAY FROM THERE.
WE'RE GONNA START.
OKAY, ALL RISE, ALL RISE.
SORRY, MURRAY.
All:
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS, MORITATI.
AAH!
WELL, SIT.
SHUT UP, HAROLD.
ALL RIGHT.
THE FLOOR RECOGNIZES
DOC RENDER.
YOUR HONOR, I CALL TO THE STAND
AS MY FIRST WITNESS
DWAYNE DORTMAN.
WHAT IS THIS,
A COURTROOM NOW?
YES, YOUR HONOR.
WE HAVE A JUDGE, A BAILIFF,
AND 40 JURORS.
EXCELLENT!
NOW, DWAYNE, DO YOU PROMISE TO
TELL THE TRUTH, THE WHOLE TRUTH,
AND NOTHING BUT THE TRUTH,
SO HELP YOU GOD?
UH, I'LL TAKE NUMBER 2 --
THE WHOLE TRUTH.
NEVER MIND.
INSTEAD, I CALL THE ACCUSED
AS MY NEXT WITNESS --
MR. NOEL CHRISTMAS.
Red:
BA BA BA BUM
NOW, THEN,
MR. CHRISTMAS --
IF THAT IS
YOUR REAL NAME,
DID YOU OR DID YOU NOT
SHOOT MY CLIENT
WITH MALICE AFORETHOUGHT
AND DIRE INTENT?
UH, I-IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
JUST ANSWER THE QUESTION,
PLEASE.
UH...YEAH, I DID.
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
OKAY.
NOW I CALL THE VICTIM
TO THE STAND --
MR. MURRAY WOOLWORTH,
OWNER OF THE FAMOUS STORE...
MURRAY'S.
MURRAY,
IN YOUR OWN WORDS,
WOULD YOU PLEASE DESCRIBE
FOR THE COURT
JUST EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED?
HE SHOT MY TUSH.
HMM.
AND WHY DID HE DO THAT?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
THINK HE WAS JEALOUS
'CAUSE I'M TALLER THAN HE IS!
YOU'RE NOT!
AHA!
WELL, NOW I SHOULD LIKE
TO CALL TO THE STAND
MY EXPERT MEDICAL WITNESS,
DOC RENDER.
I OBJECT!
YOU'RE NOT A REAL DOCTOR.
SO?
I'M NOT A REAL LAWYER EITHER.
NOW THEN [CLEARS THROAT]
DOC RENDER [SNIFFS]
YOU HAVE EXAMINED
THE POSTERIOR IN QUESTION?
I HAVE.
AND, UH, IN YOUR EXPERT
MEDICAL OPINION,
WOULD YOU SAY
THAT THE WOUND WAS CAUSED
BY DELIBERATE MISUSE
OF A FIREARM?
WELL, IT'S HARD TO SAY.
I, UH, I THINK --
YOU THINK?!
[ Scoffing ] YOU THINK?
I ASK YOU TO CONSIDER THAT
A MAN'S CAREER IS AT STAKE HERE.
NOW, ASK YOURSELF --
COULD IT HAVE BEEN AN ACCIDENT?
WELL, IT'S HARDLY
FEASIBLE THAT --
YES OR NO?!
I, UH...YES, IT --
IT COULD HAVE BEEN AN ACCIDENT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOUR HONOR, I MOVE, THEN,
THAT THE CHARGES
OF ATTEMPTED MURDER
BE REDUCED TO ONE OF ACCIDENTAL
DISCHARGE OF A WEAPON
IN A RESTRICTED AREA.
[ SNIFFS ]
I REST MY CASE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
DID YOU JUST LOSE THIS CASE
FOR ME?
WELL, THE LAW
IS A FUNNY THING, MURRAY.
THAT'S WHY I BECAME
A DOCTOR.
WELL, YOU CAN PAY
FULL PRICE
JUST LIKE EVERYONE ELSE,
MR. RENDER.
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
WAIT, NOW, WAIT, NOW.
MAYBE WE CAN MAKE THIS
JUST A LITTLE BIT FAIRER.
NOEL, WHY DON'T YOU AT LEAST PAY
FOR MURRAY'S DAMAGES?
HEY, THAT SHOULD BE ENOUGH
FOR YOU, SHOULDN'T IT?
NO.
I THINK SO.
I'M GONNA MAKE THAT MOTION.
ALL IN FAVOR OF THAT HAPPENING,
SAY "AYE."
AYE!       AYE!
AYE!                        AYE!
ANYBODY OPPOSED?
NAY! NAY.
THAT MOTION CARRIED.
THAT'S IT.
THAT -- THAT'S IT?
AW.
ALL RIGHT, THEN. OKAY.
I WANT A NEW PAIR OF SLACKS --
$51
A BRAND-NEW WALLET --
THAT WAS REAL NAUGAHYDE -- $49.
I WANT LOSS OF INCOME -- $90,
A BAND-AID -- $1.
AND A NEW PAIR
OF UNDERWEAR.
NO, THE BULLET WENT THROUGH
AN ALREADY-EXISTING HOLE.
BUT I DO WANT PAIN
AND SUFFERING -- $1 MILLION!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
YEAH, MAKE A LIST, MURRAY.
OKAY, ANY OTHER BUSINESS
ON THE THING THERE, BILL?
NOTHING GOING ON?
OKAY, LET'S GET NOEL UP HERE
TO ENTERTAIN US.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I THINK IT'S ONLY APPROPRIATE,
AT THIS TIME
THAT, AS THE HEAD
OF LODGE SECURITY,
WE DEAL WITH, UH,
SAFETY WITH FIREARMS.
SO I HAPPEN TO HAVE BROUGHT
A RIFLE UP HERE.
THIS BEAUTY IS LOADED,
SO I WANT YOU ALL TO REALIZE
THAT THIS IS A DANGEROUS THING.
WELL, I THOUGHT THEY COULD
SETTLE THAT WITH A FEW WORDS,
ESPECIALLY IF ONE OF THE WORDS
IS "MONEY."
AND NOW MURRAY CAN GO
FROM BEING 600% OVERPRICED
TO BACK TO HIS USUAL 300%.
AND BESIDES WHICH,
HE'S GOT SOMETHING HE CAN SHOW
HIS GRANDCHILDREN,
OR AT LEAST DESCRIBE.
ANYWAY, UH, IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AND SO NOW WOULD PROBABLY
BE A GOOD TIME
TO POP MY FLANNEL PAJAMAS
INTO THE TOASTER OVEN.
IF I NOTICE THAT YOURS
ARE IN THERE, TOO,
I'LL TREAT THAT AS A SIGN.
SO, UNTIL NEXT TIME,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
NOW, WHEN YOU PULL IT UP HERE,
LET THIS SNAP,
BECAUSE IT'LL FIRE.
BUT RIGHT NOW -- OKAY, THE GUN
IS NOW COCKED, OKAY?
WE ARE READY TO KILL
AT THIS POINT.
SO, WILL YOU HOLD STILL
OUT THERE
WHEN I'M TRYING TO LECTURE,
OR YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET
THE FINE POINTS OF THIS WEAPON
IF YOU'RE GONNA BE JUMPING
ALL OVER!
OKAY, NOW, IT'S COCKED,
IT'S READY TO GO.
YOU AIM.
NOW, THIS IS IMPORTANT, OKAY?
OKAY, YOU AIM AND YOU --
ALL RIGHT.
SO YOU'RE LOOKING
DOWN THE BARREL AT THE SIGHT,
AND YOU CAN PRETTY WELL
SEE EVERYBODY.
THINGS MOVING QUICKLY,
LIKE BOB OVER THERE, YEAH.