WHEN I WAS TWENTY I WEIGHED
150 POUNDS IN MY SHORTS
WELL, IN ANYBODY'S
SHORTS, REALLY.
AND NOW THAT I'M NOT 20,
MY DOCTOR GETS A BIG KICK
OUT OF WEIGHING ME
EVERY TIME
I GO IN THERE,
NO MATTER WHAT I WENT
IN FOR IN THE FIRST PLACE.
SORE THROAT, MR. GREEN?
STEP UP UP ON THE SCALE.
PULLED MUSCLE, MR. GREEN?
UP ON THE SCALE.
LAWN DART THROUGH THE FOOT?
UP YOU GO.
TALK ABOUT ADDING
INSULT TO INJURY.
AND NOW HE SAYS HE'D
LIKE ME TO LOSE 15 POUNDS.
WELL, I'D LIKE HIM
TO DROP DEAD.
HERE'S ANOTHER OPTION:
IT'S NOT AS VIOLENT,
BUT IT IS DISHONEST,
SO IT HAS THAT GOING FOR IT.
ALL'S YOU GOT TO DO
IS HIDE ONE OF THESE KIDS'
INFLATABLE SWIM RING THINGS
UNDER YOUR CLOTHES.
THEN JUST FULL HER UP
WITH A LIGHTER-THAN-AIR GAS
LIKE HYDROGEN,
OR IN THIS CASE, HELIUM,
AND, BINGO,
YOU GO FROM A HEAVYWEIGHT
TO A WELTERWEIGHT
WITHOUT EVEN TRYING.
THERE.
TIME TO MAKE MY DOCTOR
LOOK FOOLISH FOR A CHANGE.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I HAVE AN
APPOINTMENT TO KEEP.
[ HORN HONKS ]
[ SOUND OF AIR DEFLATING ]
in high-pitched voice:
OH, THE HUMANITY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT. THANK YOU.
AS YOU CAN SEE, WE'VE
HAD ANOTHER ONE OF OUR
FREAK SNOW STORMS
UP AT THE LODGE.
YOU KNOW I THINK
IT'S THE POLLUTION LEVELS
IN POSSUM LAKE THAT DO IT.
'CAUSE LAKES ARE SUPPOSED TO
FREEZE IN THE WINTER, RIGHT,
NOT CONGEAL?
Harold:
UNCLE RED!
UNCLE RED, HELP!
WHERE ARE YOU, HAROLD?
I'M STUCK OUTSIDE!
I CAN'T GET IN!
OH, OKAY.
HANG ON. HANG ON.
I'LL HELP YOU.
HELP!
OH!
OKAY, HAROLD, LOOK,
I'M GOING TO HAND THE
SKI IN THROUGH THE DOOR.
OKAY, YOU GRAB THE
END AND I'LL PULL YOU
INSIDE, ALL RIGHT?
OKAY. GOOD IDEA.
OH, HAROLD! YOU TOOK
IT RIGHT OUT OF MY HANDS.
SORRY!
CAN WE TRY IT AGAIN?
ALL RIGHT.
HERE COMES THE OTHER ONE.
OKAY.
GOOD. YEAH.
OKAY. YEAH.
I'M SORRY. MY FAULT.
WHAT AM I GOING
TO DO NOW?
PUT THE SKIS ON,
GO TO THE BACK DOOR.
WELL, LIKE I SAY, YOU KNOW,
THE ROADS ARE ALL CLOSED.
THE TOWN'S PRETTY
MUCH SHUT DOWN.
EVEN THE POLICE
AREN'T WORKING TODAY.
HI.
I LOVE THIS WEATHER!
[ APPLAUSE ]
I JUST SENT HAROLD
AROUND THE BACK WAY.
DID HE MAKE IT?
OH, YEAH HE MADE IT.
HE'S JUST OUT DIGGING
THE SNOW OUT OF HIS UNDERWEAR.
YOU KNOW, MR. GREEN,
I REMEMBER SEEING
THIS MOVIE ONCE
WHERE THESE PEOPLE WERE
STRANDED IN A SNOWSTORM,
AND, LIKE, THE ONLY
WAY THEY COULD SURVIVE
IS IF THEY ATE
ONE OF THEM.
OOH! UNCLE RED --
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I THINK WE'RE STUCK
HERE FOR THE DURATION.
WE SHOULD JUST CURL UP WITH
A GOOD BOOK OR SOMETHING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HE'S TENDER.
WOULD YOU LIKE
A DRINK, HAROLD?
YES. PLEASE.
I WAS OUTSIDE AND I GOT
ALL STUCK OUTSIDE.
WHAT IS THAT?
MARINADE.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TONIGHT'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FROM ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
IT'S OUR NEW HIGH-TECH
COMPUTER ROOTER TREATMENT.
HAS A BIG DOWNLOAD
CLOGGED YOUR LINE?
DOES YOUR HARDWARE
MAKE UNNECESSARY BACKUPS?
LET US COME AND GIVE YOUR
SYSTEM A LITTLE EXTRA RAM.
OKAY. COVER YOUR
EARS, THERE, DALTON.
OKAY, RED,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, DALTON,
WHAT DO YOU DO WHEN
YOU'RE TRYING TO
LOOK THINNER?
STAND FARTHER BACK.
OKAY, SAY YOU WANNA
HAVE A DRINK
BUT YOU'RE TRYING TO LOSE
WEIGHT, SO YOU DON'T
HAVE A REGULAR SODA,
YOU HAVE A...
A MINI-SODA.
OF COURSE, IT DIDN'T  DO
MUCH FOR MINNESOTA FATS, HUH?
NOT EVEN
CLOSE, THERE.
OKAY, NOW, MOOSE THOMPSON
WENT TO THE DOCTOR LAST WEEK,
AND THE DOCTOR SAW HE WAS
UP WAY OVER 300 POUNDS, OKAY?
HE PUT HIM ON A...
OH, A STRONGER CHAIR.
OKAY. OKAY. OKAY.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT YOUR
WIFE IS ON ALL THE TIME.
[ sighs ]
THE WAR PATH.
RED, YOU'RE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME HERE.
OKAY. OKAY. OKAY.
DALTON, IMAGINE
THAT YOU'RE SANTA CLAUS.
THAT'D NEVER HAPPEN, RED.
NO, OKAY. OKAY.
IMAGINE THAT YOU
LOOK LIKE SANTA CLAUS.
YOU GOT THE BOWL FULL
OF JELLY BELLY THING
GOING ON THERE.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
TO IMPROVE YOUR APPEARANCE?
IF I HAD ALL THAT
WHITE HAIR, I'D DYE IT.
YEAH!
Red: YOU KNOW, AS PEOPLE
GET OLDER THEY TEND TO
NOT LIKE PROGRESS.
THAT'S BECAUSE WHEN SOMEBODY
COMES OUT WITH A NEW WAY
OF DOING SOMETHING YOU'VE
BEEN DOING YOUR WHOLE LIFE,
IT'S REALLY THEIR
WAY OF SAYING,
HEY, YOU'RE A MORON.
AND THAT'S WHY GUYS LIKE ME
ARE ALWAYS LOOKING FOR WAYS
TO SHOW THESE YOUNG BUCKS
THAT WE DID IT BETTER
IN THE OLD DAYS.
LET ME GIVE
YOU AN EXAMPLE.
HERE WE HAVE A STOVE THAT
WE USED TO DO MOST
OF OUR COOKING.
NOT ALL OF OUR COOKING,
BECAUSE SOMETIMES
WE LIKE TO BARBEQUE.
SEE, NOW, THAT'S A MAN'S WAY
OF HELPING OUT WITH DINNER
WITHOUT ACTUALLY EVER HAVING
TO SET FOOT INSIDE
THE KITCHEN.
THEN WHEN WE'RE ALL DONE
AND IT'S TIME TO
DO THE DISHES,
WE JUST TURN ON
THE HOT WATER
AND AWAY WE GO.
AND LATER ON IN THE EVENING,
THE HOUSE CAN GET PRETTY COOL,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU
WERE LATE COMING HOME
FROM WORK -- OR WHATEVER.
SO ALL'S WE DO
IS CRANK UP THE FURNACE.
BUT WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT HAVE I GOT HERE?
I GOT A GAS BILL FOR
THE FURNACE AND THE STOVE,
AN ELECTRIC BILL
FOR THE HOT WATER HEATER,
AND A PROPANE BILL
FOR THE BARBEQUE.
SEPARATE BILLS FOR FOUR
THINGS THAT DO EXACTLY
THE SAME THING...
PRODUCE HEAT.
HOW CRAZY IS THAT, HUH?
WELL, I THINK IT'S
TIME TO GET BACK
TO THE WAY OUR
FOREFATHERS DID THINGS.
REMEMBER WHEN YOUR WIFE
DRAGS YOU ON THAT HISTORICAL
TOUR OF WILLIAMSBURG, EH?
REMEMBER THE FIREPLACE
THEY HAD THERE
THAT THEY COOKED ON
AND HEATED WATER ON
AND HEATED THE HOUSE WITH?
WELL, SEE, NOW, I THINK
THEY HAD THE RIGHT IDEA.
THEY JUST DIDN'T
HAVE THE RIGHT TECHNOLOGY.
WELL, WE HAVE THAT NOW.
IT'S CALLED A FURNACE, HUH?
OKAY, YOU SEE HOW THEY
HAVE IT ALL CLOSED IN?
THAT'S SO YOU CAN'T SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON IN THERE.
AND DOWN HERE YOU HAVE
THE FLAME IN THIS AREA.
AND THEN ABOVE THAT IS
THE AIR CHAMBER WHERE
THE AIR GETS HEATED.
AND THEN YOU HAVE
THE FAN
THAT FIRES THE WARM
AIR UP INTO THE HOUSE.
AND THAT'S ALL IT DOES.
WHAT A WASTE
OF ENGINEERING.
WELL, I THINK WE CAN DO
A LITTLE BETTER THAN THAT.
OKAY, NOW WE'RE COOKING.
SEE I MOUNTED
THE OVEN DOOR ON HERE,
'CAUSE THIS ISN'T
JUST A FURNACE ANYMORE.
NOW IT'S A --
IT'S A --
WELL, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT IT IS,
BUT IT'S NOT JUST A FURNACE.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
OKAY, YOU'VE GOT YOUR FURNACE
BURNER RIGHT DOWN AT
THE BOTTOM
SO THIS IS WHERE YOU
DO ALL YOUR BARBEQUING.
YOU MIGHT EVEN THROW A FEW
BRIQUETTES ON THE BURNER.
THINK HOW GOOD THAT'S GOING
TO MAKE YOUR HOUSE SMELL.
THAT'S A NICE
CHANGE, ISN'T IT?
OKAY, NOW, THIS COOKIE SHEET
BECOMES THE BOTTOM
OF MY OVEN, SEE?
BUT BECAUSE IT'S
SO FAR ABOVE THE FLAMES,
I CAN ACTUALLY BAKE
ON THE BOTTOM OF THE OVEN.
I MEAN THE EFFICIENCIES
JUST KEEP ON COMING.
I'D SAY THESE COOKIES WILL
BE DONE IN ABOUT 20 MINUTES.
EVEN SOONER IF
WE HAVE A COLD SNAP.
OH, YEAH, AND I'M USING
THIS OLD GAS CAN
AS MY HOT WATER HEATER.
A COUPLE OF THINGS
TO REMEMBER HERE...
NUMBER ONE, DON'T
USE A PLASTIC GAS CAN.
OF COURSE, HINDSIGHT
IS ALWAYS 20-20, ISN'T IT?
AND THE OTHER THING IS
YOU WANT TO BE CAREFUL WITH
YOUR OVERHEAD PIPE JOINTS.
AS ANY PLUMBER WILL TELL
YOU THEY'RE TRICKY
TO DUCT TAPE.
OH, AND HERE'S
ANOTHER BONUS...
I'M USING MY
PULL-OUT FILTER
AS A PIZZA OVEN.
OKAY,
LET'S FIRE HER UP.
NOW, OBVIOUSLY THE
STANDARD FURNACE THERMOSTAT
IS NOT GOING TO GIVE US
THE KIND OF BTU'S WE NEED,
SO I REPLACED IT WITH THE
HEAT CONTROL OUT OF THE OVEN.
BUT YOU GOT TO KEEP
AN EYE ON THIS BABY.
IF YOU DON'T PAY ATTENTION
YOU CAN GET THE HOUSE
UP TO 450 DEGREES.
THAT'LL COST YOU A FORTUNE.
I SMELL COOKIES.
[ FIRE ALARM BLASTING ]
[ ALARM STOPS ]
I WANT TO TALK A LITTLE
BIT ABOUT MIXED MARRIAGES.
A MORNING PERSON SHOULD
NEVER MARRY A NIGHT PERSON.
BELIEVE ME, IT'S GOING TO
CAUSE NOTHING BUT TROUBLE
IN THE LONG RUN.
FIRST OF ALL,
AT THE CRACK OF DAWN,
THE MORNING PERSON IS ALL
BRIGHT-EYED AND BUSHY-TAILED,
WHILE E NIGHT PERSON IS
BLEARY-EYED AND BUSHY-TONGUED.
AND ON THE OTHER HAND,
IN THE WEE SMALL HOURS...
MRS. MERRY MORNING IS DEEP
INTO HIBERNATION ON THE COUCH
SNORING SO LOUD
THAT MR. NIGHT OWL
CAN BARELY HEAR
HIS INFOMERCIALS.
SEE BURNING THE MATRIMONIAL
CANDLE AT BOTH ENDS,
WELL, THAT PUTS A STRAIN
ON ANY KIND OF RELATIONSHIP.
AND NO AMOUNT OF COFFEE
CAN TURN A MORNING PERSON
INTO A NIGHT PERSON
OR VICE-VERSA.
WHAT YOU GOT HERE IS
AN UNNATURAL UNION, OKAY?
AND THERE'S ONLY
ONE WAY TO SAVE IT.
YOU GOT TO CONCENTRATE
ON THE AFTERNOON.
THAT'S THE ONLY TIME OF
THE DAY WHEN BOTH OF YOU
ARE NOT TOO TIRED
OR TOO CRANKY.
THAT'S YOUR WINDOW OF
OPPORTUNITY,
SO DRAW A
CURTAIN OVER IT
AND GO FOR A LITTLE
AFTERNOON DELIGHT, OKAY?
JUST MAKE SURE
YOU GO HOME FIRST --
UNLESS YOU BOTH
WORK AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU ALWAYS GET
YOUR SEPTICS PUMPED.
YOUR TANK'S AS
CLEAR AS A BELL.
BUT BE SURE YOUR
NEIGHBOUR GETS HIS DONE TOO,
OR YOU'LL BE A VICTIM
OF SECOND HAND SMELL.
WE'RE HAVING
A LITTLE PROBLEM.
THE DRINKS AND
THE STOCKS ARE HOLDING OUT,
BUT THE TV RECEPTION
IS TERRIBLE.
ALL WE GET IS SNOW.
SO WE GOT HAROLD
UP ON A LADDER THERE,
HOPING THAT HE CAN TURN THE
AERIAL FROM INSIDE THE ROOF.
YOU KNOW, MR. GREEN,
I COULD USE SOME HELP HERE.
HAROLD'S GOT
A LOT OF MEAT ON HIM.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO
EAT HIM, MIKE, OKAY?
[ HAROLD SCREAMING ]
WHAT IS IT,
HAROLD?
Harold:
THERE'S A LOT
OF BATS UP HERE.
CAN YOU REACH THE
AERIAL POLE FROM
INSIDE THE ROOF?
Harold: NO!
BUT THERE'S A TRAP DOOR.
WHY WOULD THERE BE
A TRAP DOOR IN
OUR ROOF?
I PUT ONE IN WHEN
I WAS LIVING UP THERE.
BUT THEN THE
CHARGES WERE DROPPED.
CAN YOU OPEN
THE DOOR, HAROLD?
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
Harold: YES!
WELL, CAN YOU REACH
THE AERIAL NOW, HAROLD?
[ METAL CREAKING ]
Harold:
NOT NOW, NO.
OKAY, SO NOW WE GOT
NO TV RECEPTION AT ALL.
WHAT NEXT?
WELL, I'M HUNGRY.
C'MON DOWN, HAROLD.
STOP IT.
STOP.
Red:
OKAY, NOW, DON'T PANIC.
IT'S JUST A
CHILI COOK-OFF.
WALTER AND I WERE THE
LAST TWO ENTRANTS IN
THE WHOLE LODGE,
AND WALTER LIKES TO DO
EVERYTHING KINDA DIFFERENT.
HE'S GOT AN APRON.
WHAT DOES, "I MASH..."
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I DON'T HAVE AN APRON.
I DON'T HAVE --
HE'S GOT THE HAT
AND EVERYTHING.
I'M HAPPY -- NO,
I LIKE THAT HAT I HAVE.
WALTER, I LIKE
THE HAT I HAVE.
THE HAT I HAVE IS FINE.
IT'S FINE.
I DIDN'T REALIZE THE FIRE WAS
GOING AND HE COULDN'T SEE --
WELL, I HELPED HIM UP.
AT LEAST HIS APRON IS
MORE ACCURATE NOW...
I'M A MORON.
SO I'M JUST MAKING
IT IN THE NORMAL PAN.
DUMP IN SOME GROUND MEAT...
NO, NO, WALTER'S GOT
TO HAVE THE SPECIAL
PRESSURE COOKER,
AND HE'S GOT TO START
WITH THE BIG HUNKS OF BEEF.
HE PUTS THEM IN THERE
AND GRINDS THEM UP.
IT'S A LOT BETTER IF THE
BEEF DOESN'T HAVE BONES
IN IT, WALTER.
YOU KNOW, IT'S LIKE
GOING TO WORK.
YOU GRIND AND GRIND,
AND YOU EVENTUALLY PULL
YOURSELF DOWN INTO IT.
MEANWHILE,
I'M JUST CARRYING ON.
I GOT THE TOMATO PASTE --
YOU'RE FINE.
GOT A LARGE JAR OF
TOMATO PASTE THAT I USE,
BUT THAT'S NOT GOOD
ENOUGH FOR WALTER.
HE'S GOT TO SQUASH
HIS OWN TOMATOES.
HE'S GOT ONE
OF THESE POWER --
YOU KNOW, I WISH I'D
SEEN HE WAS DOING THAT.
I WOULD HAVE GOTTEN OUT
OF THE WAY OVER THERE.
OH!
THANK YOU, WALTER.
SO I DON'T THINK HE'S GOING
TO GET ANYTHING REAL
USABLE OUT OF THAT.
NO. NO. OKAY.
AND NOW WE GET INTO THE REAL
COMPETITION WITH CHILI,
WHICH IS THE AMOUNT OF HOT
STUFF YOU CAN PUT INTO HER.
I HAD THE CHILI POWDER
GOING PRETTY GOOD THERE.
SO WALTER'S GOT TO KINDA
ONE BETTER ME THERE.
HE JUST DUMPS HER RIGHT IN,
AND, BOY, THAT'S GOT
TO BE GETTING HOT.
NOW, I WAS NOT
IMPRESSED WITH THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
HAVE A LOOK AT THIS, WALTER.
I CAN JUST SPRINKLE THIS
ON MY HAND AND JUST --
NO PROBLEM, NO PROBLEM,
NO PROBLEM.
YEAH?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
THAT'D BE TOBASCO.
A LITTLE DAB OF THAT
ON YOUR TONGUE, WALTER.
OH, BOY. OH, BOY.
OH, BOY.
OH, NO. OH, NO.
YOU'RE GOING TO PAY.
UNDAUNTED I GET
OUT A REAL HOT PEPPER
AND JUST BITE
THE END OFF OF THERE.
HEY, TRY THAT.
TRY THAT, IF YOU'RE A MAN.
OH, MY GOSH.
NOW THE HEAT OF THE MOMENT
IS STARTING TO SET IN,
AND WE'RE BOTH
FEELING THE EFFECTS.
WE LOOK OVER TO THE SIDE
AND WHAT DO WE SEE BUT
A RAIN BARREL.
AND I'M THINKING, JUST
EXCUSE ME A MINUTE, WALTER.
SO I GRAB THE PAIL --
JUST HANG ON A MINUTE LET
ME JUST GET A DRINK.
YOU CAN HAVE THE
PAIL IN A SECOND.
BUT OF COURSE, WALTER
CAN'T WAIT FOR THAT.
HE'S GOT A PROBLEM.
HE CAN REALLY DRINK, WALTER.
BOY, OH, BOY.
OF COURSE, WHAT WE FORGOT
WAS THE PRESSURE COOKER
SITTING ON THE FIRE,
AND SHE WAS REALLY
STARTING TO BUILD UP.
OH, BOY.
AND THE PRESSURE
RELEASE IS GONE ON HER,
AND I JUST DUCK DOWN BEHIND
WAITING FOR THE EXPLOSION,
AND BUT WALTER WANTED
TO GET HER SOMEWHERE SAFE.
NO, WALTER, NO.
I SURE WISH I'D
SEEN HIM DO THAT
BUT HE THINKS HE'S --
OKAY, OKAY.
YEAH, YOUR
PROBLEMS ARE OVER.
I'M TAKING MY CHILI,
AND I FIGURE I WON
BY DEFAULT.
HIS CHILI'S GONE.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHERE IT WAS.
BUT AS I HEAD TO THE VAN,
WALTER SUDDENLY REALIZES
THAT I'M GOING TO GO HOME
IN THE SAME VEHICLE
I ARRIVED IN.
AND HE'S SAYING --
HE'S TRYING TO --
I GUESS HE WAS
TRYING TO STOP ME,
BUT AT THIS POINT I KIND
GOT MYSELF SET OFF ON
MY WAY HOME.
I GET IN THERE AND DON'T
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THE
CHILI IN THE BACK
AND... OH, BOY.
CHILI WILL DO THAT.
[ Red chuckling ]
BUSTED.
YOU MARRIED GUYS
KNOW THE SITUATION.
YOU PROMISED YOUR WIFE YOU'D
BE HOME FROM POKER NIGHT
AT 11:00,
AND THE ONLY WAY
YOU CAN POSSIBLE MAKE IT
IS IF YOU PRESET ALL THE
CLOCKS IN THE HOUSE TO
HONOLULU TIME.
NOW, WHAT YOU WANT IS A
WAY TO GET YOUR VEHICLE
UP THE DRIVEWAY SAFELY
WITHOUT WAKING ANYBODY INSIDE.
SEE, THAT'S WHAT
THIS POWER WINCH IS FOR.
I ATTACH MY BOAT TRAILER
TO THE REAR WALL OF MY GARAGE.
SHE'S NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
I USED EYE BOLTS,
WHICH MAKE SENSE.
'CAUSE EVERY TIME MY WIFE
ASKS ME, WHAT'S THAT FOR,
I BOLT.
NEXT, I GOT MYSELF
EXTRA-LONG WINCH CABLE.
AND A LITTLE EXTENSION WIRING
FOR MY ELECTRICAL HOOKUP.
NOW WHEN I PLUG IN
MY ELECTRICAL HOOKUP,
THE WINCH'LL BE RUNNING
OFF THE VAN BATTERY,
AND IT'LL PULL THE VAN
SLOWLY UP THE DRIVEWAY,
WHISPER QUIET, EH, WITHOUT
HAVING TO PUT THE
HEADLIGHTS ON.
SO SWEET DREAMS.
[ METAL CREAKING ]
OH, MAN,
THE EMERGENCY BRAKE.
[ METAL SCRAPING ]
BOY, IT'S GETTING PRETTY
DESPERATE AROUND HERE.
WE GOT NO FOOD.
WE GOT NO WATER.
AND WORST OF ALL,
WE GOT NO TV.
I MEAN, IT'S
STARTING TO GET UGLY.
UNCLE RED!
YOU KNOW WHAT WE CAN DO NOW?
KNOW WHAT WE CAN DO NOW?
NOW WE CAN PLAY, LIKE,
ANOTHER ROUND OF WHO AM I?
WHO AM I?
YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW
WHO YOU ARE, HAROLD.
I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
WHY DON'T YOU GO
HIDE SOMEWHERE?
I'LL COUNT TO 100
AND THEN HAVE A NAP.
[ KNOCKING ]
SOMEONE'S AT
THE DOOR!
WE'RE SAVED!
IT'S DALTON!
IT'S DALTON.
WE'RE SAVED!
OH, DALTON.
THANK YOU.
THEY WERE GOING
TO EAT ME.
HAROLD,
GET AWAY FROM ME.
RED, I TUNNELLED ALL THE WAY
OVER HERE FROM MY HOUSE.
JUST SO I COULD
BE AT THE LODGE.
YOU MEAN YOU DIDN'T
COME HERE TO SAVE US?
NO. NO.
I CAME HERE TO SAVE ME.
COME ON, NOW.
WE GOT NO FOOD.
WE GOT NO WATER.
WE GOT NO T.V.
WE'D BE WAY BETTER
OFF AT YOUR PLACE.
C'MON, HAROLD.
LET'S GO.
OKAY, RED, BUT YOU ARE
GOING TO BE THERE ALL ALONE
WITH MY WIFE ANN MARIE
AND MY DAUGHTER.
THEY'RE TRYING
ON DRESSES.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
SORRY, HAROLD.
YOU GO AHEAD --
I'M SORRY.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE SNOW PLOWS.
AND DON'T WORRY,
I KNOW HOW TO GET HOME.
I HAVE A LOT
OF FUN AT THE LODGE,
BUT NONE OF THESE GUYS
HAVE WHAT YOU GOT.
AND IF THEY EVER GET IT,
I'M QUITTING.
FOR THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
OH BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WE'VE GOT A
MEETING HAPPENING.
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
HERE HE COMES.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red:
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN,
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, WE HAVE
A PRETTY SERIOUS CHARGE
IN FRONT OF US
HERE TONIGHT.
HAROLD CLAIMS THAT
DURING OUR CURRENT
CRISIS,
MIKE ASSAULTED HIM.
OH, NO, NO.
NOT ASSAULTED.
SALTED.
HE SALTED ME.
OVER AND OVER.
I'M WELL MARBLED.