REMEMBER THESE THINGS, HUH?
THE PAPER SHEARER.
TEACHER USED TO GET ME TO
TRIM ALL HER TEST PAPERS
WHILE THE OTHER KIDS
LEARNED STUFF.
I ALWAYS TOOK
THAT AS A COMPLIMENT.
I DIDN'T REALIZE
SHE'D GIVEN UP ON ME.
BUT IF YOU EVER SEE
ONE OF THESE FOR SALE
AT MAYBE A YARD SALE OR ART
AUCTION OR ANYTHING,
YOU PICK IT UP,
AND I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
SOMEWHERE A MAN
IS GOING HUNGRY,
AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE HE
FINDS HIMSELF ALONE IN
A STRANGE PLACE...
THE KITCHEN.
AND IN HIS CONFUSION,
HE CAN'T SEPARATE
THE PRECIOUS,
LIFE-GIVING HOT DOG
FROM ITS FROZEN BROTHERS.
WELL, NO MORE.
AND FOR DESSERT.
[cheers and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE THAT.
THANK YOU.
WELL, BIG NEWS AT THE
LODGE THIS WEEK.
ACTUALLY, POSSUM LODGE
HAS BEEN SINGLED OUT
FOR RECOGNITION BY
THE LOCAL TOWN COUNSEL.
APPARENTLY WE ARE THE NUMBER
ONE SOURCE OF AIR POLLUTION
IN THE ENTIRE
POSSUM LAKE AREA.
AND THEY GOT THE SATELLITE
PICTURES TO PROVE IT.
WE'RE NUMBER ONE.
UNCLE RED.
I GOT A SOLUTION TO
THE POLLUTION PROBLEM.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF
THE KYOTO PROTOCOL?
IS THAT LIKE
THE HONDA ACCORD?
NO, NO, THE KYOTO PROTOCOL
IS AN INTERNATIONAL
AGREEMENT
TO CUT GREENHOUSE
GAS EMISSIONS.
WHY WOULD I CARE, HAROLD?
I DON'T HAVE A GREENHOUSE.
GREENHOUSE GAS EMISSIONS.
THEY'RE CREATED BY
BURNING FOSSIL FUELS.
YOU KNOW, LIKE LAWN MOWERS
AND OUTBOARD MOTORS
AND LEAF BLOWERS
AND SNOW BLOWERS
AND POSSUM VANS.
ANYTHING THAT BURNS GAS.
I'M NOT SHUTTING OFF
THE POSSUM VAN
WHEN IT TAKES ME 45
MINUTES TO GET
IT STARTED.
YEAH, I KNOW,
BUT HERE'S THE GOOD PART.
WITH THE KYOTO AGREEMENT,
YOU'RE ALLOWED TO TRADE OFF.
SO WHAT YOU DO, IF YOU HAVE
A LOT OF POLLUTION
IN ONE AREA,
YOU CAN BALANCE THAT
BY CUTTING POLLUTION
IN ANOTHER AREA.
AND NEXT TO THE LODGE,
YOU KNOW WHO THE BIGGEST
POLLUTER IS?
GOT TO BE
STINKY PETERSON.
NO. NO. NO,
IT'S NOT.
IT'S THAT COAL BURNING
ELECTRICAL GENERATING
STATION
UP AT PORT ASBESTOS.
SO YOU KNOW HOW WE'RE
GOING TO SATISFY THE
KYOTO PROTOCOL?
WE PLEAD INSANITY?
NO! NO! WE'RE GOING
TO MAKE A WINDMILL.
WE'RE GOING TO GENERATE
OUR OWN POWER.
AND IF WE BUILD
IT BIG ENOUGH,
WE CAN GENERATE ENOUGH
POWER FOR THE WHOLE TOWN.
YOU MEAN TO SAY WE'D
GET FREE POWER
AND BE ABLE TO SELL POWER
TO THE REST OF THE TOWN
AND BE ABLE TO MAKE
SOMETHING HUGE
AND DANGEROUS
ALL AT
THE SAME TIME?
YEAH!
WELL, I THINK YOU'VE
REALLY DONE IT THIS
TIME, HAROLD.
WELL, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
YOU MAY TURN INTO
A MAN YET.
DON'T SPOIL IT.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
TONIGHT'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FOR TWO TICKETS
TO THE POSSUM LAKE
LITTLE THEATRE PRODUCTION OF
"THE BEST LITTLE
WAREHOUSE IN TEXAS."
IT'S THE STORY OF A WOMAN
AND HER RISE TO THE TOP,
AND THE FORKLIFT OPERATOR
WHO TRIED TO PUT HER THERE.
ALL RIGHT, COVER
YOUR EARS, ED.
OKAY, RED, YOU'VE GOT
30 SECONDS
TO GET ED FRID TO SAY
THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, ED,
IF YOU GET A CALL
TO CAPTURE A FEROCIOUS
BEAR THAT'S ON THE LOOSE
THE FIRST THING YOU
HAVE TO DO IS...
GIVE IT A REALLY
BIG HEAD START.
NO. OKAY.
NO. NO. NO. NO.
THIS IS A WORD
THAT STANDS FOR
WHAT THE BEAR LEAVES
BEHIND ON THE GROUND.
I'M NOT SAYING THAT
WORD ON TELEVISION.
ED, I'M TALKING
ABOUT THE PAWS.
OH, LONG.
YEAH, THE BEAR TAKES
QUITE A LONG PAUSE
TO MAKE A
PILE THAT BIG.
NO. NO. NO.
ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
HERE, RED.
OKAY, ED, THINK
TRAIN --
ATTACK.
WHAT?
MOST PEOPLE TRAIN
THEIR DOGS TO ATTACK.
TO ATTACK
ME.
AT LEAST THAT'S BEEN
MY TRACK RECORD.
THERE WE GO.
[quirky upbeat music]
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THIS IS WHERE WE ADDRESS THE
THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S TRUE,
ISN'T IT?
OKAY, TODAY'S LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS --"
♪ LA-LA-LA-LA!
"LATELY, MY TEENAGE SON
HAS BEEN HANGING OUT
AT THE MALL,
"SMOKING CIGARETTES
AND SLACKING OFF.
"MY HUSBAND WON'T
DISCIPLINE HIM
"BECAUSE HE DOES
EXACTLY THE SAME THING.
"IS THERE SOME WAY I CAN
ECOURAGE MY SON TO BE
A BETTER PERSON?"
WELL, YOU KNOW, TEENAGERS ARE
KIND OF LIKE FIRECRACKERS.
YOUR BEST BET IS TO STAND WAY
BACK AND COVER YOUR EYES.
NO, NO, NO, THAT'S
JUST IGNORING YOUR
RESPONSIBILITIES.
YES, IT IS.
UNCLE RED, YOU CAN'T
JUST STOP BEING A PARENT.
YOU KNOW, I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO AGREE WITH
HAROLD ON THIS POINT,
AND, AS YOU KNOW, IT
HURTS ME DEEPLY
TO SAY THAT.
YOU HAVE TO INVOLVE YOUR
PARENTS IF YOU'RE
A TEENAGER.
LIKE I REMEMBER,
WHEN I WAS A TEENAGER,
IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN SO GREAT
TO BE ABLE TO TALK
TO ANY ONE OF MY DADS.
YES. YES, MIKE IS
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP OPEN
THE LINES OF COMMUNICATION.
YES, AND YOU HAVE
TO BE VERY AWARE
OF WHO YOUR SON IS
HANGING OUT WITH,
ESPECIALLY HIS GIRLFRIEND.
OH, YOU NEVER HAD THAT
PROBLEM, DID YOU, HAROLD?
MY GIRLFRIENDS WERE
A BAD INFLUENCE ON ME.
I MEAN, MY LIFE WOULD
HAVE BEEN TOTALLY
DIFFERENT
IF I'D DATED NUNS.
SO WOULD THEIRS,
I'M THINKING.
YOU KNOW, I THINK PARENTS
HAVE MORE INFLUENCE
OVER THEIR KIDS
THAN THEY THINK,
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE IF
PARENTS RESPECTED THEIR KIDS
THEN THE KIDS WOULDN'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO REBEL AGAINST,
OR THEY WOULDN'T BE HANGING
OUT WITH THE WRONG CROWD.
YEAH, YOU SEE,
MY LIFE WENT DOWNHILL
BECAUSE I HUNG OUT WITH THE
WRONG CROWD WHEN I
WAS A TEENAGER.
AND THEN LATER
WHEN I WENT TO PRISON,
MY SOCIAL CIRCLE CONTINUED
TO BE UNINSPIRING.
REALLY?
BUT THAT'S MY POINT.
THAT'S MY POINT, THOUGH.
SEE, NOBODY EVER
GETS ANYWHERE
BY HANGING OUT WITH A
BUNCH OF LOSERS.
OH, YEAH?
IT GOT ME A TELEVISION SHOW.
LET ME SHOW YOU WHAT HAPPENED
TO ME THE OTHER NIGHT.
BATTERIES WENT DEAD
IN MY TV REMOTE.
THAT HAPPENS
TO ME A LOT,
ESPECIALLY DURING
THE PLAYOFFS.
BUT WHEN I POPPED
OUT ONE OF THE BATTERIES,
IT FLEW THROUGH THE AIR --
AGAIN, THIS IS JUST
A RE-ENACTMENT --
AND DROPPED RIGHT INTO
A CAN OF ROOT BEER
THAT I WAS FORCING
MYSELF TO DRINK
BECAUSE THERE'S NOTHING
ELSE IN THE FRIDGE.
BUT IMAGINE MY SURPRISE
AT WHAT HAPPENED NEXT.
AND WHEN I TOUCHED THE CAN,
I GOT A SHOCK.
YES, VERY SIMILAR TO WHAT
JUST HAPPENED IN OUR
RE-ENACTMENT.
SO THEN I THOUGHT, HEY,
WHY DON'T I HOOK UP
MY TEST LIGHT
AND SEE WHAT
HAPPENS, HUH?
[light buzzing]
WELL, NOW I STARTED TO
GET PRETTY EXCITED --
ESPECIALLY AFTER THE FEELING
CAME BACK INTO MY HAND,
BECAUSE I FIGURE I HAVE A
SOURCE OF PRETTY CHEAP ENERGY.
AND ALL I NEED IS A
BUNCH OF DEAD BATTERIES.
I LOOKED THE WHOLE THING UP IN
THE ENCYCLOPEDIA IDIOTICA,
AND WHAT HAD HAPPENED WAS
THE ACID FROM THE POP
WAS ACTING AS
AN ELECTROLYTE,
AND THAT WAS DISSOLVING THE
CHEMICALS IN THE BATTERY,
GENERATING AN
ELECTRICAL CHARGE.
SO TODAY
ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO USE
THIS NEW KNOWLEDGE --
IT'S ACCIDENTAL
KNOWLEDGE, REALLY,
AS MOST OF MINE IS --
TO MAKE MYSELF AN
ENVIRONMENTALLY FRIENDLY
ELECTRIC TRUCK.
OKAY, MY FIRST STEP WAS TO
INSTALL A KIDDIE POOL,
SLIDE AND ALL,
INTO THE BED
OF MY PICKUP.
I GOT HER FILLED
UP WITH WATER.
NOW ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS ADD THE ACID.
I'M GOING TO GO
WITH VINEGAR --
OR AS WE CALL
IT AROUND HERE,
BUSTER HADFIELD'S
HOME-MADE WINE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, THAT'S NOT
GOING TO GIVE US ENOUGH JUICE,
SO I'M GOING TO THROW
IN A LITTLE CAUSTIC SODA.
THAT'S DRAIN CLEANER
TO YOU AND ME,
TAX WRITE-OFF TO WINSTON.
SO HE'LL NEVER MISS THIS.
[choking and coughing]
OKAY, I TOOK THE MOTOR OUT OF
BERNICE'S WASHING MACHINE.
USE THAT AS MY
POWER PLANT.
LUCKILY, THE ORIGINAL GAS
ENGINE HAD DROPPED OUT,
WHEN I SLAMMED OVER THE
SPEED BUMP OUTSIDE THE
SENIOR'S HOME.
SO ONE OF THESE CABLES
BECOMES MY GROUND WIRE,
AND THE OTHER ONE, HERE,
THAT'S MY LIVE WIRE.
NOW, FOR MY SPEED CONTROL,
I WIRED THE MOTOR
INTO THIS DIMMER SWITCH
OFF THE DINING ROOM
CHANDELIER.
THIS IS THE FUTURE YOU'RE
LOOKING AT RIGHT HERE, FOLKS.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT
LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
[applause]
[quirky upbeat music]
YOU KNOW, WHENEVER YOU
SEE A MARRIED COUPLE
TELLING A STORY TOGETHER
TO A THIRD PARTY,
THERE'S GOING
TO BE TROUBLE.
NOW, THE ONE PERSON WHO'S
TELLING THE STORY --
USUALLY THE WIFE,
SHE KIND OF BECOMES
LIKE THE PROSECUTOR.
AND THE ONE WHO THE
STORY'S ABOUT --
ALWAYS THE HUSBAND,
WELL, NOW, HE BECOMES KIND OF
LIKE THE DEFENCE ATTORNEY.
AND THE LISTENER -- USUALLY A
FRIEND OR A NEIGHBOUR,
WELL, THAT PERSON BECOMES
THE JUDGE AND THE JURY.
AND THESE TRIALS
HAVE NO RULES.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PRESENT
EVIDENCE OR PROVIDE WITNESSES
OR EVEN TELL THE TRUTH.
I MEAN, THE TWO FAKE
LAWYERS, THEY --
FIRST OF ALL, THEY START
WITH THEIR SUMMATIONS,
AND THEN THEY JUST KIND OF
INTERRUPT EACH OTHER
WHENEVER THEY WANT,
TRYING TO GET THE JUDGE
TO SEE IF THEIR WAY.
AND THE POOR JUDGE'S GOT NO
HARD EVIDENCE TO GO ON,
SO THEY JUST END UP SIDING
WITH WHO EVER THEY
LIKE BETTER.
AND THE FRIENDSHIP
GOES OUT THE --
SO, I TELL YOU WHAT,
WHENEVER YOU AND YOUR WIFE
HAVE A STORY TO TELL,
NEVER TELL IT TOGETHER.
LET HER TELL IT HER WAY
TO HER FRIENDS.
AND YOU TELL IF YOUR WAY
TO YOUR FRIENDS.
NEITHER ONE OF YOU IS
TELLING THE STORY
THE WAY IT ACTUALLY
HAPPENED ANYWAY,
SO IT DOESN'T
REALLY MATTER.
AND IF YOU EVER GET INTO A
SITUATION WHERE BY ACCIDENT
YOU END UP TELLING THE
STORY TOGETHER TO SOMEBODY,
ASK FOR A RECESS,
TAKE YOUR WIFE ASIDE,
SETTLE OUT OF COURT.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
WHEN THE AIR AROUND YOUR
PLACE IS SO GREEN IT GLOWS,
AND YOUR ONCE FRIENDLY
NEIGHBOURS HAVE ALL
BECOME FOES,
CALL ME AND I'LL BE THERE,
QUICK WITH MY HOSE.
NO NEED FOR DIRECTIONS,
I'LL JUST FOLLOW MY NOSE.
WELL, WE GOT OUR WINDMILL
UP AND RUNNING.
AND MOST OF POSSUM LAKE
IS USING OUR POWER.
GOOD THING WE HAD
ALL THOSE JUMPER CABLES.
OF COURSE, WHEN YOU SWITCH
FROM COAL TO WIND POWER,
YOU KNOW, YOU GET
THE ODD DIP.
THERE'S NOT MUCH OF
BREEZE TODAY, UNCLE RED.
HAROLD, JUST
RELAX, EH?
NOBODY CAN PUSH US
AROUND ANY MORE.
WANT TO KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE WE'RE THE
ELECTRIC COMPANY NOW.
WE GOT POWER.
WE GOT PROBLEMS.
[phones rings]
HOW COME THE
PHONE STILL WORKS?
BECAUSE WE'RE NOT
THE PHONE COMPANY.
HELLO, POSSUM LODGE
POWER COMPANY.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YA?
YEAH, OKAY, DID YOU CHECK
THE FUSE BOX?
WELL, MAYBE YOU'D THINK
ABOUT CHECKING THAT
BEFORE YOU JUST AUTOMATICALLY
BLAME THE POWER COMPANY.
YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU HAVE ONE TOO.
BYE.
[phone rings]
[as recorded message]
YOU HAVE REACHED THE POSSUM
LODGE POWER COMPANY.
FOR SERVICE IN ENGLISH,
PLEASE HANG UP.
[laughter and applause]
YEAH?
RED!
THE POWER'S BEEN OUT IN
MY STORE FOR FOUR HOURS!
TRAFFIC LIGHTS ARE OUT.
MY CASH REGISTER
STOPPED WORKING.
MOOSE THOMPSON'S STUCK
ON THE ESCALATOR.
YOU CAN'T GET STUCK
ON AN ESCALATOR.
YOU JUST
WALK DOWN.
NOT WHEN YOU'RE
MOOSE THOMPSON.
HE'S GOT HIS BUTT WEDGED
BETWEEN THE HANDRAILS.
PLUS, MY FREEZER'S OFF,
SO ALL THE ICE CREAM'S MELTED.
I'M GIVING IT AWAY.
OH, WOW!
EXCELLENT!
I'M GIVING IT AWAY
AT 10% OFF.
I OWE YA.
YOU KNOW WHAT
THE PROBLEM IS?
IT'S NOT
THE WINDMILL,
BECAUSE THE MILL
PART WORKS FINE,
AS LONG AS THE
WIND IS GOING.
SEE, THE PROBLEM IS,
AS SOON AS THE
WIND DIES OFF,
WE GOT NO POWER.
TAKE IT EASY ON THE
ICE CREAM THERE,
HAROLD.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET
YOURSELF A BRAIN FREEZE.
NO, IT'S GOOD.
I LIKE ICE CREAM.
ICE CREAM IS GOOD.
I'VE GOT SOME ICE CREAM,
AND IT'S GOOD, SO I'M
EATING IT.
HEY, I JUST
GOT AN ID ---
IS YOUR CAR HERE,
DALTON?
NO, I WALKED.
THAT WAS CLOSE.
I THOUGHT YOU DID.
OKAY, HERE'S
WHAT WE DO...
WE HOOK UP YOUR CAR
AND MY POSSUM VAN
AND ANY OTHER
VEHICLES WE CAN FIND,
WE HOOK THE DRIVE WHEELS
ONTO THE WINDMILL
AND WE GET HER
SPINNING THAT WAY.
THAT'S THE WAY WE
GENERATE THE POWER.
IS THAT GOOD?
ALL IN FAVOUR SAY AYE.
AYE.
[exclaiming in pain]
Red [voiceover]:
WE DON'T HAVE A CASINO
IN THE POSSUM LAKE AREA,
SO SOMETIMES WE JUST COOK UP
A GAME OF BINGO OURSELVES.
AND I THOUGHT THE THREE
OF THEM WERE ALL PLAYING,
BUT IT WAS ACTUALLY
JUST WALTER AND MIKE,
BECAUSE DALTON WAS --
HE HAD A CROSSWORD.
I DIDN'T REALIZE IT WAS
A CROSSWORD PUZZLE
HE HAD GOING.
I WAS OFFERING
A PRETTY FANCY PRIZE...
A FISHING VEST
WITH EVERYTHING YOU'D
EVER WANT ON IT.
AND THE BOYS ARE PRETTY
EXCITED OVER THAT.
AND WE HAD TO MAKE
EVERYTHING OURSELVES.
WE HAD A LEAF BLOWER
BLOWING THE --
WE GOT PING-PONG BALLS.
ANYWAY, THE NUMBER
COMES DOWN,
AND IT'S G-53.
I JUST MARK HER
ON THE BOARD,
AND THE BOYS
CHECK THEIR CARDS --
WELL, WALTER AND MIKE
CHECK THEIR CARDS.
DALTON'S STILL WORKING
ON THE CROSSWORD.
I GOT ANOTHER
ONE HERE, B-12.
AND MARK THAT UP ON THE --
IT'S LIKE A
VITAMIN, THAT ONE.
AND THEN MIKE DOESN'T
HAVE ONE, SO HE SEES --
SO HE'S GONNA SNEAK --
AND WALTER --
THEN BANG!
SO NOW OF COURSE THE BINGO
BALLS ARE EVERYWHERE.
SO I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
YOU GUYS GO FIND THE BALLS,
AND THEN ANY
BALL YOU FIND,
I'LL REGISTER THE NUMBER,
AND IF YOU GOT THAT NUMBER,
THEN YOU -- SO WE CAN
CARRY ON WITH OUR GAME.
THAT WAY I DIDN'T
HAVE TO DO ANYTHING.
SO MIKE'S OUT THERE LOOKING,
AND HE SEES A BINGO BALL.
AND HE PICKS IT UP,
AND HE'S ALL EXCITED,
UNTIL HE REALIZES
THAT IT'S NOT A NUMBER
THAT HE HAS ON ANY
OF HIS BINGO CARDS.
BUT THEN HE REMEMBERS
HE DOES HAVE SOMETHING...
A MARKER.
SO I-30 SUDDENLY
BECOMES N-38.
SO I MARK THAT
DOWN ON THE CHART.
AND THEN WALTER'S
CARRYING ON THERE.
AND HE SEES A BALL,
AND HE PICKS IT UP,
BUT THERE ARE NO --
FOR SOME REASON,
THE NUMBERS MUST
HAVE COME OFF --
I DON'T KNOW WHY
THERE WOULD BE NO --
OH, YEAH, I SEE.
RIGHT.
AND DALTON'S STILL WORKING
ON THE CROSSWORD.
MEANWHILE, THERE WERE A
COUPLE OF BALLS STILL
FLYING ALONG,
AND THEY ROLLED
DOWN A HOLE.
AND MIKE'S HOT
ON THE TRAIL.
HE'S ALL EXCITED.
THEN HE'S SOMEWHAT
LESS EXCITED.
THAT CAN HAPPEN.
AND WALTER SAW
ANOTHER BALL,
KIND OF MUD ALL OVER IT.
AND THEN IT TURNS OUT IT
WASN'T ACTUALLY A BALL.
IT WAS THE TIP
OF SOMETHING.
SOME TYPE OF SIGN.
"DANGER QUICKSAND."
THAT'S NOT A
GOOD SIGN.
ANYWAY, WE GOT WALTER
OUT OF THERE.
GOT HIM BACK TO THE TABLE.
AND I WAS JUST RECOUNTING
ON ALL THE NUMBERS,
GOING THROUGH THEM ALL.
AND THEY WERE JUST
CHECKING THEM ALL OFF,
BUT NOBODY WAS
GETTING A WINNER.
MEANWHILE, AS I SAY,
DALTON WAS LOOKING FOR
A FIVE-LETTER WORD
FOR VICTORY.
HE'S RUNNING IT
OVER IN HIS MIND,
AND THEN HE COMES
UP WITH IT...
B-I-N-G-
AND HE YELLS OUT, BINGO!
AND OF COURSE, THESE GUYS
JUST RIP UP THEIR CARDS.
THEY FIGURE THEY'VE LOST.
THEY CRUNCH THEM ALL UP
AND WALK AWAY IN DISGUST.
AND THEN DALTON COMES
OVER TO SHOW ME.
HE WAS ACTUALLY
DOING A CROSSWORD,
SO WHAT I SAY TO HIM IS,
PLEASE, HELP ME ON
WITH MY PRIZE.
[applause]
[quirky upbeat music]
YOU KNOW, MY WIFE'S REAL
GOOD ABOUT LETTING ME
HAVE A FEW BUDDIES OVER TO
WATCH THE FOOTBALL GAME
OR GO FOR THE INDOOR PIZZA
EATING RECORD OR WHATEVER.
SHE ONLY ASKS THAT I
GET THEM TO USE COASTERS.
AND BELIEVE ME,
THESE ARE GUYS
WHO CAN'T AFFORD ANOTHER
STRIKE AGAINST THEM.
SO I TRIED USING SOME
OF THESE THICK COASTERS,
JUST SPREADING
THEM AROUND THE TABLE
IN KIND OF A RANDOM ORDER.
THEN THE GUYS KIND OF GET
THEIR GLASS HALF ON, HALF OFF.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW YOU'VE
GOT A TIDAL WAVE OF BEER
COMING OFF THE COFFEE TABLE
AND INTOXICATING THE DOG.
THEN I TRIED A DEAL
WHERE I GLUED MY OLD
IRISH ROVERS ALBUMS
TO THE BOTTOM
OF A FEW GLASSES.
PROBLEM THERE WAS EVERY
TIME THE GUYS TOOK A DRINK,
THEY THOUGHT THEY
WERE GOING BLIND.
THEN I GOT THE IDEA OF
CUTTING THE LIDS OUT
OF TIN CANS,
BECAUSE THEY'RE NOT TOO BIG,
BUT THEY'RE NICE AND THIN.
BUT STILL, I NEEDED
A WAY TO MAKE SURE
THAT THEY'RE ALWAYS
UNDER THE GLASSES.
SO I GLUED A FRIDGE MAGNET
TO THE INSIDE OF THE BOTTOM.
IDIOT-PROOF --
OR EVEN BETTER,
IDIOT-READY.
OH, AND ONE MORE THING...
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE WHO
DON'T USE COASTERS
ARE THE SAME KIND OF PEOPLE
THAT TEND TO LEAVE STUFF LYING
AROUND WHEN THEY'RE GONE.
WELL, YOU KNOW
WHAT THEY SAY...
THE BEST IDEAS ARE THE ONES
THAT PAY FOR THEMSELVES.
OKAY, WE'RE ALMOST SET
TO FIRE UP OUR
MOTORIZED WINDMILL.
WE'VE GOT ABOUT SEVEN
VEHICLES POWERING THE UNIT.
WE HAD TO LAY A COUPLE OF
THE S.U.V.'S ON THEIR SIDES,
BUT THEY'RE USED TO THAT.
NOW, HAROLD INSISTED
THAT WE HOOK ALL THE ENGINES
UP TO THIS REMOTE STARTER.
THAT WAY NOBODY HAS TO
STAND TOO CLOSE,
WHICH SAVES YOU BEING CALLED
IN AS A WITNESS LATER.
WE GOOD TO GO
THERE, HAROLD?
HAROLD, ARE WE GOOD TO GO?
GOOD TO GO, UNCLE RED!
[multiple engines starting]
SHUT IT OFF!
HAROLD, IT'S FINE.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY FINE.
THIS IS HOW WE SHOULD HAVE
GENERATED THE POWER IN
THE FIRST PLACE.
WE DON'T NEED WIND.
WE DON'T NEED
STORAGE BATTERIES.
HEY, WE'RE COMPLETELY
SELF-SUFFICIENT,
AND WE'RE GETTING
POWER FOR FREE.
OH, ARE WE GETTING
GASOLINE FOR FREE TOO?
WELL, WHAT DOES GASOLINE
HAVE TO DO WITH IT?
[engines die]
WHY IS THERE
ALWAYS A CATCH?
WHAT?
HEY, RED! GOOD NEWS!
CITY HALL SAYS THAT WE GOT
THE BEST AIR QUALITY INDEX
IN 10 YEARS.
THE LODGE IS BACK
IN THE GOOD BOOKS!
HOW CAN THAT BE?
YOU'RE POLLUTING
MORE THAN EVER!
IT'S 'CAUSE OF
THE WINDMILL.
WE'VE BLOWN ALL OF
OUR POLLUTION UP TO
PORT ASBESTOS.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD,
YOU NEVER WANT TO BE
DOWNWIND OF
A BIG POLLUTER.
AND YOU'D KNOW THAT
IF YOU'D EVER GONE
ON A CANOE TRIP.
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME.
YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
[chuckling] OH, MAN.[applause]
ALL RIGHT,
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING HOME
STRAIGHT AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M OUT OF POWER AND
LOW ON GAS,
BUT I'M HOPING
YOU'LL WAIT UP
BECAUSE I'M LOOKING FOR A
SPARK OR TWO STILL LEFT
SOMEWHERE IN MY LIFE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheers and applause]
HAVE A SEAT. HAVE A SEAT.
MEETING'S COMING TO ORDER.
SIT DOWN. EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR
HEADS FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, I HAVE SOME
TERRIBLE NEWS FOR YOU.
I'M WASHING MY HANDS OF THE
WHOLE WINDMILL PROJECT THING.
WE'VE GONE BACK TO PAYING
FOR OUR ELECTRICITY.
[applause]