♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN
AND THIS TIME AROUND HAROLD'S
GOING TO PRETEND HE'S GOD,
BILL'S GOING TO LAUNCH A BOAT,
AND I'M BUILDING A KIDDIE RIDE
FOR THE BACKYARD.
(RIFLE SHOT FIRING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: AND NOW HERE'S
A MAN WHO'S BEEN CALLED ONE OF
CANADA'S NATIONAL TREASURES
YOUR HOST, MY UNCLE,
MR. RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU,
THANK YOU SO MUCH AND
HELLO TO HAROLD WHO IS ALSO
A NATIONAL TREASURE
AND IF I HAD MY WAY WOULD
BE BURIED BY PIRATES.
>>HAROLD: WELL UNTIL THAT TIME
LET'S JUST LET MY FINGERS
WALK THE PLANK.
NOTHING HAPPENED,
MY A.D.O. DIDN'T VIDEO
FLANGE THE IMAGE.
>>RED: NO AND YOUR DO-DING
JUST DIDN'T FLIP FLOP
THE THINGY THERE.
>>HAROLD: EXACTLY, YEAH,
WELL YES, MY SKEW IS OFF.
>>RED: HMM, YOU KNOW THERE'S
SOMETHING THAT I DO TO OUR
TV AT HOME, WHERE'S THE
HORIZONTAL HOLD ON THIS THING?
>>HAROLD: WELL IT'S THAT
ONE RIGHT THERE.
>>RED: THERE?
>>HAROLD: MMM.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT
JUST HOLD STILL.
IT USUALLY WORKS AT HOME,
MIND YOU WE HAVE THE BETA.
INTERESTING WEEK UP AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK,
ALL THE POWER WENT OFF DURING
A BIG THUNDERSTORM SO THE GUYS
ALL WENT OUT AND GATHERED
UP FIREWOOD, SO THAT WE COULD
KEEP WARM AND THEN WHEN THE
POWER CAME BACK ON,
WELL IT DIDN'T YOU KNOW,
SO WHAT HAD HAPPENED WAS
JUNIOR SINGLETON HAD CUT DOWN
A POWER LINE POLE TO USE
AS FIREWOOD, SO NOW WE'RE
THINKING WHAT ELSE CAN WE USE
FOR ELECTRICITY AROUND HERE?
AND WE STARTED THINKING
ABOUT POSSUM LAKE.
NOW POSSUM LAKE'S GOT SO MUCH
ACID IN IT AND IT'S GOT LEAD,
CADMIUM AND ZINC,
YOU KNOW IN A CERTAIN WAY
THE LAKE IS LIKE A BIG BATTERY,
SO WE GOT THINKING AND DRINKING
AND OUT WE COME WITH ALL
OUR JUMPER CABLES,
WE HOOKED UP ALL THE
JUMPER CABLES TO THE CAR
BATTERIES AS WE TRIED TO
JUMPSTART POSSUM LAKE.
NOW UNFORTUNATELY SOMEBODY HAD
REVERSED THE POLARITY ON THEIR
CABLES AND SOMETHING REAL
STRANGE HAPPENED AND WE ENDED
UP MAGNETIZING THE WHOLE LAKE.
WOW YOUR VIDEO EFFECTS HAVE
JUST ARRIVED HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: WHAT THE?
THAT'S LIKE 40 SECONDS LATE,
WHOA HO, HO, HO, HO, WOO!
>>RED: DO YOU KNOW WHAT,
IT MIGHT HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH POSSUM LAKE,
THERE'S A MAGNETIC FIELD
AROUND HERE NOW,
LIKE EVERYBODY'S WATCH
IS RUNNING BACKWARDS.
>>HAROLD: IT'S LIKE AN
EPISODE OF THE TWILIGHT ZONE,
♪ HUMMING TWILIGHT ZONE SONG ♪
>>RED: YEAH OR BEWITCHED.
♪ HUMMING BEWITCHED THEME SONG ♪
>>RED: OH NEVER MIND HAROLD!
ANYWAY WE'RE ALL WORKING HARD
TO DEMAGNETIZE THE LAKE BECAUSE
EVERYBODY'S BELT BUCKLE IS
POINTING NORTH AND IT'S REAL
HARD TO WALK INTO TOWN.
BUT HOPEFULLY NONE OF THIS WILL
GET IN THE WAY OF A REAL
ATTRACTIVE SHOW WE HAVE
FOR YOU TONIGHT,
SO JUST BEAR WITH US AND
PLEASE DON'T ADJUST YOUR SET.
>>HAROLD: ESPECIALLY YOUR
CHANNEL KNOB.
>>RED: TAKE US AWAY HAROLD.
OH BOY...
I ALWAYS WANTED TO DIRECT.
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ WHEN A MAN CAN LIVE ALONE ♪
♪ IN THE WOODS ♪
♪ WITH ONLY HIS WITS ♪
♪ AND A BIG KNIFE ♪
♪ OR EQUIVALENT ♪
♪ WITHOUT THE COMFORT ♪
♪ OF A HOME ♪
♪ OR A JOB OR A FRIEND ♪
♪ BOY THAT'S REALLY SOMETHING ♪
♪ IF HE CAN LIVE THERE ♪
♪ WITHOUT COMING TO AN END ♪
♪ IT FILLS HIS HEART ♪
♪ WITH SO MUCH PRIDE ♪
♪ IT'S NOT EXACTLY ENJOYABLE ♪
♪ BUT IT'S A LOT LESS ♪
♪ HUMILIATING THAN TRYING ♪
♪ TO BORROW MONEY ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' I THOUGHT
I'D SHOW YOU HOW TO
MAKE YOUR OWN AMUSEMENT PARK.
NOW I GOT THIS IDEA FROM
HAROLD AND HIS TEENAGE BUDDIES,
THEY GO DOWN TO THE PINE CONE
FESTIVAL THERE AND THEY PAY
$3 BUCKS EACH FOR THE PRIVILEGE
OF RIDING AROUND ON ONE OF
THEM THINGS WHERE THEY SPIN
IN A CIRCLE FOR 40 SECONDS
AND THEN THEY BARF UP THEIR
SLUSH PUPPY AND THEIR
CHEESE DOG.
AND I THOUGHT TO MYSELF,
GOLLY THERE'S GOT TO BE A
CHEAPER WAY TO HAVE THAT
KIND OF FUN, SO TODAY I'M
GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW TO
MAKE YOUR VERY OWN
BACKYARD KIDDIE RIDE.
NOW THE FIRST THING YOU'RE
GOING TO NEED IS ONE OF
THEM OLD-FASHION CLOTHESLINES,
I WAS LUCKY ENOUGH TO FIND
THIS ONE JUST STICKING OUT
OF THE GROUND BEHIND
SOMEBODY'S HOUSE.
NOW THE FIRST THING YOU NEED
TO DO IS GET YOURSELF A PIECE
OF PIPE, I GOT AN ALUMINUM PIPE
HERE AND YOU JUST SET THAT
WHERE YOU WANT THE RIDE TO
START AND YOU JUST TAP HER
INTO THE GROUND.
ALL RIGHT, YOU NEED ANOTHER
KIND OF PIPE, MAYBE SOMETHING
OTHER THAN ALUMINUM,
YEAH GO WITH YOUR STEEL ON THAT.
THE ALUMINUM IS NOT GOING
TO DO, BUT HERE WE'RE ALL
SET AND DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT USING A PIECE OF
EAVESTROUGH AND OF COURSE
THE PLASTIC DRAIN PIPE,
OUT OF THE QUESTION.
OKAY NOW STICK THIS INTO
OUR PIPE HERE AND WE'RE
ALMOST READY TO START CHARGING
$3 BUCKS A POP, BUT WE'RE GOING
TO NEED SOMETHING TO HANG ON
HERE FOR THE LITTLE KIDDIES
TO SIT IN.
WELL FOR STARTERS HOW
ABOUT A BUCKET SEAT?
OR THESE OLD MILK CARTONS CAN BE
TURNED INTO SEATS AND YOU CAN
GET THESE FOR FREE BEHIND
ONE OF THEM VARIETY STORES
IF THEY'RE CLOSED.
AND OF COURSE YOU KNOW WHEN
I WAS GROWING UP WE ALWAYS
USED TIRES, SO WHY NOT USE
A TIRE AS ONE OF YOUR SEATS
AND THAT'S 3 OF THE 4 CORNERS.
AND FOR THE FOURTH CORNER
SOMETHING A LITTLE INTERESTING,
GET YOURSELF AN OLD POTTY
SEAT AND HOOK THAT ON,
IT MIGHT ACT TO BE KIND
OF DANGEROUS ON A WINDY DAY.
ALL RIGHT I'VE USED THESE
STUFFED ANIMALS TO REPRESENT
KIDS, CRASH TEST TEDDIES
I CALL THEM...
I GOT THEM OFF OF MOOSE'S BED.
BUT OF COURSE NOW WE NEED
SOME SORT OF A POWER TO
DRIVE THIS UNIT.
NOW YOU COULD USE SAY AN
OLD ELECTRIC DRILL OR MAYBE
A LAWNMOWER OR SOMETHING,
OR YOU COULD TAKE SOME BED
SHEETS AND MAKE A WIND POWER
UNIT, BUT WHAT I'VE DONE IS
I'VE ATTACHED A PLASTIC
COVERED WIRE, A CLOTHES WIRE
TYPE THING HERE AND COILED IT
ALL AROUND THE SHAFT AND THEN
HOOKED IT RIGHT UP TO THE
BACK OF THE POSSUM VAN,
IF YOU DIDN'T HAVE A POSSUM VAN
YOU COULD HOOK IT UP TO THE
BACK OF YOUR CAR OR WHATEVER,
AND THE IDEA BEING OF COURSE
WHEN YOU DRIVE AWAY IT TENDS
TO SPIN THIS AND WHAT YOU COULD
DO HERE IS THE FIRST THING IN
THE MORNING YOU POP YOUR KIDS
INTO THEIR RIDE AND THEN YOU
JUST FIRE OFF TO WORK AND THEN
PROBABLY BY THE TIME YOU COME
HOME THEY'VE STOPPED SPINNING.
SO JUST BEFORE I GIVE HER A TRY
I WANT YOU TO REMEMBER UNTIL
NEXT TIME OF COURSE,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY,
ALL RIGHT THE MIDWAY IS OPEN.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>HAROLD: THIS IS THE PART OF
THE SHOW WHERE WE EXPOSE THE
3 LITTLE WORDS THAT MEN FIND
SO DIFFICULT TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW.'
SO HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT IS
MY UNCLE RED AND OF COURSE
HIS BESTEST, MOST BEST FRIEND,
MR BOB STUYVESTANT.
ALL RIGHTY, HERE WE GO,
'DEAR EXPERTS, MY NEPHEW
IS COMING TO STAY WITH
ME FOR THE SUMMER.'
>>RED: WELL YOU CERTAINLY HAVE
MY SYMPATHY, GO AHEAD HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: 'AND I DON'T REALLY
HAVE A LOT OF HABITS OR
ACTIVITIES THAT WOULD INTEREST
A 10 YEAR OLD BOY,
DO YOU HAVE ANY SUGGESTIONS?'
>>BOB: I DON'T THINK I REALLY
UNDERSTAND THE QUESTION.
>>RED: ME NEITHER HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: WELL HIS NEPHEW,
HE'S COMING TO STAY AND HE WANTS
TO MAKE SURE THAT HE HAS FUN SO.
>>BOB: RIGHT.
>>HAROLD: WELL HE WANTS TO MAKE
SURE THAT THE BOY HAS FUN IN
THE SUMMER WHEN HE'S THERE.
>>RED: WHY?
>>BOB: WELL I MEAN COME ON
THERE'S PROBABLY HUNDREDS OF
THINGS THAT A YOUNG LAD CAN DO
TO HAVE FUN IN THE SUMMER,
I MEAN LET'S SEE THERE'S,
WELL, WELL THERE'S GOLF,
GOLF IS GREAT FUN.
>>HAROLD: WELL HE'S 10,
HE MIGHT BE A BIT
SMALL FOR GOLF.
>>BOB: OKAY, MINI GOLF.
>>HAROLD: OKAY, WELL ARE
THERE ANY OTHER IDEAS?
>>BOB: WELL SURE, I MEAN THERE
MUST BE LOTS OF THINGS YOU CAN
DO WITH A KID AREN'T THERE RED?
>>RED: OH YEAH, YEAH.
>>HAROLD: COULD WE BE
A LITTLE MORE SPECIFIC?
>>BOB: YOU KNOW MY SISTER
WHEN SHE USED TO COME AT
CHRISTMAS AND BRING THE KIDS,
I USE TO PLAY THIS LITTLE
GAME WITH THEM CALLED 'ADAPT'
AND THAT WORKED OUT
PRETTY WELL.
>>HAROLD: 'ADAPT' OH, OKAY,
HOW DOES THAT WORK?
>>BOB: WELL IT'S EASY REALLY,
THE ADULTS, THEY DO ABSOLUTELY
ANYTHING THEY WANT AND THE
KIDS HAVE TO ADAPT,
SORT OF AN OLD-FASHION,
FAMILY TRADITION THING.
>>RED: SOUNDS LIKE AN
EDUCATIONAL GAME TOO HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: I'M GUESSING YOU
DON'T HAVE ANYBODY STAYING
WITH YOU THIS SUMMER?
>>BOB: NO,
SO FAR IT'S WORKING GREAT.
>>RED: IT IS WINTER,
WHEN I WAS YOUNG WE NEVER
HAD FIGHTS IN HOCKEY,
BUT WE ALSO NEVER HAD HELMETS
OR PROTECTIVE PADS OR SHIELDS
ON OUR SKATE BLADES OR
SMOOTH ICE, WE USED BROKEN,
SPLINTERED STICKS AND A BRICK
FOR A PUCK AND BIG, HARD ROCKS
FOR THE POSTS BUT WE NEVER HAD
FIGHTS, WE DIDN'T NEED FIGHTS.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: HAP, HAP IS THAT YOU?
>>HAP: OH HI RED,
DO YOU LIKE MY OUTFIT?
>>RED: YEAH IT'S SHINY.
>>HAP: YEAH, IT BRINGS BACK
MEMORIES OF MY DAYS AS
AN ASTRONAUT, ONE SMALL STEP
FOR NEIL ARMSTRONG,
A PIECE OF CAKE FOR ME.
>>RED: ASTRONAUT RIGHT.
WELL I SUPPOSE IF IT STOPS THE
MAGNETISM FROM BOTHERING YOU.
>>HAP: MAGNETISM, WHAT
MAGNETISM IS THAT RED?
>>RED: WELL HAP THE
WHOLE LAKE IS MAGNETIZED,
DIDN'T YOU HEAR ABOUT THAT?
>>HAP: OH BUSTER HATFIELD
MENTIONED SOMETHING ABOUT
THAT BUT YOU KNOW THAT GUY
AND HIS STORIES,
HE'S THE WORST LIAR I'VE
MET SINCE HOWARD HUGHES.
>>RED: YEAH, WELL HAP IF YOU
DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
THE MAGNETISM, WHAT'S THE
ALUMINUM FOIL FOR?
>>HAP: OH IT'S PART OF AN
EXPERIMENT I'M DOING ON TIME
TRAVEL BUT I CAN'T GO INTO
DETAILS ON THAT NOW.
>>RED: GOOD, GOOD.
NONE OF OUR OUTBOARD MOTORS ARE
WORKING BECAUSE OF THAT MAGNET
THING AND I'M THINKING YOU'VE
GOT THE DIESEL ENGINE HERE,
IF THIS THING MIGHT WORK YOU
COULD MAYBE GIVE ME
A RIDE INTO TOWN.
>>RED: SURE, LET ME
JUST GROUND THE BOAT,
WHERE'S MY BOAT HOOK?
(SIZZLE OF ELECTRIC SHOCK)
>>RED: YOU ALL RIGHT HAP?
>>HAP: YEAH I'M FINE,
YOU LEARN TO DEAL WITH PAIN
WHEN YOU'RE AN ASTRONAUT.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
>>HAP: NO, HUH.
WELL I BETTER TRY A LITTLE
TRICK THAT HEMINGWAY SHOWED ME.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
>>HAP: NO, SORRY RED,
THIS MAGNETIZING THING MUST OF
MESSED UP MY MOTOR OR I'M OUT
OF FUEL OR SOMEBODY HAS
SABOTAGED MY BOAT,
I MADE A LOT OF ENEMIES WHEN
I WORKED WITH THE C.I.A.
>>RED: WELL THANKS ANYWAY HAP
AND GOOD LUCK WITH THAT TIME
TRAVEL EXPERIMENT THING.
>>HAP: YEAH IF IT WORKS AND
I GO BACK IN TIME I'LL TRY TO
PREVENT THE LAKE FROM
GETTING MAGNETIZED.
YOU KNOW WITH TIME TRAVEL
I CAN CHANGE HISTORY
AND ALTER THE PAST.
>>RED: OH YOU DON'T NEED TIME
TRAVEL TO DO THAT HAP.
>>RED: BOY THAT MAGNETISM IN
POSSUM LAKE, MAN, IT'S REALLY
MESSING UP THE ELECTRONIC
EQUIPMENT AND ALL OF OUR
ZIPPERS AND EVERYTHING,
HAROLD TOUCH MY FINGER
WILL YOU?
>>HAROLD: NO WAY,
I KNOW THAT TRICK.
>>RED: NO HAROLD,
I JUST NEED YOU TO GROUND ME.
>>HAROLD: OH, OKAY, OH HERE,
I GOT SOME ANTI STATIC SPRAY
FOR MY SWITCHER, WE'LL USE THAT
IT'S GOOD STUFF.
(RED COUGHING)
>>RED: THANKS HAROLD AND
DON'T EVER DO THAT AGAIN.
>>HAROLD: IT'S OKAY UNCLE RED,
DO YOU THINK MAYBE WE SHOULD
LIKE MAYBE PHONE THE GOVERNMENT
OR MAYBE EVEN SOMEBODY
WHO KNOWS SOMETHING?
>>RED: NO WE CAN'T HAROLD,
THE PHONE LINES ARE HUMMING
WITH STATIC, YOU CAN'T EVEN
DRIVE INTO TOWN BECAUSE ALL THE
CARS ARE STUCK TO AN OLD FIRE
HYDRANT AND THAT WHOLE MESS IS
BEING CIRCLED BY SOME PRETTY
UNHAPPY DOGS I'LL TELL YOU.
>>HAROLD: DO YOU KNOW WHAT
UNCLE RED, MAYBE THIS IS
LIKE ALIENS OR SOMETHING,
THERE COULD BE ALIENS AND
THEY'RE PLANNING TO LAND
ON POSSUM LAKE.
>>RED: WELL HAROLD IF THEY
CAPTURE YOU MAKE IT CLEAR TO
THEM THAT YOU'RE NOT A NORMAL
EARTH PERSON OKAY,
THERE'S NO TELLING WHAT THEY'D
DO IF THEY THOUGHT WE WERE
ALL LIKE YOU.
OH NO HAROLD DON'T DO THAT,
I'M NOT FINISHED TALKING YET.
>>HAROLD: WELL I KNOW BUT IT
TAKES 40 SECONDS YOU KNOW
BECAUSE OF THE MAGNETISM SO.
>>RED: YEAH BUT I DON'T
LIKE A DEADLINE HAROLD,
WHAT DO I DO NOW?
>>HAROLD: JUST TALK FOR
40 SECONDS, WELL 30 BECAUSE
YOU AND I TALK, BUT TALK.
>>RED: YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
OKAY 30, OKAY, OKAY 30 SECONDS,
HELP ME OUT HERE HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OH WELL BECAUSE OF
THE MAGNETISM TELL THEM HOW
THE ALUMINUM BOAT IS STICKING
TO THE UNDERBELLY OF
THE DIVING BOARD.
>>RED: YEAH, ALL RIGHT, OKAY,
THE ALUMINUM BOAT YEAH, YEAH,
NO, NO, NO, I KNOW SEPTIC TANK,
SEPTIC, SEPTIC.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
>>RED: WE'VE GOT A STEEL
SEPTIC TANK, SHE'S GALVANIZED
ON THERE BUT SHE STARTED SHAKING
BACK AND FORTH LIKE THIS AND
OF COURSE THERE'S A SUNDAY
SCHOOL PICNIC ABOUT
50 YARDS AWAY.
♪ IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER ♪
♪ HOW OLD AND TIRED YOU GROW ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS WILL REMEMBER ♪
♪ THAT FIRST KISS ♪
♪ SO LONG AGO ♪
>>RED: WHO ARE YOU KIDDING?
♪ I GOT MY FIRST KISS ♪
♪ FROM MARY BROWN ♪
♪ IT WAS LOVELY, IT WAS SWEET ♪
♪ I OPENED MY LIPS ♪
♪ AND ATE IT ♪
♪ BECAUSE IT WAS A ♪
♪ HALLOWEEN TREAT ♪
♪ ONE OF THEM BROWN ONES ♪
♪ HAROLD WITH A BLACK ♪
♪ AND ORANGE WRAPPER ♪
♪ I TRIED TO PICK ♪
♪ THE BEST ONE ♪
♪ BECAUSE I FIGURED ♪
♪ IF I COULDN'T HANDLE ♪
♪ THE TREAT, A TRICK ♪
♪ WOULD BE OUT OF ♪
♪ THE QUESTION ♪
>>RED: UP AT THE LODGE WE HAVE
AN ATTITUDE ABOUT SIGNS AND
THAT PRETTY WELL EXPLAINS IT.
ALL EXCEPT OF COURSE FOR THIS
SIGN BECAUSE IT IS TIME FOR
'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'.
BILL HAD ASKED ME TO DROP
DOWN BY THE LAKE AND HE
IS GOING TO LAUNCH A BOAT.
AND THAT'S KIND OF
A BEAUTY ISN'T IT?
THE TRAILER IS A LITTLE
BIT OF OVERKILL,
ANYWAY WE HOISTED IT UP THERE
AND PUT HER ON AND ONE THING
I DIDN'T REMEMBER AT THIS POINT.
>>BILL: WHOA!
>>RED: WHICH IS YOU'RE
SUPPOSE TO TIE THE FRONT
OF THE BOAT DOWN.
ANYWAY BILL WILL FIGURE IT OUT,
RIGHT BILL?
YEAH WE KNOW, WE KNOW.
ANYWAY HE PULLED THAT DOWN
AND HOOKED HER UP AND THEN,
BUT BY GOLLY WHAT A BEAUTIFUL
DAY FOR LAUNCHING A BOAT.
BILL'S GOING TO GET IN THERE
AND AWAY YOU GO, OH, OH, OH!
>>BILL: (SHOUTING) OH!
>>RED: AS I SAY A REAL NICE
DAY, AND YOU GET A BIG LINEUP
THERE, PEOPLE WAITING TO LAUNCH
THEIR BOATS AND WHATEVER.
>>BILL: (SHOUTING) AH!
>>RED: YOU KNOW IT'S FUNNY,
YOU'D THINK BOATERS WOULD
BE KIND OF FREEWHEELING,
EASY TO GET ALONG WITH
BUT BY GOLLY YOU KNOW
THEY'RE STARTING TO GET
A LITTLE UPSET, HONKING THEIR
HORNS AND WHAT HAVE YOU.
I FELT WE WERE MAKING OUR
BEST EFFORTS YOU KNOW TO GET
THE BOAT IN, IT'S NOT EASY,
IT'S NOT EASY LAUNCHING A BOAT
I MEAN YOU'VE HAD THE WHOLE
WINTER WHERE YOU HAVEN'T
HAD A CHANCE TO YOU KNOW
PRACTICE LAUNCHING THE BOAT
OR ANYTHING, SO THIS IS THE
FIRST TIME IN FOR US AND
BY GOLLY LET'S HAVE A
LITTLE PATIENCE HERE.
OKAY THINGS GO WRONG,
THAT CAN HAPPEN.
ANYWAY WE'RE GETTING,
NOW WE'RE GETTING THERE,
THAT A BOY BILL, AND GOT TO GET,
YEAH, YEAH, CRANK HER UP THERE,
HE'S GOING TO, WHAT HE'S TRYING
TO DO NOW IS LINE UP THE HITCH
WITH THE HITCH, NO THE BALL
WITH THE HITCH ON THE, AND I'M
GOING TO BACK BECAUSE I'VE GOT
THE BALL AND THEN W'RE
TAKING IT, WHAT A BEAUTIFUL DAY,
AND I COME BACK THERE AND
OH, OH, OH, OH, AND BILL,
WE DIDN'T QUITE.
>>BILL: (SHOUTING) AH!
>>RED: WE NEEDED A THIRD PERSON
ALL RIGHT, SOMEONE TO KIND OF
COORDINATE, ISN'T THAT A
BEAUTIFUL DAY, LOOK AT THAT,
LOOK AT THE BOATS,
LOOK AT THE DUCKS THERE,
FLY LITTLE DUCKIES FLY.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH,
OH THAT'S GREAT BILL,
LOOK AT THE BALANCE EH?
HE SHOULD TRY WATERSKIING
MAYBE LATER ONCE WE GET
THAT BOAT IN THE WATER.
ANYWAY WE GET HER ALL SET UP
AND WE'RE OKAY NOW AND
EVERYTHING, HE'S GOING TO RIG
HER UP, NOW THIS IS SMART,
YOU SEE THIS IS A TIMESAVER,
YOU PUT YOUR STUFF IN THE BOAT
BEFORE YOU LAUNCH YOUR BOAT AND
THAT WAY YOU'RE NOT HOLDING THE
OTHER PEOPLE UP YOU KNOW,
THEY CAN JUST LAUNCH THEIR BOATS
BECAUSE YOU'RE OUT OF THE WAY,
OH WELL, BY GOLLY IT'S A
BEAUTIFUL DAY, YEAH, YEAH.
THIS IS WHEN FINALLY
WE FIGURED IT,
UNFORTUNATELY HERE I WAS SO
UPSET THAT I BACKED UP A
LITTLE CROOKED AND THE BOAT
WENT RIGHT OVER BILL.
>>BILL: (SHOUTING) AH!
>>RED: WELL I HOPE HE'S OKAY.
BILL? BILL? YEAH...
>>RED: AND NOW HERE'S SOMETHING
FOR KIDS WHICH DOES NOT
REPRESENT THE VIEWS OR OPINIONS
OF ANY INTELLIGENT HUMAN
LIFE FORM, HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: HI, THIS NEXT SEGMENT
IS A PILOT FOR A BRAND NEW SHOW,
WELL YOU KNOW I THINK IS
REALLY GOING TO CATCH ON
BECAUSE IT'S GOT ALL THE GREAT
INGREDIENTS YOU KNOW,
IT'S GOT LIKE ACTION, ADVENTURE,
EXCITEMENT AND ME.
THIS IS A SHOW THAT LETS PEOPLE
LIVE THEIR DREAMS YOU KNOW,
IT'S ENTITLED
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, SO ALL YOU HAVE
TO DO IS SEND IN YOUR VIDEOS
SHOWING ME WHAT YOU WOULD
DO IF YOU WERE GOD.
BUT BECAUSE IT'S A PILOT
YOU KNOW THERE'S NO WAY
YOU COULD HAVE SENT IN YOUR
VIDEOS YET SO I GUESS I'M
GOING TO HAVE TO DO THE FIRST
ONE OKAY, SO HERE I GO I'M
GOING TO DO THE FIRST ONE.
WELL IF I WERE GOD I'D END
ALL WARS AND DISEASES AND
STARVATION BUT I WOULD MAKE
SURE THAT EVERYONE HAS CABLE.
>>RED: HAROLD WHAT ARE YOU
DOING IN HERE?
>>HAROLD: I'M PRETENDING
THAT I WAS GOD.
>>RED: WELL YOU CAN'T DO
THAT HAROLD, GOD DOESN'T
HAVE HOMEWORK.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH, OH YEAH,
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, I'M JUST
GOING TO DO IT RIGHT NOW.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT.
>>HAROLD: I WONDER WOULD HAPPEN
THOUGH IF I WERE GOD?
>>RED: WELL THAT WOULD PROBABLY
PUT AN END TO RELIGION.
>>HAROLD: YEAH.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: BOY GLEN YOU SEEM PRETTY
CHIPPER IN THE FACE OF DISASTER,
THE LAKE IS MAGNETIZED
OR DIDN'T YOU KNOW?
>>GLEN: OH NO I KNOW RED,
BUT THE R.V. IS 60 PERCENT
ALUMINUM SO YOU KNOW THAT'S
NOT MAGNETIC OF COURSE.
>>RED: YEAH AND THE REST
IS ALL BONDO AND DUCT TAPE,
BUT I WAS MORE CONCERNED
ABOUT YOUR BOATS AND MORE
IMPORTANTLY YOUR CUSTOMERS
WHO BOUGHT THEM.
>>GLEN: OH YEAH, YEAH, WELL
NONE OF THE BOATS ARE RUNNING
RED, SO NOBODY'S CALLED TO
COMPLAIN YET.
>>RED: YEAH WELL THE PHONES
AREN'T WORKING EITHER.
>>GLEN: OH YEAH.
>>RED: WELL GLEN I JUST
WONDERED IF YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT WE COULD DO TO DEMAGNETIZE
THE LAKE, HAVE YOU EVER HAD ANY
KIND OF EXPERIENCE LIKE THAT?
>>GLEN: WELL YOU KNOW RED I DID
HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THE FRIDGE
ONCE IN THE R.V. HERE
IT KEPT SLIDING BACK AND
FORTH, IT KEPT SQUISHING
THE CAT SO I MAGNETIZED IT.
>>RED: AH HAH.
>>GLEN: AND THAT WAS NO GOOD SO
I HAD TO DEMAGNETIZE IT BECAUSE
THE DOOR, I COULDN'T GET
IT OPEN.
>>RED: OH GOSH,
SO HOW DID YOU DEMAGNETIZE IT?
>>GLEN: WELL I TOOK A BALLOON
AND I RUBBED IT AGAINST MY HEAD
AND I TOUCHED IT,
I WAS PULLING YOUR LEG RED,
I'M SORRY, NO WHAT I DID WAS
I MADE MYSELF AN ELECTROMAGNET
AND I HOOKED IT UP TO THE
R.V. BATTERIES SO IT
WAS 4 TIMES 72 AMPS.
>>RED: YOU KNOW SOMETHING
LIKE THAT JUST MIGHT WORK GLEN.
>>GLEN: WELL I HOPE NOT RED,
I KIND OF GET USE TO THE
PHONE NOT RINGING.
>>RED: OH GLEN HOW CAN YOU SAY
THAT, YOU GOT ABOUT 1,000
PEOPLE MAD AT YOU,
YOU CAN'T DO ANY REPAIRS
AND YOU CAN'T SELL ANY BOATS?
>>GLEN: YEAH I KNOW,
I BLAME THE ECONOMY.
>>RED: OH YEAH IT'S
ROUGH OUT THERE.
>>GLEN: THE GOVERNMENT YEAH,
WE VOTED THEM IN.
>>RED: THEY TAKE AWAY
YOUR INITIATIVE.
>>GLEN: WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO?
>>RED: WHAT'S THE
POINT IN TRYING?
>>GLEN: WHAT ARE
YOU GOING TO DO RED?
>>RED: NOT A FLAMING THING.
>>GLEN: YOU GO OUT THERE AND
YOU BUST YOUR HUMP AND WHAT
HAPPENS, YOU GOT NO LEISURE
TIME, YOU GOT NO TIME TO ENJOY
ANYTHING, ALL IT IS WORK, WORK,
WORK, WORK, WORK.
>>RED: BOY THIS IS INCONVENIENT,
WELL WE FIGURED OUT HOW TO
DEMAGNETIZE THE LAKE,
WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO IS
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A GIANT
ELECTROMAGNET OUT OF THE
POSSUM VAN, WE'VE WRAPPED HER
WITH ABOUT I THINK 500 YARDS
OF TINFOIL AND WE'RE GOING TO
HOTWIRE THAT WHOLE UNIT INTO
THE LOCAL POWER GRID,
WHICH WE CAN TAP INTO WE FIGURE
50 TRILLION MEGAVOLTS WHICH
I BELIEVE GIVES US SOMEWHERE IN
THE RANGE OF 5,000 KILOWATTS,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT WHICH WILL
BE JUST ENOUGH TO EXACTLY
DEMAGNETIZE THE LAKE OR
POSSIBLY REVERSE THE EARTH'S
POLARITY AND SEND THE MOON
HURTLING INTO THE SUN.
OH HERE WE GO.
(CRACKLING OF ELECTRICITY)
(LOUD CRASH OF THUNDER)
>>RED: WELL THAT WAS
A TOTAL SUCCESS.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED.
>>RED: HOLY JEEZ HAROLD,
WHAT ARE YOU THE TERMINATOR
OR THE TIN MAN?
>>HAROLD: MY RETAINER GOT
WELDED TO MY FILLINGS,
I CAN'T TALK.
>>RED: OH NOW THAT'S
A SETBACK HAROLD.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH IT'S MEETING TIME.
>>RED: YEAH, YEAH I KNOW,
DON'T TALK WITH YOUR MOUTH FUSED
YOU GO AHEAD AND I'LL
BE RIGHT DOWN.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
>>RED: WELL HOPEFULLY THE NORTH
POLE'S BACK WHERE IT SHOULD BE,
WHERE THE SUN DON'T SHINE
AND THAT'S ABOUT IT
FOR THIS SHOW.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING HOME STRAIGHT
AFTER THE MEETING, MAYBE WE
CAN DO A LITTLE TEST TO SEE
IF OPPOSITES ATTRACT,
IT MIGHT HELP IF WE WERE
POLISH RIGHT?
LODGE HUMOUR, GOT TO LOVE IT!
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND MR
MAGNETO HEAD AND THE WHOLE
GANG UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING
AND KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUONDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT,
WELL I GUESS YOU REALIZE
THAT ALL THE MAGNETISM HAS
GONE OUT OF THE LAKE AND
GONE SOMEWHERE ELSE.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca