You know, back
when I was a kid
everybody wanted
to be a cowboy
like Hop-a-Long Cassidy
or Roy Rogers
or even Gene Autrey
until he sang that
Christmas song.
But the biggest kick
was wearing the cap guns.
Of course this was before
airport security.
But these cowboys like
me are the same ones
who refuse to
wear seatbelts.
To them it looks wussy.
If a cowboy can ride
a mustang across the
desert without one
then you should be able
to drive a Pinto to the
mall without one.
So we have to find a way
to make seatbelts part
of the cowboy experience.
Okay, I've turned my seatbelt
into a pretend ammo. belt.
Now instead of looking
like a crossing guard,
I look like John Wayne.
Time to head em up
and move em out.
[ POLICE SIRENS ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Thank you very much.
Appreciate it.
Big, big week up at
the lodge this week.
Yeah, yeah.
We're having a big
drought up here.
It hasn't rained
in a long, long time.
The fountain down at city
hall is blowing smoke
and the bird baths have
switched to dry cleaning.
Uncle Red?
I had like a canteen
hidden in my room.
Yeah, I told you
not to tell anybody.
Unfortunately, you'd
already told me, so...
You drank the water?!
No, no, no.
The possum van
did, Harold.
Well she was
overheating like crazy.
It was going to turn into
an espresso machine in there.
So, I mean --
Hey, you don't want
to seize that engine.
Yes I do.
That engine's the reason
we don't have an ozone.
This drought is the
fault of you guys.
You know and your emissions.
Harold, the ozone
doesn't make it rain.
Oh no?
What does the ozone
do, Uncle Red?
[ LAUGHTER ]
The ozone filters
the sun's rays
so the Earth doesn't
fry up like burrito.
And rain is caused by
the evaporation of water.
Which doesn't work
around here
because technically
Possum Lake is not water.
Hey Harold,
it's a liquid,
that's close enough,
all right?
It's a blob.
It's jelly.
We don't have waves.
We have undulations.
This whole thing, you
know, it's your fault
because you've been throwing
vehicles and lawnmowers
and chainsaws in there
for the past 50 years.
You know what, Harold,
for the first time ever
I think you're --
you could be and when
I think we're --
doesn't really matter
who's right or --
You know what, all we have
to do to fix the whole
thing is make it rain.
No! No, no, no.
You don't need
to make it rain.
You need to ask for
professional help.
You should talk.
Harold, we created
the problem.
We're going to
create the solution.
That's called being a man.
Ya, well I don't think
I want to be a man.
Looks like you're safe.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Today's winner receives
this pass for a free visit
to Crazy Lou's Leech Farm
where our motto is there's
a sucker born every 2.3 seconds.
Okay, cover your
thingys, Dalton.
Okay, Mr. Green,
you've got 30 seconds
to get Dalton Humphrey
to say this word.
Okay, okay.
And go!
Okay Dalton, this is something
you take to a funeral.
Business cards.
No, okay, no, okay.
These are colourful and
you find them everywhere
in the woods
around the lodge.
Empties.
No, okay, no, no.
This is pretty
and it has petals.
Malibu Barbie Pink Bicycle.
Okay, no, no, no.
Okay.
This is something that
your wife wants from you.
It rhymes with tower.
Power.
No, no, no.
This is something you
would give your wife.
A wide berth.
Okay, no, no, okay, okay.
When you started going
out with Anne-Marie,
what would you take
with you on a date?
Ear plugs.
No, no, no.
Okay, okay.
These have long stems
and they're kind of
frilly on the end.
Women love them as gifts.
Dusters.
No.
We're almost out
of time, Mr. Green.
Yeah, okay, okay.
I know.
Dalton, what does a bride
throw at a wedding?
Tantrum.
Anne-Marie went ballistic.
I had to get a proctologist
to take the flowers out.
Yes!
[ BELL RINGING ]
Welcome to Harold's
Hobby House
where we examine
not just the hobby
but the man
behind the hobby.
And when you think
of the man behind,
you think of
Winston Rothchild.
Winston's the
manager and staff
of Winston Rothchild's
Sewage and Septic
Sucking Services.
And Winston, what
type of hobby
did you bring
for us tonight?
Well, Harold, for the
last several years,
I've collecting home
décor accessories
with historical
significance.
Yeah, you know, like dishes
and vases and what have you.
Oh, well then,
what have you?
Okay, this first piece is a
turn-of-the-century candy bowl.
Would you care
for a prune?
Oh no, thank you.
Yeah, I don't like
them much myself
but they're great
for business.
This next piece
is a beautiful
Wedgewood china serving
dish circa 1920.
The cookies are
a little more recent.
Well no cookies
for me, thank you.
Good call,
they're dog biscuits
but I thought they sort of
enhanced the presentation.
Yeah very much so
but I think I saw
one of our stagehands
eating a couple of those.
I was wondering why he was
licking himself like that.
Well, you know, of all
the pieces you have,
do you have a
favourite piece?
I do and I brought
it with me.
You did?
Well you asked
me to, Harold.
This is a 19th century,
sterling silver tea service.
Shall I pour?
[ SAID WITH BRITISH ACCENT ]
Oh yes, please.
I really love tea.
Tea is delicious.
Well this is
a pekoe blend
with just a hint
of rose hemp.
Ooh.
Oh, it's delicious!
It is, that's --
You know what I
think is amazing
is that you have a hobby
that is so far removed
from what you do
for a living.
It's not that
far removed.
I fished each one of these
pieces out of septic beds.
[ APPLAUSE ]
You know, there comes a time
in the life of any appliance
when it's over.
And then that time
comes you'll know.
But what do you do when
you have an old fridge
and stove that the
garbage men won't take
and you don't live
next to a ravine.
Well I guess if you're
real good with a can opener,
you could get rid of them
a little bit at a time
but if you're a handyman
or even better,
a handyman
with a teenager,
here's what you can do.
Step one, take the
top off the stove.
back off the stove.
Take the door off
the stove.
Then you remove
the top and back
because once you get
the top and the back
off the unit,
this is no longer a stove,
it's an office chair for
your teenager's workstation.
Got a fully-reclining backrest,
a place to keep his books...
or her books...
It's so hard to tell
with kids these days.
And here's an extra bonus,
retractable foot rest
so your kid doesn't get
carpel tunnel in his butt.
But how's he going to know
when his homework is done?
Well that's what this
homework timer is for.
Just set it to well done.
And for extra safety
and comfort,
I would suggest you
line the whole unit
with an air mattress
because I believe there
could be an exposed
sharp edge or two...
and I'm right.
Now here's a question.
Can I rig up these burners
to make a red, hot,
reading light?
No.
You know it's good
for a teenager to
sit in a stove
because you want him
in the hot seat
but you also want
him to be cool
so this fridge becomes
his computer desk
and that automatic
fridge light means
you don't need any of those
goofy-looking desk lamps.
Now the door is
kept horiontal
thanks to these little
chains I got from the bank.
They even have
pens on them.
The shelves are great
for holding my files
and these ice cube trays
handle all your office supplies.
And oh, what's that?
A mouse.
No wonder the cat
was in there.
And check this out,
the icemaker makes a
dandy pencil sharpener.
And that's how you turn a
couple of burned-out appliances
into a high-tech workstation.
So remember, if the women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
Boy, this is educational.
I learned something.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
There's a big push
on these days
to make us all get into
High-Definition television.
You know, those big
flat screen T.V.'s
that hang on your wall
with a better view
than any of your windows.
And they're focusing
the sales pitch
on guys my age because they
know we're the only ones
who have a chance of coming
up with that kind of cash.
The problem there
is those of us
from the 8-track generation
don't have the keen
senses to appreciate
the new technology.
What good is high-def
when you're half-deaf
and half-blind?
Sadly, this is just
another example
of not being to afford
something until it's too late
like open-heart surgery
or dance lessons
or underarm deodorant.
So the best approach
is to buy what you want
without waiting until
you can afford it.
That's what credit
cards are for.
And when the Visa
bill comes in,
just pay it with
your American Express.
By the time the
repo. man shows up,
you'll have finished enjoying
whatever it was
you bought anyway.
Speaking of which, if my
bank manager is watching,
I'll be dropping the
Hi-Def T.V. off
at your house right
after the playoffs.
Remember, I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
If you can see the future,
that makes you a psychic.
If you can the past,
that makes you a customer.
I've been doing some research
on how to make it rain.
I went down to our
local public library.
Was it ever quiet in there.
I looked up cloud seeding.
Apparently all you got to
do is fire some chemicals
up into the clouds
and bingo, you got rain.
So I built myself
a little cannon,
emptied about a thousand
shotgun shells into her, there,
Put in a wireless detonator
so that I can stand well back
when I fire it off
with my T.V. remote.
I just got one more
chemical to stick in here
and we'll be good to go.
I should never leave
you unsupervised.
Harold, you can call
me the rain man.
I'm an excellent driver --
excellent driver.
Bang your head
on something, Harold?
No, that's from the
movie the Rain Man.
Oh, I don't like any movies
that were made after 1959.
Oh, no, no,
there was one...
Duct Tape something.
Check this out, Harold.
All I got to do is
fire my cannon,
send the chemicals up on top
of those clouds out there.
See, I got the far end
attached to that tree
with no branches on it.
That's not a tree.
That's a high-tension
electric pole.
You know they seed
clouds with airplanes?
I know that Harold.
You think I'm going
to hotwire a plane
and fly around
without a license?
That would be stupid
and dangerous.
Uncle Red, you know
I never stop you
from doing
your crazy things.
That could be part
of the problem.
Well, exactly, exactly.
And I know you don't mean
to poison our atmosphere
and defoliate the trees
and end life as we know it.
Not when you put
it that way, no.
All right, so let's not
fire off the cannon,
let's do the smart thing.
All right, Harold,
all right, yeah.
Really?
Yeah?
Oh.
Yeah.
Okay, okay,
that's good.
Because you know it might
rain on its own anyway.
It might rain.
You know what, let's check
it out on the weather channel.
Oh Harold, no,
no, Harold!
This adventure starts with
the difference between
Dalton Humphrey and a canoe.
A canoe tips.
Okay, the boys are going
out for a day of camping.
Watch the rope there.
Watch out Bill,
don't straddle a rope.
Don't ever... oh boy.
You know what,
you can adopt.
So Mike and Ed get into
kind of an argument.
Bill's saying, why are
you arguing in nature's
beautiful environment?
Bill pulls out a telescope
and he just says,
it's just so beautiful.
Why don't you just enjoy
nature for all it is.
That's fine, he's right.
Just enjoy the day.
There's some bugs there.
You know, you get the
black flies and mosquitoes
and the deer flies.
This is getting crazy here
so they're slamming away
on each other and --
Now Ed has some kind of
an insect repellent
or something that's he got.
These two are --
Now wait, that's a bit,
that's a bit much.
No, no, come on now.
Come on, now.
Easy now, come on now.
So Ed has some type
of bug fogger and that's --
Oh boy!
Turn her down.
But you know it,
it did the job.
It cleared the air --
Cleared the air.
But they come back,
that's what I find anyway.
They come back so then
Bill says I'm going
to go pitch the tent.
They got the screen
windows in it
and we can all get in there
and get out of the bugs.
It's one of these tents --
You know you kind of flash them
and they stand up on their own.
Okay now get in the tent.
Everybody get in the tent.
Get in the tent.
In the tent, way you go.
Get in the tent, yeah
and then zip the zipper.
Okay, there's a few bugs
in there but not very many
and within a few minutes
they realize --
Okay, okay, they're good.
Everything's good.
It's good.
Then they feel something
coming up from underneath.
They pitched the tent
right over an ant hill.
So now they stand up
in a tent --
not a good idea.
Okay, plan B, they all
get into sleeping bags.
Bill takes his
telescope apart
and he's got
snorkles attached
so they can get inside,
zip themselves in
and still be able to breathe
just by leaving the
telescope outside.
What they didn't realize
is there are tarantulas
in our area and...
it's really only
a matter of time.
Ooh.
Okay, so it's time for
a total rethink.
They're going to just
get in the canoe
and get the heck out of there
and for all you animal
lovers out there,
the tarantula is just fine.
So they hop in the canoe
and here's something you
youngsters should learn,
no matter how hard you paddle,
you're not as strong
as a rope that's tied up.
So, finally --
You might want to think
about undoing the --
Yeah, undo the rope there.
Just yank it.
Oh boy... Ooh!
They don't just head
back to the lodge,
they're making a bee line.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Okay...
Trying to seed the clouds
with my homemade cannon
was not a complete success.
Instead of a fine,
dispersal pattern,
the chemicals kind of all
glomed together and...
and splashed right
into Possum Lake
like a giant
pop rock
and then it started frothing
and bubbling and...
I tell you, I haven't
seen that much foam
since Moose Thompson
shaved his back.
I know, I know.
I know.
I've never seen a lake
evaporate before.
I know.
It was like a giant bromo.
Fish were falling
out of the sky.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
You should have seen
the one that got away.
You know, Harold,
think about this,
there are people that
live their whole lives
and never see anything
like that though.
Oh, I envy them.
C'mon Harold, look
at the bright side.
I mean, the lake will
eventually ooze back
into place
and meanwhile, we can
get all our appliances
and snowmobiles
off the bottom.
You know, Uncle Red,
that sometimes
when you make a mistake but
everything turns out hunky-dory.
No, I no, this is not
one of those times.
This is hunks of dorys.
No, it's hunky-dory.
What?
Well, the foam will extinguish
all the forest fires --
You're kidding?
Yeah, well the concussion from
the cannon being triggered off
well it caused this
atmospheric reaction
and apparently it's
raining in Port Asbestos
and it's heading this way.
Oh ho, ho, ho!
Hey, you know
what that means?
That means that my
idea and my ingenuity
and my instinct to
do something crazy
has once again
saved the day.
Huh? Huh?
Oh, no, no, no!
No, you did something
dumb, period.
Me? You're the one
who fired the cannon.
That was an accident.
Accidents happen.
Just ask your parents.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Meeting time.
Well away you go, then.
Oh boy, wow.
Okay, if my wife
is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting.
I'm kind of on a roll
so I'm thinking maybe we
should do something crazy.
Let's try to stay up
to 10 o'clock tonight.
I'm not quite sure how
we'll fill in the time
but I'm hoping my medication
will help me think of something.
And to the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself, Harold
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge...
Keep your stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Guys! Guys!
Sit down!
Guys!
Sit down back there!
Sit down guys, sit down.
Everybody sit down.
All rise.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the man's prayer.
I'm a man
but I can change
if I have to
I guess.
All right men, apparently
Harold has an announcement
of some kind.
Well now since the
drought is over
so you should all
stop drinking beer.
[ LODGE MEMBERS ]
Boo!!