THEY STILL GOT
A FEW FLAWS IN 'EM.
FOR EXAMPLE,
HEADLIGHT DESIGN.
HEADLIGHTS ONLY POINT IN THE
DIRECTION THAT YOU'RE GOING.
HOW ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO
SEE STREET SIGNS OR HOUSE
NUMBERS OR HITCHHIKERS?
WHAT YOU NEED IS SOME KIND
OF MOVABLE SEARCH LIGHT
THAT POINTS WHEREVER
YOU'RE LOOKING.
I'M NOT ONE OF THOSE USELESS
DRIVERS THAT NEEDS TO KEEP
HIS EYES ON THE ROAD,
AND WITH THIS RIG
I CAN SEE EVERYTHING.
I CAN EVEN LOOK BEHIND ME.
[crash]
DID NOT SEE THAT COMING.
[cheering and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU. APPRECIATE THAT.
[whistling and applause]
WELL, BEEN KINDA QUIET
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
NOT THE KIND OF QUIET THAT
HAPPENS JUST BEFORE
THE ENTIRE SIOUX NATION
COMES UP OVER THE RIDGE.
NO, I'M TALKING ABOUT
A PEACEFUL QUIET;
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU CAN JUST
LAY BACK, CLOSE YOUR EYES,
AND BATHE IN
THE SOUNDS OF NATURE.
MR. GREEN!
OKAY, THAT WAS MORE
OF A SPONGE BATH.
WHAT IS IT,
MIKE?
MR. GREEN, WERE YOU UP
WALKING AROUND LATE LAST
NIGHT IN THE LODGE?
OH, YEAH, PRETTY LATE,
9:30, MAYBE 10:00.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
LIKE 2:00 IN THE MORNING,
WALKING BACK AND
FORTH IN HERE.
OH, NO, IF I WAS UP
AT 2:00 IN THE MORNING,
I WAS IN A LOT
SMALLER ROOM THAN THIS.
I KNEW IT!
WE HAVE A GHOST.
I CAN ALWAYS TELL.
WELL, YOU'RE FAMILIAR
WITH SPIRITS, I KNOW THAT.
NO, NO, I CAN SENSE THE
PRESENCE OF THE SUPERNATURAL.
I HAVE BEEN
TOUCHED BY THE GIFT.
NOW, I KNOW YOU
DON'T BELIEVE ALL THAT.
WELL, I BELIEVE
THE TOUCHED PART.
MR. GREEN, THIS IS A GHOST,
AND HE'S HERE.
HAVE YOU EVER FELT THE ROOM
SUDDENLY GO COLD?
MIKE, EVERY MARRIED
MAN IN THE WORLD HAS
EXPERIENCED THAT.
[laughter and applause]
WE HAVE ALL KINDS OF THINGS
IN THE LODGE THAT COULD
PASS AS GHOSTS.
WE GOT MICE IN THE WALLS;
THERE'S SQUIRRELS IN THE --
THERE'S SOME CHEESE DOWNSTAIRS
THAT'LL STAND UP AND
TALK TO YOU.
THAT'S FINE.
YOU CAN BE SKEPTICAL.
BUT I'M TELLING YOU,
THERE IS A GHOST
SOMEWHERE IN
POSSUM LODGE.
[slam]
HE'S OUT RIGHT NOW.
WOULD YOU CARE TO
LEAVE A MESSAGE?
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheering and applause]
TODAY'S WINNER RECEIVES THIS
DELUXE TATTOO REMOVAL KIT.
OKAY, DALTON, COVER UP
THE OL' SIDE MIRRORS THERE.
HAROLD, YOU'VE GOT
30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON HUMPHREY
TO SAY THIS WORD...
OKAY, OKAY.
THANK YOU, WINSTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, THIS IS A PEST
THAT COMES AROUND
AND BOTHERS PEOPLE
WHEN THEY'RE EATING.
RICHARD SIMMONS?
BIRDS AND BEES CAN DO IT.
OH, SORRY.
I USED TO KNOW.
OKAY, THIS IS
SOMETHING BIRDS CAN DO
AND MOST PEOPLE
WISH THEY COULD.
OH, OH, RELIEVE THEMSELVES
WHENEVER THEY WANT.
NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT IT.
THIS IS SOMETHING YOU WOULD
FIND ON THE FRONT
OF YOUR PANTS.
SOUP STAINS.
YOU'RE ALMOST OUTTA TIME.
NO!
IT'S HIM!
TELL HIM!
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, UM,
IF YOU SUDDENLY FIND
YOURSELF UP IN THE SKY
ABOVE YOUR HOUSE,
WHAT WOULD YOU BE DOING?
LIGHTING MY BARBECUE.
COME ON, DALTON!
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF
A CARTOON CHARACTER
NAMED DUMBO?
OH, HE WAS SO CUTE
WITH THOSE BIG EARS.
OKAY, WHAT COULD HE DO?
HE COULD HEAR,
THAT'S FOR SURE!
YES, HE COULD HEAR, BUT HE
COULD DO SOMETHING SPECIAL.
TO PEOPLE.
HE WAS NICE
WHAT?
THAT'S NOT WHAT
I'M LOOKING FOR!
WELL, NOBODY IS.
THEY DON'T APPRECIATE
A GENTLE SOUL LIKE DUMBO.
WOULDN'T HURT A FLY.
[ringing bell]
THAT'S IT.
WHEN YOUR SEPTICS GO BAD,
THERE'S NO ONE TO BLAME.
NO NEED TO APOLOGIZE
OR COWER IN SHAME.
CALL FOR A PUMP-OUT,
ROTHSCHILD'S THE NAME.
IT BEATS LOSING YOUR HOME
IN A HUGE PURPLE FLAME.
OH, MAN, A DENT!
DON'T YOU HATE THAT?
YOU TRY TO KEEP YOUR
VEHICLE LOOKING MINT,
AND THEN SOME
BONEHEAD COMES ALONG
AND NAILS YOU WITH HIS
DOOR IN A PARKING LOT.
AND OF COURSE
NO NOTE OR ANYTHING.
OH, NO.
THE GUY DOESN'T EVEN HAVE THE
GUTS TO ADMIT HIS MISTAKE
AND FACE IT LIKE A MAN.
I TELL YOU SOMETHING,
I'VE GOT AN IDEA THAT MIGHT
JUST BE CRAZY ENOUGH TO WORK.
AND I GUARANTEE YOU THIS,
I'M AT LEAST CRAZY
ENOUGH TO TRY IT.
[tires squealing]
ALL RIGHT, THIS HERE
IS AN ARC WELDER.
OH, YEAH,
THERE YOU ARE.
THIS IS AN ARC WELDER HERE.
I JUST USED IT TO FIX
THE FRAME ON THIS BICYCLE.
YOU GET A REAL STRONG
WELD TO THIS BABY.
LOOK AT THIS.
YOU KNOW, I'M THINKING THIS
IS GONNA BE THE KEY COMPONENT
IN MY PARKING LOT CRIMINAL
IDENTIFICATION DEVICE.
I'M GONNA NEED A
BETTER NAME BEFORE
I GO NATIONAL WITH THIS.
BUT MY FIRST AND
ONLY REAL PROBLEM IS
COMING UP WITH ENOUGH
PORTABLE ELECTRICITY
TO POWER THE UNIT.
YOU KNOW, THERE ARE
A LOT OF GREAT ADVANTAGES
TO HAVING VEHICLES LYING
AROUND YOUR PROPERTY.
YOU CAN USE 'EM AS TOOL SHEDS,
BUS SHELTERS FOR THE KIDS,
AND GUEST CABINS
FOR YOUR WIFE'S RELATIVES.
HERE'S A BONUS
THAT I TAPPED INTO.
EVERY ONE OF THOSE VEHICLES
HAS GOT A BATTERY IN IT,
SO I CAN HOOK THEM ALL UP
TO RUN MY ARC WELDER.
I'M GONNA HOOK THEM UP
IN UNEVEN SERIES HERE.
[zap!]
OKAY, WE'RE GOOD TO GO HERE.
GOTTA SET MY TRAP.
FIRST THING YOU WANNA DO
IS TAKE THE GROUND WIRE
OF THE ARC WELDER
AND ATTACH THAT
TO THE GROUND.
OKAY, NOW YOU WANNA
TAKE THE LIVE END
AND ATTACH THAT
DIRECTLY TO THE VAN.
I WOULD SUGGEST YOU
DO THAT KINDA QUICK.
OKAY, AND YOU'RE
GOOD TO GO.
NOW IF SOMEONE SHOULD COME
ALONG AND HAPPEN TO
TOUCH THE VAN
WITH, SAY, THEIR DOOR,
WELL, THEY GET TO LEARN JUST
A LITTLE BIG MORE ABOUT
ELECTRICITY.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[chuckling]
HEY, BUDDY,
YOU LOOKIN' FOR SOMEONE?
UH, I THINK THE OWNER
OF THE VAN IS IN
THE STORE.
HAVE A GREAT DAY.
[cheering and applause]
MEN HAVE TROUBLE
COMMUNICATING.
THEY SAY WE DON'T
TALK VERY MUCH.
YOU OLDER GUYS KNOW
WHAT I MEAN.
REMEMBER 20 YEARS AGO WHEN YOU
ASKED YOUR WIFE TO MARRY YOU
AND SHE'S BEEN WAITING FOR
A HALF DECENT FOLLOW-UP
QUESTION EVER SINCE?
AND IT'S NOT, "ARE YOU GONNA
FINISH THAT SANDWICH?"
BUT I FIND THAT
AS MEN GET OLDER
THEY ACTUALLY TALK MORE
THAN THEY DID WHEN
THEY WERE YOUNG.
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS THEY'RE
THE ONLY ONES IN THE ROOM.
YOU'VE ALL BEEN
THERE, HAVEN'T YOU?
WANDERING AROUND THE HOUSE,
LOOKING FOR YOUR CAR KEYS.
PRETTY SOON YOU'RE MUTTERING
AWAY LIKE THAT WEIRD GUY
IN THE PARK
WHO THINKS YOUR
DOG IS A COMMUNIST.
OH, SURE, SOMETIMES
WE TRY TO COVER
BY TALKING TO
THE TV OR THE RADIO,
BUT I THINK WE ALL KNOW THAT
DEEP DOWN THAT THE GUY
SELLING SPEED STICK
CAN'T HEAR YOU TELLING HIM
WHERE TO SPEED STICK IT.
BUT IN MY OPINION, TALKING TO
YOURSELF IS NOTHING TO
BE ASHAMED OF.
I MEAN, YOU HAVE THINGS
THAT NEED TO BE SAID,
AND YOU DON'T
WANNA OFFEND ANYBODY.
YOU KNOW, BY SAYING THEM TO
YOURSELF WHEN YOU'RE ALONE
YOU'RE PROBABLY SAVING
YOUR JOB, YOUR MARRIAGE,
MAYBE EVEN YOUR LIFE.
SO LADIES, WHEN YOU SEE US
TALKING TO OURSELVES,
JUST LEAVE US ALONE.
YOU'LL KNOW WHEN WE'RE READY
TO HAVE A CONVERSATION
BECAUSE WE'LL CLAM UP.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
YEAH! YEAH!
( waking up )
HEY, RED, YOU IN THERE?
WELL, YOU FINALLY
MADE IT, HUH, WINSTON?
YEAH, WELL, I'M IN
A BIT OF A HURRY,
SO IF YOU HAVE
ANYTHING TO TELL ME,
YOU BETTER FIRE AWAY.
OH, OKAY, WELL, I KNOW
YOU DON'T GO ON DATES
VERY OFTEN, WINSTON,
AND I JUST WANTED TO
GIVE YOU A FEW TIPS.
FOR EXAMPLE, PICKING
HER UP ON FOOT
IS NEVER PARTICULARLY
IMPRESSIVE, ALL RIGHT?
OH, IN KNOW THAT.
I'M JUST PARKED
DOWN THE ROAD.
ANYTHING ELSE?
IS THERE
OH.
YEAH, WELL, OKAY.
WELL, FOR STARTERS,
YOUR WARDROBE CHOICE
DOESN'T EXACTLY
SCREAM ROMANCE.
HEY, I'M PRESENTING MYSELF
AS A SUCCESSFUL
ENTREPRENEUR.
I DON'T CARE IF SHE KNOWS
I'M IN THE SEWAGE BUSINESS.
WELL, SHE'D BE ABLE
TO FIGURE THAT OUT
NO MATTER WHAT
YOU WERE WEARING.
OH, MAN, ARE YOU PICKING
HER UP IN YOUR
SEPTIC TRUCK?
HEY, THIS IS A
$90,000 VEHICLE.
IT'S LIKE BEING PICKED
UP IN A MERCEDES.
BESIDES, IT'S GONNA
BE DARK BY THEN,
AND THIS BABY LOOKS
PRETTY SHARP AT NIGHT.
YOU KNOW, WINSTON,
DARKNESS DOESN'T
HIDE AROMA.
IF YOU WERE MARRIED,
YOU'D KNOW THAT.
OH, I GOT HER
THESE FLOWERS.
GEEZ, WHAT
HAPPENED TO 'EM?
OVER FERTILIZED?
I GUESS SO.
ANYWAY, I GOTTA
GET GOING.
I GOTTA PICK HER
UP AT 8:30.
OH, I MEANT TO ASK YOU,
AND I WAS THINKING I COULD
JUST DO IT ON THE WAY
TO THE DRIVE-IN.
YOU KNOW, GIVE HER A CHANCE
TO SORT OF SEE ME IN ACTION.
OR SHOULD I JUST
CANCEL THE PUMP-OUT?
NO, DON'T CANCEL.
IF YOU'RE PICKING
HER UP AT 8:30,
I FIGURE THE DATE'LL
BE OVER BY NINE.
GREAT!
[coughing]
WELL, MIKE'S GOT
EVERYBODY STIRRED UP
ABOUT THIS
LODGE GHOST THING.
HE'S THE ONLY
ONE WHO'S SEEN IT.
BUT NOW THE OTHER GUYS ARE
SAYING STUFF IS BEING MOVED,
AND THE LODGE
IS ALL MESSED UP.
I HAVEN'T NOTICED ANYTHING.
I THINK I KNOW
WHO THE GHOST IS.
I FOUND THIS OLD OBITUARY
COLUMN FROM THE '50s.
DID YOU EVER HEAR OF A LODGE
MEMBER BY THE NAME OF
HENRY THORKELSON?
OH, SURE,
THE POSSUM LAKE WIGGLER.
DID HE HAVE
A NERVOUS TWITCH?
NO, HE INVENTED A LURE.
HE CALLED IT
THE POSSUM LAKE WIGGLER.
HE ONLY MADE ONE OF 'EM.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
A LOT OF THE TIME,
GHOSTS ARE PEOPLE
WHO DIED UNEXPECTEDLY,
AND IT SAYS IN
THIS COLUMN HERE
THAT HENRY THORKELSON WAS
IN A BOATING ACCIDENT.
NO, NO, NOT REALLY.
HE JUMPED ON THE MAIN DOCK
AND THE BOARD COME UP,
HIT HIM ON THE HEAD
AND KNOCKED HIM INTO
THE SPINNING PROP
OF THE FLOAT PLANE.
SO IT WAS REALLY
MORE OF A PLANE CRASH.
WERE THEY ABLE
TO SAVE HIM?
WELL, THEY SAVED
A FAIR BIT OF HIM.
audience: O-O-H!
YOU KNOW THE SAD THING
WAS HE NEVER GOT TO
USE THAT LURE.
HE WAS SO PROUD
OF THAT THING.
ODD LOOKING.
IT WAS YELLOW
AND ORANGE.
IT HAD A RUBBER
WING ON IT,
AND THE EYES LOOKED LIKE
THEY WERE JEWELS, YOU KNOW.
IT'S AROUND THE
LODGE SOMEWHERE.
UH -- WELL -- NO.
I ACTUALLY BELIEVE
THAT THAT LURE
SOMEHOW FOUND ITS WAY
TO MY PLACE.
NOW, I DON'T KNOW HOW
THAT COULD'VE HAPPENED.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE I
SLIPPED IT HOME IN MY TOOLBOX
AFTER LAST WEEK'S
MEETING OR ANYTHING.
I THINK I'LL JUST GO
BACK HOME -- NIP BACK HOME
AND I'LL BRING THE
LURE BACK HERE, OKAY?
MAKE THE GHOST
MORE SATISFIED,
HAPPY, AND --
YEAH, YOU KNOW, MIKE,
I THINK THAT'S A
GREAT IDEA.
I MEAN, IT'S NO
BIG DEAL, RIGHT?
I MEAN, YOU SAID YOURSELF
IT WAS A LOUSY LURE.
I MEAN, IT NEVER
CAUGHT ANYTHING.
NOT UNTIL NOW, NO.
Red: UH, ONCE A YEAR
WE GO OUT THE BACK
AND TRY TO CLEAN UP LODGE.
I HATE THAT DAY.
DALTON SAID HE'D HELP,
AND HE HAD SOME KIND
OF A PLAN.
HE WAS GONNA
BRING A MACHINE.
I WASN'T QUITE SURE
WHAT HE WAS GONNA DO.
WE HAD A DUMPSTER
ALL SET THERE.
THERE'S DALTON NOW.
HE'S GOT THE TRUCK.
HE'S GOT SOMETHING IN THE
BACK HE'S GONNA USE FOR
THE CLEAN-UP HE SAID.
I DIDN'T KNOW --
BY GOLLY, I BELIEVE THAT'S
A JET ENGINE, ISN'T IT?
FIRST THING WE GOTTA DO,
WE GOTTA GET HER OUTTA THE --
THEY'RE HEAVY.
THOSE UNITS ARE HEAVY.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THEY FLY.
THEN DALTON GETS AN IDEA.
IT'S A JET ENGINE.
IT'LL GET ITSELF
OUTTA THE TRUCK.
THERE WE GO.
SO NOW WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO
IS USE THE JET ENGINE
AS BASICALLY A
VACUUM CLEANER.
SO WE DUCT TAPED HER TO
THE SIDE OF THE DUMPSTER.
THEN WE RAN A HOSE
OFF THE INTAKE SIDE.
THEN DALTON SAID --
I'LL FIRE IT UP,
AND LET'S SEE
HOW SHE'S GOES.
OH, BOY.
OH, MY GOSH!
THAT THINGS GOT A LOT --
HOLY COW!
THERE'S THE
GARDEN HOSE EVEN.
WOW!
LOOK AT THAT THING GO!
THAT'S GOT A LOT --
OH, MY GOODNESS.
LOTTA SUCTION.
YEAH, IT WORKS ON
DRY STUFF, DALTON.
BUT HOW DOES SHE FARE
WITH THE WET STUFF, HUH?
THAT'S WHAT I
ALWAYS WANNA KNOW.
OH, MY GOLLY,
PRETTY DARNED GOOD.
LOOK AT THAT.
OH, HO-HO.
OH, BOY.
AND THERE'S OUR WHOLE YARD
CLEANED UP IN ABOUT
FIVE MINUTES.
FANTASTIC JOB.
WELL, I JUST --
THAT'S ENOUGH FOR ME.
I WANNA JUST -- I'LL GO IN
AND WATCH THE GAME NOW.
BUT, DALTON, HE WANTS TO --
I DON'T WANNA --
DALTON, I DON'T CARE.
NO, I KNOW IT WORKS.
IT'S FINE.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
I'VE SEEN A DUMPSTER
FULL OF GARBAGE BEFORE.
WHAT?
WELL, THIS ONE ISN'T.
WHERE THE HECK?
OH, DALTON.
I THINK YOU MISJUDGED WHERE
YOU PLACED THE JET ENGINE.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, NOW HE
GETS TO DRIVE IT AWAY.
[applause]
TODAY ON THE TALKING
ANIMALS PORTION
OF OUR SHOW,
LOCAL ANIMAL
CONTROL OFFICER, ED FRID,
IS GONNA TELL US
ALL ABOUT FOXES.
YEAH.
THAT'S RIGHT, RED.
OR AS THEY'RE KNOWN IN THE
SCIENTIFIC COMMUNITY,
Vulpes vulpes.
WOW!
WHAT DOES Vulpes MEAN?
FOX.
SO THE SCIENTIFIC
NAME IS FOX FOX?
SEEM A LITTLE
REDUNDANT TO YOU?
WELL, NOT IF YOU
GOT ONE CHASIN' YOU.
YOU KNOW,
FOX! FOX! FOX!
OKAY.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
FOX! FOX! FOX!
I UNDERSTAND.
OKAY.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU
BRING HIM OUT HERE?
YEAH.
OKAY, UH --
ACTUALLY, RED, YOU KNOW,
IT'S A SHE,
AND YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO REFER
TO THE FEMALES AS VIXENS.
I'M NOT DOING THAT,
THANKS, ANYWAY, ED.
JUST GET THE FOX
FOR US, WILL YOU?
YEAH. MM-HMM.
RIGHT.
UH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
SOMETHING ELSE I
JUST REMEMBERED
IS FOXES REALLY
AREN'T ALL THAT SLY.
THAT'S JUST
A MYTH.
I FIND THAT THEIR
INTENTIONS ARE VERY CLEAR.
GET THE FOX, ED.
YOU GOT IT.
YOU KNOW, RED,
UM, I THINK MOST
PEOPLE ALREADY KNOW
WHAT A FOX LOOKS LIKE.
ED, YOU'RE DOIN' A SEGMENT
ON MY SHOW ABOUT FOXES.
OF COURSE YOU DO.
TO SEE A FOX.
I THINK WE NEED
ALL RIGHT, FOR THOSE OF YOU
HERE IN THE STUDIO AUDIENCE,
I WOULD CAUTION YOU,
DO NOT MAKE ANY SUDDEN MOVES,
OR CROSS YOUR LEGS IN
SUCH A WAY THAT THE ANIMAL
COULD MISTAKE YOU
FOR A CHICKEN.
OH, BOY.
EASY. EASY.
OH, BOY. OH, BOY.
EASY. OKAY, EASY.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOOD.
DON'T ANYBODY PANIC.
OKAY, THERE YOU GO.
[laughter]
THAT'S A DOG, ED.
IT'S A MEMBER OF
THE CANINE FAMILY, YES.
THIS IS A
FOX TERRIER.
WELL, LET'S NOT ARGUE
ABOUT SEMANTICS, RED.
YOU TOLD ME YOU WERE
BRINGING A FOX,
AND YOU BRING ME
A FOX TERRIER?
WELL, THIS SHOULD
BE GOOD ENOUGH.
I MEAN, IT'S GOT
THE WORD FOX IN IT.
JUST USE YOUR IMAGINATION.
I'M PAYING YOU 100 BUCKS,
AND YOU BRING IN
A FOX TERRIER?
NO, YOU'RE PAYIN'
ME 200 BUCKS.
NO, I'M PAYIN' YOU 100 BUCKS.
JUST USE YOUR IMAGINATION.
THE SMART HANDYMAN KNOWS
THAT YOUR BEST PROJECTS
ARE DONE ALONE.
THAT WAY THERE'S NOBODY
THERE TRYING TO TELL YOU
HOW STUPID OR
IMPOSSIBLE THEY ARE.
UNFORTUNATELY...
IT MEANS YOU HAVE TO DO ALL
THE HEAVY LIFTING BY YOURSELF.
WHEN YOU WANNA TAKE
THE PROJECT INDOORS
TO, SAY, THE DINING
ROOM TABLE,
THERE'S NO ONE THERE TO
HOLD THE DOOR OPEN FOR YOU.
WELL, HERE'S A
SIMPLE SOLUTION.
MOUNT A ROPE FROM THE DOOR
INTO THE CHUCK OF YOUR
ELECTRIC DRILL.
THEN PLUG THE DRILL
INTO A MOTION DETECTOR.
THAT'S THE PART THAT'LL OPEN
THE DOOR WHEN IT SEES
YOU COMING.
NOW, TO CLOSE THE DOOR,
TAKE THAT OLD THIGH MASTER
FROM THE BOTTOM OF
YOUR WIFE'S TO DO LIST,
AND HOOK THAT ON THERE AS YOUR
SPRING LOADED DOOR RETURN.
AND SHE WORKS LIKE A CHARM.
AS SOON AS I GET
PAST THE THRESHOLD,
THE MOTION DETECTOR
SHUTS THE DRILL OFF,
AND THE THIGH MASTER
CLOSES THE DOOR.
OH, MAN.
[applause]
WE AT ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES
WOULD LIKE TO REMIND YOU
IT'S CABBAGE SEASON.
TIME TO PUT US ON
SPEED DIAL.
WHERE DO YOU WANT ME TO PUT
THIS, MR. GHOSTBUSTER?
RIGHT IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE ROOM.
GHOSTS ALWAYS LIKE TO BE
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE ROOM
SO THEY CAN SEE
ALL THE EXITS.
CAN'T THEY FLOAT
THROUGH WALLS?
UH, WELL, YEAH,
SOMETIMES.
I MEAN, THERE'S DIFFERENT
LEVELS OF GHOST, YOU SEE.
THEY'RE CALLED
DIFFERENT LEVELS.
DIFFERENT LEVELS?
YEAH, YEAH, EXACTLY.
LIKE, SOME GHOSTS
CAN WALK THROUGH WALLS;
AND SOME GHOSTS
CAN GO THROUGH --
MENOPAUSE?
ARE YOU GONNA BE
SERIOUS ABOUT THIS?
YOU KNOW, IT DOESN'T SEEM
TO BE GOING THAT WAY, NO.
OPEN THE TRUNK.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GONNA GET
IN THERE, MIKE?
NO, NO.
I'M GONNA DROP THE POSSUM
LAKE WIGGLER IN THERE.
THEN WHEN OUR
GUEST COMES ALONG,
HE'LL GO INSIDE THERE.
I FLIP THE LID SHUT.
WE GOT HIM.
I MEAN, WHAT BETTER LURE
TO CATCH THE GHOST OF
HENRY THORKELSON
THAN THE ONE
HE INVENTED HIMSELF?
THAT'S PRETTY
GOOD DETECTIVE WORK.
OF COURSE, YOU'VE
MET SO MANY OF THEM,
HAVEN'T YOU, MIKE?
OKAY, YOU GOTTA BE QUIET.
GO TURN OUT THE LIGHT,
AND FIND SOMEWHERE TO
SIT AND WAIT, OKAY?
WHY DO I HAVE
TO BE QUIET?
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO SPOOK A GHOST.
WE DON'T WANT HIM
TO NOTICE US.
NOTICE US?
HOW STUPID IS THIS GUY?
WELL, HE WAS A
LODGE MEMBER.
ALL RIGHT, FAIR ENOUGH.
BOY, IT'S GETTING COLD
IN HERE, ISN'T IT?
HERE IT IS!
OH, BOY.
audience: OOOH!
WHERE'S HE GOING?
OH, THERE HE IS!
OVER TO THE TRUNK!
GO GET HIM!
GET HIM! GET HIM!
GET HIM!
GOT HIM!
WAY TO GO, MIKE.
[screaming]
GET OFF!
[possum squealing]
NOT WITHOUT ME!
MEETING TIME.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I DON'T CARE WHATEVER
I'VE SAID IN THE PAST,
I LIKE ALL OF YOUR RELATIVES
THAT HAVE EVER BEEN BORN
SINCE THE
BEGINNING OF TIME.
AND TO THE
REST OF YOU,
THANKS VERY MUCH
FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HENRY THORKELSON
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP
HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[cheering and applause]
COME ON IN HERE AND SIT DOWN.
COME ON.
COME ON IN.
HAVE A SEAT.
MEETING COMING
TO ORDER HERE.
SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, I'M REAL
PLEASED TO ANNOUNCE
THAT THE LATE
HENRY THORKELSON
IS NO LONGER LATE.
HE'S NOT COMING.
[applause]