It's a new red green show.
And now here's the man who brings the
outdoors indoors to your door.
The man you adore coming
through that door, Mr.
Red Green.
Thank you. Appreciate it very much.
Well, this morning I was walking around
downtown, downtown.
We're downtown. We have we hardly have a
town, let alone a downtown where its downtown
is that.
Where the Roads Cross Herald, OK, we got a
building on each corner around here, that's
an urban core.
So anyway, I'm walking around downtown, got
the shock of my life.
Oh yeah, I meant to tell you. Murray
installed a full length mirror in front of
his store.
I'm talking about what was in the store,
Harold had a satellite dish in there for the
TV and I'm thinking to myself, Boy, you
know, if we had one of those up at the lodge,
we could watch outdoor shows from all over
the world kind of compare our show to theirs.
Mind you, I guess that would be like
comparing apples and oranges.
Or apples and a lemon.
Sounds like sour grapes from a second
banana to me.
What do you think?
On today's show, we have the usual animals,
plus a four legged one visiting up at the
lodge, Ranger Gordon is watching out for fire
again.
There's one there and a report that and this
here, I really can't explain it.
You're just going to have to stay and watch.
I thought you said you'd never, ever, ever,
never, never, ever buy a satellite dish for
the launch.
I didn't buy one, Harold.
I made one. Oh no, not that patio umbrella
that you lined with
Foil potato chip bags.
Now, Harold, that one blew away one night
right in the middle of Baywatch.
No, no, we got a new one. This is a real
solid, made it out of the roof from the top
of the corn silo over at Farmer Nash's
place.
The roof? Yeah. Did he give it to you?
One of the finders keepers.
We've got a satellite dish.
Oh yeah, we got all the stations.
Oh yeah, we're already getting about a
million stations, but now we're going to put
a motorized unit on there so that you can
change the game, you know, from satellite to
satellite without leaving the comfort of
your TV room.
Oh wow, this is great.
We can use like the satellite to scan the
universe for signs of intelligent life.
Oh, we're not interested in intelligent life.
We want television. Coming up later on,
Bill's going to try.
He's going to try a pogo stick.
Bill is a man of action.
I got a pogo stick is all action, and I'll
tell you something for every action.
There's an equal and opposite reaction.
And sometimes some water, OK?
This is the big one
For a free ice cream cone with any purchase
of a scoop of ice cream from the House of
Vanilla. All right. All right.
You have 30 seconds to get Mr.
Stevenson to say this word.
Thirty seconds go.
All right, Bob, wedding, divorce.
Wedlock head look.
Matrimony. Alimony.
Not now, Bob, I think you've had five
ex-wives, so you've experienced this five
times.
Sex.
Oh, there are so many things your head can do
it and see thing, feel, talk and smell your
head as a part of your body, you should use
the most because it does so many things to a
darn well. Use your head wisely.
Clean it protected. You can never go wrong.
But if you find yourself banging it against
a wall for hours and hours on end, that's a
pretty good chance. I've been married a
little bit too long.
Now we get a lot of questions for a range of
guard up here on the line.
And unfortunately, the only one I can repeat
on television is Ranger Gordon.
How many forest fires have you spotted from
the tower here?
Oh, well, red. Do you mean just this year or
all together?
No.
Altogether, yeah. Altogether, yeah.
Let's see.
You can just round it off. Yeah, yeah.
Non fiction. Yeah.
Want to know the secret in being an
effective forest ranger or that coffee
coffee? That's right.
And I grind my own blend ranger Gord Java.
It consists of peach pits, acorns and these
coffee plant leaves.
No Gordon. I believe that's poison ivy.
You got there, really?
Yeah. Wow. Well, it works.
It works like the Dickens, you know, one cup
of this, and I'm up scratching my lips all
night. Here, let me mix you up a batch of
Ranger Gordon Java OK,
Cups, gasoline kind of high.
And also. Typekit, Mayday, Mayday, Mayday.
This is Fire Watch Tower 13, Fire Watch
Tower 13.
We've got a fire.
The coordinates. Where am I?
I'm up in my tower here.
Send a water bomber right away with lots of
people.
Ok? All right.
Fire is kind of out here. It's kind of it's
gone.
It's done, it's done there.
So, yeah,
You know, it's a good thing that I was here
to spot it and report
It and start it up.
At the lodge, we turn accidents into
opportunities as most of our parents did so
this week on Handymen Corner, I'm starting
with an accident.
This is the kind of thing that can happen
when you leave your car park between two
railroad tracks, and both trains come along
at the same time.
Now, I suppose we could collect up the
pieces and put them back together again.
But the problem there is the front end is
over in Halifax in the back half in
Vancouver. At times like this, you wish you
had a smaller country.
So instead I'm going to take this unit and
turn it into something else.
Now what are the two favorite things that
men love to do most?
All right. Well, now since this is a family
show, although I'd certainly be frightened to
meet that family now, we're going to
restrict our two choices to driving a car and
watching television.
Now what if we can combine those two?
I'm not talking about just putting the
television set into a car.
I'm talking about somehow combining the
driving experience with watching television.
So what I'm going to do is take a little bit
of ingenuity and this piece of garbage here
and a piece of duct tape, a major railroad
accident.
I'm going to turn this dashboard into a
television remote controller, a man sized
Zapper. Sound ingenious.
Sound incredible. Sound impossible.
Who cares? I'm not listening.
It's going to work great with our new
satellite dish.
Let's start her up.
By flooding it.
There we go. There we go. Here she comes.
There she goes. Oh yeah.
And I can control the volume on the unit,
which is with my radio knob here.
When I want to change channels, I just turn
the steering wheel.
I can call this turner broadcasting.
This has been taken and the beauty is I
don't use my turn signals, which I don't use
anyway, actually. And I got my panel light
dimmer there to control the brightness of the
TV. Inefficient spill, some stuff on there,
maybe even some pasta or any sort of meals,
or what have you on to the screen, to the
TV?
I can clean that off because I got it all
hooked up to my washer and wiper control.
All right now, I can just reach over to your
glove compartment.
Get out your TV guide.
You're browsing through that.
I tell you something else. You know what's
great? The cigarette lighter can use that to
heat up your coffee. Know.
Here we go. Just like that.
And the ashtray is a perfect spot to keep
any of your favorite snacks like good.
Way down on the bottom.
Listen to the radio, uh, smoky flavor.
And when there's nothing on TV, I just
switch over to my VCR where I've got fast
forward or I've got freeze frame.
What am I going to watch this? This is my
favorite show.
Oh yeah. Oh, here's another feature I can
block out whatever Harold saying.
Come on. Hurry up. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Yeah.
So remember, if the women don't find you
handsome, they should at least find your
handy. Oh hey, I like this part.
Oh, I'm going to watch that again.
Rewind.
Ranger Gord doesn't have his head in
the clouds, he's got the clouds in his head.
Stay tuned.
Lot of you guys are asking me,
Red, I'm 40 something, but am I really
middle aged? I'll tell you what.
Here's a few signs that I'll let you know.
You may already have lined up for a ticket
to Geyser City.
Have you started putting the screws into a
glass jar?
And I'm not talking about this cruise, I
mean, old rusty pastry now with the bunged up
slots on them because it gives you a chance
to use your new label maker.
Have you turned down a hot tub party with
attractive naked people so you could stay
around the house and putter as your
underwear gotten all homely and threadbare?
Because there's no chance anybody other than
you, the wife and the heart attack emergency
unit are ever going to see you. Well, I'm
telling you, just relax, you're a normal,
virile male in the prime of life.
Middle age is just a state of mind.
And if you don't mention the state of mind
mind, I'll be happy to overlook yours.
However, I'm pulling for you, we're all in
this together.
I with the satellite dish up and running
there, we thought we motorized her with a
couple of garage door openers, you know, and
kind of spin around this.
Then I got the idea why don't we use the
garage doors to have everything kind of
hidden away? Then when you want to watch TV,
you push a button.
She flips up, you know, and then all the
satellite dishes kind of move around and then
you can flip a right back around when
there's a storm coming or something, you
know? That's cool.
Yeah, that's really cool. You know what
that's like?
That's like that show, Thunderbirds.
That's my most favorite show, right?
Yeah. Yeah, because when someone phones
international rescue, right, Mr.
Tracy goes, Thunderbirds go and
Then they watch like.
The tough call, that's a very good shot, you
know,
Oh, you know what, because then brains, he's
like my most favorite character in the whole
show is the brains. He's great because he'll
go launch Thunderbirds, right?
And then all these secret doors, they just
open right and come to this launch pad.
And there's this this red one, right?
It's the first one, and it goes and it goes,
it's gone, right?
This is the first one he was told to go.
You go right. So then the sudden the
president goes, Thunderbird go, and the
second one goes and he's like, green, you
know, like a like a frog or moose Thompson or
something, right? So he goes, he's got to
write Thunderbird three go.
And then this door where he goes Thunderbird
three, he's out of there, right?
I'll say, you know what happens? No, what
happens?
What happens now? What happens?
Doors close, doors close.
And it just looks like an island like
Gilligan's Island, which is my second most
favorite job. Well, right.
It is. I like Mary and I like Mary.
I do. I like hearing a lot of people like
Ginger.
I think she's shallow. I do.
She thought her desert island while she's
thinking about us.
Oh, how do I look? You know, like that?
All right.
What are we talking? I have no idea.
Hi, ranger, Gord. Way up here at Fire
Watchtower, 13.
You know, a lot of people ask me, Do you
ever get bored up here?
Well, I say to them, Hey, how can I ever get
bored when I've got my imagination in so many
different clouds? Like, look at that one
that looks like Barbara Beam cutting the
line. Hey, look at that one.
That one looks like Raquel Welch sharpening
her pencils.
Oh, look at that one that looks like one of
the women from Gilligan's Island.
Well, there's a woman smiling at me and
waving, and she just has a towel on.
Ok, so let's say you're in real trouble.
Doesn't matter what for. Never does.
No, but whatever the trouble is, we have a
few golden rules that all men follow to sort
of help you ease the
Squeeze rules that men have followed for
hundreds of years.
We're going to pass them on to you.
Yeah.
Ok, first of all, don't argue back.
It just it just winds them all up.
The more you let her blow it all off, the
quicker you can get back to your normal
routine.
There's nothing that bugs a woman more than
someone who
Disagrees with him. No, that brings us to
rule number two.
Always agree with her, no matter what she
says.
Yeah, you got to look her straight in the eye
and go, You know something dear.
You're absolutely right.
Oh, the time, not a completely disarm them,
the
Only trick, though, is you've got to be
humble for at least an hour afterwards, they
otherwise you'll realize that you're pulling
Your chain. That brings us to rule number
three.
Never underestimate a woman, OK?
A woman is the most sophisticated, clever,
intuitive creature on the face of the Earth.
You, on the other hand, are just a man.
Tell you one thing, if you're talking
safety, you are not talking to us, Sherwin.
Hey, hey, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa. Thank you.
You got a safety tip first.
Hey, two words red ATV.
All right. All right. I know what talking
about the all terrain vehicles.
That's right. That's right. No, I got one.
So I know they are overpowered.
They are skittish. They are hard to stop.
Talk about fun. Whoa.
So be careful you can get injured.
You mean from them tipping over easy or from
falling off?
No, no. It seems to be the brakes.
They they are just like, totally useless
when they're wet.
So remember that safety first?
Well, maybe the brakes just need to be
adjusted.
Do you have the owner's manual buzz?
Yeah, it's in the compartment under the
seat.
Well, why don't you go get that?
And we'll see what it says? Ok.
Oh. Well, I hope that that satellite dish
thirty six hours ago and the guys
haven't stopped watching TV.
You know, the more average North American
watches six hours of TV a day, you know that?
Yeah, I heard that if we didn't watch that
much TV, we'd have like time to earn six
college degrees, maintain five hobbies and
being peak physical condition.
Wow. Is that true? Where'd you hear that?
I don't know. Some show I was watching.
Mean these guys haven't even taken a bathroom
break.
Junior sink was down there hopping from one
foot to the other, yelling Buy a foul by a
vowel.
That's buy a vowel.
Uncle Ray, they're watching
Wheel of Fortune now they're watching E.R..
Ok, I'll get him out of the TV room, don't
you worry.
All right. All right. I tell you what you can
do smack on the head with that if you have
to.
A New York City phone book?
No, no. That's the satellite TV guide.
Look at all these mindless stuff.
Look at that. Huh? Boy, Thunderbirds
Guttenberg.
Channel five hundred and sixty two.
That's a I've only seen this one five times,
it's a group.
The safety smart, handy man knows you should
always start each new project with a clean
workspace. Today, we got an adventure with
Bill for all of you teenagers who
should be studying physics instead of
physics.
We're going to kind of concentrate on one of
Newton's laws here, and I don't mean the one
with the fig in it. This is the one that
says for every action, there's an equal and
opposite reaction.
I got the pogo stick there and Bill's adding
energy, so I'm going to try to subtract a
little bit jumping down on the pogo stick.
There he compresses it.
Oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, all right.
Now you see, that wouldn't have gone nearly
as far if he hadn't put as much energy into
the pole, because that's a that's a valuable
lesson.
About 80 bucks.
I think it was. Phil's got an idea.
Oh boy, is that good news?
I'm thinking. Probably not.
This is the TV antenna tower that we no
longer need now that we got the satellite
dish. So Bill thinking, Hey, wait a minute,
maybe I can just use this for a project.
Still fun to watch, isn't he?
What? There's the action, there's a
reaction.
Appreciate that, Bill.
And recycle the air and oh no, it's fine,
you don't care, it's not your truck anyway,
she's going to use a tower part like at this
point, we've kind of made a commitment.
So we want to be down there and just walk.
You should warn a person when you put
something down.
Took me a while to catch my breath.
I was OK. I should have kept my eye out
bill, I guess.
We'll be back to finish that when I regained
consciousness.
Stay tuned.
Well, thirty seven hours and
counting since I hooked up the satellite
dish, not one person who's wandered into
that TV room has come out alive.
I haven't seen that many slack jawed, dull
eyed blank expression since my Grade 10 class
picture.
It's so quiet in here.
The mice are coming out of the wall and just
joining us.
It's just. It's too quiet.
I hate it way, way too quiet here to join
the lodge and be here to join the lodge
because we can on the TV room.
Yeah, it's that way.
Oh, oh, I'm OK.
Ok, read read you OK, man, I'm OK.
Oh, you're going to fly like that?
Get doors on the plane. Yeah.
What's in the expert portion of the show and
on this week's expert parts of the show, we
have the experts Michael Redd and its good
friend, Doug E.
Franklin. Our first letter goes as follows
Dear
experts, huh?
Recently, recently, my girlfriend and I were
out cruising in my Camaro on our way to a
street race when she pulled her scarf off my
rearview mirror and told me it was all over
between us. Oh all right, the next night,
next night, I saw her on the back of some
guy's motorcycle.
How can I win back the girl of my dreams?
Rap in Boston?
Well, I'll tell you, fella, I
Think if you want her back, this is what you
got to do.
You got to get your vehicle into the shop.
You got to get your rings done and your
headers chrome.
What you're saying is this romance just needs
a little tune up.
Well, yeah, in a matter of words, yeah, a way
of speaking.
I would say that romance red.
She is like your internal combustion engine.
If you want her to run smooth, you got to
maintain your spark.
Now my advice to bereft is check your timing
gap your plugs.
You may not need that jump start.
All right. I don't think it's very
flattering.
People don't want their love life compared
to a slant.
Six.
It's an accurate comparison, though, and I
think Berraf has just got to hope that the
problem is only the spark, because if it
ain't the spark, then it's the gas.
We all know how quickly you can kill a
romance when you are backfiring
Down lovers lane.
Meanwhile, back at the science lesson, I got
an ice pack on my head there, and Bill's got
a drainpipe and he's got this thing and he's
got a bungee.
Meanwhile, back at the science lesson, I
have two ice packs and the bill has cut the
tower down. He's got a drainpipe.
He's got bungee cords.
And he's what? He's done this.
What has he done? Oh my gosh.
He's made a gi gundu pogo stick.
Holy mackerel. You know you got to hand it
to cold.
Bill dries my ear.
I recently brought the van in which I wish
he had explained to me earlier.
He's going to jump up on top of her there,
so he has a higher mountain.
And then if young people are listening to
this, you should pay attention to because you
see your father from the center of the
Earth.
And I believe the gravity pulls down on you
with more gravity, and I'm a prop that up to
him. And here's the action he's going to
take by stepping on that.
And here's the reaction I'm going to take if
I get the heck out of the way.
There he goes. Look at the world's largest
pogo stick between evil, an evil entity that
won't watch your bill is a big hit, big
hole.
Oh, don't you look at that reaction?
Oh my.
Class is dismissed.
Ok. Something's wrong with the satellite
feed, we're not getting a good picture, a
comment. Oh really, Harold.
I'm sorry, I was gone. How long is it gone?
Like half an hour, huh?
Twelve and a half hours, Harold?
No. Oh yes, we know.
I just saw because I just watched like that
one rerun of vanished.
And then there's a little bit of the car
race, you know, and then I watch Best
Celebrity Circus, you know?
And then there was there was those few game
shows in there and some music videos.
And then there's those people line dancing.
But I watch that infomercial about the
sunglasses, you see the watch and then model
Zinke was on. And what year is it now?
Oh, to hear that, to hear that, I think
there's an episode of Lassie starting here.
That's a call meaning.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, because, you know, because it sounded
like Star Trek or Next Generation
Carol, it's the meet and get down there right
now.
It's the meat. Yeah.
Right.
So if my wife is watching, I'll be coming
straight home after the meet and I am sick to
death of television.
I'm going to stop at
the video store and get a movie.
Rest of you, thanks so much for watching on behalf of
myself and Harold and the whole gang up here
at Possum Lodge,
keep your stick on the ice.
(Possum squealing)
Quando omni flunkus moritati.