IT'S THE "NEW RED GREEN SHOW."
(APPLAUSE)
AND NOW HERE'S THE
MAN WHO PUSHES
THE ENVELOPE,
BUT DOESN'T HAVE
SUFFICIENT POSTAGE
TO SEND IT ANYWHERE,
YOUR HOST,
YOUR HERO,
MY UNCLE,
RED GR-E-E-N!
(APPLAUSE)
THANKS.
GOT AN EXCITING
GROUP HERE TONIGHT.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE'VE GOT
A BIT OF AN EMERGENCY
UP AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK.
ONE OF THE LODGE
MEMBERS IS MISSING.
VANISHED WITHOUT A TRACE,
AND HE'S NOT EVEN MARRIED.
SO THAT CAN ONLY
MEAN ONE THING...
ALIEN ABDUCTION?
OH, NO, HAROLD.
NO, NO.
IF THE ALIENS EVER
COME HERE, YOU'LL BE
THE FIRST ONE THEY'LL GRAB.
COOL.
I GOT A FEAR OF
FOUL PLAY GOING ON HERE,
BECAUSE THIS GUY HASN'T
MOVED MORE THAN 20 FEET
IN THE LAST 18 YEARS.
NOT OLD MAN SEDGWICK?
NO, NOT OLD MAN SEDGWICK.
MELVIN DUFFY.
HAROLD, HAROLD!
MELVIN DUFFY IS DEAD.
WELL, YOU DIDN'T SAY
WHY HE HASN'T MOVED.
IT'S RANGER GORD.
RANGER GORD IS MISSING
FROM HIS TOWER.
WE'RE GOING TO GO LOOK
FOR HIM AS SOON AS WE GET
THE 4X4s ALL GASSED UP.
EVERYTHING YOU GUYS DO
IS ALL GASSED UP.
WE SHOULD BE LOOKING
FOR HIM ON FOOT.
WHERE'S THE FUN
IN THAT, HAROLD?
SEARCHING FOR SOMEBODY
ISN'T SUPPOSED TO BE FUN.
OH, YEAH?
WELL, HOW COME
THEY CALL IT A
SEARCH PARTY?
(QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC)
THESE ARE ALL SCENES FROM
THIS EPISODE OF OUR SHOW.
WE EVEN HAVE GOT A SPECIAL
SURPRISE FOR YOU.
SO A SECRET KIND OF
THING GOING ON HERE.
NO, DON'T SHOW THEM THAT.
THEY BLEW IT.
OKAY, HAROLD --
HEY, GUYS -- GUYS.
OKAY, HAROLD, I SPOKE TO ALL THE
GUYS, AND THEY'RE WILLING TO LET
YOU JOIN THE SEARCH PARTY.
BUT YOU CAN'T KEEP YELLING
"SLOW DOWN,"
AND IF YOU FALL OFF THE
ROOF RACK, WE'RE NOT
GOING BACK FOR YOU.
OKAY, THAT SOUNDS FAIR.
I'M IN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
RANGER GORD IS MISSING.
I WENT UP THERE TO
FIRE WATCHTOWER 13,
AND THE WHOLE DEAL
HAD FALLEN OVER.
LOOKED LIKE BEAVERS HAD KIND OF
GNAWED ON THE FRONT LEGS THERE,
AND THE WHOLE THING COLLAPSED.
AND RANGER GORD IS GONE.
EVERYTHING'S GONE.
HIS CLOTHES, HIS STAMP
COLLECTION, HIS EIGHT TRACKS,
THE LAVA LAMP, EVEN THE
DISCO BELT, SO THIS IS SERIOUS.
UNCLE RED, OH -- OKAY --
YOU KNOW, I DON'T -- THIS IS
GOING TO BE EVEN SCARY TO SAY.
I MEAN, I HATE TO
EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
WHAT HAPPENS IF --
THE WORST CASE SCENARIO IS...
HE COMES BACK
TO THE LODGE?
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT IT.
OH, LIFE IS FULL OF MYSTERY
THINGS THAT BOTHER
YOU AND ME
LIKE, HOW COME
EVERYONE ELSE IS OVERPAID?
BUT THE BIGGEST MYSTERY
TO MICE AND MEN
IT COMES UP IN CONVERSATION
AGAIN AND AGAIN AND AGAIN
IS HOW IN HOLY BLAZES
ARE SAUSAGES MADE?
WELL, THEY TAKE A LITTLE
OF THIS AND A BIT OF THAT
GROUND UP HOOVES
AND LOTS OF FAT
HIDE AND HAIR AND
BONE AND BARK AND TWIGS
VEINS AND ARTERIES,
GRISTLE AND GRIT
AND THEY GRIND IT UP FINE,
SO THAT IT'LL ALL FIT,
CRAMMED UP INTO THE
EXIT RAMP OF A PIG
WELCOME TO
"THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME."
AND THIS WEEK'S GRAND PRIZE IS
FOR 100 ASSORTED TREETOPS
FROM BUD SHERWOOD'S
HELICOPTER RIDES.
OKAY, UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30
SECONDS TO GET Mr. DOUGIE
FRANKLIN TO SAY THIS WORD.
LOVE.
GO! -- LOVE -- LOVE...
OKAY. ALL RIGHT. DOUGIE, WHEN
THERE'S SOMEONE WHO YOU CAN'T
LIVE WITHOUT, THAT'S...
A KIDNEY DONOR.
NO, THIS IS WHAT A MAN AND WOMAN
FEEL BETWEEN EACH OTHER...
GEAR SHIFT?
OKAY. WHEN A COUPLE KISS AND
CUDDLE, THEY'RE IN...
THE BACK SEAT.
NO.
PASSION.
MONSTER TRUCK.
NO, I MEAN, YOU KNOW, THOSE
ROMANTIC SONGS, THEY'RE
ALWAYS ABOUT...
CARS AND SURFIN'.
ALL RIGHT, DOUGIE.
YOUR HEART IS POUNDING.
YEAH.
YOU'RE BARELY TOUCHING
THE GROUND.
YEAH.
YOU'RE IN...
FOURTH GEAR.
JUST A
MINUTE NOW.
OKAY, YOU'RE WITH THE
ONE YOU DREAM ABOUT,
YOUR EVERYTHING, OKAY?
YOU'RE IN...
MY GARAGE.
ALMOST OUT OF TIME,
UNCLE RED.
COME ON, DOUGIE, THERE'S MORE
TO LIFE THAN CARS AND
MONSTER TRUCKS.
OH, YOU'VE NEVER
BEEN IN LOVE, HAVE YOU?
THERE YOU GO!
(BELL RINGING FRANTICALLY)
IT SEEMS THESE DAYS,
MORE AND MORE PEOPLE ARE TAKING
LONGER AND LONGER VACATIONS.
THAT'S BECAUSE MORE AND MORE
PEOPLE ARE GETTING HOISTED OUT
OF THEIR JOBS THERE, YOU KNOW?
SO YOU WANT TO HOLIDAY CHEAPLY,
BUT YOU WANT TO GO IN STYLE.
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER,"
WE'RE GOING TO TURN THE POSSUM
VAN INTO A PALACE ON WHEELS.
THAT'S RIGHT, ALL THIS STUFF IS
GOING TO GO INTO THE VAN THERE.
WE'RE GOING TO BE
TRAVELLING IN STYLE.
ALL RIGHT. WE START BY LAYING A
REMNANT CARPET IN THERE THAT
WE GOT FROM STINKY PETERSON.
ACTUALLY, HE OWED IT TO ME
SINCE HIS DOG WAS SICK.
BUT, NOW, CARPETING IS
SOMETHING YOU MIGHT OVERLOOK.
BUT, YOU KNOW WHAT? THE
CARPETING MAKES IT LOOK LIKE
YOUR VAN WAS CUSTOMIZED BY A
PROFESSIONAL CUSTOMIZER.
SO THINK CUSTOMIZERLY.
SO ONCE YOU GOT YOUR WHEEL TO
WHEEL CARPETING IN THERE,
YOU WANT TO TOSS IN YOUR VERY
FAVOURITE RECLINER ROCKER.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET PRETTY TIRED
AFTER A HARD DAY OF DRIVING,
AND YOU NEED SOMETHING
COMFORTABLE TO SIT ON, HUH?
YOU'RE ON VACATION,
SPOIL YOURSELF.
IF THIS RECLINER IS ROCKING,
DON'T BOTHER KNOCKING.
OR, MORE THAN LIKELY, IF IT'S
RECLINING, DON'T BOTHER CHIMING.
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE GONNA NEED
SOMETHIN' TO KEEP YOUR FOOD
FRESH AND YOUR BEVERAGES COLD.
YOU COULD BUY ONE OF THEM
UNDERSIZED, OVERPRICED
R.V. FRIDGES.
BUT I SAY, WHY BOTHER?
WHEN YOU ALREADY OWN
ONE JUST LIKE THIS?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
ALL RIGHT, NOW, JUST ADD A BED,
MICROWAVE,
ENTERTAINMENT CENTRE THERE,
YOUR CLOCK RADIO,
A COUPLE OF GAS LAMPS,
PICNIC TABLE,
A CHEMICAL TOILET,
YOU'RE IN BUSINESS.
ALL RIGHT, I'M THINKING WE NEED
TO MAYBE SCALE DOWN OR SCALE UP,
OR MAYBE EVEN LOSE
SOME WEIGHT HERE.
(CRASH)
ALL RIGHT, TIME FOR A RE-THINK.
WAIT'LL YOU SEE HOW I GOT
EVERYTHING ARRANGED IN HERE.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE
HOW MUCH OPEN SPACE.
I NEVER THOUGHT FOR A SECOND
THAT THE POSSUM VAN COULD TURN
INTO SOMETHING --
WATCH YOURSELF ON THE
RUNNING BOARDS HERE.
YOU KNOW, OF COURSE, THE SECRET
WHEN YOU'RE DOING A
PROJECT LIKE THIS
IS TO PLACE EVERYTHING SO THAT
IT USES THE SPACE ECONOMICALLY,
ERGONOMICALLY,
AND, WELL, ASTRONOMICALLY.
I'VE GOT THE WASHER HERE
AND THE DRYER
AND THE WHOLE UNIT SET UP HERE.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE, ISN'T IT,
JUST HOW MUCH SPACE WE'RE
GETTING OUT OF THE VAN?
COURSE, ANOTHER SECRET IS THE
ORIENTAL ART OF THE 'FENG SHUI,'
WHICH IS AWFUL GOOD
WITH THE BREADED CHICKEN.
AND THAT CREATES SOME SPACE
AND GIVES YOU A FLOW.
AND YOU WANT TO TALK
ABOUT FLOW, HOW ABOUT
HOT AND COLD RUNNING WATER?
AND A SPARE TIRE RIGHT THERE
ANY TIME YOU NEED IT.
I MEAN, IS THIS COZY OR WHAT?
YOU CAN LIVE LIKE A KING AND
TAKE IT ON THE ROAD WITH YOU.
IMAGINE JUST SITTING IN HERE,
DRIVING ALL DAY LONG, HUH?
NOW THAT'S A HOLIDAY.
THAT'S LIVING.
AND, OF COURSE, WITH THIS
UNIT HERE, YOU'VE GOT ALL
THE CONTROLS RIGHT AT
YOUR FINGERTIPS.
YOU GOT YOUR WIPERS,
YOU GOT DEFROST,
AIR CONDITIONING.
SO THERE YOU HAVE IT,
THE ULTIMATE MOTOR HOME.
WHY DON'T WE TAKE HER FOR
A LAP AROUND THE BLOCK, AND
SEE HOW SHE HANDLES?
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU'RE HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
(QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC)
I'M HOPIN' TO TALK TO YOU OLDER
GUYS ABOUT SELF-IMPROVEMENT.
YOU KNOW THESE SELF-HELP GURUS
TRYING TO SELL YOU THEIR
PROVEN METHOD
OF HOW YOU CAN BE IN
PERFECT SHAPE OR TOTALLY HAPPY
OR, THE BIG ONE,
HAVE MONEY FOR RETIREMENT?
HEY, DON'T LISTEN TO THEM.
THEY ALL HAVE THE
SAME BASIC SECRET...
YOU GOTTA WORK HARD.
YOU DON'T WANNA HEAR THAT.
IF YOU HAD WORKED HARD IN THE
FIRST PLACE, YOU WOULDN'T BE
BUYING THEIR TAPES NOW,
YOU'D BE RICH AND PEOPLE WOULD
BE BUYING YOUR TAPES.
YOU DON'T WANT A SENSIBLE PLAN,
YOU WANT A SHORTCUT.
YOU DON'T NEED THE SEVEN HABITS
OF EFFECTIVE PEOPLE,
YOU NEED THE ONE QUICK CHEAT
OF LAZY GOOF-OFFS.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
YOU DON'T WANT ADVICE,
YOU WANT A MIRACLE.
AND I'M GUESSING YOU CAN'T BUY A
MIRACLE FROM A SMILING BALD GUY
ON AN INFOMERCIAL.
SO DON'T LET HIM SUCK YOU IN.
WHEN HE TALKS ABOUT
HAVING MONEY FOR RETIREMENT,
HE MEANS HAVING YOUR MONEY
FOR HIS RETIREMENT.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
SEARCH PARTY, COME IN.
THIS IS POSSUM BASE.
COME IN, SEARCH PARTY.
ANY SIGN OF RANGER GORD?
OVER.
(INDISCERNIBLE SHOUTING)
ROGER.
OVER AND OUT.
THEY'RE FINE. THEY'RE JUST
TALKING ABOUT WHO'S GOING TO
DRIVE THE LEAD VEHICLE
AND STUFF.
YOU KNOW, GUY TALK.
ROPE, HAROLD.
NEED ROPE TO GET
HIM OUT OF THE GORGE,
AND DYNAMITE TOO.
WHAT? RANGER GORD
FELL IN A GORGE?
NO, BUSTER HADFIELD
ON HIS A.T.V.
DOING THIS STUPID SHOWING
OFF WITH THE BLINDFOLD.
AND THEN STINKY WENT TO GET HIM,
AND THEY'RE BOTH DOWN THERE NOW.
ANY SIGN OF
RANGER GORD?
WHO?
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I'LL TELL YOU, IF HE'S
ANYWHERE WITHIN 20 MILES,
HE'S GOING TO SEE THE SMOKE.
OH, SEE, THAT'S A GOOD
IDEA,THEY'RE USING
SIGNAL FLARES.
NO, NO, STINKY'S PICK-UP
HAD A TOUCH OF SPONTANEOUS
COMBUSTION THERE, HAROLD.
BARBECUE FELL
OFF THE TAILGATE.
THOSE IDIOTS THAT DESIGN
TRUCKS AND PUT THE GAS
TANK AT THE BACK.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, YOU MAYBE
WANT TO HELP US SEARCH HERE TOO.
NO, NO, NO, I THINK I'LL
JUST STAY HERE AND HELP
DIRECT AMBULANCES.
WELL, HERE ON
"TRICKS OF THE TRADE,"
WE USUALLY HAVE A GUY WHO'S
"BEEN THERE, DONE THAT."
THIS TIME, WE'VE GOT SOMEONE
WHO'S BEEN CAUGHT, DONE TIME.
HERE'S MIKE HAMAR.
TAKE IT AWAY, MIKE.
(APPLAUSE)
THANKS, Mr. GREEN.
YOU KNOW, WHEN PEOPLE
FIND OUT I'M AN EX-CON,
THEY ALWAYS ASK ME HOW
TO AVOID GETTIN' MUGGED.
HEY, I COULD USE THE CASH.
WHY SHOULD I TELL YOU?
OH, GEE, I LOVE THAT
TYPE OF HUMOUR.
OKAY, IF YOU WANT TO AVOID
GETTIN' MUGGED, THE THING TO
DO IS STAY AWAY FROM MUGGERS.
NO, SERIOUSLY.
LOOK, IF YOU'RE FAR AWAY
FROM A MUGGER,
HE CAN'T MUG YOU, RIGHT?
NOW, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
THE LONG ARM OF THE LAW,
BUT A CRIMINAL'S ARM IS
ONLY ABOUT YAY LONG.
CAN'T REACH YOU, SEE?
NOW, IF YOU'RE REALLY STUPID
ENOUGH TO HANG OUT WITH
A BUNCH OF MUGGERS,
YOU SHOULD LEARN THIS
SELF-DEFENCE MOVE.
HERE, TAKE IT.
THAT'S IT.
YOU JUST REMEMBER --
JUST REMEMBER THOSE THREE LITTLE
WORDS:  "HERE, TAKE IT,"
AND YOU HAND OVER YOUR WALLET,
AND YOU'LL BE BROKE,
BUT HEALTHY.
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW, I WOULDN'T
WORRY ABOUT IT AT ALL
BECAUSE THE ODDS AGAINST GETTING
MUGGED IN A BIG CITY ARE
ABOUT 1 IN 1,000.
SO THAT'S, LIKE,
365 DAYS IN A YEAR,
INTO 1,000 AND YOU CARRY --
WELL, IT WORKS OUT TO
ABOUT THREE YEARS, RIGHT?
SO, ONE DAY OUT OF
EVERY THREE YEARS,
STAY HOME.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
I GOT DOWN TO THE POND A LITTLE
BIT AHEAD OF BILL THERE,
AND I WAS SKIPPING STONES.
BROUGHT BACK --
LEAVE ME ALONE, BILL --
AND BROUGHT BACK A LOT
OF MEMORIES WHEN I WAS
A KID AND EVERYTHING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE ADVENTURE
WAS, BUT I WAS JUST KIND OF --
WHAT ARE WE?
OH, SO THOSE WEREN'T JUST
ORDINARY -- I'VE GOT ONE LEFT.
ONE:  THAT'S STILL
A COLLECTION.
EVEN ONE, YEAH,
ONE IS A COLLECTION.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, OH, ALL RIGHT.
NOW, COME ON.
THERE'S LOTS OF STONES, BILL.
THERE'S STONES ALL OVER
THE PLACE.
STONES IN THE HILLS
AND IN THE VALLEY.
YEAH, THERE YOU GO.
IT'S EASY TO PERK
HIM UP, YOU KNOW?
SO BILL GOES OUT LOOKING
FOR MORE ROCKS;
GOTTA START AGAIN
WITH THE ROCK COLLECTION.
IF AT FIRST YOU
DON'T SUCCEED --
WATCH YOUR HEAD...
OW-OH.
AND YOUR FOOT.
ALL RIGHT.
NO, WE'RE FINE.
WE'RE GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, BILL
SEES A STONE THERE.
HE SEES A ROCK?
OW. OH-OH-OH.
ALL RIGHT, BILL SEES A ROCK.
HE'S -- GOT THE MAG --
LOOK AT THE MAGNIFYING GLASS.
MAGNIFIES SO HE CAN SEE VARIOUS
GRAINS AND MAYBE SOME OF
THE MINERALS AND --
THIS IS THE KIND OF THING THAT
THE BRE-X PEOPLE SHOULD'A HAD.
THERE'S SOMETHING THAT YOU
YOUNGER KIDS MIGHT WANNA WATCH.
SEE, THE SUN IS ACTUALLY GOING
THROUGH THE GLASS --
WELL YOU CAN --
(SNIFFING)
I DUNNO.
IT'S NOT THE ROCK.
WHAT IS IT?
OH, THERE IT IS.
THERE IT IS.
IT'S YOUR FOOT, BILL.
IT'S YOUR FOOT.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
OH, IN THE POND.
IN YOU GO.
THERE.
FEELS GOOD.
I THINK THAT'S HOW
TEA WAS INVENTED.
ANYWAY, WE'LL GET
THAT SHOE OFF.
EMPTY IT OUT, BILL.
QUITE A BIT OF WATER.
BOY, THAT HOLDS A LOT.
MUST BE ONE OF
THOSE WATER JORDANS.
ANYWAY, WE GET BACK TO LOOKING
FOR THE ROCKS THERE AND --
LOOK OUT, BILL,
THERE'S A ROCK.
NOT A ROCK -- IT'S A RAKE.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE A ROCK.
IT CERTAINLY FELT LIKE A ROCK.
WELL, BILL'S GOT ONE THERE.
AND GOT THE --
I'M FINE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME, BILL.
I'M OKAY BACK HERE.
NO, NO, I'M FINE, REALLY.
NO, NO, DON'T BOTHER YOURSELF.
LATER THAT SUMMER, BILL HAD
ACTUALLY UNCOVERED THE ROCK.
MAN, I WAS JUST SITTING
DOWN FOR A COUPLE
OF WEEKS THERE.
AND, ANYWAYS,
HOW ARE YOU GOING --
WHAT ARE YOU DOING THERE?
OH, ALL RIGHT. THIS IS GOOD.
A LITTLE BIT OF PHYSICS HERE.
WE GOT THE LAW OF THE LEVER.
AND HE'S GOING TO STICK
THAT IN AND HOPEFULLY
JUST LEAVE 'ER.
NO, HE'S NOT -- OH, BOY.
THESE ARE GROWN MEN
THAT ARE TRYING THIS.
BEAR THAT IN MIND.
ANYWAY, WE'RE TRYING TO GET
THAT THING GOING --
AND THEN, POOF!
UP SHE GOES.
THERE YOU GO, BILL.
THERE'S YOUR ROCK.
GO GET IT.
IT'S YOURS, BILL.
IT'S ALL YOURS.
OH, OH, OH.
AND THERE'S BILL'S
ROCK COLLECTION.
WELL, THAT'S NOT PERFECT, NO.
NO, SOMETHING WRONG WITH THAT.
THERE WE GO.
PERFECT.
(QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC)
I'LL TELL YOU, THE SEARCH PARTY
FOR RANGER GORD
TURNED INTO THE RESCUE PARTY
FOR THE OTHER HALF OF
THE SEARCH PARTY.
WE SAVED ALL THE LIVES,
OVER HALF OF THE TRUCKS,
AND MOST OF THE HOT DOGS.
NO SIGN OF
RANGER GORD, THOUGH.
NO, NO.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
WOW.
LOOK AT ALL
THOSE PEOPLE.
RANGER GORD, WE WERE
LOOKING EVERYWHERE FOR YOU.
NO, NO,
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S OKAY.
DID YOU GO INSANE FROM
LONELINESS AND RUN OFF?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
WE DIDN'T KNOW WHERE
YOU WERE OR NOTHING.
WE WERE LOOKING FOR YOU.
I'M FINE.
OKAY. GOOD.
NO, I CALLED OUT
TO YOU GUYS IN THE WOODS,
BUT YOU DIDN'T HEAR ME,
I GUESS, OVER ALL THE
ENGINE NOISE.
NO, NO, WE WERE
LOOKING FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW, TOWER WAS
TIPPED RIGHT OVER THERE.
WE ASSUMED
THE WORST.
OH, YEAH. WELL, I FINALLY
RAN OUT OF CREAMED CORN,
SO I WAS FORCED TO EAT
THE FRONT TWO LEGS OF MY TOWER.
I COULDN'T EAT THE BACK LEGS
BECAUSE THEY'RE MAPLE AND,
AS YOU KNOW, RED,
I'M HARDWOOD INTOLERANT.
SO YOU JUST WALKED AWAY,
JUST LIKE THAT?
WELL, NOT EXACTLY.
I MEAN, IT'S BEEN 17 YEARS
SINCE I LAST GOT A PAYCHEQUE,
SO I DECIDED
TO TAKE A STAND.
ALL RIGHT.
YEAH.
THEY LAID ME OFF.
GOVERNMENT
CUTBACKS.
OH, YEAH, NO, NO,
THERE'S A LOT OF THAT
THESE DAYS, YEAH.
NO, THIS WAS 17 YEARS AGO
WHEN THEY LAID ME OFF.
THE POST OFFICE LOST A LETTER
CONTAINING MY PINK SLIP.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
CAN YOU IMAGINE IF THE FORESTRY
DEPARTMENT WAS RUN AS BADLY
AS THE POST OFFICE?
BOY, THE LETTERS
WE WOULDN'T GET.
ANYWAYS, I'M BACK
IN CIVILIZATION.
OH, NO, YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE AT POSSUM LODGE.
I'VE NOTICED THAT YOU TEENAGE
BOYS ARE KIND OF INTO THE
FAST FOOD, FAST CARS AND
FAST COMPUTERS;
WHEREAS THE GIRLS
ARE JUST INTO FASTING.
SPEED IS A BIG ISSUE
WITH YOU YOUNG FOLKS.
IT SEEMS THE FASTER THINGS GO,
THE HAPPIER YOU ARE.
I GUESS YOU NEVER HEARD THE
STORY ABOUT THE TORTOISE
AND THE HARE, EH?
BECAUSE, TO ME, YOU YOUNG GUYS
ARE KIND OF LIKE THE HARE,
AND US OLDER FELLOWS ARE MORE
LIKE THE TORTOISE...
WE DON'T HAVE THE HAIR ANYMORE.
I'LL TELL YOU, IF LIFE HAS
TAUGHT ME ONE THING,
AND IT'S PROBABLY ALL IT HAS,
IS THAT THE FASTER YOU GO,
THE MORE YOU MISS.
AS YOU GET OLDER,
YOU'RE GOING TO REALIZE
THAT WE'RE ALL, PRETTY MUCH,
HEADING FOR A BRICK WALL.
THE QUESTION IS:  HOW HARD DO
YOU WANT TO HIT IT?
REMEMBER, ANYTHING WORTH DOIN'
IS WORTH DOIN' SLOW.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW.
THAT PART OF THE SHOW WHERE WE
EXAMINE THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
Audience:  I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S SO COOL.
ALL RIGHT, JOINING UNCLE RED
ON THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW THIS WEEK
IS HIS GOOD FRIEND AND THE OWNER
OF HUMPHREY'S EVERYTHING STORE,
Mr. DALTON HUMPHREY.
(APPLAUSE)
WELCOME.
OKAY.
THIS WEEK'S LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS...
"MY WIFE AND I HAVE
BEEN MARRIED FOR 32 YEARS."
WELL, THERE'S VERY LITTLE
WE CAN DO FOR YOU NOW.
THAT'S NOT IT.
THERE'S MORE.
JUST LET ME
FINISH HERE.
"RECENTLY, THE LAST OF OUR
SEVEN CHILDREN GRADUATED
FROM HIGH SCHOOL
"AND MOVED OFF TO GO TO
MCDONALD'S UNIVERSITY.
"EVER SINCE OUR LAST CHILD LEFT,
MY WIFE HAS BEEN IN A
TERRIBLE BLUE FUNK.
"WHAT'S HER PROBLEM?"
NO IDEA.
NOW, DID I HEAR RIGHT?
THEY HAD SEVEN KIDS,
THE KIDS HAVE GONE.
AND NOW THAT THE KIDS
ARE GONE, SHE'S UPSET?
DID THE KIDS
COME BACK HOME?
NO, NO, THEY GREW UP AND THEN
THEY WENT OFF TO UNIVERSITY,
SO SHE'S HOME ALONE
WITH HER HUSBAND, SO...
SHE RAISED THE CHILDREN, YOU
KNOW, ALL THOSE YEARS
AND, YOU KNOW, NOURISHED
THEM AND FED THEM, WATCHED
THEM GROW, SUPPORTED THEM,
AND THEY MOVED OUT ON TO
UNIVERSITY AND --
SHE'S ALONE WITH A MAN NOW --
HER HUSBAND -- AND THEY'RE
ALONE IN THE HOUSE...
AND, YOU KNOW, AND HE
DOESN'T UNDERSTAND HER
MOODS OR NEEDS AND WANTS.
IT'S AN EMPTY NEST SYNDROME,
IS WHAT IT IS, YOU KNOW!
EMPTY NEST SYNDROME,
YOU KNOW?
THIS POOR WOMAN
IS GOING THROUGH
A BIG CHANGE IN
HER LIFE.
OH, THE CHANGE.
OH, YES, I KNOW
WHAT THE CHANGE IS.
I JUST NEVER
HEARD IT CALLED
"EMPTY NEST."
THAT'S A BIT GRAPHIC.
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
YOU KNOW, YOU TURN
THE THERMOSTAT DOWN,
IT'LL BE FINE.
NO, HER CHILDREN ARE GONE.
HER CHILDREN HAVE MOVED ON.
HER LIFE...
YOU DON'T GET IT, DO YOU?
NO, YOU DON'T.
OH, YOU GUYS SHOULD BE SO
ASHAMED. YOU DON'T EVEN GET IT.
WHAT'S HIS PROBLEM?
PUBERTY.
RANGER GORD IS COMING.
DON'T UPSET HIM, ALL RIGHT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?  WHAT?
APPARENTLY, HE SPENT
18 YEARS IN THE WOODS;
HE'S GOT NOTHING
TO SHOW FOR IT, OKAY?
EVENTUALLY HE'S
GOING TO REALIZE
HE WASTED HIS LIFE.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
HI, GUYS.
OH, LOOK,
IT'S GORD!
OH, HEY, GORD.
HI, HOW ARE
YOU DOING?
JUST WANDERING AROUND
THE LODGE, SEEING HOW
THINGS HAVE CHANGED,
I GUESS.
A LOT OF THINGS HAVE
CHANGED IN 18 YEARS.
NOTHING.
SORRY.
HAROLD.
WHAT?
(WHISTLING)
NO, THE LODGE IS
PRETTY MUCH THE SAME.
FURNITURE IS THE SAME.
THE SAME GARBAGE
IN THE CORNER.
SAME TUB OF COTTAGE CHEESE
IN THE FRIDGE.
WE GOTTA
THROW THAT OUT.
I'LL MAKE A NOTE.
STINKY'S STILL
ON WORKMEAN'S COMP.
BUSTER'S STILL
DATING THAT WAITRESS.
MOOSE'S NICKNAME
STILL FITS HIM.
NOBODY'S GONE BACK TO WORK OR
STARTED A NEW JOB OR
GONE BACK TO SCHOOL.
NOTHING.
18 YEARS AND NOTHING
TO SHOW FOR IT.
OH, NOW, GORD, NOW
DON'T BE HARD ON YOURSELF.
ME? NO, I'M GOING TO CASH IN ON
EVERYTHING I'VE LEARNED IN THE
LAST 18 YEARS IN THE WILDERNESS.
YEAH, I'M GOING TO CREATE
A CHARACTER THAT'LL TEACH
KIDS ABOUT THE WILDERNESS.
YOU KNOW, LIKE SMOKEY THE BEAR
OR AYLMER THE SAFETY ELEPHANT.
I'M GOING TO BE GOPHER GORD.
OKAY, GOOD FOR YOU, GREAT.
(POSSUM CALL)
OH, SEE, THAT'S A
SQUEAL OF A POSSUM.
THAT MEANS MEETING TIME.
OH, WOW, YOU GUYS
STILL DO THAT?
YEAH, WE DO.
IT'S RIGHT
DOWN HERE.
WHOO!
BOY, YOU KNOW, IT'S SAD, YOU
KNOW, WHEN PEOPLE DON'T REALIZE
THEY'RE WASTING THEIR LIVES.
MAYBE THEY JUST
DON'T WANT TO LOOK.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETIN',
AND I HOPE THE FURNITURE IS
BACK THE WAY I LIKE IT...
IN THE STORE WINDOW.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTER.]
Harold:  ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red:  SIT DOWN.
Harold:  ALL RIGHT, I'VE JUST
GOT THE ONE ANNOUNCEMENT
FOR TONIGHT...
AND IT'S FROM RANGER GORD.
HE'S INVITING EVERYONE BACK TO
HIS CABIN FOR A SLEEPOVER.
AND THERE'LL BE PRIZES.
OH, GREAT THERE'S GOIN'
TO BE PRIZES. TERRIFIC.
FOR THE SCARIEST STORY
AND FOR THE BEST
BARRY WHITE IMITATION,
WHICH ACTUALLY IS
SORT OF THE SAME THING...