THERE'S A GENERAL FEELING
AMONG THE GUYS
THAT ANYBODY WHO HAS
A LOT OF KNOWLEDGE,
EDUCATION OR
ACCURATE INFORMATION
IS PROBABLY BORING.
WE PREFER TO GO
ON GUT FEELING.
NOT THAT WE HAVE
LOT OF GUTS
BUT MOST OF US
HAVE A LOT OF GUT.
NOW, DON'T CONFUSE
THIS WOMEN'S INTUITION
BECAUSE WITH MEN
IT'S DIFFERENT.
WOMEN'S INTUITION
IS USUALLY RIGHT.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU,
MEN GET A LOT MORE FUN
OUT OF A GOOD HUNCH
THAN THEY DO OUT
OF A SOLID FACT.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT MAKES
US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
ON TODAY'S SHOW, HAROLD'S
GOING THROUGH SOME OF HIS
NORMAL TEENAGE ANGST,
BILL'S GOT A LITTLE
SQUIRREL THERE
WITH A REAL BIG
NUT TO DEAL WITH,
I'M GOING TO
DO SOME DRIVING
AND SHOW YOU HOW TO
FIND A PARKING SPOT
EVEN DURING RUSH HOUR.
AND NOW HERE
IS THE REASON THEY
INVENTED LIFE JACKETS,
MY UNCLE RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AND HERE IS THE REASON
WE DON'T WEAR LIFE
JACKETS,
MY NEPHEW, HAROLD.
THINGS ARE REAL HECTIC
UP AT THE LODGE
THIS WEEK.
WE JUST GOT THE
WEATHER REPORT IN.
HUGE STORM WARNING
COME THAT'S GOING TO
BLOW ALL THE BOATHOUSES FLAT.
I DIDN'T HERE ANYTHING
ABOUT A STORM WARNING
EFFECT ON THE RADIO.
OH, HAROLD, WE DON'T
LISTEN TO THE RADIO FOR
OUR WEATHER REPORT.
WE GET OUR WEATHER
STUFF DIRECT FROM OLD
MAN SEDGEWICK'S BODY.
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S
BODY CAN'T PREDICT
THE WEATHER
EXCEPT FOR MAYBE
A COLD FRONT MOVING IN.
OH SURE IT CAN, HAROLD.
STIFF NECK MEANS SNOW,
WHEN HIS LEFT HAND
CRAMPS UP LIKE THAT
MEANS IT'S GOING TO
BE A COLD SUNNY DAY
JUST AROUND FREEZING,
SHOULDERS GET SORE,
TEMPERATURE IS GOING
TO GO UP.
THIS MORNING HIS
HIP SEIZED UP SO BAD
WE KNOW THERE'S A
BIG STORM COMING.
AND JUDGING BY THE
WAY HE'S HUNCHED OVER,
I THINK YOU CAN
EXPECT A LOT OF WIND.
THIS IS WAY MORE
ENTERTAINING THAN
STARING AT A FOREST.
WELL, THIS IS THE STORY
ABOUT LUCY DEPP
SHE HAD A HUSBAND
THAT SNORED
AND NOTHING WOULD STOP
HIM AND NOTHING WOULD HELP
AT LEAST NOTHING THAT
LUCY COULD AFFORD
THEY SAY YOU SHOULD
WAKE A SNORER UP
SO THAT'S WHAT LUCY DID
THE GOOD NEWS IS IT
STOPPED HIS SNORING
BUT LUCY NOW
HAS 17 KIDS
OKAY.
YOU GOT A PROBLEM.
YOU GOT AN ANNIVERSARY
THAT YOU THINK IS
COMING UP
BUT IN FACT IT'S
NOT COMING UP,
IT HAS GONE BY.
IT WAS YESTERDAY.
YOU PULLED A COMPLETE
BLANK, TOTAL AMNEMIA.
AND NOW YOU GOT TO
BE DIGGING YOURSELF OUT,
BECAUSE, BROTHER,
YOU'RE IN THE
DEEP STUFF.
WHICH, YOU
KNOW, HAPPENS TO
BE MY SPECIALTY, EH?
SO YOU COULD SAY
OH, GEEZ, I FORGOT
ABOUT OUR ANNIVERSARY.
YOU COULD SAY
THAT, YOU KNOW.
AND YOU COULD JUST
LIE A LITTLE BIT
AND SAY, OH,
WELL, THAT DOESN'T
MATTER, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE SHE WOULD
FORGIVE YOU.
SHE WON'T.
AND WHY SHOULD SHE?
BUT HERE IS
WHAT YOU DO,
YOU TELL HER YOU
POSTPONED THE
ANNIVERSARY
'TIL THE WEEKEND
BECAUSE THE SPECIAL GIFT
THAT YOU GOT
HER WON'T BE
DELIVERED 'TIL THEN.
THIS IS GREAT.
NOW YOU GOT 'TIL THE
WEEKEND TO GET THE GIFT.
NOW, IF YOU FORGET TO
GET HER A GIFT ON
THE WEEKEND,
YOU'RE ON
YOUR OWN BUD.
OR PLAN B, PLAN B,
YOU WHIP OUT
YOUR WALLET
AND YOU POINT
TO LAST YEAR'S
CALENDAR CARD.
YOU GO, THERE'S YOUR
PROBLEM, RIGHT DAY,
WRONG YEAR.
LOOKS LIKE NEXT
YEAR WE'LL JUST HAVE
TO CELEBRATE THE
ANNIVERSARY TWICE.
THAT MIGHT WORK.
OF COURSE IF IT
DOESN'T, YOU KNOW,
YOU MIGHT NOT EVEN
BE CELEBRATING THE
ANNIVERSARY THE ONCE.
YOU KNOW, OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
HAS GOT ME THINKING
ABOUT SOMETHING
THAT WE DON'T DO
VERY WELL UP HERE
AT THE LODGE,
ADVERTISE.
HE HAS THE ABILITY
TO PREDICT WEATHER
WITH HIS BODY
AND HE'S NOT
MAKING A THIN
DIME OFF OF IT.
IF HE WAS THAT
RONCO GUY, HE'D
PROBABLY MARKET IT
AS THE POMPEEL POCKET
POOL WEATHER PICKER.
BUT OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
REFUSES TO GET UP OFF
HIS ASSET AND ADVERTISE.
YOU GOT TO BLOW
YOUR OWN HORN,
EVEN AT HIS AGE.
AND SO DO WE.
WE WANT TO KEEP THE
RED GREEN SHOW ON THE AIR
DESPITE THE CRITICS
AND THE RATINGS AND
THE NETWORKS.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO ADVERTISE, TOO.
NOW, I SUPPOSE, WE
CAN TAKE OUT AN AD
IN SOMETHING LIKE
THE NEW YORK TIMES
OR PUT THE NAME
OF THE SHOW
ON THE EXPOSED BODY
PARTS OF EXOTIC DANCERS,
BUT THAT
COSTS MONEY.
I GOT A BETTER IDEA
THAT I STOLE FROM
WINSTON ROTHCHILD,
THE LOCAL SEPTIC TANK
PUMPER GUY AROUND HERE.
HITTING YOUR NAME
AND/OR PRODUCT RIGHT
ON TO YOUR VEHICLE.
IT'S FREE, IT'S MOBILE
AND IT WILL BE SEEN BY
EVERYBODY YOU PASS,
BACK INTO OR
DRIVE OVER.
I HAVEN'T JUST STOPPED
AT PUTTING THE NAME
ON THE CAR HERE,
NO, SIR, I PAINTED
'ER UP JUST LIKE
THE POSSUM VAN,
WHICH IS WORLD FAMOUS
IN PARTS OF ALASKA.
I EVEN PUT SOME
OF THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET ROLL BAR
IN HERE UP ON
THE CORNERS.
WELL, TECHNICALLY THIS
ISN'T ACTUALLY MY CAR,
IT'S BUSTER'S,
BUT I THINK HE'LL
REALLY LIKE WHAT
I'VE DONE WITH IT.
I EVEN PUT TEETH
ONTO THE FRONT BUMPER
JUST LIKE I GOT ON
THE POSSUM VAN,
AND I PUT THE POSSUM
BROTHERHOOD CREST UP
HERE ON THE HOOD
SO IT WILL BE SPOTTED
BY THEM TRAFFIC HELICOPTERS.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
THEY TELL ME THAT FOR
SOMEBODY TO HAVE AN AD
SINK INTO THEM,
THEY'VE GOT TO
SEE IT 25 TIMES.
WELL, YOU CAN'T DRIVE
PAST SOMEBODY 25 TIMES
ON THE HIGHWAY
WITHOUT INCURRING A
LOT OF ANGRY GESTURES
OR POSSIBLE GUN PLAY.
SO I'M SAYING WHY
DON'T I DRIVE THIS
THING AT A PLACE
WHERE I'LL GET A ROTATING
HIGH FREQUENCY OF
VENUES IN FRONT
OF MY TARGET AUDIENCE,
WHICH IS TO SAY I'M
GOING TO DRIVE 200
LAPS IN A CAR RACE.
ANNOUNCER: CAR NUMBER 11,
RED GREEN FROM
POSSUM LODGE.
RED GREEN: WELL, OBVIOUSLY A
LOT OF GUYS HAD
THE SAME IDEA,
BUT AT LEAST
I'LL WAVE
MAYBE THEN I'LL STAND
OUT A LITTLE BIT
FROM THE REST.
ANNOUNCER: THE GREEN
FLAG IS DOWN AND
WE ARE RACING.
AND AWAY WE GO AND
THE IMPORTANT THING
HERE IN CAR RACING
IS TO GET ONE OF
THE OUTSIDE LANES
SO YOU'RE OUT THERE
WHERE THE PEOPLE
CAN SEE YOU
AND JUST DO
WHATEVER YOU CAN TO
DRAW ATTENTION TO YOURSELF.
I'M KIND OF SCANNING
THE AUDIENCE, SEE HOW
MANY OF THEM ARE LOOKING,
READING THE
RED GREEN SHOW SIGN.
AND MAYBE POSSIBLY
THERE'S A POSSIBILITY
I TOOK MY EYES OFF
THE ROAD A LITTLE
BIT TOO LONG.
I THINK IT'S
JUST BUSTER'S
CAR DOESN'T CORNER.
OH GEEZ, I STALLED HER.
OH MAN.
COME ON.
COME ON, BABY.
THERE WE GO.
AND JUST MERGE,
MERGE, MERGE.
EXCUSE ME.
THERE WE GO.
NOW THE DIRT --
THAT'S NOT A
GOOD THING,
IT'S HARD TO --
ANYWAY, NOW I'M
IN THE MIDDLE LANE
SO I'M BEING EXPOSED TO
AN ENTIRELY DIFFERENT
SET OF DRIVERS
BUT MAYBE NOT SO
MUCH TO THE STANDS.
AND THERE I'M BACK
OUTSIDE, BACK OUTSIDE.
THERE WE GO.
NICE MOVE.
THAT CAR IS LOOKING
GOOD, ISN'T IT?
GLAD WE WASHED HER.
THERE'S THIS DARN
CURVE AGAIN.
OH BUSTER.
GOSH.
OH NO.
STALLED HER.
ANNOUNCER: RED GREEN'S,
CAR NUMBER 11,
HE IS HEADED IN THE
WRONG DIRECTION.
RED GREEN: I THOUGHT
I WOULD GIVE THEM
A LITTLE DIFFERENT
ANGLE HERE
SO THEY GET TO SEE THE
SIGN FROM BOTH SIDES.
I TELL YOU ONE THING,
THEY WON'T FORGET ME.
I DARE YOU GUYS TO HIT ME.
I WAS KIDDING.
RED GREEN: STAY TUNED.
DALTON IS GOING TO
SELL YOU ONE
OF HIS PRECIOUS
ANTIQUES,
AND, LOOK, IT'S SAP
TIME UP AT THE LODGE.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
YOUNGER VIEWERS OUT
THERE ABOUT GUNS.
I HEAR WHERE KIDS
ARE CARRYING GUNS,
TO HIGH SCHOOL,
TO JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL,
EVEN TO PUBLIC SCHOOL.
AND THESE KIDS ARE NOT
PART OF THE SCHOOL'S
BIATHLON TEAM.
SEEMS THAT "SHOW AND TELL"
HAS GIVEN WAY
TO SHOOT AND ASK
QUESTIONS LATER.
NOW, I'LL ADMIT THAT
THERE'S A CERTAIN
AMOUNT OF HUNTING
THAT GOES ON UP
HERE AT THE LODGE,
BUT IT'S ALL LEGAL,
IT'S IN SEASON
AND IT'S DONE WITH ALL
THE SAFETY RULES IN MIND.
AND, BESIDES, NOTHING
EVER GETS SHOT BECAUSE
THE ANIMALS HAVE THE
INTELLECTUAL EDGE.
GUNS ARE FOR SPORT,
NOT FOR SCHOOL.
I BLAME THE PARENTS.
I THINK YOU GOT TO
WATCH FOR THE SIGN
WHEN A KID HAS SOME
BAD STUDY HABITS.
FOR, EXAMPLE WHEN YOU
GOT A NINE YEAR OLD
GOING TO SCHOOL WITH
A SEMIAUTOMATIC WEAPON,
THERE'S A PRETTY GOOD
CHANCE HE DOESN'T HAVE
HIS HOMEWORK DONE.
I THINK MAYBE THAT'S
TIME FOR DAD TO SIT DOWN,
HAVE A FATHER-SON
TALK AND GIVE HIM THE
GUIDANCE THAT HE NEEDS.
MAYBE GIVE HIM A HUG
OR TELL HIM HOW MUCH
YOU CARE ABOUT HIM.
START TO REBUILD THAT
RELATIONSHIP THAT YOU'VE
LET SLIP AWAY.
JUST MAKE SURE HE
KEEPS HIS HANDS OUT
WHERE YOU CAN SEE THEM.
WE ARE MOMENTS AWAY
FROM THE BIGGEST RIP
SNORTING STORM
TO HIT THIS AREA SINCE
THE ONE THAT WASHED
AWAY POSSUM HILL.
EVERYTHING AROUND
THE LODGE OF VALUE
HAS BEEN NAILED DOWN,
TIED DOWN,
BOLTED DOWN
OR BURIED.
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S
HIPS ARE SEIZED UP SO BAD
HE HAD TO GET
SOMEBODY ELSE TO
DO HIS PAPER ROUTE.
UNCLE RED,
I'VE SCANNED THE
CLEAR BLUE HORIZON,
THERE'S NOT A
CLOUD IN THE SKY.
THE BEST WEATHER COMPUTERS
AND SATELLITE PHOTOS
SAY THERE IS GOING
TO BE NO STORM.
EVEN THE COLOUR RADAR
ON THE WEATHER CHANNEL
SAYS THERE'S NO
PRECIPITATION
IN THE AREA,
AND YOU KNOW
TELEVISION DOESN'T LIE.
YEAH, RIGHT.
WELL, JUNIOR DOESN'T
AGREE WITH YOU, HAROLD.
HE TOOK ALL THE
SHINGLES OFF HIS ROOF
AND PUT THEM DOWN
IN THE BASEMENT
SO HE KNOWS WHERE
TO FIND THEM WHEN
THE STORM IS OVER.
MOOSE THOMPSON HAS
BOARDED UP HIS WINDOWS
AND FLINTY MCCLINTOCK
EVEN TOOK DOWN HIS
CHRISTMAS LIGHTS.
YOU SEE THE PANIC
YOU'RE CAUSING?
THERE IS GOING
TO BE NO STORM.
HAROLD, I'M ONLY
GOING TO SAY
THIS ONCE,
IF YOU CARE ABOUT YOUR
CHICKENS AS MUCH AS
YOU SAY YOU DO,
I THINK YOU BETTER
GET OUT THERE AND
TIE UP THAT COOP
AND BATTEN DOWN
THE HATCHES.
WHY?
BECAUSE SOME OLD
MAN IN THE WOODS
WITH A CALCIUM DEFICIENCY
IN HIS HIP JOINTS --
WHAT'S THAT?
IT WASN'T
ME, HAROLD.
MAYBE IT
WAS THE STORM.
MY CHICKENS.
MY CHICKENS!
FORGET IT, HAROLD,
THEY'RE HALFWAY
TO OZ BY NOW.
YOU KNOW TO MOST
PEOPLE MOTHER NATURE
IS JUST A QUAINT FAIRYTALE.
BUT TO NATIVE PEOPLE,
EARTH MOTHER IS A
VERY REAL SPIRIT.
TO ME SHE'S A BIG
SUMAC NAMED GWENDOLYN.
WE'RE OUT HERE BY
THE MAIN HIGHWAY
AT HUMPHREY'S
EVERYTHING STORE
TO KIND OF ASSESS
THE AMOUNT OF DAMAGE
DONE BY THE STORM.
AND IT LOOKS TO ME
LIKE THERE'S BEEN
PLENTY HERE.
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD NEWS
FOR OUR RESIDENT CURIO
AND ANTIQUE COLLECTOR,
DALTON HUMPHRIES.
DALTON, EXACTLY HOW
MUCH DAMAGE DID YOU
SUSTAIN OUT HERE?
DAMAGE?
WOAH.
NOT ENOUGH FOR ME
I'LL TELL YOU.
JUST WISH I HAD A
CHANCE TO GET MORE
FURNITURE OUT IN THE RAIN.
YOU LOST ME
THERE, DALTON.
YOU KNOW, ANY ANTIQUE
DEALER WORTH HIS SALT
KNOWS HOW TO USE
WEATHER TO HIS
ADVANTAGE.
NOW, TAKE YOUR ACID
RAIN, YOUR TOXIC RAIN,
NOTHING DISCOLOURS
A STAIN MORE EVENLY
OR AGES MORE
BEAUTIFULLY.
YOU CAN'T GET TEXTURE
LIKE THIS OUT OF
A CAN.
OH, SO RAIN IS GOOD.
OH, RAIN IS GOOD, YEAH.
SNOW IS BETTER.
WOW.
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE
THE SENSE OF HISTORY
YOU GET WITH FREEZING
TEMPERATURES AND THEN
A SLOW THAW.
LOOK AT THIS THING.
THIS IS MONEY
IN THE BANK.
ALL THIS LATENT PAINT
JUST SCREAMS OLD
TO PEOPLE.
YOU CAN'T FAKE THIS
KIND OF STUFF WITH
A HEAT GUN.
I'VE TRIED.
NO, NO, SNOW, THAT'S
WHAT GIVES YOU THE
PERFECT FLAKE JOB.
SO THIS IS WHY THE
ANTIQUE DEALERS LEAVE
ALL THEIR STUFF OUTSIDE.
TRADE SECRET.
YEAH, PRECIPITATION,
THAT'S THE KEY, HUH?
YEAH,
PRECIPITATION.
AND, YOU KNOW,
SUN IS GOOD, TOO.
YOU KNOW THIS
THINNING OZONE LAYER
HAS BEEN A REAL BOOM TO
THE ANTIQUE INDUSTRY.
OH SURE.
HERE.
LOOK.
LOOK AT THIS.
HOW OLD WOULD YOU
SAY THIS IS?
MID-40S.
YEAH?
BOUGHT IT BRAND NEW
TWO YEARS AGO,
LEFT IT ON THE ROOF
OF THE OLD TOOL SHED.
YEAH, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
$15 TURNED TO 200.
WELL, THANK YOU,
DALTON.
IT'S ALWAYS GOOD TO
KNOW THIS STUFF,
ISN'T IT FOLKS?
OH BOY, LOOKS LIKE
IT'S TURNING NICE.
MAYBE WE'LL GET
A HEAT WAVE, HUH?
MAKE THOSE CHAIRS OVER
THERE JUST TURN IN
LIKE PRETZELS.
HOW COME SOME GUYS ARE
SO TERRITORIAL ABOUT
THEIR CARS, UNCLE RED?
TERRITORIAL, HAROLD?
THESE ARE GUYS, NOT
TIMBERWOLVES.
THEY DON'T GO AROUND
MARKING THEIR CARS
WITH THEIR SCENT.
WELL, AT THE LAST
TAILGATE PARTY
THEY DID.
OKAY, LIKE JUNIOR
SINGLETON, RIGHT?
EVERY MORNING HE'S
OUT THERE AND HE'S
WASHING HIS CAR
AND AT LUNCH HE'S OUT
THERE WAXING IT
AND RIGHT AFTER SUPPER
HE'S OUT THERE
BUFFING IT.
HE'S RUBBING THAT
THING FROM TOP
TO BOTTOM
FIVE TIMES A DAY.
HE'S JUST PROTECTING
HIS INVESTMENT,
HAROLD.
HE'S TRYING TO KEEP
THE VALUE UP
ON WHAT MANY PEOPLE
CONSIDER TO BE A
CLASSIC EXAMPLE
OF AUTOMOTIVE
STYLING AND
ENGINEERING.
AN '86 OMNI?
WELL, I DON'T
KNOW, HAROLD.
I MEAN, THERE'S SOMETHING
ABOUT A CAR, THAT'S ALL,
THE STYLE,
THE POWER,
SOMETHING.
A GIRL IN MY CLASS
TOLD ME THAT A
MAN'S VEHICLE
IS JUST A SUBSTITUTE
FOR HIS YOU KNOW WHAT.
THAT'S A GOOD
THING, HAROLD,
'CAUSE LIGHTS, MIRRORS
AND MUD FLAPS
LOOK A LOT BETTER
ON A CAR, BELIEVE ME.
WOODEN TOBOGGAN,
BY ME.
WHEN I GO TOBOGGANING,
I RIDE ON ONE
THAT'S WOOD.
IT'S FASTER
THAN ALUMINUM AND
I THINK FAST IS GOOD.
AND WOOD WILL BEND
IF YOU HIT ROCKS,
NOT LIKE SLEDS
MADE OF METAL.
AND WOOD MAKES
A GOOD STRETCHER
FOR THE RIDE
TO THE HOSPITAL.
RED GREEN:
TIME FOR ADVENTURES WITH BILL.
BILL SAID HE'S GOING
TO STOP ON THE WAY
AND GET SOME BREAKFAST.
HE PICKED UP SOME
WAFFLES, WHICH --
I USUALLY LIKE WAFFLES
BUT THESE ONES,
I DON'T KNOW,
THEY WERE PRETTY
DRIED OUT.
YEAH.
VERY DRIED
OUT I'D SAY.
BUT ANYWAY THE
IDEA IS -- OH,
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
THE IDEA IS BILL IS
GOING TO LOOK AND
FIND SOME --
NOT IN THERE BILL.
BILL IS GOING TO LOOK
AND FIND SOME SYRUP
TO PUT ON.
HE'S GOT THIS STICK
APPARENTLY HE USES
TO TAP ON THE TREE.
WELL, YOU KNOW, ONE
LESS ISN'T GOING
TO HURT.
VERY DEFINITELY
DRIED OUT.
SO HE TAPS ON
THE TREE AND THAT
ONE SOUNDS KIND OF HOLLOW.
NO.
NOW, THIS IS
INTERESTING,
THE STUMP
IS COMPLETELY
COVERED WITH THE SYRUP.
I GUESS --
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH,
OH, THAT STUFF
IS VERY, VERY STICKY.
I GUESS THE STUFF
HAD ALL GONE DOWN
INTO THE STUMP.
WHAT'S THAT?
OH, OH, OH,
FOR GOSH SAKE,
A LITTLE SQUIRREL
ALL STUCK TO THE SYRUP.
BILL HELP HIM OUT THERE.
GET HIM OFF THAT TREE.
THERE HE GOES.
OH, HE'S FINE.
HE'S FINE.
OH, ISN'T THAT
A CUTE LITTLE GUY.
WELL, THERE GOES
YOUR STICK, BILL.
THAT DOESN'T MATTER,
WE KNOW THERE'S
SYRUP IN THAT THING.
SO WE JUST TAKE A
PIPE WITH A VALVE
ON THE END.
BILL DRIVES
IT IN THERE.
HE'LL BE BACK BUT HE
WON'T BE SWINGING
THE HAMMER
WITH ME HOLDING HER,
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
SO I DRIVE HER IN,
HE HANGS THE BUCKET ON,
YOU JUST OPEN THE
VALVE AND WATCH THE
SYRUP JUST FLOW, FLOW.
OH MY GOSH.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW BILL?
WELL, BILL IS NEVER
SHORT OF AN IDEA,
NOT A GOOD IDEA,
BUT AN IDEA.
HE'S GOT THE TENSOR
BANDAGE THERE FOR
ALL HIS INJURIES
AND HE STARTS UNWINDING
THAT OFF HIS LEG
AND I BELIEVE THAT
GOES RIGHT UP TO
HIS ARMPITS.
I'M NOT GOING TO HELP
HIM, YOU NOTICE THAT.
AND HE STARTS WINDING
THAT AROUND THE TREE
REAL TIGHT
SO THERE'S
TENSION ON THERE.
I'M AWFUL GLAD PEOPLE
DON'T WALK ALONG AS
WE'RE DOING THIS,
THEY MIGHT HAVE
SOME EMBARRASSING
LESSONS FOR US.
NOW HE OPENS UP --
OH MY GOSH.
TOO MUCH PRESSURE.
TURN IT DOWN, BILL.
TURN IT DOWN.
GET THE WAFFLES.
NO, BILL, GET THE WAFFLES.
BILL FORGET YOUR JACKET,
GET THE WAFFLES.
MIGHT AS WELL GET
THE SYRUP ON THERE.
THERE YOU GO.
WOW JUST IN THE
NICK OF TIME, TOO.
THAT PRETTY WELL
DRAINED HER DRY,
I GUESS.
AND THERE'S ALL
THE WAFFLES ALL
DONE AND EVERYTHING.
NO THANKS, BILL.
I'LL FEED MINE
TO THE ANIMALS.
RED GREEN: STAY TUNED
FOR SPECIAL GUEST
GRAHAM GREENE IN HIS
MOST EXPLOSIVE ROLE.
WINSTON ROTHCHILD HERE
FOR ROTHCHILD'S
SEWAGE AND SEPTIC
SUCKING SERVICES,
WHERE OUR MOTTO IS
WASTE NOT PUMP NOT,
1-800-555-SUCK.
OKAY, I GOT A MEMO
HERE FROM STINKY PETERSON.
IT SAYS: TO ALL MEMBERS
OF POSSUM LODGE,
PLEASE STOP CALLING
ME STINKY, I'M
SICK OF IT.
OH, GOOD FOR YOU STINKY --
MR. PETERSON, SORRY.
MY NEW NICKNAME
IS AERO MATIC.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, NOW, THAT
WAS A HUMDINGER.
I LOVE THE WAY THE
STORM CLEARS THE AIR,
NO MORE PAINT FUMES
OR DIESEL FUMES.
OH, HAROLD, I FORGOT
TO ASK, HOW WERE
YOUR CHICKENS?
YOU KNOW AS WELL
AS I DO THEY
FLEW THE COOP.
LUCKILY THE
COOP FLEW, TOO.
I FOUND IT NINE
MILES DOWN THE
HIGHWAY.
WHO SAYS CHICKENS
CAN'T FLY, EH HAROLD?
ALL THEIR LITTLE
FEATHERS ARE BLOWN
OFF TOO.
SOMERSAULTED
INTO TOWN.
NOW, YOU WON'T HAVE
TO SCRAMBLE THEIR EGGS.
MY ROAD ISLAND RED,
ROAD ISLAND RED
CAUGHT UNDER A TREE...
TINY CHICKEN
MCNUGGETS.
YEAH, I HEARD,
HAROLD.
THAT'S TOO BAD,
YOU KNOW.
AND THE TALL PINE
TREE WENT DOWN,
THE BIG ONE THAT'S BEEN
IN TOWN FOR SO DARN
LONG THERE.
IT FELL OVER LIKE
A RELATIVE AT
AN OPEN BAR.
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
THAT TREE IS A PART
OF OUR HERITAGE.
WELL RIGHT NOW THAT PINE
TREE HAS THE HIGHWAY
COMPLETELY CLOSED.
LIFE IN POSSUM LAKE
HAS GROUND TO A HALT.
HOW CAN YOU TELL
THE DIFFERENCE?
WELL, HAROLD, IT'S
GIVEN US THE OPPORTUNITY
TO HAVE A CHAINSAW PARTY.
SIX HOURS AND 130
DECIBELS FROM NOW,
THE HIGHWAY WILL BE OPEN
AND EVERYBODY WILL HAVE
ENOUGH FIREWOOD TO
LAST THE WINTER.
YOU COMING HAROLD?
NO, I'M JUST GOING
TO GO LOOK FOR MY
LAST CHICKEN.
WELL, YOU KNOW, IT'S
PROBABLY UNDER THE
PINE TREE
LIKE IN THAT JOKE,
WHY DID THE PINE
TREE CROSS THE ROAD?
TO GET TO THE
OTHER CHICKEN.
OKAY, HERE'S ONE NOW
FROM MOOSE THOMPSON.
MOOSE WRITES: I'M TIRED
OF MY NICKNAME,
IT MAKES ME SOUND BIG
AND DUMB AND STUPID,
SO EVERYONE STOP CALLING
ME MOOSE THOMPSON.
MY NEW NICKNAME IS
MOOSE JOHNSON.
WE'RE UP HERE
WITH OUR FRIEND,
RANGER GORD.
HI RED.
HI EVERYONE.
I MISS YOU.
ALL RIGHT, GORD.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING TODAY?
MAKING PARTY
INVITATIONS, RED,
BECAUSE I REALIZE THAT
PEOPLE AREN'T
SHOWING UP
FOR MY GET-TOGETHERS
HERE AT THE FIRE TOWER
BECAUSE OF THE BLAND,
ORDINARY INVITATIONS
I'M SENDING OUT.
WELL, IT MAY NOT BE
THAT BIG OF A FACTOR.
SURE IT IS.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN,
BECAUSE WHO
DOESN'T LIKE
FIMO PARTIES
OR SLEEPOVERS, HUH?
SO I THOUGHT
THAT AFTER THE
CHAINSAW PARTY,
WE COULD ALL
COME UP HERE
AND I COULD BUILD
A BIG BONFIRE
AND TELL A STORY
ABOUT THE HISTORY
OF POSSUM PINE.
BOY, THEY'LL BE
SCALPING TICKETS FOR
THAT ONE, WON'T THEY?
OH YEAH.
AND TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS INVITATION.
IS THAT
GROOVY OR WHAT?
THERE'S NOTHING
WRITTEN ON THIS, GORD.
HA, HA,
HA, GOTCHA.
SEE, THIS IS
GOOD CAMP FUN.
EVEN THE KIDS CAN
GET IN ON THIS GAG.
IT'S WRITTEN IN
INVISIBLE INK.
AND ALL YOU NEED
IS SOME LEMON JUICE
AND A MATCHSTICK
LIKE THIS, SEE?
AND THEN YOU WRITE
OUT YOUR INVITATION.
OH FOR GOSH SAKES.
SEE?
THIS IS A FAR MORE
INTERESTING INVITATION.
IT'S ENVIRONMENTALLY
FRIENDLY
AND IT HELPS PEOPLE
GET INTO THE SPIRIT
OF THE PARTY
BEFORE THEY
EVEN GET THERE.
IT'S TRUE.
AND IT WON'T STOP WITH
INVISIBLE INVITATIONS.
I'M GUESSING
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
INVISIBLE GUESTS, TOO.
GREAT.
THEY CAN MEET ALL MY
OTHER INVISIBLE FRIENDS.
AND FINALLY THERE'S
ONE FROM MY UNCLE RED.
I'M TIRED OF BEING
CALLED RED GREEN.
FROM NOW ON I
WANT TO BE CALLED AN
UNPRONOUNCEABLE SYMBOL
THAT REPRESENTS THE
SINGER WHO USED TO
BE CALLED PRINCE.
AND WELCOME TO THE
EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW.
THIS WEEK CLAIMING
TO BE AN EXPERT
WITH MY UNCLE RED IS
MR. EDGAR K.B. MONTROSE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
THIS WEEK'S LETTER
IS FROM BUTT, MONTANA.
THAT'S PRONOUNCED
BYOOT, HAROLD.
REALLY?
YEAH.
THEY MOVED, NOW THEY'RE
LIVING IN BUTTE, MONTANA.
DEAR EXPERTS, ONE OF
THE CASEMENT-STYLE
WINDOWS
IN OUR DINING
ROOM IS STUCK SHUT.
WHAT'S THE BEST WAY
TO GET IT SLIDING
AGAIN?
WELL, YOU'VE JUST
PROBABLY PAINTED
HER SHUT THERE.
YOU GOT TO CUT THAT
THROUGH WITH A RAZOR
BLADE OR A SHARP KNIFE.
THAT'S PRETTY
LABOUR INTENSIVE, RED.
MAYBE THE WINDOW
IS STUCK BECAUSE
THE HOUSE IS SETTLING.
YOU SEE, WHEN A
HOUSE GETS TO BE
SAY 40 YEARS OLD,
IT SETTLES AND
SAGS AND BUCKLES.
I'VE BEEN THERE.
YOU'RE STILL THERE.
WELL, IN THAT CASE YOU
TAKE APART A COUPLE OF
22 SHELLS, YOU SEE,
AND YOU POUR THE POWDER
INTO THE CORNER OF
THE FRAME
AND SWOOM YOU CAN POP THAT
WINDOW OUT OF THERE IN
NO TIME FLAT.
THAT SOUNDS
PRETTY DANGEROUS.
HUH?
DANGEROUS.
IT SOUNDS DANGEROUS.
OH NO, NO, HAROLD
IT'S NOT SO DANGEROUS.
FOR SOME REASON DYNAMITE
IS ONE OF THOSE EXPRESSIONS
THAT SCARES PEOPLE,
LIKE AH... LIKE NERVE GAS.
SO WOULD YOU
BLOW OUT THE
ONE WINDOW, EDGAR,
OR ALL THE
WINDOWS?
WELL, IF YOU'RE
GOING TO TAKE OUT
MORE THAN ONE,
YOU'RE FURTHER AHEAD
JUST TO TAKE OUT
THE WHOLE HOUSE.
15 CHARGES ALL THE
WAY AROUND THE PERIMETER,
A DOUBLE RIGHT IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE
CELLAR FLOOR
AND YOU CAN
MAKE THAT THREE
BEDROOM BUNGALOW
GET UP AND
DO A JIG.
BUT WOULDN'T OUR
VIEWER HAVE TO REBUILD
HIS WHOLE HOUSE THOUGH?
SO?
IF YOU PLANT YOUR
CHARGES PROPERLY,
WHEN YOU BLOW
UP YOUR HOUSE,
YOUR BRICK AND YOUR
WOOD AND YOUR
PLUMBING
ALL LAND IN THREE
SEPARATE PILES.
WELL, THERE'S NOTHING
I HATE WORSE THAN
CANCELLING A
CHAINSAW PARTY.
WE JUST TOOTED OUR
HORNS, PUT ON OUR HATS,
WE WERE READY TO GO
THERE AND OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK YELLS OUT,
WOAH, THE HIPS ARE SEIZED UP,
GOT ANOTHER STORM COMING.
MY CHICKENS.
OH, NO, MY CHICKENS.
NO, NO, HAROLD,
HAROLD, HAROLD,
IT WAS JUST
A FALSE ALARM,
IT WASN'T A STORM.
TURNS OUT HE HAS
A MEDICAL PROBLEM.
IT WASN'T THE
WEATHER AT ALL.
TALK ABOUT THOUGHTLESS.
WELL, HE OUGHT TO
THINK ABOUT HAVING
A HIP REPLACEMENT.
WELL, THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT HE'S DOING.
HE'S OVER AT POSSUM
COUNTY HOSPITAL RIGHT
NOW HAVING A HIP REPLACEMENT.
I THOUGHT THEY WOULD
NEED A DONOR
BUT I GUESS
THEY'RE GOING TO USE
A COUPLE OF BALL JOINTS
OUT OF AN OLD
BUICK OR SOMETHING.
NO, UNCLE RED, THEY'RE
MADE OUT OF PLASTIC
WITH TEFLON COATING.
THEY'RE EXCELLENT.
MY ENGLISH TEACHER
HAD HIS HIPS REPLACED
AND HE FELT SO MUCH
BETTER, YOU KNOW,
TWO WEEKS LATER HE
WENT SKIING, BROKE
BOTH HIS LEGS.
WELL, WE DON'T NEED
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
TO FEEL BETTER,
WE NEED HIM TO
FEEL WEATHER.
WELL, MAYBE THE LODGE
CAN COME OUT OF
THE DARK AGES
AND BUY LIKE SAY
A BAROMETER?
NO, WE DON'T
NEED IT, HAROLD,
WE'RE GOING
TO GET OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK'S HIPS.
THE DOCTOR IS GOING
TO GIVE THEM TO US
AFTER HE TAKES THEM OUT.
WE'RE GOING TO USE
THEM AS HINGES ON
THE OUTHOUSE DOOR.
OH.
AND IF YOU GO OUT
THERE AND YOU PULL
ON THE DOOR
AND SHE FEELS
STIFF TO YOU,
YOU KNOW YOU'RE IN
FOR STORMY WEATHER.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
IT'S MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
OH, OH, THAT
REMINDS ME,
BUSTER HADFIELD FOUND
A BUNCH OF YOUR CHICKENS
THAT SURVIVED THE STORM.
THEY WERE ALL WEDGED
INTO THE SOCCER NET
OVER AT THE SCHOOLYARD.
OH, EXCELLENT.
MY CHICKENS?
YEAH.
MY CHICKENS.
IF MY WIFE
IS WATCHING,
I'M GOING TO BE A
LITTLE BIT LATE
'CAUSE I'M GOING
TO DROP BY THE HOSPITAL
AND WISH OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
THE BEST OF LUCK
WITH THE HIP
REPLACEMENT THING.
AND WHILE I'M THERE
I MIGHT JUST BROWSE
THROUGH THE HOSPITAL
PARTS DEPARTMENT,
YOU KNOW, FOR
FUTURE REFERENCE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH
FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF
HAROLD AND MYSELF
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
UNTIL NEXT TIME,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ APPLAUSE AND CHEERING ]
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
HAROLD: ALL RISE
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI
RED: SIT DOWN, GUYS.