One of the downsides of
having a vehicle
for a while.
and perhaps not keeping
it as clean and tidy
as you should have,
is that over time you can
build up an aroma
that is extremely
odiferous in nature...
[ SNIFFING ]
especially on a hot day.
But here is a quick,
easy solution,
because when it comes
to a bad smell,
you don't have
to clean it out,
you just have
to drown it out.
So get the foot pump
off your air mattress,
take the hose off there.
Now go into your cupboard
and get all those
ten-year-old, half-full
bottles of aftershave
people used to give you
for your birthday and
Christmas,
until they finally gave up
on making you smell good
and then just pour them
into the foot pump.
This is the only Spice Girl
you'll ever get close to...
Old Spice.
Just stick the foot pump
in the middle of the
driver's seat,
attach the end of the hose
to the rearview mirror.
Now every time you get
into your vehicle,
you'll be pumping
up daisies.
[ COUGHING ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
Well, big, big week up
at the lodge this week.
I've decided to
put on an air show
featuring old airplanes,
wartime airplanes
from the olden days.
Now, ordinarily
we'd never be able
to afford to do
something like that
but last week we got a big
cheque from the government.
Turns out there was
a federal rep up here
and he saw the
condition of the lodge.
He figured we'd been the
victims of a terrorist attack,
so they sent us five grand
to tear the place down.
Uncle Red?
Yeah.
You know what
I was thinking,
maybe you should
let me decide how
to spend the $5,000.
Oh, no, no,
no, Harold, no.
The invention of
the computer is proof
that bad things happen
when nerds have money.
Plus, I have already
invested the five grand.
Oh...
well, you know beer
is not an investment.
Come on, Harold, what
do people around here
love to watch flying
through the air?
The Dukes of Hazzard.
They do.
Vintage war
planes, Harold,
bombers and fighters
soaring through the sky
with the original
pilots in the cockpits.
Where you going to find
a bunch of old pilots
in vintage airplanes?
Through old man Sedgewick.
A couple of the guys went
to school with his grandson.
And I'm not just talking
a fly-by, Harold.
They do spins and rolls and
even a simulated air strike.
There's one guy,
Bomber McKenna,
he dropped more bombs
than anybody in the
history of aviation
Wow.
Yeah.
Did he get a
medal for that?
No, he got three
years less a day
because it was
during peacetime
Oh, see, that's what
I mean, Uncle Red.
See I don't think an
air show is a very
good idea, no.
Harold, I've already sold
over a thousand tickets.
We got this deal that
if you buy five tickets
or more,
we promise not to
crash on your house.
See, now, that's
called marketing.
No, that's
called extortion.
Uncle Red, I mean do you
have any things like insurance
and permits to
have an air show?
How do you mean?
[ SPEAKING SLOWLY ]
Permits, insurance.
I don't remember.
Oh.
All right, come on, let's
go down to city hall.
I know the procedure.
Do you want me to
do the talking?
No, I'll do the talking.
You do the
waiting in the van.
It's time for the
Possum Lodge Word Game.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Today's winner
gets this coupon
good for one free
18th century musket
courtesy of the Canadian
Military Historical Society.
Musket may be recalled by
the Canadian Armed Forces
in the event of war.
Mike, cover your ears.
Red, you have
30 seconds
to get Mike
to say the word...
All right, Glen.
Go.
All right, Mike, this
is an expression,
don't look...?
Suspicious.
Okay.
No.
If you take something
that's not yours,
you should
always give it...?
A couple of days before
you wear it in public.
No.
Okay.
If a friend double-
crosses you,
they stab you in the...?
Exercise yard.
Okay.
This is a phrase you
will hear somebody say,
take one step forward
and two steps...?
Away from the rest
of the line-up.
No, no.
Okay.
When you were a kid,
you'd go on a road trip
with your dad and he'd
say climb in the...
Trunk.
Okay, okay.
No, okay.
Arnold Schwartzenegger
said this...
I'll be...
President.
Okay, okay.
No, no.
Okay.
You see this at a
construction site,
it's a hoe...?
Aunt Trixie?
You're running
out of time, Red.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
Mike, where do they keep
the safe in the bank?
Well, I can't tell
you that, Mr. Green,
because I might lose my
job as a security officer.
You're a bank
security officer?
You got that job?
Yeah.
See, there was no
background check.
[ BELL RINGING ]
There we go.
Welcome to the talking
animals portion of the show
where local animal
control officer Ed Frid
is here to tell
us all about --
I'm going to take a wild
guess and say, the bear.
Yes, Red.
Yes.
And judging by the fact
that you're not wearing
a suit of armor or
wetting your pants,
I'm kind of assuming this is
some kind of toy stuffed
bear of some -
[ ANIMAL GROWLING ]
Oh, a little jumpy
there, Red, eh?
Boy, it really
makes me laugh
to see how some people are
afraid of wild animals, huh?
Oh, yeah, you're
awful calm there.
You've been hypnotized
or tranquilized?
Not me, Red,
but he will.
Oh, yeah, I'm not
shooting blanks,
I'm shooting tranks.
Oh, yessiree, Red.
Bears may have
claws and teeth,
but I got
my dart gun
I love my dart gun.
Can I see that
for a second?
Sure.
whenever you're
handing a firearm
to a school
chum or teacher,
turn it around so you always
hand them the grip first.
Yeah, and make sure
the safety is on, right?
Well, that goes
without saying.
I always have
the safety on.
Oh, yeah, okay.
There we go.
Safety --
[ BEAR GROWLS LOUDLY ]
I don't have the gun,
do you have the gun?
I don't have the gun.
Do you think the
bear has the gun?
Very much so, yes.
Okay.
Don't panic.
Don't forget, the
safety is still on.
Right.
[ SAFETY CLICKS OFF ]
Oh.
Okay, if you stand
still, he won't shoot.
It was just a theory.
Hey, Ed, you're okay,
there's only one
dart in that gun.
Oh.
Well, it was
just a theory.
Some of you young people
may not know what this is.
Heck, most of you
aren't even watching.
Well, this is a water wheel
used to power the old flour
mill down by Mercury Creek.
The rushing water turned the
wheel and ground the wheat.
Mind you, we don't do
it that way anymore.
I'm going back like
six months ago.
But just because something
is old and rotten
and smells funny doesn't
mean it's useless.
Hey, that could be
the new lodge slogan.
We're going to think
outside the box.
Might as well, you're not
going to do much thinking
once you're in the box.
Everybody is harping
now about emissions
and how global warming is making
the whales sweat to death.
we're just throwing it away.
So this time on
Handyman Corner,
we're going to make
a car that runs on water.
I happen to have a car here
that the engine fell out of.
I guess I was
just born lucky.
Oh, no, wait a sec, the
engine is still in there.
This project is going to take
a little longer than I thought.
There we go.
Get yourself a bathtub
that nobody is using,
maybe from a frat house.
I'm just filling her up
here at self-serve.
By the way, you might want
to have a real loud radio
in the vehicle,
because if all you hear
is the water tinkling,
you'll be stopping at
every rest area you come to.
I got a piece of down spout
running from the drain
so I can direct the water
and this valve controls it.
This is the linkage from my
gas pedal to open the valve
and I got a bungie on
there to shut her off.
I got her set up so the
water comes down the pipe
and falls onto
my water wheel,
which is hooked into
the transmission,
so I'll be grinding gears
instead of flour.
Now, the bathtub holds
about 50 gallons,
so I figure I should get
at least 100 miles
between fill-ups,
even more if it rains.
You people that live
on the west coast
will be able
to go for months.
So there you have it,
I've built a zero emissions
fuel efficient car
and I've saved the
planet for free.
Now, you're probably thinking
I'll get a Nobel prize
for physics.
Forget about it.
Talk about people who don't
return phone calls.
But, hey, that's all water
under the bridge
or as I call it,
water under the car.
So, remember, if the women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
Oh, oh, oh, I forgot,
this thing runs
on high test.
There are a few things that
separate men from the animals.
We get to walk upright and talk
to good looking women,
they get to live in the
woods and eat their young.
On the other hand, we
get to pay income tax
and they get to
lick themselves.
But the main thing we have
that the animals don't
is foresight,
the ability to predict
the long-term outcome
of our actions and change
our behaviour accordingly.
The truth is, most men don't
start out with much foresight,
and the longer they live,
the less of it they retain.
It's why men have
thoughts like,
why would I stop for gas
when I still have
a sixty-fourth
of a tank left?
Or, I'll just leave
this drawer open
while I stick my head into the
cupboard directly below it.
Or, hey, if I feel this
good after two beers,
imagine how good I'll
feel after five?
We know we're going
to pay later,
but we do it anyway.
It's almost like the
guy we are right now
really doesn't like
the guy we will be
ten minutes from now.
And if you're married,
you not only suffer
from your lack
of foresight,
you may have to put up
with an annoyed wife
who criticizes
you for acting
without thinking of
the consequences.
Well, you just go
ahead and remind her
that she is
not much better.
You're not the only
one who said "I do".
Or maybe that's just something
you and I can know and
not mention.
That's called foresight.
Remember,
I'm pulling for you.
We're all
in this together.
Roses are brown,
violets are smothered?
time to call Rothschild's
before the whole lawn
is covered!
Man, we go down to city
hall to get the permit
for our air show,
Honest Abe here tells them
we're like recreating
the London blitz.
Well, I think it's always
best to be completely
truthful.
I can't wait 'til
you get married.
Well, you can't pretend
it's a picnic
and have all these antique
planes flying overhead
dropping bombs
and everything.
I think somebody
might notice.
It's no wonder we
were refused a permit.
Yeah, so, okay.
Now I need a
different plan, see.
A true promoter always
figures a way out.
What would P.T. Barnum do
if he lived in Possum Lake?
Move.
Wait a minute
Oh, no.
What do we have here
in Possum Lake, Harold?
Inbreeding?
We have a model
airplane club.
We'll put on the air show
using model airplanes.
Oh, oh, oh!
Why didn't
I think of that?
Oh, I know why,
because it's ridiculous.
It's not ridiculous.
It's brilliant,
Harold, okay?
People will come
to an air show,
model planes will fly by,
up near the sun so they're
squinting, you know.
They got themselves
an air show.
People see what
they want to see.
Yeah, but what about
what they hear?
I mean,
a real plane goes...
[ ENGINE SOUNDS ]
A model airplane goes...
[ MODEL ENGINE SOUND ]
I don't think people
are that gullible.
Oh sure they are,
you got engaged.
Oh.
RED: Boy I wish Bill would
stay sitting down.
Anyway, can't do anything
about that now.
We're on our way over
to one of these places
where they have these
rope ride things,
I don't know what
you call them.
But Bill's door was kind
of jammed so I came in
to help him,
but he was...
well, you know, he's out.
Okay, no harm done.
No harm done.
Okay, some harm done.
They find something.
So there's like the
demonstrator guy
and it's way up on a pole
and what he does is he
hooks kind of a tether
on to this line
and away he goes.
And I wasn't quite
sure why we were here.
I thought, okay,
that's good,
but Bill was really
excited about it.
And -- ow!
And so the fellow comes over
and for some reason
he hands me the harness
and the helmet.
I don't know.
What?
No, no.
They both seem to
have the impression
that I would somehow
be interested
in doing something
along that line.
And no, Bill,
you're so excited,
you know what,
you go 12 times
and then I will
think about it.
No, no, I'm
saying no, you go.
Okay.
So I got an idea,
so call heads or tails,
okay, heads or tails.
Now, Bill has got
to make a decision,
that's heads and he makes it
tails and back to heads
and then I see my life
passing in front of my eyes
so finally -- I don't have a
coin anyway, it doesn't matter.
So now he tries
to go up the pole.
Bill, this may not be the pole
you really want to climb.
The way it works with
these rope things,
you don't actually
climb up,
they have like the tether
rope and it comes down
and hooks onto your harness,
and then you get somebody
to pull down,
which would be me, and that's
supposed to lift you up.
Well, I tell you what -- oh.
But I just didn't,
you know,
you get them to
a certain height
and you can't get your
hands to go up and over.
And I thought what am
I going to do?
You know, I'm thinking
to myself
there's got to be a better
way and there is.
So Bill gets up on top of
the little stand there.
And, I mean, I have to
admire his courage.
I was saying, I have to
admire your courage, Bill.
Oh, I can't watch this.
Come on Bill, come on,
no come on, come on.
I'm not coming up
there for you,
you might as well go,
you might as well jump.
So finally he just
gives it a go
and it doesn't go so good.
He starts heading
for the van.
Oh!
And the tether rope flies up
and hits the high tension wire.
And, boy, Bill has never
looked so electrically
charged up there.
Oh!
All right.
And that's Bill's adventure.
You see a lot of unusual
things in people's bathrooms.
It's fun to look actually.
One thing you hardly ever
see is a smoke detector.
I guess it reminds them
of being on a plane,
I don't know.
But to me that's
shortsighted.
Now, you may be thinking,
I won't be able to hear that
smoke alarm from the bedroom,
or where am I going to smoke
so the kids won't see me now?
Or change
the channel, honey.
But, hey, smoke detectors are
not only sensitive to smoke,
they're also
sensitive to steam.
And nothing steams me more
than house guests
taking showers
that are too long,
too hot and too expensive.
Long, hot and expensive are
three things that
are never good
unless you're talking about
one of those late night
movies on cable.
Here is how to shorten
those showers.
Once you have installed
the smoke detector,
get yourself one of these sound
activated goofy looking dolls
that dance like
old man Sedgewick
after he's had a
couple of Mai Tais.
You know, the Santa doll
is a great choice
because most of our house
guests come at Christmas,
making peace on earth
that much harder.
Now, I asked Harold
to take a shower,
a hot shower for a change
so I can demonstrate
my brilliance.
The steam will trigger
the smoke alarm,
the smoke alarm will
trigger the dancing Santa
and the dancing Santa
will trigger Harold.
[ HAROLD HUMMING ]
[ SMOKE ALARM SOUNDS ]
[ SANTA PLAYS SONG ]
[ HAROLD SCREAMING ]
Ho, ho, ho.
[ CRASH! ]
Well, that was
a fun day.
That was not
my fault, Harold.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no,
no, of course not.
We just dive bombed
a thousand people
with 20 gas-powered
model airplanes.
Everything else
was just bad luck.
Okay.
See, the problem was that
the models looked too tiny
way up in the sky,
so I told the operators
to bring them down low
so they looked
like real planes.
Yeah, they may
have overreacted.
Yeah, I think flying
under the picnic tables
was probably a mistake.
There were some injuries.
Yeah, Buster Hadfield's afraid
he won't be able to
have children.
Hey, lucky for them.
I couldn't believe
how mad everybody got.
Here I am trying to
entertain people
and all they could
do is complain
about getting their
clothes shredded.
I mean, who wears
good clothes to an
air show anyway?
They just wanted
their money back.
Well, I was
very fair, Harold.
I told them a model airplane
is 10 percent the size
of a real plane
so I gave them 10 percent
of their money back.
And there was
no damage Harold.
Plus all 20 planes have
been accounted for.
Oh no, no, no, no,
just 19 of them actually.
Oh.
[ MODEL PLANE BUZZING ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALS ]
Meeting time,
Uncle Red Baron.
Well, thank you, stupid.
That's Red Baron
in Snoopy.
I know.
So if my wife is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting.
And today I learned that
you should always choose
the real thing over a model
so aren't you glad that you
married me instead of a model?
I'll lie if you will.
And to the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself
and Snoopy
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge,
keep your stick
on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Everybody sit down over there.
Sit down.
All rise.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the man's prayer.
I'm a man
but I can change
if I have to
I guess.
All right, men, in fairness
to the model airplane club,
I need some
volunteers to help
glue all the airplanes
back together.
Now, we're going to be working
in a well-ventilated area,
which with you guys
is never a bad idea.