[breezy folk music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> A GREAT PERSON FROM HISTORY
ONCE SAID, "TRULY CREATIVE WORKS
ARE NEVER FINISHED; THEY ARE
ABANDONED."
AND SINCE WE DIDN'T
FINISH THE SHOW, IT'S TIME TO
ABANDON IT.
ABANDON IT BEFORE IT TURNS WILD.
AND WHO BETTER FOR THE JOB THAN
A MAN OF WILD ABANDON AND THE
STAR OF THE RED GREEN SHOW, AND
MY UNCLE, BECAUSE HE'S MY
FATHER'S BROTHER--THAT'S WHAT
MAKES HIM MY UNCLE.
HERE HE IS, MR. RED GREEN!
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
NOT THE BEST INTRODUCTION I'VE
EVER HEARD IN MY LIFE, BUT
UNCLES CAN'T BE CHOOSERS.
>> SORRY, UNCLE RED.
I'M SORRY.
>> NO MORE THAN I AM, HAROLD.
BY THE WAY, HAROLD HERE IS NOT
ONLY MY NEPHEW, HE'S ALSO MY
PRODUCER AND MY DIRECTOR.
>> YEAH.
AND I ALSO HAVE CONTROL OF THIS
VIDEO-EFFECTIVE PANEL HERE.
LOOK AT THIS.
I CAN DO THINGS LIKE THAT, AND
IT GIVES THE SHOW A LOOK.
I LIKE TO THINK EVERYTHING
SHOULD HAVE A LOOK.
>> YOU GET LOOKS EVERYWHERE YOU
GO, DON'T YOU, HAROLD?
>> THAT'S MY JOB,
LOOKS, ANGLES, VISUALS.
>> YEAH.
WELL, ANYWAY, WE GOT A GREAT
SHOW FOR YOU TONIGHT.
WE GOT A LOT OF FILM CLIPS.
WE GOT A LOT OF SPECIAL GUESTS.
AND I HAVE A GREAT STORY ABOUT
MOOSE THOMPSON AND ELVIS.
>> WHY DON'T WE JUST GET RIGHT
ON WITH, LIKE, THE VIDEO CLIPS
AND, OF COURSE, THE GUESTS.
>> WELL, WHAT ABOUT THE MOOSE
THOMPSON AND ELVIS STORY?
>> OH, WELL, YOU KNOW, LET'S
SAVE THE BEST FOR LAST...
IF THERE'S TIME.
[light guitar and spoon music]
>> THERE ARE CERTAIN THINGS
YOU SHOULD NEVER DO
LIKE DON'T EAT THINGS
THAT YOU FIND ON YOUR SHOE
DON'T TAKE A NAP
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE ROAD
AND DON'T EVER LICK A TOAD
DON'T LICK A TOAD
DON'T LICK IT
YOU'D BE BETTER OFF
TO KICK IT
OR BETTER STILL,
JUST LEAVE IT ALONE.
IT WASN'T BOTHERING YOU.
>> NO.
>>  DON'T LICK A TOAD
DON'T LICK IT
JUST SAY NO TO TOADS
I GUESS YOU CAN TELL, THIS IS
KIND OF A SPECIAL DAY.
YOU KNOW, ONCE IN A WHILE, I DO
LIKE TO SPEND SOME TIME WITH,
WITH THE YOUNGSTERS.
AND THIS IS SOMETHING I THINK
MORE AND MORE ADULTS CAN DO...
OR EVEN PARENTS.
IF YOU ARE A PARENT AND YOU DO
HAVE A CHILD, AND IT'S NOT LIKE
HAROLD, YOU MIGHT WANT TO SPEND
SOME OF YOUR VALUABLE TIME WITH
THE CHILD.
PAYS OFF IN SPADES.
OR A KID DOWN THE STREET, YOU
KNOW, OR IF YOU GET INVOLVED
WITH THE BIG BROTHERS, HIGHLY
RECOMMEND THAT.
AND I'M SPENDING SOME TIME TODAY
WITH...
>> MAX.
MAX HAS BROUGHT A, HAS BROUGHT
AN AIRPLANE HERE.
THIS IS MAX'S OWN, OWN MODEL
PLANE.
DO YOU WANT TO--OH, NO, NO.
ACTUALLY, YOU'D BETTER NOT TOUCH
THAT.
WHAT YOU CAN DO, MAX, WE'RE
GONNA FLY THIS PLANE TODAY.
AND THIS IS, WELL, THIS IS KIND
OF FUN FOR ME TOO, I CAN TELL
YOU.
MAX, YOU, YOU UNTANGLE THE
STRING, AND I'LL WORK ON THE
PLANE.
GET RID OF ALL THE JUNK.
YEAH, HE'S GOT THE WHOLE KIT
HERE.
HE REALLY HAS.
HE HAS THE WHOLE THING ALL SET
UP.
YOU KNOW, I NEVER HAD ONE OF
THESE.
WHEN I WAS A KID, I ALWAYS
WANTED ONE.
BUT OF COURSE, NOW, MY DAD, HE
WOULDN'T SPEND THAT BIT OF TIME.
AND SO IT DIDN'T PAY OFF FOR
HIM, YOU KNOW.
AND I THINK, IN A WAY, THAT--
HERE I AM SPENDING TIME WITH A
YOUNG FELLOW, AND LOOK WHAT'S
HAPPENING FOR ME.
I'M GETTING TO FINALLY GET THE
THING GOING WITH A MODEL PLANE,
WHICH I ALWAYS WANTED AS A KID
AND NEVER DID GET--
AND THIS IS...SO YOU SEE HOW IT
WORKS OUT.
BETTER HURRY IT UP, MAX.
HAVEN'T GOT ALL DAY.
AND THEY ENJOY IT TOO, JUST AS
MUCH AS, JUST AS MUCH AS--I'M
GONNA GET MY GLOVE.
I DON'T HAVE MY GLOVES.
SO I'VE GOT THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON HERE, WHICH WE
CALL AN "A.G.," ALTERNATE GLOVE.
AND WHAT I'M GOING TO DO IS WRAP
THIS AROUND WHAT'S GOING TO BE
THE CUT.
AND I'LL USE THIS TO ACTUALLY
START THE--HOW ARE YOU, HOW ARE
YOU DOING THERE?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU'RE DOING IT ALL WRONG.
DOING IT ALL WRONG.
COME ON OVER HERE.
START HERE.
YOU GOT TO UNTIE IT.
THERE, THERE. THERE. THERE.
THERE. THAT'S IT.
THEY LIKE THE GUIDANCE.
DON'T WANT TO JUST SIT BACK AND
LET THEM DO IT ANY OLD WHICH
WAY, BECAUSE THIS IS HOW THEY
CAN LEARN.
THIS WEEK IN "HANDYMAN CORNER,"
WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU HOW TO GET
MORE AND MORE USES OUT OF YOUR
ELECTRIC DRILL.
YOU KNOW, A LOT OF PEOPLE ASK
ME, "RED," THEY SAY, "IF I ONLY
CAN AFFORD TO BUY ONE POWER
TOOL, WHAT SHOULD I BUY?"
WELL, NOW THAT THEY'VE MADE
FLAMETHROWERS ILLEGAL, I WOULD
HAVE TO RECOMMEND THE POWER
ELECTRIC DRILL.
FIRST OF ALL, YOU CAN USE IT FOR
DRILLING.
[drill buzzing]
YOU CAN ALSO USE IT TO COOL DOWN
THE WORKSHOP.
[drill buzzing]
JUST, YOU KNOW, HANG THAT FROM
THE CEILING WITH THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
NOW, THEY TRY TO SELL YOU ONE OF
THOSE FANCY AUTOMATIC POWER
SCREWDRIVING DEALS, AND THEY
COST ANYWHERE UP TO SEVEN OR
EIGHT MILLION DOLLARS.
WELL, ALL YOU NEED TO DO IS TO
GET THE BIT, WHICH IS ABOUT
$1.49 AND JUST PUT IT INTO YOUR
NORMAL DRILL, AND IT JUST WORKS
JUST ABSOLUTELY FINE.
[drill buzzing]
YOU GET THE IDEA.
NOW, YOU KNOW, THEY TRY TO SELL
YOU A BUNCH OF ATTACHMENTS FOR
YOUR DRILL, BUT THE TRUTH IS,
THE ATTACHMENTS REALLY DON'T
MAKE THAT MUCH DIFFERENCE.
THE REAL REASON THAT THE DRILL
WORKS IS THROUGH YOU HORSING
DOWN ON HER AND REALLY PUTTING
SOME TORSION ON IT.
YOU CAN CUT A HOLE WITH ANYTHING
FROM A TOOTHBRUSH TO A CAR KEY
IF YOU GET ENOUGH JUICE ON HER,
YOU KNOW.
SO, FOR EXAMPLE, THEY'LL SELL
YOU A REAL EXPENSIVE SAW BLADE
THAT GOES ON YOUR DRILL.
WELL, THAT'S REALLY NOT
NECESSARY.
I'LL SHOW YOU RIGHT HERE HOW YOU
CAN, YOU CAN CUT A PERFECTLY
GOOD LINE JUST USING YOUR
ORDINARY DRILL WITH A DRILL BIT
IN IT HERE.
[drill buzzing]
ALL RIGHT,
YOU'VE GOT TO BE PREPARED TO
GIVE IT A LITTLE MORE TIME THIS
WAY, BUT YOU'RE SAVING UPWARDS
OF FIVE DOLLARS.
NOW, HERE'S SOMETHING THAT YOU
WOULDN'T ORDINARILY THINK TO USE
A DRILL FOR.
AND THIS IS WHAT I'M TRYING TO
SAY, IS THAT YOU'RE ONLY LIMITED
BY YOUR OWN IMAGINATION.
AND YOU CAN DEAL WITH THAT AS
YOU MAY.
BUT HERE'S A SITUATION WHERE YOU
TAKE TWO WIRES THAT YOU WOULD
WANT TO STRAND TOGETHER, MAKE
SOME SORT OF A BRAIDING PATTERN.
JUST TWIST THEM TOGETHER, MAKE A
NEATER LOOK FOR
WHATEVER IT IS, MAYBE YOU'RE
REWIRING YOUR STOVE OR WHATEVER.
WHAT YOU DO IS, YOU PUT BOTH
ENDS OF THE WIRE IN THERE, AND
YOU TAKE YOUR TWO STRANDS, AND
YOU TURN ON THE DRILL FROM A
REMOTE SETTING AND THEN SLOWLY
JUST WALK TOWARDS IT WHILE IT
WINDS IN.
IT'S A HECK OF A RIG, AND IT'S
NOT SOMETHING YOU WOULD
ORDINARILY THINK OF WITH A
DRILL.
SO WHY DON'T WE JUST GIVE THIS,
GIVE THIS A TRY.
ALL RIGHT, BOYS, YOU WANT TO HIT
THE POWER THERE?
[drill buzzing]
THERE WE GO.
JUST LOOK AT THAT.
[wire whipping]
ALL RIGHT, DO YOU WANT TO KILL
THAT?
KILL THAT NOW.
ALL RIGHT, SO IF YOU ARE
THINKING OF BUYING A POWER TOOL,
I'D RECOMMEND YOU GO OUT AND GET
YOURSELF A NEW DRILL.
LOOKS LIKE I'M GONNA HAVE TO.
ANYWAY, SO UNTIL NEXT TIME,
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE
FUN IN THE FOREST, MORE FILM
CLIPS, AND MORE ABOUT MOOSE AND
ELVIS.
>> [singing] TREAT ME LIKE A FOOL
OR WHAT, EH?
>> OKAY.
THIS IS EXCITING AND LOOKS VERY,
VERY DANGEROUS.
WELL, MAYBE IT'S NOT THAT
DANGEROUS.
I'LL JUST WAIT FOR THE PAIN TO
GO DOWN A BIT.
YEP.
>> "IT IS WINTER.
THE RABBITS GROW A WARM WINTER
COAT.
THE FOXES, TOO, GROW A THICK
WINTER COAT, AS DO THE MINKS AND
THE RACCOONS.
BUT WE CANNOT GROW A THICK COAT,
SO WE JUST KILL THEM AND TAKE
THEIRS."
OKAY, NOW, I WAS
TELLING YOU ABOUT MOOSE THOMPSON
AND ELVIS.
MOOSE WAS DOWN AT THE
SUPERMARKET, AND HE TOLD
EVERYBODY THAT HE SAW THE GHOST
OF ELVIS IN THE CHINESE FOOD
SECTION.
BUT NOBODY BELIEVED HIM.
AND THEN HE REMEMBERED THAT IT
WASN'T THE CHINESE FOOD SECTION.
IT WAS IN THE DELICATESSEN.
AND SUDDENLY THE STORY HAD AN
EERIE RING OF TRUTH TO IT.
>> UNCLE RED, HOW COME YOU CAN'T
TALK ABOUT, LIKE, GUNS N' ROSES
OR NEW KIDS ON THE BLOCK, YOU
KNOW?
SOMETHING THAT OUR YOUNGER
VIEWERS MIGHT LIKE, NOT JUST OLD
PEOPLE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST A THOUGHT.
WHAT ABOUT THAT?
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
HAROLD?
>> WELL, THESE STORIES ARE
REALLY GOOD.
JUST THAT NOBODY LIKES 'EM.
MAYBE WE SHOULD PUT A MUSIC
VIDEO IN HERE, YOU KNOW,
SOMETHING, SOMETHING WITH SOME
RAP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GIVE ME YOUR KNUCKLES.
>> NO, I MEAN LIKE PAULA ABDUL,
YOU KNOW?
SHE'S REALLY GOOD.
MAYBE PEOPLE WOULD LIKE TO HEAR
HER RATHER THAN ABOUT MOOSE
THOMPSON'S HALLUCINATIONS.
PEOPLE UNDER 80 WOULD RATHER
HEAR THAT, I THINK.
>> THIS WASN'T A HALLUCINATION,
HAROLD.
I MEAN, ELVIS COULD NOT BE A
HALLUCINATION, OKAY?
>> OH, YEAH?
YOU DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE SOMETHING LIKE THIS
HAPPENED.
>> DID YOU JUST CUT ME OFF,
HAROLD?
>> NO, IT WAS A HALLUCINATION.
[light guitar and spoon music]
>> I HEAR THE SIZZLE
OF BACON ON THE ENGINE BLOCK
I SEE A HANDFUL
OF HASH BROWNS
LYING IN MY SOCK
I WATCH A STACK OF PANCAKES
GO ROLLING DOWN THE DOCK
BREAKFAST IS HELL
WHEN THE STOVE BLOWS UP
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT WE HAVE TO DO NOW IS ADJUST
THE MOTOR.
MAX, GIVE ME THE FUEL.
GET ME THE FUEL.
IT'S IN THE--GET THE FUEL.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THIS--NO--ALL RIGHT.
>> OH, UNCLE RED.
GREAT. EXCELLENT.
IT'S THE PART OF THE SHOW THAT
YOU LIKE BEST.
>> OH, ALL RIGHT.
SO LONG AND THANKS FOR WATCHING.
>> OH, NO, NO, NO.
UNCLE RED, I MEANT, LIKE, MALE
CALL.
THE PART WHERE WE ANSWER VIEWER
MAIL?
>> AH.
>> I GOT A LETTER RIGHT HERE.
IT'S HARD TO READ, THOUGH.
IT'S LIKE, ON COLORED PAPER IN
CRAYON.
"DEAR POSSUM, I REALLY LIKE YOUR
SHOW.
I HAVE ALL OF THEM ON TAPE.
I'VE WATCHED EVERY ONE OF THEM
50 TIRES--TIMES.
50 TIMES.
I THINK YOU ARE VERY WISP.
WISE."
HE THINKS YOU'RE VERY WISE,
UNCLE RED.
"I AM YOUR BIGGEST FAR."
WHAT'S A FAR?
>> WELL, THAT WOULD BE A FAN.
BIGGEST FAN.
>> LOOKS LIKE "FAR."
>> WELL, IT'LL BE "FAN."
LET ME SEE.
LOT OF TIMES, SMALL "N" LOOKS
LIKE A SMALL "R."
>> YEAH, BUT THAT'S A CAPITAL
"R."
>> MUST BE THE BIGGEST "FAR."
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
I'VE GOT A FAR. THAT'S NICE.
I GOT ARE FANS; "FAR" IS KIND OF
A NICE CHANGE.
>> IT SAYS, "I WANT TO START A
FAR CLUB."
>> I THINK HE MEANS A FAN CLUB
THERE, HAROLD.
>> "I THOUGHT A FAR CLUB WOULD
BE NICE SINCE YOU PROBABLY
ALREADY HAVE A FAN CLUB.
TO START THE FAR CLUB, I WILL
NEED YOUR APPROVAL.
IS THAT OKAY WITH YOU?
SIGNED, 'X.'"
>> WELL, YEAH, SURE.
I MEAN, HAROLD, EVERY STAR
DREAMS OF HAVING THEIR OWN FAR
CLUB, DON'T THEY?
>> SURE.
>> HOW FAR DOES HE WANT THIS FAR
CLUB TO GO, DO YOU THINK?
>> PROBABLY PRETTY FAR.
IT'S A FAR CLUB.
>> THE FARTHER THE BETTER, IF
YOU ASK ME.
OKAY, SURE.
WHOEVER YOU ARE, GO AHEAD, START
THE RED GREEN FAR CLUB.
>> SAYS HERE HE WANTS TO CALL IT
THE "RED GROIN FAR CLUB."
>> THAT'S EVEN BETTER.
OKAY, THE "RED GROIN FAR CLUB."
PERFECT.
IF ANY OF YOU VIEWERS AT HOME
WANT TO BECOME A MEMBER OF THAT
BEAUTIFUL-SOUNDING CLUB, HAROLD,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST HOLD UP THE
RETURN ADDRESS.
YOU CAN GET DIRECTLY IN TOUCH
WITH THIS GUY.
>> DIDN'T EVEN SEND ONE.
JUST LIKE A CHEWED-UP WAD OF GUM
AND A ROCK IN A PLASTIC BAG,
UNCLE RED.
>> IT'S QUITE A COUNTRY WE GOT
HERE, HAROLD.
GOT TO HAVE A LICENSE TO BUY A
GUN, BUT THEY'LL SELL ANYBODY A
STAMP.
WHAT KIND OF GUM IS IT?
>> IT'S DOUBLE-BUBBLE OR
SOMETHING.
>> OH, I'LL HAVE THAT.
YOU HAVE THE ROCK.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> WE DO GET WINTER IN THIS
COUNTRY, AND BILL AND I THINK
THAT ONE OF THE KEYS TO MAKE THE
BEST OF WINTER IS TO GET OUT AND
ENJOY IT AND ACTUALLY TAKE
ACTIVITIES AND JUST DO THEM, YOU
KNOW.
BECAUSE WHEN YOU GET GOING--
HERE HE IS, GOING DOWN ON A
SLED, AND, YOU KNOW,
HE'S HAVING SO DARN MUCH
FUN THAT HE REALLY DOESN'T
NOTICE THE COLD OR THE, OR THE,
ANY KIND OF--THERE'S NO--OH, MY
GOD.
BUT IT'S--THAT'S ALL PART OF THE
FUN, ISN'T IT?
HE'S--HE LOOKS ALL RIGHT.
YEAH.
YEAH, YEAH.
BUT WE WANTED TO SHOW YOU TODAY
HOW YOU CAN HAVE SOME FUN WITH
THE WINTER.
AND IT DOESN'T MATTER IF YOU
DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO JOIN AN
EXPENSIVE SKI CLUB OR ANY SUCH
THING AS THAT.
IT HELPS IF YOU CAN'T READ.
BUT EVEN IF YOU HAVE JUST A
CARDBOARD BOX, I BELIEVE THIS IS
FROM A DRYER OR A WASHER, OR IT
MIGHT'VE JUST BEEN THE DOUGHNUTS
THAT WE GOT.
AND THEN INTO THE BOX, YOU SEE.
AND WELL, THAT WASN'T--YOU DON'T
WANT TO GO DOWN ON THAT.
YOU WANT TO GO DOWN STANDING
UPRIGHT IN THE, IN THE THING.
AND BILL WILL SHOW YOU.
THIS IS A LOT OF FUN 'CAUSE YOU
REALLY CAN'T SEE WHAT YOU'RE
GONNA HIT.
WELL, I DON'T THINK THAT WAS
BILL'S TOP END.
COME ON, BILL, COME ON.
UP YOU GO. UP YOU GO.
THERE HE IS.
WELL, WE JAM HIM DOWN THERE AND
FLIP HIM OVER AND AWAY HE GOES.
AND HERE'S ANOTHER INEXPENSIVE
SLED YOU CAN USE.
THIS IS A GARBAGE CAN LID, AND
YOU KNOW, THERE ARE THE
PLASTIC--[stammering]
AND THIS IS SOMETHING I--JUST TO
ANOTHER WRINKLE, PUT HIM RIGHT
INTO THE CAN.
YOU KNOW, IT'S REALLY WHERE BILL
BELONGS MOST OF THE TIME ANYHOW,
YOU KNOW.
AND THIS WOULD MAKE IT MORE
EXCITING FOR HIM, KIND OF LIKE
SPACE MOUNTAIN AT DISNEY WORLD.
OH, HE'S HAVING A GOOD TIME.
AND, GOLLY, THAT WOULD MAKE YOU
DIZZY, WOULDN'T IT?
I SAID, "BILL, WHEN YOU FINISH,
IF YOU'RE OKAY, JUST GIVE US THE
WAVE, YOU KNOW?"
AND THERE IT IS.
YEAH, YEAH, HE'S FINE.
"IT IS WINTER, WHEN PEOPLE WAVE
TO YOU FROM THE WARMTH OF THEIR
CARS OR SHOUT 'HELLO!' AS THEY
HURRY BY WITH THEIR PACKAGES.
BUT YOU CAN'T ANSWER, BECAUSE
YOUR TONGUE IS FROZEN TO YOUR
SLEIGH."
THIS IS THE TIME IN THE
SHOW WHERE WE JUST TAKE A MINUTE
OUT FROM THE ENTERTAINMENT AND
THE PLEASANTRIES AND HAVE A
CHANCE JUST TO BE SORT OF BORED
OUT OF OUR MINDS.
HAROLD.
>> OKAY, I'M GONNA TALK ABOUT
YOUR FIRST DATE.
OKAY, MANY OF YOU, UNLIKE ME,
HAVE NEVER BEEN OUT ON A REAL
DATE WITH A GIRL.
OKAY, FIRST THINGS FIRST.
OKAY.
DON'T, DO NOT TRY AND KISS HER
IN THE HALLWAY WITH HER PARENTS
THERE.
DON'T.
SECOND, NEVER MAKE FUN OF PEOPLE
WHO PLAY LOTTERIES UNTIL YOU'VE
ASCERTAINED IF INDEED SHE PLAYS
LOTTERIES.
AND, THE WORST--WHOEVER THOUGHT
THIS COULD'VE HAPPENED, BUT IT
WAS HORRIBLE--MAYBE HER FAMILY
MAKES THEIR LIVING SELLING
LOTTERY TICKETS.
AND, AND WHEN YOU GET OUT TO THE
CAR AND HER FOOT'S NOT INSIDE
THE CAR, DON'T SLAM THE DOOR.
DON'T DO THAT.
LIKE, DON'T, LIKE MAYBE YOU
THINK IT'S THE SEAT BELT OR
SOMETHING AND YOU KEEP SLAMMING
IT.
IT'S NOT, IT'S HER LEG.
IT SMARTS, ACCORDING TO PEOPLE
WHO HAVE BEEN THERE.
AND NEXT, WHEN YOU GO OUT TO
DINNER, AND SAY, SAY YOU DON'T
HAVE ENOUGH MONEY TO COVER THE
BILL, OKAY?
DON'T START CRYING.
DON'T.
DOESN'T HELP.
JUST BE REALLY CAS AND COOL
ABOUT IT, RIGHT?
JUST SAY, "YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T THINK I'M GONNA HAVE
GRAVY ON MY FRIES."
LOOK AT THAT, RIGHT?
YOU'RE OUT OF THE SITUATION.
SLICK, RIGHT?
OKAY.
THEN, YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE YOU
DON'T DO?
DON'T GO TO A GERMAN ART FILM.
AND DO NOT READ THE SUBTITLES TO
HER UNTIL SHE LOOKS AT YOU REAL
SWEET-LIKE AND GOES, "WOULD YOU
SHUT UP?"
DON'T DO THAT.
AND, AND THEN FINALLY, WHEN
YOU'RE GOING HOME AND YOU'RE
KISSING HER GOOD-NIGHT AND SHE
DOESN'T WANT TO, DON'T ASK HER
WHY.
BELIEVE ME, IT HURTS.
THANK YOU.
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
WE GOT THE END OF THE MOOSE AND
ELVIS STORY COMING UP.
>> ENQUIRING MINDS DON'T CARE.
>> GIVE ME THE FUEL THERE, MAX.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
>> YOU SPEND A LITTLE TIME WITH
THESE KIDS, AND BEFORE YOU KNOW
IT--YOU GOT TO PUSH DOWN ON THAT
WHILE YOU'RE TURNING IT.
CAN'T YOU READ?
PUSH DOWN. NO, NO.
PUSH DOWN HARDER WHILE YOU'RE
TURNING IT.
TURN THAT AND PUSH DOWN.
PUSH DOWN AND TURN THAT.
TURN--PUSH--PUSH--PUSH--YEAH.
YEAH.
YEP.
DON'T KNOCK IT OVER.
YOU DO THOUGH, YOU DO.
YOU DO IT. YOU DO IT.
OKAY, CAREFUL. CAREFUL.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW PUT THE LID ON IT.
PUT THE LID ON IT.
I'M HERE TODAY WITH A MAN WHO IS
LIVING HIS DREAM.
BY DAY, HE DELIVERS FOOD FOR
PEOPLE, AND ON THE WEEKEND, HE
DRIVES HIS MONSTER TRUCK AROUND,
CRUSHING CARS.
MY GOOD BUDDY, DOUGIE FRANKLIN.
>> THANK YOU, RED.
AS THE SIGN SAYS, I LOVE THIS
TRUCK, AND I LOVE THE WORK I DO
IN IT.
YOU SHOULD SEE THE LOOK ON SOME
OF THESE PEOPLE'S FACES WHEN
THEY SEE THIS VEHICLE COMING
ACROSS THEIR FRONT LAWN.
>> OH.
>> AND BEING SO HIGH UP, TOO,
THEY DON'T EVEN HAVE TO COME
DOWNSTAIRS FOR THEIR DINNER.
I CAN JUST SLIP IT RIGHT THROUGH
THE SECOND STORY WINDOW TO THEM.
IT'S A CONVENIENT THING.
BUT YOU KNOW, RED, SOME OF THESE
PEOPLE, THEY GOT NOTHING.
THEY GOT NO FOOD; THEY GOT
NOTHING.
IT'S--THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG
WITH A SOCIETY WHEN SOME PEOPLE
HAVE SO MUCH AND OTHER PEOPLE
HAVE SO LITTLE.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, IT'S LIKE WE
GOT OUR PRIORITIES SCREWED UP
SOMEWHERE ALONG THE WAY.
>> OH, THAT IS SO TRUE, DOUGIE.
>> YEAH.
>> SO WHAT WOULD A TRUCK LIKE
THIS COST?
>> ABOUT $86,000.
$86,000.
THAT'S FULLY LOADED, THOUGH.
I USED TO HAVE A HONDA CIVIC.
WE TOOK HER TO THE TRACTOR AND
TRUCK PULL THING, BUT WE DIDN'T
FARE VERY WELL AT ALL, SO I HAD
TO GET RID OF IT.
>> YEAH, BUT, DOUGIE, THERE IS A
LOT MORE TO THIS SPORT THAN JUST
LINING UP IN FRONT OF A BUNCH OF
OLD CARS AND FLYING THROUGH THE
AIR AND THEN COMING DOWN AND
CRUSHING THEM.
>> NO, NO, NO, I THINK THAT'D
SUM HER UP IN A NUTSHELL, I
THINK, WHAT THE SPORT'S ALL
ABOUT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IF I MIGHT JUST
GET SERIOUS FOR JUST A SECOND,
RED, I'D LIKE TO TALK TO YOU
KIDS AT HOME.
IF YOU KIDS AT HOME HAVE GOT AN
OVERSIZED TRUCK WITH HUMONGO
TIRES LIKE THIS, YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE TRYING THE STUFF THAT WE
DO.
LEAVE IT TO THE PROFESSIONALS.
BECAUSE YOU GET INTO, LIKE, UH,
THINGS THAT COULD HAPPEN TO YOUR
HEAD, AND YOU CAN DEAL WITH SOME
HEAD INJURIES, AND YOUR HEAD
COULD GET, UH, YOU COULD HURT,
UH, HEADS.
YOU CAN GET INJURED THERE BAD.
DID I SAY THAT?
I THINK I DID.
>> I WAS JUST, WHILE YOU WERE
SPEAKING THERE, I WAS JUST
WONDERING IF MAYBE A SEATBELT
MIGHT BE A GOOD IDEA IN A SPORT
LIKE THIS.
>> OH, YEAH, YOU BET YOUR BOTTOM
DOLLAR ON THAT.
NOW, I HAVE A SEATBELT, BUT IT'S
CRAWLED AND SNUCK BACK HERE INTO
THE CRACK OF THIS SEAT HERE.
AND I CAN'T GET AT IT.
IT'S BEEN WELDED INTO, INTO
PLACE.
I CAN'T GET AT HER.
BUT YOU KNOW, IT'S A SAFE, IT IS
A SAFE SPORT, RED.
I MEAN, NOBODY IS GONNA GET
HURT.
>> NO.
>> UNLESS, OF COURSE, THEY GOT
THEIR FACE STARING UP THE BARREL
OF MY EXHAUST WHEN I FIRE THIS
BABY UP.
BOY, THAT'D SET YOU FREE, I TELL
YOU.
THERE'S A STORY BEHIND THAT ONE.
>> YEAH.
MAYBE SOME OTHER TIME, HUH?
>> I NEVER KNEW TOUPEES COST SO
MUCH MONEY, I'LL TELL YOU THAT
RIGHT NOW.
>> THAT'S DOUGIE FRANKLIN.
A MAN WHO'S COMBINED HIS HOBBY
AND HIS WORK INTO ONE HUGE,
GREAT BIG, GIGANTIC TRUCK HERE.
>> OR THAT THEY WERE FLAMMABLE
TOO.
THAT SUCKER, PSHEW.
HE WAS A CUE BALL.
UNBELIEVABLE.
JUST, YOU KNOW, COME IN, LOOK
LIKE TOM SELLECK, AND HE WENT
OUT LOOKING LIKE KOJAK.
>> SO ANYWAY, AFTER MOOSE
THOMPSON HAD SEEN THE GHOST OF
ELVIS, IT KIND OF CHANGED HIS
PERSONALITY.
OR, I SHOULD SAY, IT GOT HIM A
PUT RHINESTONES ALL OVER HIS
PLAID SHIRT AND HIS HUNTING VEST
AND HIS TENT.
AND HE WENT AROUND SAYING, "UH,
THANKYOUVERYMUCH."
YOU KNOW, AND
HE BOUGHT HIS MOTHER A MOTOR
HOME, CALLED IT "GREASELAND."
WELL, NOW, WE TRY TO BE TOLERANT
OF PEOPLE FOR A COUPLE OF
MINUTES OR SO.
BUT THEN IT GOT TO THE POINT
WHERE HE WAS REALLY GETTING ON
OUR NERVES.
SO WE KNOCKED HIM DOWN, STEPPED
ON HIS FACE, AND SLANDERED HIS
NAME ALL OVER THE PLACE.
NOW HE THINKS HE'S MAMA CASS.
ANYWAY, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M GONNA BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME, AND I'VE DECIDED NOT TO
PUT MY HAIR INTO A DUCKTAIL,
BECAUSE I COULDN'T GET THE DUCK
TO GO FOR IT.
ANYWAY, ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND--
>> HAROLD.
>> YEAH, CLOSE ENOUGH, AND THE
REST OF US UP AT THE LODGE, KEEP
YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
[engine buzzing]
ALL RIGHT. LET HER GO.
YEAH, THAT'S IT.
NOW, THAT'S FLYING AT ITS BEST,
ISN'T IT?
TAKE THIS LITTLE EXTRA TIME, AND
THE YOUNGSTERS GET TO HAVE SOME
FUN, AND--IS IT OKAY?
AH, IT WILL BE.
WE GOT SOME DUCT TAPE IN THE VAN
THERE AND...BOY, I'M THIRSTY.
CLEAN THAT UP, WILL YOU, MAX?