IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW!"
AND NOW HERE'S THE MAN WHO'S
FORGOTTEN MORE ABOUT
RATIONAL BEHAVIOUR
THAN HE EVER KNEW,
YOUR HERO,
YOUR HOST,
MY UNCLE...
RED GR-E-E-E-N!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU. APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP AT THE
LODGE THIS WEEK.
WE HAD OUR REMOTE CONTROL
LAWN MOWER RACES.
TALK ABOUT FUN,
ESPECIALLY FOR THE WINNER,
OR, AS WE CALL HIM...
THE GUY WHO STILL HAS HIS TOES.
YOU KNOW, UNCLE RED,
I COULD'VE TOLD YOU
THAT WASN'T GONNA WORK.
I COULD'VE TOLD HIM
BECAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
'CAUSE MOST REMOTE CONTROL
FREQUENCIES, THEY'RE
ALL THE SAME, RIGHT?
I KNOW.
SO WHAT HAPPENS IS THAT MAKES
YOUR LAWN MOWERS GO ALL CRAZY
AND WACKY LIKE THEY DID.
YEP.
YEAH.
WAS THERE MUCH PERSONAL
SERIOUS INJURY?
WELL, YES AND NO, HAROLD.
BUSTER HADFIELD ESCAPED
WITH JUST A TRIM,
BUT JUNIOR SINGLETON WAS
PRETTY WELL MOWED AND MULCHED.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE DOWN AT
THE HOSPITAL EXTENDING
YOUR BEST WISHES?
NO, THAT WOULD BE AN
ADMISSION OF GUILT, HAROLD.
BESIDES, MY PRESENCE HAS BEEN
REQUESTED AT A MEETING OF THE
TOWN COUNCIL.
I GOT SOME 'SPLAININ' TO DO.
YOU WANT A RIDE DOWN?
(POLICE SIREN)
WON'T BE NECESSARY, HAROLD.
THERE'S MY RIDE NOW.
[QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC]
HERE ARE A FEW SCENES FROM
THIS PARTICULAR SHOW.
AND I DON'T LIKE
TO HYPE YOU TOO MUCH,
BUT, BY GOLLY, IF THIS
DOESN'T MAKE YOU WANT
TO WATCH THIS SHOW,
THEN, WELL, YOU OBVIOUSLY
HAVE A LIFE.
WELL, POSSUM LODGE DIDN'T GET
OFF TOO BAD, THERE, ON THE
LAWN MOWER FIASCO.
THE TOWN COUNCIL DIDN'T
FINE US OR ANYTHING.
THEY JUST FORCED US TO
ADOPT A HIGHWAY.
SO NOW WE ARE THE PROUD
CUSTODIANS OF THE THREE-MILE
STRETCH UP AT THE FAR END
OF THE LAKE.
YOU ADOPTED ORPHAN'S BEND?
YES, WE DID, HAROLD.
AND WE GOT SOME BIG, BIG,
BIG PLANS FOR HER...
GONNA JACK UP THE SPEED LIMIT,
BAN SENIORS, AND THROW A
TOLL BOOTH IN THERE.
NO, NO, NO, YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO DO IT LIKE THAT, UNCLE RED.
YOUR JOB IS TO KEEP THAT PIECE
OF THE HIGHWAY CLEAN AND SAFE.
LIKE, ONE TIME, OUR JUNIOR
RANGERS TROOP, LIKE, ONE SUMMER,
RIGHT, WE ADOPHIGHWAY TOO,
AND FOR THE ENTIRE SUMMER
THAT WAS OUR JOB.
ON THE VERY FIRST DAY -- VERY
FIRST DAY -- FIRST DAY --
I CLEANED UP MORE CUPS AND TIN
CANS THAN ANYBODY ELSE,
SO FOR THE REMAINDER OF THE
MONTH, I GOT TO CLEAN UP THE
HIGHWAY WHILE EVERYBODY ELSE
WENT TO THE SWIMMING POOL.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
NO, THAT'S OKAY.
MY MOM WOULDN'T LET ME
GO TO THE SWIMMING POOL.
YOU KNOW HOW EVERYBODY FLICKS
THEIR TOWELS AND STUFF?
YOU KNOW, THAT COULD INTERFERE
WITH MY ABILITY TO...
YOU KNOW...
WALK?
NO, NOT WALK...
REPRODUCE?!
THAT COULD HAPPEN.
I PRAY A LOT.
YOU KNOW, HAROLD, I'M THINKING
YOU COULD USE A LITTLE EXERCISE.
WHY DON'T YOU COME UP TO THE
HIGHWAY AND HELP US CLEAN THAT
UP, JUST FOR A LITTLE WHILE, EH?
WELL, YEAH, I COULD DO THAT.
I GOT SOME SPARE TIME.
ALL RIGHT. AND WHEN YOU GET UP
THERE, HAROLD, JUST CLEAN IT
UP AS FAST AS YOU CAN, OKAY?
DON'T TALK TO THE
OTHER GUYS, ALL RIGHT?
HOW COME?
'CAUSE THEY'LL
KILL YOU, HAROLD.
(APPLAUSE)
OH, THE DEVIL
CHALLENGED EVEL KNIEVEL
TO A CONTEST OF
IMPOSSIBLE JUMPS
THE WINNER WOULD
GET A HELL OF A PRIZE
AND THE LOSER WOULD
TAKE HIS LUMPS
OH, THEY JUMPED A CANYON,
A MOUNTAIN AND A LAKE
AND A FIELD OF
HUNGRY BOLL WEEVILS
AND THE DEVIL DISCOVERED
TO HIS SURPRISE
HE WAS THE LESSER
OF TWO EVELS
IT'S THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
AND IF YOU LOVE BRITISH CARS,
YOU'RE GONNA LOVE TONIGHT'S
GRAND PRIZE...
A BUSINESS CARD FROM
FLINTY'S TOWING.
ALL RIGHT, UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE
30 SECONDS TO GET Mr. DALTON
HUMPHREY TO SAY THIS WORD...
PARANOID.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, DALTON,
PERSECUTION COMPLEX...
THE COURTHOUSE.
NO, NO, THAT'S A
PROSECUTION COMPLEX.
OKAY, IF YOU'RE SUSPICIOUS OF
EVERYONE FOR ABSOLUTELY NO
APPARENT REASON,
THEN YOU WOULD SAY
THAT'S BEING...
NORMAL.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT. LET'S SAY
YOU'RE NEGATIVE, AND YOU HAVE NO
CONTACT WITH REALITY WHATSOEVER.
THAT WOULD BE...
MY DAUGHTER.
LET'S GO ANOTHER WAY
ON THIS ONE, DALTON, OKAY?
YOU GOT TWO SLIPPERS.
THAT MAKES A...
PAIR.
OKAY. SOMEONE BUGS YOU,
YOU GET...
ANNOYED.
RIGHT! PUT 'EM TOGETHER.
PUT 'EM TOGETHER.
YOU SAYIN' SOMEONE'S HIDING MY
SLIPPERS TO ANNOY ME?
YOU KNOW, IT'S PROBABLY
MY NEIGHBOUR.
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE
HE'S TRYIN' TO GET ME.
HE THINKS I SNEAK INTO
HIS HOUSE AT NIGHT AND
REARRANGE HIS FURNITURE.
ALL RIGHT, AND HE THINKS THAT
WAY BECAUSE HE'S...
CAUGHT ME DOIN' IT.
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
(CRASH)
YOU KNOW HOW EVERY ONCE IN A
BLUE MOON THE WORLD GIVES
YOU CREDIT, HUH?
IT HAPPENS TO ME
ONCE EVERY YEAR.
YOU KNOW ON THAT SPECIAL
GARBAGE DAY WHEN PEOPLE CAN
PUT OUT ANYTHING THEY WANT
OF ANY SIZE,
AND THE GARBAGE COLLECTORS
HAVE TO TAKE IT?
WELL, THAT'S THE DAY WHEN
EVERYBODY WISHES THEY HAD
A VAN LIKE MINE.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
HUH? WHAT DO YOU SEE HERE, HUH?
BATHTUBS, TAPS, SHOWER NOZZLES,
DRAINS , U-JOINTS...
NOW, I SUPPOSE YOU COULD USE
THIS STUFF TO PUT IN A GUEST
BATHROOM IN YOUR HOUSE,
BUT WHAT'LL THAT GET YOU?
GUESTS!
I LOOK AT THIS STUFF, AND I SEE
COOKING OVER CHARCOAL.
THAT'S RIGHT... A BATH-E-QUE.
ALL RIGHT, THERE'S OUR
BATH-E-QUE...
ONE TUB FOR THE BASE, ONE FOR
THE BAR-B-QUE, AND ONE
FOR THE LID.
NOW ALL WE GOTTA DO IS
ADD A HINGE ON THERE,
SO THE LID WILL
OPEN UP THIS WAY.
OKAY. WE COULD BOLT HINGES ON
THERE, BUT THAT WOULD INVOLVE
PROBABLY NINE HOURS OF WORK
PLUS STEALING A DRILL.
INSTEAD, I RECOMMEND THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON...
DUCT TAPE.
HERE WE GO.
GIVE 'ER A TRY HERE.
OH, MAN, I'LL TELL YA, YOU RAISE
THAT UP AND DOWN A FEW TIMES
COOKIN' A STEAK,
YOU'RE GONNA WORK UP
AN APPETITE.
SOMETHIN' TO HOLD 'ER OPEN. OH,
THERE WE GO. SHOWER CURTAIN ROD
OUGHTA DO 'ER.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, WHAT IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT STEP WHEN YOU'RE
BUILDING A BATH-E-QUE?
BEFORE YOU FIRE 'ER UP,
YOU REALLY WANNA GET THE
BATH MAT OUT OF THERE.
OTHERWISE, YOU COULD GET
YOURSELF A BAD CASE
OF ATHLETE'S FOOD.
OKAY, NOW THE BIG QUESTION...
DO WE GO WITH GAS, OR DO
WE GO WITH CHARCOAL?
CHARCOAL'S REAL GOOD, YOU KNOW?
'CAUSE WHEN YOU'RE DONE,
YOU JUST SWEEP THE ASHES
RIGHT DOWN THE DRAIN.
BUT, TODAY, WE'RE GONNA
GO TOP DRAWER.
WE'RE GONNA BUILD A BATH-E-QUE
THAT'S GONNA BE A GAS GRILL.
ISN'T THAT SOMETHIN', HUH?
HERE WE GOT THE COPPER PIPES,
THERE, CARRYING THE GAS.
AND WE GOT SHOWER
NOZZLES AS BURNERS.
ALL RIGHT. NOW THEY'RE
ALL HOOKED UP TO OUR
PROPANE UNIT, HERE.
BUY IN BULK, YOU'RE
GONNA SAVE BIG.
WELL, I GUESS IT'S TIME
TO FIRE 'ER UP.
OR, IN THIS CASE,
HIT THE SHOWERS.
(SOUND OF LEAKING PROPANE)
OH, MAN, THAT COULD USE A LITTLE
EXTRA COATING OF DUCT TAPE.
THERE WE GO.
THAT'S FINE.
TELL YOU ANOTHER FEATURE OF THIS
UNIT, IT'S GOT THE ELECTRIC
SPARKER ON IT.
ALL RIGHT, I'VE ADDED A FEW
FEATURES TO HER THERE.
I GOT THE CHEESE SLICES
ALL READY TO GO.
YOU WANNA LIMIT YOUR GUESTS TO,
MAYBE, TWO SLICES A PIECE
ON THAT.
THEN WE GOT THE SHOWER RACK,
HERE, WITH OUR SHAMPOO BOTTLES,
BUT I'VE EMPTIED THEM OUT,
AND I'VE PUT THE KETCHUP
IN THIS ONE, AND THE
MUSTARD IN THIS UNIT,
AND WE'VE GOT THE SPECIAL
BATH-E-QUE SAUCE IN HERE.
AND HERE'S AN EXTRA LITTLE
FEATURE I'VE ADDED...
A COLD WATER TAP, THERE, HOOKED
INTO A COLD WATER SHOWER;
KINDA DEAL WITH THE
FLARE-UPS, YOU KNOW?
KEEP THE FLAMES DOWN IN THERE
'CAUSE I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHIN',
NOTHIN' TAKES THE FIRE OUT
OF YOUR LOIN CHOPS LIKE
A COLD SHOWER.
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE ASKIN'
"WHAT'S COOKIN'?"
WELL, COME TAKE A LOOK.
LOOK AT THAT. IS THAT
BEAUTIFUL OR WHAT?
SEE, YOU GOT THE
HOT DOGS ON THERE,
AND OVER HERE, COURSE,
WE GOT OUR CHICKEN.
AND, BY GOLLY, I THINK YOU
KNOW EVERYBODY LOVES A
BURGER, DON'T THEY?
EITHER PLAIN OR, HEY, LET'S GO
FIRST CLASS HERE:  THROW A
HUNK OF CHEESE ON THERE.
OH-HO-HO, WE GOT OUR
CONDIMENTS IN THIS AREA HERE.
AND I'LL TELL YA SOMETHIN',
YOU GOTTA REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY
SHOULD AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
LOOK AT THAT. THERE'S AN
AMERICAN STANDARD.
I WANT TO TAKE A MINUTE AND
TALK TO SOME OF YOU OLDER
FELLAS OUT THERE.
MAYBE ANOTHER DRIVER CALLED YOU
A MORON, OR YOU HAD A BIT OF A
RUN-IN WITH A BAD SALES CLERK,
MAYBE AN ANNOYING CO-WORKER,
OR EVEN A ROTTEN RELATIVE,
AND YOU START ASKIN'
YOURSELF THE QUESTION,
"AM I TOTALLY SURROUNDED
BY STUPID PEOPLE?"
THE ANSWER, OF COURSE, IS...
YES.
OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, YOU ARE ONE OF THE
LAST SMART PEOPLE LEFT
IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
NOW, KIDS TODAY DON'T KNOW NEAR
AS MUCH AS YOU DID WHEN YOU
WERE THEIR AGE.
EVERY GENERATION OF RELATIVES
IS DENSER THAN THE LAST.
HECK, THEY'RE NOT EVEN MAKIN'
DOGS AS SMART AS THEY USED TO.
YOU, SIR, ARE THE LAST
OUTPOST OF INTELLIGENCE.
YOU LET THEM CALL YOU AN IDIOT.
LET THEM LAUGH AT YOU, EH?
WHO'S THE GUY THAT GOT 17 YEARS
OUT OF THAT CAR, HUH?
WHO'S THE GUY WITH THE
GREENEST LAWN ON THE STREET?
AND AREN'T YOU THE GUY THAT GOT
ALL YOUR CHRISTMAS SHOPPING
DONE IN JULY...
AT A YARD SALE?
SO WHO'S THE IDIOT NOW?
WHO'S THE MORON NOW?
AND IF YOU'RE AS SMART
AS YOU THINK YOU ARE,
YOU WON'T ANSWER
THOSE QUESTIONS.
REMEMBER, US MORONS ARE
PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(APPLAUSE)
ALL HAIL THE HIGHWAYMAN,
RED GREEN!
(APPLAUSE)
KNOCK IT OFF.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
HE'S JUST GOOFIN' AROUND.
YOU CAN LAUGH ALL
YOU WANT, HAROLD.
I'M TELLIN' YOU, THIS
ADOPT-A-HIGHWAY THING,
WHAT A GOLD MINE!
I GOT THREE BUCKS
IN BOTTLES HERE.
I'VE GOT FIVE HUBCAPS,
AND SOME KIDS ON A
SCHOOL BUS TRIED TO
WING AN APPLE
AT HAROLD,
AND I CAUGHT IT.
STILL GOT THE
SOFT HANDS.
I'VE STILL GOT THE HARD HEAD.
UNCLE RED, THAT OPERATION OUT
THERE IS A CLEANUP OPERATION,
NOT A SCAVENGER HUNT.
WELL, HAROLD, IT CAN
BE A BIT OF BOTH.
AT LEAST,
IT CAN NOW.
YOU KNOW, WHEN WE FIRST GOT UP
THERE, YOU KNOW, THE DARN PLACE
WAS SO CLEAN, THERE WAS NOTHING
FOR US TO DO.
YEAH, SO, WHAT DO THEY DO --
WHAT DO THEY DO?
THEY TAKE ALL THE GARBAGE OUT OF
THEIR VEHICLES AND DUMP IT ON
THE SIDE OF THE ROAD.
BUT WHAT A LOCATION!
HOLY MACKEREL!
THERE'S A LOT OF ADVANTAGES
WHEN YOU OWN YOUR OWN HIGHWAY.
WHOA-A-HA. YOU DO NOT
OWN THE HIGHWAY.
WELL, I DRIVE
LIKE I DO.
BUT LOOK AT THE OPPORTUNITY
HERE, HAROLD, EH?
HOLY SMOKE. PEOPLE SLOW DOWN
FOR ORPHAN'S BEND ANYHOW,
WHY NOT HAVE 'EM STOP
AND SHOP, EH?
WE COULD HAVE...
A SOUVENIR SHOP,
HOT DOG STAND,
TIRE RETREADING THERE,
THE BLACK VELVET PAINTINGS.
THIS IS NOT JUST A ROAD,
THIS IS A FOUR-LANE MALL.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE CLEANING
UP THE SIDE OF THE ROAD,
NOT DEVELOPING IT.
YOU GOTTA
THINK BIG, HAROLD.
YOU GUYS AREN'T
EQUIPPED TO THINK BIG.
WHO SAID THAT?
WELL, GET YOURSELVES
COMFORTABLE BECAUSE WE GOT
A REAL AMBITIOUS ADVENTURE
WITH BILL TODAY.
HE'S GONNA TRY AND MOVE
THAT STUMP THERE.
THAT STUMP'S BEEN THERE BEHIND
THE LODGE SINCE, AH, WELL,
SINCE OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
WAS AROUND 70.
SO IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
AND THESE ARE A
BUNCH OF TOOLS.
ACTUALLY, THESE ARE JUST A
FEW ODDS AND ENDS THAT I
CARRY IN MY VAN.
THERE'S ANOTHER LESSON
FOR YOU YOUNGSTERS...
HAVE SOME TOOLS IN THE BACK OF
YOUR VAN AT ALL TIMES.
REALLY HELPS THE TRACTION
IN THE WINTER.
DIDN'T REALIZE THAT I HAD
THAT MANY IN THERE.
THAT'S SOME SERIOUS CHOPPIN'.
ALL RIGHT, JUST START
CHOPPIN' AWAY ON 'ER THERE.
MY GOSH, HE'S SAYIN' SHE'S A
LITTLE SPONGY -- GET 'ER
OUTTA THERE.
OKAY, SWITCH TO THE PICKAXE.
GET THAT OUTA THERE.
OKAY, LET ME HELP
YOU THERE, BILL.
ONE AND TWO AND...
PULL!
YEP, A FEW TOOLS LODGED INTO
THE STUMP AT THIS POINT.
HE WAS TRYIN' TO DRILL
A HOLE FOR THE DYNAMITE,
BUT HERE'S WHAT HAPPENED.
NOW, DON'T, BILL.
DON'T DO THAT.
(EXPLOSION)
YEP, YOU'VE DETONATED IT.
NOPE, EVERYTHING'S FINE.
BY GOLLY, LOOK AT THAT.
WE GOT RID OF ALL THE TOOLS.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE THEY ARE.
OH, HERE THEY COME NOW.
VERY DANGEROUS TO WORK WITH
BILL ON A CLOSE BASIS, THERE.
WELL, THE CHAINSAW WASN'T
RUNNIN', SO IT WASN'T
REALLY THAT BAD.
ALL RIGHT, WHAT NOW, BILL?
OKAY, NOW WE HOOK UP A ROPE.
AND THIS IS THE BEAUTY
OF HAVING A UNIT LIKE
THE POSSUM VAN.
YOU GOT THE BIG EIGHT
IN THERE --
I WOULDN'T STAND ON
THAT ROPE, BILL.
DON'T STAND ON THE ROPE.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO GET OFF THAT.
GET OFF IT.
THERE, YOU'RE OFF IT NOW.
O-O-H, BY GOLLY, YOU KNOW,
I WOULDN'T RECOMMEND THAT
ON A FULL STOMACH.
YOU ALL RIGHT THERE, BILL?
OH, JUST POPPED HIS ARM OUT OF
HIS SLEEVE AND PROBABLY OUT
OF HIS SHOULDER.
OH, NO, HE'S FINE.
HERE'S ANOTHER THING FOR
YOU YOUNGSTERS...
YOU DON'T QUIT;
YOU TRY ANOTHER WAY.
TERMITES!
SO BILL'S GOT A CAN
OF TERMITES THERE.
JUST SPRINKLE A FEW AROUND.
I THINK YOU'LL NEED MORE
THAN THAT, BILL.
PRETTY BIG STUMP.
TAKE A LOT OF TERMITES,
I WOULD THINK.
THERE, NOW YOU'RE TALKIN'.
NOW YOU'RE TALKIN.
THERE YOU GO.
SPARE THE TERMITES; SPOIL
THE STUMP. THAT'S WHAT WE SAY.
GONNA TAKE A WHILE,
BILL, I THINK.
DON'T BE IMPATIENT, NOW.
WELL, IT'S BEEN 10-20 MINUTES.
I'LL GIVE 'ER A TRY.
DOESN'T LOOK TOO BAD.
ALL RIGHT, AND NOW WE'RE
GONNA TRY ANOTHER APPROACH.
WE GOT THE CHAIN AROUND THE
TREE, AND THIS IS A SPECIAL
DEAL WE'RE GONNA DO.
WE'RE GONNA PUT A ROPE AROUND
SOMETHING REAL SOLID.
WHAT COULD BE MORE SOLID THAN
ONE OF THE OLD STONE HOUSES
DOWN AT THE END OF
THE LANE WAY?
THESE PEOPLE GO TO
FLORIDA EVERY WINTER.
THEY GOT A BIG SURPRISE WHEN
THEY GET HOME, I'LL BET.
ANYWAY, WE HOOK THAT UP TO THE
CHAIN ON THE STUMP, AND THAT
LITTLE TOOL BILL HAS THERE --
I MEAN, THE ONE THAT'S IN
HIS HAND -- THAT'S CALLED
A COME-ALONG.
WE'RE GONNA USE THAT TO KIND
OF WINCH THAT STUMP.
IT'S STARTIN' TO COME UP SNUG,
AND WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN NOW
IS IT'LL PULL THAT STUMP
RIGHT OUT OF THE GROUND.
NOW, HERE'S ANOTHER THING
FOR YOU YOUNGSTERS.
WE NEED A LITTLE MORE OF WHAT
THEY CALL LEVERAGE.
LEVERAGE:  THAT'S SOMETHIN' YOU
NEED WHEN YOU GO TO THE BANK.
AND YOU PUT THAT ON THERE, AND
YOU CAN REALLY...
O-O-O-H.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, THIS IS --
THIS IS PROBABLY NOT...
NO, I DON'T THINK THAT'S
GONNA WORK, BILL.
I KNOW WHAT WE SHOULD DO...
LET'S LEAVE.
YOU KNOW, YOU TRY TO
HELP YOUR COMMUNITY;
MAYBE STIMULATE
THE LOCAL ECONOMY;
SHOW A LITTLE IMAGINATION.
WHERE DOES IT GET YOU?
TROUBLE AT
ORPHAN'S BEND?
YOU KNOW, WE GOT SUCH A
GREAT THING GOIN' UP THERE,
AND THEN SOMEBODY
GOES AND COMPLAINS.
REALLY?
WELL, YOU KNOW, I HEARD YOU GUYS
HAD SO MUCH STUFF AT THE SIDES
OF THE HIGHWAY, THAT IT'S
DOWN TO ONE LANE, HUH?
HAROLD, WE GOT A TOURIST
ATTRACTION GOIN' THERE, EH?
YOU KNOW, ONE TIME
THE MAYOR SAID TO ME,
"HOW COME EVERY TOURIST
WHO STOPS AT POSSUM LAKE
HAS CAR TROUBLE?"
THAT'S BECAUSE, IF THEY
DIDN'T HAVE CAR TROUBLE,
THEY WOULDN'T STOP HERE.
SO WE FINALLY HAVE A BONA FIDE
REASON TO STOP, AND EVERYBODY'S
GIVIN' US GRIEF.
WELL, YOU KNOW, MAYBE IT'S
THE RIGHT IDEA, JUST THE
WRONG LOCATION.
THE SIDE OF A HIGHWAY MIGHT
NOT BE THE BEST PLACE
FOR A THEME PARK.
OH, HAROLD, IT MAKES
SO MUCH SENSE THERE.
WE GOT REFRESHMENTS;
WE GOT WASHROOMS;
WE GOT THIS DRIVE-THROUGH
MIDWAY;
WE GOT A BIG CARDBOARD CUTOUT OF
AN ELEPHANT WITH A GARBAGE PAIL
HANGIN' FROM HIS TAIL.
CARS DRIVE UP.
YOU PAY A BUCK.
YOU THROW YOUR GARBAGE.
YOU HIT JUMBO IN THE CAN,
YOU WIN A DUST BUSTER.
I'M TELLIN' YOU, HAROLD,
ORPHAN'S BEND IS DANGEROUS.
NOW THEY SLOW DOWN.
WE'VE ACTUALLY MADE IT SAFE.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT? THESE ARE
THE KINDS OF THINGS YOU SHOULD
BE SAYING TO THE TOWN COUNCIL.
WELL, AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I'M GOING DOWN THERE
IN A FEW MINUTES,
BUT I'M NOT GONNA LET THEM
SHUT US DOWN, HAROLD.
I WANT YOU TO MEET ME IN THE
POSSUM VAN UP AT ORPHAN'S
BEND IN A COUPLE OF HOURS.
WE'LL MAKE A ROADBLOCK
IF WE HAVE TO.
OKAY, OKAY, WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO
DROP YOU OFF DOWNTOWN ON MY WAY?
(POLICE SIREN)
NOT NECESSARY, HAROLD.
THIS IS THE REPAIR SHOP PART
OF THE SHOW WE CALL,
"IF IT AIN'T BROKE,
YOU'RE NOT TRYIN'".
EDGAR MONTROSE, HERE, HAS
BROUGHT IN SOMETHIN'
FOR US TO FIX.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
FOR US, EDGAR?
OH, NO THANKS, RED.
MY MOM WANTED HER
DINING ROOM SET REFINISHED.
I STARTED IT, BUT I WAS KINDA
HOPING YOU'D HELP ME FINISH.
WELL, I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN DO.
WELL, YOU GOT 'ER BURNED
UP THE SIDE, THERE.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING, USING A
HEAT GUN ON THE VARNISH, THERE?
NO, THAT WAS FROM THE EXPLOSION.
DO YOU WANNA TELL US
ABOUT THAT, EDGAR?
NO, RED, IT'S NOT
MY PROUDEST MOMENT.
ALL RIGHT,
WE'LL SKIP IT.
WELL, HERE YOU CAN
USE DUCT TAPE.
YOU STICK IT ON THE VARNISH, AND
YOU PEEL IT OFF SLOW, AND SHE'LL
JUST LIFT RIGHT OFF THERE.
OH, NO, NO, NO, I DON'T WANT
TO REFINISH THAT CHAIR.
I JUST BROUGHT IT IN
AS A REFERENCE.
SEE, I WANNA REPAIR THE
OTHER THREE CHAIRS SO
THEY MATCH THIS ONE,
SO THEY'RE A
COMPLETE SET AGAIN.
OH, THE REST OF THE DINING ROOM
SET THAT WAS MAYBE HURT BY
THAT EXPLOSION YOU DON'T
WANNA TALK ABOUT.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
YOU GO GET THE
OTHER CHAIRS.
OH, OKAY.
BUT, HERE AGAIN, EVEN WITH
REPAIR WORK, YOU CAN USE THE
DUCT TAPE ON THAT
BECAUSE THE SPINDLES, SOMETIMES
THEY GET LOOSE, OR YOU CAN DO
THE CANING WORK, OR EVEN IF
YOU GOT A, YOU KNOW...
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
SO, AH, ARE THESE THE
OTHER THREE CHAIRS?
AND THE DINING ROOM TABLE.
JUST LET ME SAY,
IN MY DEFENSE,
THAT CHEMICAL PAINT STRIPPER
AND NITROGLYCERIN
ARE BOTH CLEAR LIQUIDS.
(LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE)
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE NEVER TOO OLD
TO LEARN THINGS.
ARE YOU EVER
TOO OLD TO LISTEN?
YOU NEVER LISTEN, SO I GUESS
THE ANSWER'S 'YES' TO THAT ONE.
I LISTEN, HAROLD.
OH, REALLY?
WELL, DID YOU
HEAR MY ADVICE?
DID YOU HEAR THE
WARNING OF THE POLICEMAN?
DID YOU HEAR THE HORN
OF THE ONCOMING TRUCK?
OKAY, OKAY, NOW THIS IS
A GOOD POINT, ALL RIGHT?
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO NEVER PAID
ATTENTION IN PHYSICS CLASS,
A MOVING OBJECT CAN HAVE
A GREAT DEAL OF MOMENTUM;
FOR EXAMPLE, A LOGGING TRUCK
DOING A HUNDRED CLICKS.
YES, YES, THAT WOULD, INDEED,
HAVE MORE MOMENTUM THAN, SAY,
OH, A PARKED POSSUM VAN.
IN FAIRNESS, IT WAS ONLY
PARKED UNTIL THE IMPACT.
NOW, IS THAT WHEN THE
LOGS BROKE LOOSE?
I DUNNO. IT'S HARD TO SAY.
ALL I KNOW IS I HAVEN'T HAD THAT
MUCH BARK BETWEEN MY LEGS SINCE
MOOSE THOMPSON'S ROTTWEILER
WENT INTO HEAT.
(LAUGHTER)
WELL, THE CONCESSION BOOTHS
WERE ALL WRECKED,
BUT THE TRUCK WAS FINE
BECAUSE THE HOT DOG BUNS
TOOK MOST OF THE HIT.
BOY, IS THE HIGHWAY
EVER A MESS, THOUGH.
WORSE THAN BEFORE YOU
GUYS EVEN ADOPTED IT.
YOU GOT A LOT OF CLEANUP
THERE, UNCLE RED.
WELL, I TOOK CARE OF IT, HAROLD.
I SPOKE TO THE JUNIOR RANGERS,
AND I GAVE THEM
YOUR HOME NUMBER.
(POSSUM CALL)
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
WATCH YOURSELF, NOW.
WELL, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I'M KINDA FED UP
NOW WITH ORPHAN'S BEND,
AND NOW I'D LIKE TO TRY
MY HAND AT WIFE'S CURVE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT THE LODGE,
YOU KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(APPLAUSE)
[CAPTIONS PERFORMED BY
CAPTION RESOURCE CENTRE]
Harold:  TAKE YOUR SEATS.
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
OKAY, ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
Harold:  OKAY, FIRST
ANNOUNCEMENT TONIGHT,
WELL, T.G.I.F.
UM, THE C.J.T.O.P.Y.S. IS
MEETING A.S.A.P. AT THE
C.A.W. HALL, ROOM B.
GUEST SPEAKER IS P.G. YOUNG,
B.A., M.A., Ph.D. FROM
I.B.M. IN THE USA.
HIS TOPIC...
THE A.B.C.'S OF MS DOS.
SOME S.R.O. TICKETS ARE
STILL AVAILABLE, C.O.D.
A "Q" AND "A" WITH P.G.
IS T.B.A.
O.K.?