I THINK THE TRICK TO
A HAPPY LIFE
IS TO TAKE A BORING JOB
AND MAKE IT FUN.
THE EXACT OPPOSITE
TO WHAT Dr RUTH DOES.
TO ME TAKING OUT THE GARBAGE
IS THE MOST DEMEANING
REPETITIVE JOB
OUTSIDE OF POLITICS.
SO I FOUND A WAY TO PUT
A LITTLE ZING INTO IT.
ALL'S YOU NEED IS AN EXTENSION
LADDER AND A SHOVEL.
TAKE YOUR SHOVEL
AND DIG A HOLE.
I KNOW DIGGING A HOLE
IS HARD TO DO,
BUT IT'S AMAZING, IF YOU GOT A
LOCAL PROSPECTORS CLUB
HOW FAST THEY'LL DIG A HOLE
IF YOU TELL 'EM THERE'S
GOLD DOWN THERE.
AND THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
I CALL IT MY "CARTAPULT."
SORRY I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO EXPLAIN THAT,
BUT IT'S GARBAGE DAY.
[ CRASHING]
[ WHOOSHING THROUGH AIR]
[ GARBAGE CLANKING ]
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
[ GLASS SHATTERING]
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
YEAH. BY GOLLY. OKAY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HEY, THANK YOU.
YEAH, I APPRECIATE THAT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP AT
THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
GUYS HAD A SPECIAL PRESENTATION
FOR ME LAST NIGHT
TO SHOW THEIR APPRECIATION THAT
I TOOK THE JOB AS LODGE LEADER
SO THEY DIDN'T HAVE TO.
BEST PART WAS THEY GAVE ME
A FLY-IN FISHING TRIP
THIS WEEKEND
UP TO PILOT LODGE ON
GREAT SLAVE LAKE.
SO I ASKED 'EM,
HOW CAN YOU GUYS AFFORD
SUCH A GREAT GIFT?
AND APPARENTLY, NOW, THERE'S
AN EMERGENCY FUND IN AN
OLD TACKLE BOX
UNDER THE MAIN DOCK.
I TELL YA, IF I'D HAVE
KNOWN THAT WAS THERE,
IT WOULDN'T BE.
RED!
I FOUND THE EMERGENCY FUND!
OH, GREAT.
OPEN HER UP.
TAKE A LOOK!
MAYBE THERE'S GOLD
IN HERE, HUH?
COULD BE.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
IS THAT MAYBE
A GOLD FISH?
I DON'T THINK SO.
MAYBE THE FISH
ATE THE MONEY.
WHAT'S THAT NOTE
THAT FELL OUT OF
THE BOX THERE?
THERE'S A NOTE THERE.
OH!
WHAT'S THAT?
LOOKS LIKE A CHEQUE.
YEAH?
YEAH.
PROBABLY SOMEBODY TOOK THE
MONEY AND LEFT AN I.O.U.
CAN YOU READ IT?
NO, IT'S ALL SMUDGED.
NO CHIT?
LET ME SEE THAT.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO GO AND
TALK TO OLD MAN SEDGWICK
ABOUT THIS.
THIS IS
HIS STATIONERY.
HOW DO
YOU KNOW THAT?
IT'S PARCHMENT.
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S PRIZE IS A 10-MINUTE
SNATCH AND GRAB SHOPPING SPREE
AT HERBY'S HOUSE OF PICKLES.
"HERBY'S, IT'S NOT
JUST A PICKLE,
"IT'S AN ALTERNATE
LIFESTYLE."
PLAYING FOR TODAY'S PRIZE
IS Mr DWIGHT CARDIFF OF
THE PORT ASBESTOS MARINA!
[ APPLAUSE ]
Mr CARDIFF, PLEASE COVER
YOUR EARS, OKAY.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I JUST WON'T LISTEN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OKAY, UH, Mr GREEN,
YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET Mr CARDIFF
TO SAY THIS WORD...
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, DWIGHT.
WHEN SOMEBODY GETS
EVERYBODY ELSE TO DO
ALL THE WORK FOR THEM,
THAT PERSON IS...
A DELEGATOR.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHEN YOU
HAVE A DAY WHERE YOU DO
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING?
AND YOU'LL SAY
TO YOUR FRIENDS,
YOU KNOW WHAT, I'M HAVING
A REAL SOMETHING DAY.
A REAL GOOD DAY.
OKAY, DWIGHT, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT A SLOTH IS?
YEAH, I GOT A GUARD SLOTH
AT THE MARINA.
IT HANGS IN THE TREE
AND PEES ON THE TRESPASSERS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT
OF TIME, Mr GREEN.
YEAH, WELL, THEN DWIGHT YOU'LL
BE FAMILIAR WITH THIS
EXPRESSION...
AS SOMETHING AS A SLOTH.
I'M FINDING THIS REALLY
TEDIOUS, RED.
C'MON, C'MON.
AS SOMETHING AS A SLOTH.
WE DON'T CONNECT
INTELLECTUALLY, RED.
THIS IS SO EASY!
AS SOMETHING AS A SLOTH.
YOU'VE SAID THAT THREE TIMES.
ARE YOU GONNA THINK
OF ANOTHER CLUE
OR ARE YOU TOO LAZY?
THERE WE GO!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
[ BELL RINGING ]
HAVE A PICKLE.
HI, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE.
NEXT TIME YOU FIND YOURSELF IN
A SEWAGE OR SEPTIC SITUATION
AND YOU HIRE ME
TO PUMP OUT YOUR TANK,
I'M GONNA THROW IN A LITTLE
SOMETHING FOR THE KIDS...
A TOY SEPTIC TRUCK!
HEY, BOBBY,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF YOUR NEW SEPTIC TRUCK?
IT REALLY SUCKS.
LET ME SHOW YOU.
NEAT, HUH?
THAT WAS MY DRINK.
THAT'S NOT ALL.
ACT NOW AND I'LL
THROW IN THIS
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
SEWAGE AND SEPTIC SUCKING
SERVICE ACTION FIGURE.
WHAT ARE HIS POWERS?
WELL, HE'S,
UH, A SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICE
ACTION FIGURE.
YOU KNOW, THE
ORIGINAL POKEMON.
WHERE'S YOUR DRINK?
MY --
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU GO RUN
ALONG AND PLAY WITH THAT, HUH!
HEY, LOOK,
THERE'S BARNEY.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS TOO
GOOD TO BE TRUE,
BUT IT IS!
ALL I WANT IS YOUR BUSINESS.
AND YOU GET...
ONE FREE TOY SEPTIC TRUCK,
PLUS THE BONUS ACTION FIGURE.
BUT SUPPLIES ARE LIMITED.
SO ACT NOW BEFORE
WE GET BACKLOGGED.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I HEAR A LOT OF PEOPLE
TALKING ABOUT
HOW LIVING IN THE COUNTRY
ISN'T AS GOOD AS LIVING
IN THE CITY.
THEY SAY THERE'S
NOTHING TO DO,
NO FANCY RESTAURANTS OR
CRACK HOUSES OR ANYTHING.
PERSONALLY, I LIKE LIVING
IN THE COUNTRY.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A PLACE
WHERE A CREATIVE PERSON
CAN EXPRESS HIMSELF ON
A LIMITED BUDGET,
AND WHERE THE LOCAL BUILDING
BYLAWS TEND TO BE
UNDERENFORCED.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I'M
TALKING ABOUT.
THIS HERE IS A DINING
TENT WHERE YOU GO IN THERE
AND ENJOY A MEAL WITHOUT
THE MOSQUITOES AND FLIES
GETTING IN THERE.
OR IF YOU LIKE
MOSQUITOES AND FLIES,
YOU CAN TAKE 'EM IN
THERE WITH YOU
AND STOP THEM
FROM GETTING OUT.
WELL, TODAY I'M GOING TO TURN
THIS RURAL DINING TENT
INTO A SWANK URBAN
REVOLVING RESTAURANT.
FIRST THING I NEED IS
SOMETHING TO USE AS ROLLERS.
I WENT WITH THESE
FOUR-INCH SEWER PIPES
BECAUSE THAT'S THE SIZE THE
ROAD CONSTRUCTION CREW
WAS USING.
ONCE I GET THEM ALL SPREAD OUT,
I'M GONNA NEED A PLATFORM
FOR MY TENT TO SIT ON.
I'M GONNA USE THESE, UH, SHEETS
OF PLYWOOD RIGHT HERE
AND, UH, I FIGURED I NEEDED A
16-FOOT DIAMETER CIRCLE,
SO I HAD MY DOG ON
AN EIGHT-FOOT LEASH
AND JUST LET HIM
RUN AROUND ME.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS CUT
ALONG THE PAWPRINTS,
AND I'VE GOT MY PLATFORM.
[ ROAR OF LAUGHTER
AND APPLAUSE ]
I'M USING THIS FIRE HYDRANT AS
AN ANCHOR FOR THE WHOLE UNIT.
IT'S STRONG,
IT'S NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
I FIGURE IT'LL COME IN HANDY
WHEN I HAVE MY KITCHEN FIRE.
ALL I DO IS LAY MY BOARDS
OVER TOP OF THESE ROLLERS,
AND I'M GONNA PUT 'EM DOWN
WITH THE ROAD SIGNS FACING UP.
THAT WAY IT'LL FEEL LIKE WE'RE
TRAVELLING ALL OVER THE WORLD --
WELL, ALL OVER MY WORLD.
THOSE OF YOU WHO
STUDIED PHYSICS --
YOU KNOW, AT THE DETENTION
CENTRE OR WHATEVER,
YOU KNOW THAT IT DOESN'T TAKE
MUCH POWER TO TURN A WHEEL
AS LONG AS THE WHEEL
IS BIG ENOUGH,
AND YOU APPLY THE FORCE TO
THE VERY OUTSIDE EDGE.
SO I GOT A WIRE BRUSH HOOKED
INTO MY ELECTRIC DRILL HERE
AND GOT HER LOCKED
IN THE 'ON' POSITION.
ALL I GOTTA DO IS PLUG HER IN,
AND WE'RE IN BUSINESS.
OH, YEAH, ONE MORE THING.
BE SURE TO RUN
YOUR EXTENSION CORD
UP THROUGH THE CENTRE
OF THE UNIT,
BECAUSE IF YOU RUN IT
ON THE OUTSIDE,
THEN WHEN THE PLATFORM TURNS,
THERE COULD BE PROBLEMS.
OKAY, WE'RE ALL READY
FOR THE FINAL STEP,
ADDING THE RESTAURANT.
I BET THEY DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
LIKE THIS IN THE CITY.
[ CHUCKLING ]
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
LET'S TAKE THIS RESTAURANT
FOR A SPIN, HUH?
SAY, WOULDN'T A DRINK OF WATER
GO GOOD ABOUT NOW?
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
I KNOW SOMETHING
ABOUT MIDDLE AGED MEN.
THEY ARGUE ABOUT
ABSOLUTELY EVERYTHING.
OH, YEAH. YEAH.
MIDDLE AGED GUYS CAN'T
LET ANYTHING DROP.
I'VE SEEN GUYS ARGUE
THAT BLACK WAS WHITE
UNTIL THEY WERE
BLUE IN THE FACE.
THIS IS NOT A GOOD
TRAIT TO HAVE
IF YOU'RE A MARRIED PERSON.
IF YOU'RE FOOL ENOUGH
TO ARGUE WITH YOUR WIFE,
YOU BETTER MAKE SURE THAT YOU
ARE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
YOU BETTER HAVE A SUPREME COURT
JUDGE, A NOBEL PRIZE WINNER
AND YOUR WIFE'S BEST FRIEND
ON YOUR SIDE FIRST,
BECAUSE ARGUING WITH YOUR WIFE
IS LIKE PLAYING POKER.
AND THE MORE YOU DIG
IN YOUR HEELS,
THE HIGHER THE ANTE.
AND THE HIGHER THE ANTE,
THE LOWER THE UNCLE.
THAT MEANS YOU'LL
BE SLEEPING ON THE COUCH.
HERE'S A BETTER WAY.
GO OVER TO YOUR WIFE,
LOOK HER IN THE EYE AND SAY,
"HONEY, I'M WRONG."
MAKE IT SOUND
LIKE YOU MEAN IT.
AND DON'T ADD "I GUESS"
OR "THIS TIME"
OR "FOR A CHANGE."
GO OVER TO HER.
DO IT NOW.
YOU AND I CAN ARGUE
ABOUT IT LATER.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
MY FLY-IN FISHING TRIP
HAS TURNED INTO THE
ONE THAT GOT AWAY.
EVEN IF WE CAN PROVE THAT IT
WAS OLD MAN SEDGWICK THAT
TOOK THE MONEY,
THERE'S NO WAY HE'S GONNA
COME UP WITH 500 BUCKS.
HE CAN BARELY COME UP
WITH A BREATH.
WELL, YOU WERE RIGHT, RED.
THIS IS OLD MAN
SEDGWICK'S I.O.U.
HIS DOG
RECOGNIZED THE SCENT.
SO DID WE GET
OUR 500 BUCKS BACK?
UH, NO.
NO, NOT EXACTLY.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK SAID
HE GAVE IT TO CHARITY.
YEAH, HE GOT A REQUEST FROM THE
HOME FOR UNWED MOTHERS,
SO HE MADE A DONATION.
ARE YOU SAYING THAT OLD
MAN SEDGWICK HAD A CHILD
OUT OF WEDLOCK?
NO! NO, NO.
NO, NO.
HE'S TRYING TO
IMPRESS HIS FATHER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
BUT HE DID IT IN THE
LODGE'S NAME BECAUSE
IT WAS OUR MONEY,
SO NOW THE LODGE HAS A FOSTER
CHILD OUT THERE SOMEWHERE.
OKAY, THAT'S GOOD.
IT'S ALWAYS GOOD TO
HELP OUT A YOUNGSTER,
EVEN IF IT MEANS I DON'T
GET TO GO ON MY FISHING --
BUT YOU KNOW, I'M GONNA
LIVE ANOTHER, WHAT,
FIVE YEARS?
SURE.
I'M SURE I'LL
GET ANOTHER CHANCE.
YEP.
YEAH, I KNEW YOU'D
FEEL THAT WAY,
SO INSTEAD OF GOING ON
THE FISHING TRIP,
I'M ARRANGING TO HAVE
OUR FOSTER CHILD
COME TO THE LODGE TO
SPEND THE WEEKEND WITH YOU,
YOU KNOW, SEEING THAT
YOU'RE THE LEADER AND ALL.
[ LAUGHTER ]
BOY, THIS NEWS JUST GETS
BETTER AND BETTER, DOESN'T IT?
YEAH, YOU WOULDN'T GO ON
THAT FISHING TRIP NOW
EVEN IF YOU COULD,
WOULD YOU, HUH?
YEAH, AS A MATTER
OF FACT, I WOULD.
COME ON.
GIVE UP A CHANCE TO MAKE
A GOOD IMPRESSION ON A KID?
IN A HEARTBEAT,
DALTON.
OH, NO, THAT'S NOT
THE RED GREEN I KNOW.
WELL, YOU'RE WRONG.
YOU CAN'T FOOL ME, RED.
APPARENTLY I CAN.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
HI, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
HERE OF ROTHSCHILD'S,
THE AFFORDABLE SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
WE'LL DRAIN YOUR TANK,
NOT YOUR BANK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THE YEAR IS 1913.
NOW, IF YOU JUST WOKE UP
ON THE COUCH AND HEARD
ME SAY THAT,
DON'T PANIC.
IT'S NOT REALLY 1913,
IT'S PROBABLY STILL THE
SAME YEAR IT WAS WHEN
YOU FELL ASLEEP.
AND NOW BACK TO THE SHOW.
THE YEAR IS 1913.
RICHARD NIXON IS BORN;
HANS GEIGER INTRODUCES THE
ALPHA RAY COUNTING DEVICE
THAT BEARS HIS NAME;
SCIENTIST H.N. RUSSELL
FORMULATES HIS THEORY
OF STELLAR EVOLUTION;
AND HERE IN POSSUM LAKE,
DIAMOND JIM BRADEN BECOMES
THE FIRST SUIT MANUFACTURER
TO PUT ZIPPERS
INTO MEN'S PANTS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THINGS WERE ROUGH AROUND HERE
WHEN DIAMOND JIM CAME TO TOWN.
OUR ONLY FACTORY HAD
JUST GONE BANKRUPT.
HUMPHREY'S BUGGY
WHIP COMPANY HAD AN
UNEXPECTED DOWNTURN IN SALES.
MY GREAT GRANDFATHER
LOST EVERYTHING WHEN
THE FACTORY WENT DOWN...
HIS JOB, HIS INCOME,
A PLACE TO SLEEP.
THEN THIS DIAMOND JIM
COMES ALONG, RIGHT.
HE SAYS HE'S GONNA
RE-OPEN THE FACTORY
AND HAUL EVERYBODY BACK TO MAKE
PANTS WITH ZIPPERS IN 'EM.
OH, THEY ALL THOUGHT
THAT WAS A GREAT IDEA.
THEN THEY GOT THIS NEW
SIGN FOR THE FACTORY...
"DIAMOND JIM'S...
"EVERYBODY WANTS
TO GET INTO MY PANTS."
I ACTUALLY HAVE THE FIRST
PAIR OF ZIPPERED FLY PANTS
THAT CAME OFF
THE ASSEMBLY LINE.
THEY PUT THE ZIPPER
IN HORIZONTALLY.
DARING AND INNOVATIVE, YES,
BUT EXTREMELY STUPID.
EVERY MAJOR CLOTHING
MANUFACTURER
WAS GOING INTO PRODUCTION
WITH ZIPPER FLY PANTS,
SO DIAMOND JIM NEEDED
TO THINK OF A SOLUTION
AND THINK OF IT FAST.
SO HE SCRAPPED
THE SIDE TO SIDE ZIPPER
AND WENT WITH THE
CONVENTIONAL UP AND DOWN.
BUT THEY SEWED THE
ZIPPERS IN UPSIDE DOWN.
SO INSTEAD OF ZIPPING UP,
THEY ZIPPED DOWN.
VERY, VERY DANGEROUS.
AND BELIEVE ME,
I KNOW DANGEROUS.
LIKE ALL SENSIBLE
FACTORY OWNERS.
ONCE DIAMOND JIM REALISED THE
COMPANY WOULD NEVER MAKE MONEY
HE SOLD IT TO THE WORKERS.
THE WHOLE ENTERPRISE WENT
UNDER INSIDE SIX WEEKS.
EVERYONE LOST THEIR
SHIRTS IN MEN'S PANTS.
SO WHAT WAS HE?
A MAN OF VISION,
A BIT OF A ROUNDER,
A MISUNDERSTOOD GENIUS,
OR JUST A GUY WHO
HAD TROUBLE WITH BUTTONS?
HERE'S TO YOU, DIAMOND JIM,
POSSUM LAKE'S HIGH FLYER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ HUFFING
AND PUFFING ]
OH, RED!
RED GREEN.
YEAH.
Quel surprise.
WELL, IT CAN'T BE
THAT BIG OF A surprise.
I JUST GOT OUTTA
THE VAN A MINUTE AGO.
YEAH, BUT, I MEAN,
WHO KNEW YOU'D MAKE IT UP
THE STAIRS IN THE SAME DAY?
[ LAUGHTER ]
YOU OKAY HERE, GORD?
OH, VERY BUSY.
HECTIC.
THINGS ARE NUTS AROUND HERE.
NUTS.
THAT WOULD'VE
BEEN MY GUESS.
JUST FINISHED MY NEWEST
EDUCATIONAL FEATURE.
COULD BE MY
BEST WORK YET.
OH, YEAH, YOU STILL DRAWING
ALL THE PICTURES YOURSELF,
MAKING ALL THE
VOICES YOURSELF?
NO, NO, I DECIDED I WAS
SPENDING TOO MUCH TIME ALONE,
SO I BROUGHT IN SOME OTHER
PEOPLE TO HELP ME
WITH THE WORK.
OH, REALLY?
NO, JUST KIDDING.
[ LAUGHTER ]
MILKWEED?
NO, THANK YOU.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ SAD MUSIC ]
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WELL, YOU KNOW, GORD,
FOR ONCE I THINK YOU AND I CAN
ACTUALLY AGREE ON SOMETHING.
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
WHAT?!
YOU THINK POLLUTION
IS BEAUTIFUL?
POLLUTION?
WHAT POLLUTION?
THAT'S THE
CLOUD MAKING FACTORY.
I SEE YOU TWO
NEED A CLOSER LOOK.
[ SCREAMING ]
HEY, WHERE DID
YOU TWO COME FROM?
(in French accent)
YOU NEED ZIE PERMIT
TO BE IN HERE, YOU KNOW.
IT'S OKAY, LADIES.
THEY'RE WITH ME.
RANGER GORD!
[ GIGGLING ]
I'M JUST GIVING
THESE TWO NUMSKULLS
A QUICK TOUR OF YOUR
WONDERFUL FACTORY.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
THE TOUR IS SO QUICK
THAT IT'S NOW OVER.
OH, RANGER GORD, WOULD YOU LET
US SEND YOU UP IN A CLOUD?
IT WOULD BE OUR PLEASURE.
(in French accent)
OH, PLEASE, PLEASE, RANGER GORD.
WE JUST FINISHED
A REAL NICE ONE.
WELL, THAT SOUNDS SWELL,
DOESN'T IT, BOYS?
O-O-OH!
A-A-AH!
YOU SURE OPENED MY MIND
TODAY, RANGER GORD.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO REALISE
THAT MANY THINGS AREN'T
WHAT THEY SEEM.
FOR EXAMPLE, WE'RE A WHOLE
LOT HIGHER OFF THE GROUND
THAN YOU MIGHT THINK.
IF WE FELL OFF THIS CLOUD,
WE WOULDN'T HIT THE GROUND
FOR A FULL TWO MINUTES.
UH, WE'RE NOT
THAT HIGH UP, GORD.
SOME PEOPLE ALWAYS HAVE
TO LEARN THE HARD WAY.
[ LAUGHING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU GET MARRIED
YOU GOTTA LEARN TO
START PAYING ATTENTION.
AT FIRST YOUR WIFE WILL
ACCEPT YOUR FAULTS,
MIGHT EVEN FIND
THEM KINDA CUTE.
BUT EVENTUALLY SHE'S GONNA START
DROPPING HINTS LIKE,
"YOU'RE DISGUSTING."
NEXT THING YOU KNOW,
SHE'S PACKING YOUR
BAGS FOR YOU,
AND YOU WEREN'T EVEN
PLANNING ON GOING ANYWHERE.
SO BEFORE IT GETS THAT FAR,
I SUGGEST YOU START TAKING
HER COMMENTS SERIOUSLY;
OTHERWISE, SHE'LL TAKE THE
MATTER INTO HER OWN HANDS.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU TOLD YOUR BUDDY
YOU'D BE HAPPY
TO HELP HIM MOVE ALL
HIS STUFF ON SATURDAY.
YEAH, BUT HE DIDN'T
TELL YOU THAT INCLUDED
HIS FULL COLLECTION
OF WURLITZER ORGANS.
HE'S GOT 17 OF THEM.
TOO LATE TO
BACK OUT NOW.
BUT IF YOU START
MANHANDLING THEM ORGANS,
YOU'RE LOOKING AT SIX
MONTHS IN INTENSIVE CARE.
HERE'S HOW TO HANDLE IT,
EASY AS PIE.
YOU TURN UP AT HIS PLACE
ALL EAGER AND ENTHUSIASTIC.
AND THEN WHEN HE SHOWS
YOU ALL HIS KEYBOARDS
AND LIES ABOUT
HOW LIGHT THEY ARE,
YOU ACT AS THOUGH YOU
WANNA GET RIGHT TO WORK.
BUT YOUR BUDDY DOESN'T
KNOW THAT YOU'VE HIDDEN
AN EMPTY PLASTIC WATER
BOTTLE UNDER YOUR SHIRT.
WHEN YOU BEND OVER TO
PICK UP THAT ORGAN...
[ SOUND OF PLASTIC BREAKING ]
IT'S GONNA POP LIKE FIVE DISKS
ALL HERNIATED SIMULTANEOUSLY.
YOU'RE OFF THE HOOK.
NOW ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS CRAWL OUT TO YOUR CAR.
OH, AND NOD GOOD-BYE,
AS IF MAYBE YOUR ARMS
AREN'T WORKING SO GOOD.
YOU MIGHT MENTION THAT
YOU PROBABLY WON'T SUE,
NO MATTER WHAT
YOUR LAWYER ADVISES.
BUDDY WON'T BE PULLING THAT
STUNT WITH YOU AGAIN.
DON'T THANK US.
THAT'S WHAT
FRIENDS ARE FOR.
WELL, THIS HAS BEEN
AN INTERESTING WEEK.
STARTED OFF NORMAL.
THEN I WON A LIFELONG
DREAM FLY-IN FISHING TRIP,
AND, OF COURSE,
THAT WAS CANCELED.
AND NOW I CAN'T GO
BACK TO NORMAL.
NO, NO, I'M SPENDING THE
WEEKEND BABYSITTING SOME
KID I NEVER EVEN MET.
RED! RED!
YEAH?
OUR FOSTER CHILD
IS HERE.
OKAY, GREAT.
SEND HIM IN.
COME ON IN, CHRIS!
[ LAUGHTER ]
YEAH, YEAH,
THIS IS CRYSTAL.
CRYSTAL, THIS IS
THE MAN I TOLD YOU ABOUT.
HELLO, Mr SEDGWICK.
NO, NO, I'M RED.
CALL ME RED.
YEP,
SHE CAN SEE THAT.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK MADE THAT
DONATION ABOUT 20 YEARS AGO.
I ALWAYS DREAMED I WOULD MEET
THE WONDERFUL STRANGERS
WHO HELPED ME
WHEN I NEEDED IT MOST.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THERE ARE VERY SPECIAL
PEOPLE IN THIS LODGE.
AND YOU'RE THE LEADER,
SO YOU MUST BE THE MOST SPECIAL.
WELL, I'M SURE THAT'S THE
WAY IT IS IN MANY LODGES,
BUT --
DALTON, DALTON!
SHE'S NOT FINISHED.
GO AHEAD, CRYSTAL.
NO, THAT WAS
PRETTY MUCH IT.
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
LOOKS LIKE YOU AND I
WILL BE SPENDING THE
WEEKEND TOGETHER.
SO WHAT DO YOU WANNA DO?
YOU WANNA BOAT RIDE?
OR MINI-GOLF?
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
RED, CRYSTAL WAS
TOO MODEST TO SAY,
BUT SHE BROUGHT US
A CHEQUE FOR $500.
IT WAS THE LEAST
I COULD DO.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU SAY
YOU AND I BLOW THAT
THIS WEEKEND?
I'M A SPECIAL
LODGE LEADER.
I CAN DO ANYTHING I WANT.
STOP KIDDING AROUND.
WE KNOW WHERE YOU WANNA GO.
YOU'RE GOING ON
A FISHING TRIP!
OH, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
I CAN'T GO ON THE FISH --
IT WOULDN'T BE FAIR TO CRYSTAL.
TOO LATE NOW.
TRIP'S BOOKED.
OH, YEAH?
WHO BOOKED IT?
YOUR WIFE, BERNICE.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
WELL, THEN I'M GOING.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, MEETING TIME.
C'MON, CRYSTAL.
I'LL SHOW YOU THE
REST OF THE GUYS.
GREAT.
STAY CLOSE NOW.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
AND I'M SURE YOU ARE,
I THINK YOU MADE THE RIGHT CALL
SENDING ME ON THE FISHING TRIP.
I'D RATHER CATCH A BIG ONE
THAN TELL A BIG ONE.
AND THEN BE A BIG ONE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
INCLUDING CRYSTAL,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
CRYSTAL, YOU CAN SIT THERE.
OH, ALL RISE.
Red: UH, CRYSTAL CAN YOU JUST
EXCUSE US FOR A MINUTE, PLEASE?
Crystal: SURE.
- Dalton: ALL RISE.
-- Red: THERE WE GO.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
(Red speaking alone)
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.