You know, leaving the guy in
charge of watching the baby
is always dangerous.
They cry; they whine;
they're always hungry;
and they're too helpless
to take care of themselves.
And it's the same
thing with the baby.
It's a focus thing.
There are very few things
that a guy will stare at.
And if he's married,
there are even fewer.
But one of 'em is whatever
you got under the hood.
For some reason a man
is drawn to an open hood
the same way a moth is
drawn to my sock drawer.
[ BABY GURGLING/CRYING ]
Those guys don't have
a clue how that
thing works,
but neither one of 'em
wants to be the first
to admit it
by looking away.
[ CRYING ]
Now that my baby-sitters
are in place,
I can go grab
a quick nine holes.
[ SIREN BLASTING ]
[ BABY CRYING ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
All right.
Thank you very much.
Appreciate it.
Got a bit of a problem
this week up at the lodge.
My wife Bernice is in a
line-dancing competition,
and her partner
is Buster Hadfield.
You know, Bernice tells me
that I'm not a very
good dancer.
I always thought that
I was light on my feet,
but she says I'm
pretty heavy on hers, so...
Hi, Uncle Red.
So what's the favour
that you need?
Hello, Harold.
How are you today?
What's the favour?
Can we not exchange
pleasantries,
a little greeting,
is that too much
to ask?
I'm fine.
What's the favour?
[ SIGH ]
Well, okay.
Do you know what
line dancing is?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's that show you
always make fun of on TV.
You know, you say it
looks like a bunch
of fat losers
stepping
on cockroaches.
No, you know,
that's just my
sense of humour.
Oh, ha!
See, coz I always thought
that humour had to be funny,
so...
Okay, Harold,
the point is...
your Aunt Bernice has
always been nice to you
when there's been
no reason to, okay.
Well, she has
a problem.
I'm looking at him.
Harold, she's made
it to the finals of the
line dancing competition
But now her partner's
come down with the flu.
Oh, and you want
me to fill in!
Yes!
Am I the first
person you asked?
Absolutely.
Boy, that's very nice.
Thank you.
But I can't.
Ah, c'mon, Harold,
everybody else
turned me down!
Hey!!
I dunno how
to line dance!
Any idiot
can line dance.
Is that you
volunteering?
Harold, c'mon, you
gotta do this for me.
I'll owe ya.
You'll owe me huge!
I'll owe
you huge, Harold.
Oh, I love this.
[ APPLAUSE ]
It's time for the
Possum Lodge word game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Today's prize
is a 5% discount
off the regular
$150 ticket price
to the Possum Lake
Historical Museum,
where our motto is:
Your value is history.
Okay, cover your
things, uh, Ed.
Okay, Mr Green,
you got 30 seconds
to get animal control
officer, Ed Frid,
to say this word...
Yeah,
all right, Mike.
And go!
Uh, okay, Ed,
how would you describe
what you see a lot in
your job as animal
control officer?
Ahhhhhhhhhh!
No, no, no, okay, um...
Okay, no, I'm talking
about like roadkill.
You see a dead raccoon on the
road, what's that called?
Justifiable homicide.
No, okay, okay.
Let's say my income was
$100,000 before expenses,
that would be
my "something" income.
Fabricated income.
Okay, no, okay,
When Hollywood
makes a movie,
what do they expect
to be really big?
The...
Oh, implants!
Okay, no, okay.
When you have 12 eggs,
you have a dozen.
But when you have
12 dozen eggs, you have a...
Frat party!
Uh, we're almost
outta time, Mr Green.
Yeah, okay, okay.
Um, I want you to imagine Old
Man Sedgwick skinny dipping.
What do you see?
Shaved albino weasel?
No, but remember
you ran over a weasel
last year with your lawn mower,
you remember that?
Uh, yeah, actually I
spent a year in therapy
trying to forget.
Thank you, Red.
Okay, okay, okay.
When you went to clean it up,
it was just too...
Much work.
I figured, you know,
I'd just wait until the
grass grows over it.
It's in there!
I heard it!
Do you know
what time it is?
Well, unless you're
on scheduled medication,
it really doesn't matter.
Welcome to
Harold's Hobby House!
Where my guest is bad-guy-
turned-good-guy, Mike Hamar.
Mike, tell us
about your hobby.
Okay, okay, well...
I used to have a really
great stamp collection
for a  while,
but I decided to give it
back to its legal owner
in return for
a reduced sentence.
So now I like to
collect things that
tell a story.
Old keys.
Oh, okay.
Keys from history.
I like to say,
Every key unlocks a story.
Every key
unlocks a heart.
Awwwww!
That's so poetic!
You've got a
very deep soul.
Did you create
that yourself?
I - I read it
on a place mat.
So are these historical
keys, like castles
and dungeons
and famous buildings
and...
uh, chastity belts?
Uh, yeah, things
like that, yeah.
Except for the
chastity belts,
I decided to donate
those to Chastity.
Ha, I think you mean
you donated them
to charity.
No, Charity
was her sister.
Actually, she was more
popular because she
gave tax receipts.
Okay...
Well, do you have
any medieval keys, or...
Well, as a
matter of fact,
uh, no.
Do you have any
famous building keys?
Oh, uh, okay, how about a
famous Ivy League university?
Yale.
That's the lock
company, Mike.
I thought you said
these keys tell stories.
Well, they do!
Um, um, okay, um.
Oh, yeah, this is the
key to the liquor store.
And this was the key
to the handcuffs.
Oh, this is the key
to the cop car.
Okay, okay, Mike!
These are just keys
you used to commit crimes.
Used to!
Past tense.
That's why I was always
tense in the past.
That key looks
pretty new to me.
And that one and
that one and this o --
That's the key
to my room!
Oh, I may have brought
the wrong bucket here.
No, don't --
That's the key
to my scooter,
and that's the key
to my briefcase.
Mike, I'm gonna
want these back.
So make me an offer.
Okay, I'm offering not
to phone the police.
That's the
key phrase.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
You ever notice that when you
have a car for a long time
it starts
to look like you?
I've had this convertible
for 30 years.
And by now the top is so
tattered you can see right
through most of it.
And you can't
put a hat on a car.
Oh, sure, I suppose you could
just buy a new convertible top,
if money is no object.
But what if money
is an object,
a huge object?
A huge, mysterious object
that isn't part of your
universe.
Is a guy on a fixed income
not supposed to have
nice things?
Not necessarily.
Every handyman loves that
new duct taped car smell.
But there's a couple of
drawbacks with this solution.
On a windy day, your hair's
going to stick to the
inside of the roof.
And when you go
to put the top down,
it sounds like you bending
over in a rental tux.
[ RIPPING SOUND ]
But rather than
get all depressed
and decide the
world is against you,
and start hitting the booze
and writing country songs,
why not use this
as a chance to upgrade?
Because you know, there's
something fancier and
more luxurious
than a convertible.
It's called
a hideaway hard-top,
a removable roof.
Step one:
go into your garage.
[ CLANGING AND BANGING ]
Or somebody's garage,
and get yourself a
garage door opener.
Okay, next step is
to remove the trunk lid.
It's as easy as pie.
Mind you, I don't bake.
Oh! Hot! Hot!
I decided to duct tape the
garage door opener
onto the hood
rather than weld it
on with the torch.
Just seemed
like a better idea.
And I took the rollers
off the garage door
and mounted them on the
sides of my trunk lid.
That way she'll
be able to roll easily
up and down the track.
Now I just hook the cable
onto the front edge here.
Oh, look at that, a rust hole
in exactly the right spot.
Some things are
just meant to be.
And to bring the roof back
when I want to go topless,
I've got a bungee cord running
off the back bumper.
[ Canada Geese Honking ]
Uh-oh!
More threatening than rain...
Canada Geese.
So remember, if the women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you in a snazzy car.
You know, as guys get older
they tend to get crankier
and they find that nobody
wants to spend time with them.
This is not
a coincidence.
People would rather bite
into an apple than
an onion, okay.
So don't turn into
a crabby, old dink.
And don't tell me all your
friends are dead.
They're probably just
using that as an excuse.
Now, people may believe
they have no control
over their moods,
but chances are you made
yourself miserable,
so you have to make
yourself happy.
Yeah, I know horrible
stuff happened to you.
A tornado flattened
your house,
somebody left
the fridge door open.
Horrible stuff happens
to everybody.
Look at Harold.
But maybe it's
not that horrible.
Sure you got
more aches and pains,
but those will prevent you
from doing things
that can
really hurt you.
Maybe you're an inch or two
shorter than you used to be.
But you've reduced your
chances of being struck
by lightning.
No matter how bad things get
just stop and think,
Hey, my pants
aren't on fire.
And smile a lot.
There's only two times
when you shouldn't smile...
when there's a bad smell
and any time your
wife's not smiling.
Often those occur
simultaneously.
So lighten up.
If you don't have a joke,
be a joke.
Look at Harold.
The point is you wanna
hear people laughing,
even if it's at
your expense.
You can afford it,
you crabby old dink.
Remember,
I'm pullin' for you.
We're all in
this together.
If your fuse panel
causes a brownout,
call an electrician.
If your septics
causes one,
call me.
Well, talk about
havin' a good day.
I got Harold to agree
to be Bernice's
substitute partner for
the line dancing contest.
So she's happy.
And then I sent him over
there to practice with her,
so I'm happy.
[ WOLF WHISTLES
AND CHEERS ]
What are you doi''
here, Harold?
Well, she cancelled
the practice.
What?
Yeah, she's coming down
with the flu.
Oh, she's going
to be okay.
She's just not going
to be able to compete
in the line dance
competition.
Oh... well, I guess that's
the end of that, eh?
Which is too bad,
coz $1,000 is a
lot of money.
Pardon me?
First prize is $1,000.
Well, w-w-wait
a minute.
We could still compete.
W-w-we?
Who we still?
You and I.
You and I
as a couple.
A couple!
Yeah.
Couple of what?
A couple of
winners, Harold.
C'mon we can --
we gotta do this, eh?
I'll owe you huge.
You'll owe me
gi-normous!
That's fine.
C'mon, you gotta
show me all the steps.
Well, aren't you afraid how
bad you'll look line dancing?
No, I'm afraid how
bad you'll look
in a skirt.
Oh --
RED: You know, I never
played socc -- oops.
Never played
soccer as a kid,
so Bill and I were supposedly
going to play some soccer.
Kind of ran over
the soccer ball there,
so it may --
He said,
Don't worry about it.
He's got another one
in his pants.
I thought he meant
soccer ball.
Wow.
Thank gosh for Medicare.
Okay, well, how're we
gonna blow that up, Bill?
Ah, no problem.
Okay. Wow.
No, thanks.
You handle the pump
until it dries.
I should'a told Bill I was
gonna pull the needle out
because it relieves the
pressure, and --
Nah, he's fine.
He's fine.
And you know, the thing
about soccer is
I think you need
to play it as a young man.
I think it may possibly be
a young man's --
it might be a
young man's game.
I think takin' the game up
at 50 is probably kinda dumb.
And you know, it's not
as easy as it looks.
So I had an idea.
I just tried to
help Bill up,
or he tried to
help me down --
I'm not sure how that --
I'll just tow you.
So the idea was that I would
duct tape the hockey stick
to the handle of the pump
and we'd get a little
more leverage,
'cause what I wanted to do
was really over-inflate
this ball.
I wanted the balls to be a
little bit larger.
Uh, you know, I may possibly
have overdone it a bit
on the size of the ball.
Now we're both afraid
it's gonna blow,
and it was the
pump that went.
We got a great idea;
we got the ball out there.
And the reason that
we need such a big ball
is that we're not
gonna kick this ball.
It's not soccer,
it's soc-car
Now you're talkin'.
All right,
so this is my goal.
I get down to this end,
and here we go!
Down the other end.
And Bill reaches
for the trunk button.
And bang!
Up and over.
I go down, and I come out
the back end of the van,
And then he's got
the door goin' good.
And he hit the post!
And then he hits her
again -- shoots her again.
We have very poor
defence on our team.
And he still keeps
hitting that post.
So I come up, and I've got
the hockey stick on the door,
and I give her
a good banger,
and up she goes.
And now he grabs the hood
release and flips
her backwards.
A great shot!
Wow!
And now he spins around.
I'm comin' right at
the darn thing.
Headed straight at him.
Thing goes right under
the hood.
Now, Bill, you can't
drive it in!
You gotta punch it in.
Red card! Red card! Red card!
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I don't mind the game,
but the celebration kills you.
No, this isn't some kind of
weird same-sex wedding gift.
It's the hose off
a vacuum cleaner.
I've extended it a bit
coz I'm gonna use it to
depopulate this beehive.
When it comes to
the birds and the bees,
I'll take the
birds any day.
[ CROW CAWING ]
This vacuum hose will
be like a tiny casino.
The bees won't be able to pass
by without being sucked in.
Now we just add
a little patience.
You know that guy who sang
that waiting is the
hardest part?
He sure wasn't
a lodge member.
[ VACUUM CONTINUES
SUCKING ]
Ah, there we go.
That was the queen.
Well, mission accomplished.
Or as Shakespeare
would say,
Hey, you sons of Bs,
where's they sting?
You're probably wondering,
what do I do now?
Now that I've got hundreds
of bees inside my
vacuum cleaner.
Well, up at the lodge,
we're environmentally friendly.
We have a catch
and release programme.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Yep, you are looki''
at the new Possum
Lake area
line dancing champions.
Thank goodness there
was no urine test.
That was fun.
I enjoyed being
a girl.
Uh-huh.
Well, it's not a
huge stretch for you.
Speaking of huge.
You owe me huge.
Yes, I do, Harold, and
I'm gonna pay you huge.
You know that
$1,000 prize?
Yeah.
I'm gonna give
it to you.
All of it?
All of it.
The whole shebang.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh, Uncle Red.
Ohhhhhhhh!
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Oh, that is
so generous.
Yeah, well,
you earned it, Harold.
I mean,
you were great.
Great eye contact
with the judges.
Your leg kicks
were incredible.
I mean, you really
sold it.
I did, didn't I?
You liked
the leg kicks?
Yeah.
But you know,
if you ever do
that again,
you might wanna make
another choice
in underwear.
But still, giving me
entire $1,000, Uncle Red.
You know what?
I'm gonna buy you something
with part of this money.
Okay. Okay.
Well, as it turns out,
it's not
$1,000 cash, okay.
It's $1,000 worth of
line dancing lessons.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Meeting time.
Yeah, you go ahead,
Tami-Sue, I'll be
right down.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Okay, if my
wife is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting.
And don't worry,
I'm gonna take care of you.
I'm a good enough line dancer
to know where the line is,
even though I may dance
around it a little.
And to the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself
and Haroldine
and the whole gang
up here at Possum Lodge,
keep your stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Sit down!
All rise!
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
RED: Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the man's prayer.
I'm a man,
but I can change
if I have to...
I guess.
All right, men, apparently
Harold has a brief
announcement.
I have been receiving a lot of
unsolicited attention lately.
Yes, the flowers
have been nice,
but I do want to remind you
that I am engaged
and I am a lady.