[quirky upbeat music]
[gunshots, explosion]
>> IT'S TIME AGAIN TO TURN OFF
YOUR ALARM CLOCK, TURN ON YOUR
VCR, PULL UP A CHAIR, PULL DOWN
THE TABLE, AND GET READY FOR,
WELL, WHATEVER IT IS.
LIKE IT'S FUN, I GUESS.
IT'S NOT REALLY EXCITEMENT.
SO YEAH, GET READY FOR SOME FUN.
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW,
STARRING THE STAR, THE HOST,
AND MY UNCLE, OF COURSE.
WELL, BECAUSE HE'S MARRIED
TO MY AUNT,
AND HE'S MY FATHER'S BROTHER.
SO HERE HE IS NOW, MY UNCLE
AND YOUR HOST, MR. RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
WE DECIDED TO HAVE KIND OF A
SAFETY WEEK UP AT THE LODGE THIS
WEEK BECAUSE WE'RE LOSIN' SO
MANY FISHING DAYS TO INJURIES.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU STUB
YOUR TOE ON A CAST IRON STOVE
AND THEN YOU'RE JUMPIN' UP AND
DOWN, AND YOU END UP FALLIN' ON
IT AND GRILLIN' YOUR OWN REAR
END ON A WAFFLE PAN THEN PUTTIN'
YOUR HEAD THROUGH THE STOVEPIPE,
YOU KNOW, THAT MIGHT BE FUNNY IN
HINDSIGHT, BUT BOY, AT THE TIME,
IT'S DARNED INCONVENIENT.
SO WE THOUGHT WE'D HAVE
OURSELVES A LITTLE SAFETY WEEK
AND MAKE THE LODGE JUST A SAFER
PLACE TO WORK AND PLAY
AND STUB YOUR TOE.
>> UNCLE RED?
>> WHAT?
ARE YOU SAYING TO ME I CAN'T
EVEN START AN INTERESTING STORY
WITHOUT YOU INTERRUPTING?
>> WELL, NO.
BY ALL MEANS, IF YOU GOT A
INTERESTING STORY,
THEN GO RIGHT AHEAD.
PLEASE ARTICULATE IT FOR US.
OH, YEAH.
OKAY, HERE'S RED GREEN WITH AN
INTERESTING STORY.
>> SO ANYWAY, WE THOUGHT WE'D
START OFF SAFETY WEEK BY
PAINTIN' UP SOME SAFETY SLOGANS.
SO WE GAVE THE JOB TO STINKY
PETERSON, BUT UNFORTUNATELY, HE
FELL OFF THE LADDER, LANDED ON
THE PAINT ROLLER.
>> UNCLE RED, THIS WHOLE SAFETY
WEEK THING IS--WELL, IN THE
BUSINESS, WE LIKE TO CALL IT
A DRAG.
DREARY.
DEPRESSING.
IT'S NOT FOR THIS KINDA SHOW.
>> WHY NOT?
IT HAPPENED.
>> YEAH, WELL, SO DID WORLD WAR
II, BUT WE DON'T TALK ABOUT IT.
THE RED GREEN SHOW SHOULD BE
BOUNCY AND ALIVE WITH LOTS OF
VISUAL EFFECTS LIKE THIS.
[laughs]
HEY, IF WE'RE GONNA WIN A GEMINI
AWARD FOR BEST SHOW DIRECTED BY
A NEPHEW, YOU SHOULD THINK ABOUT
THINGS LIKE THIS.
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST INTRODUCE
THE NEXT SEGMENT,
AND I'LL TAKE US INTO IT, HUH?
>> THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'LL KEEP THE STORY MOVIN',
HAROLD.
I'LL JUST--ALL LEAVE OUT THE
PART ABOUT MOOSE THOMPSON AND
THE BOATHOOK.
>> WELL, IT'S NOT THE BEST SEGUE
I EVER HEARD, BUT I GUESS I CAN
LIVE WITH THAT.
>> HAROLD, ARE YOU WEARING
STEEL-TOED SHOES?
>> NO.
>> GOOD.
[folksy guitar and spoons music plays]
WHEN I WAS JUST A LITTLE LAD
MY FATHER GAVE TO ME
A STRANGE AND ALMOST
BAFFLING LITTLE TOY
THAT FILLED MY HEART
AND PARTS OF MY LUNG
WITH GLEE
I SHOOK IT A COUPLE TIMES
FLIPPED IT OVER
ONCE OR TWICE
AND THEN
SORT OF RATTLED IT OFF
THE OLD MAN'S SHIN
CAN YOU IMAGINE MY SURPRISE
WHEN IT TURNED OUT TO BE
A BOTTLE OF GIN?
THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW TO PREVENT THIS
THAT I HAVE IN MY HAND HERE.
NOW, THIS IS NOT
A CHARCOAL BRIQUETTE.
THIS IS A PIECE OF BREAD, THE
KIND OF BREAD THAT HELPS BUILD
STRONG CRAMPS 12 WAYS.
THE REASON IT LOOKS LIKE THIS IS
BECAUSE THIS PARTICULAR PIECE OF
BREAD JUST SPENT A LITTLE TOO
MUCH TIME IN THIS UNIT
RIGHT HERE.
THIS IS THE KIND OF THING THAT
HAPPENS WHEN PEOPLE ARE TOO
CHEAP TO BUY YOU
A DECENT WEDDING GIFT.
BUT TODAY I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW TO FIX A TOASTER.
NOW, THE FIRST THING YOU DO IS
TAKE SOMETHING LIKE A FORK OR A
KITCHEN KNIFE,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
STICK IT DOWN IN THERE AND SEE
OF SOMETHING'S KIND OF GOT IT
JAMMED IN THERE.
[electricity zapping]
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
THAT TELLS US THE POWER'S ON,
BUT I THINK WE SHOULD
UNPLUG THIS.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, WE GOT HER UNPLUGGED
THERE, AND I'LL TELL YOU,
THERE'S ONLY ONE OF TWO THINGS
THAT CAN BE WRONG
WITH A TOASTER.
NUMBER ONE, YOU GOT YOUR
POP-TART DRIPPIN'S IN THERE, AND
THEY'VE SEIZED UP THE EJECTION
MECHANISM, BUNGED HER ALL UP.
SO WHAT I USE FOR THAT IS THE
WD-40 OR WHAT WE CALL THE
HANDYMAN'S LIQUID WRENCH.
I MEAN, THIS STUFF COULD LOOSEN
THE INTESTINES OF A WARTHOG
AFTER A CHEESE DINNER.
FIRE THAT DOWN IN THERE, AND
NOW, THE OTHER THING THAT COULD
POSSIBLY BE WRONG WITH IT IS
THAT THE HEAT SENSOR IN
THE--INSIDE THE UNIT IS STUCK IN
THE "ON" POSITION AND JUST NEEDS
SOME OF A JARRING MOTION TO KIND
OF LOOSEN THAT UP.
SO HOPEFULLY BETWEEN THE TWO,
WE'VE GOT THIS THING PRETTY WELL
SQUARED UP.
WHY DON'T I JUST PLUG HER BACK
IN, AND WE'LL JUST GIVE HER
A TRY.
I THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE
SURPRISED.
[electricity zapping]
QI'M GONNA NEED
A COUPLE MORE OF THOSE UNITS.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S JUST SEE
WHAT HAPPENS HERE.
[clears throat]
WELL, SHE'S NOT BURNIN',
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
SHE'S NOT EVEN HEATIN' UP.
SO WE--WE'VE DONE IT.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
REMEMBER UNTIL NEXT TIME, IF THE
WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
WE'RE GONNA TAKE A SHORT BREAK,
AND THEN WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK
WITH A LOT MORE INFO
ON THE SAFETY WEEK THING.
>> WELL, IT'S NOT ABOUT THE FIRE
EXTINGUISHER IN THE OUTHOUSE,
IS IT?
>> OH, NO.
WE'LL LET OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
TELL THAT WHEN HE GETS OUT OF
INTENSIVE CARE.
>> "IT IS SUMMER.
THE SUN BLAZES FOR HOURS.
YOU LEAN AGAINST A BLACK CAR,
AND THEN GINGERLY ENTER
THE VARIETY STORE
WHERE YOU EMPTY A BAG OF ICE
INTO THE SEAT OF YOUR PANTS.
IT'S NOT ONLY REFRESHING.
IT'S GOOD SENSE."
SO ANYWAY, WE'RE REALLY GETTING
INTO THIS SAFETY WEEK THING HERE
AT THE LODGE, SO WE THOUGHT WE'D
CLEAR OUT ALL THE LITTER AND
JUNK LYIN' AROUND, NOT COUNTIN'
THE FURNITURE, YOU KNOW.
SO WE STARTED PICKIN' UP ALL THE
CRAP, THE TREE STUMPS AND
THE--AND THE RUBBER TIRES AND
THE HUNKS OF BOATS, YOU KNOW,
AND THE PIECES OF PLYWOOD AND
THE--AND THE TRACTOR RADIATORS,
AND A LOT OF THE DRIVE SHAFTS
AND THE MUFFLING EQUIPMENT
AND SO ON.
AT LEAST WE GOT THE FRONT
HALLWAY CLEARED UP.
AND THEN MOOSE THOMPSON STARTED
COUNTIN' UP THE LIFE JACKETS,
AND WE ENDED WITH, I THINK,
SEVEN COMPLETE LIFE JACKETS, AND
I GUESS ABOUT NINE OF WHAT YOU'D
CALL PIECES OF LIFE JACKETS THAT
WE JUST DUCT-TAPED THEM TOGETHER
AND MADE A FLOTATION RING
FOR THE BEER COOLER.
>> WELL, THAT WAS GREAT,
UNCLE RED.
THAT WAS JUST GREAT.
KEPT THE PACE UP AND EVERYTHING.
THAT WAS WAY--
WANTASTIC, WAY TO GO.
WHY DON'T WE JUST MOVE RIGHT
ALONG INTO THE NEXT PART
OF THE SHOW?
[chuckles]
>> WHY DO YOU KEEP INTERRUPTING
ME, HAROLD?
>> BECAUSE THE VIEWERS WANT
SOMETHING UPBEAT.
>> HOW ABOUT SOMETHING BEAT-UP?
>> WHOA, RED GREEN.
>> YEAH.
>> I THOUGHT I HEARD A VOICE.
WELL, I HEAR LOTS OF VOICES,
BUT THIS TIME IT'S REALLY YOU.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> A REAL, LIVE PERSON.
>> YEAH.
>> GREAT.
CAN I TOUCH YOU?
YEAH!
GREAT, YOU'RE REAL!
A REAL, LIVE PERSON.
>> SO, SO, SO, RANGER GORD.
>> YEAH.
>> GUARDIAN OF THE FOREST.
HOW'S IT GOIN', HUH?
>> HOW'S IT GOIN', HUH?
HOW'S IT GOIN'?
[crying]
>> OH.
>> GREAT.
>> OKAY.
>> NO PROBLEM.
NO PROBLEM.
>> GOOD, GOOD, THAT'S GREAT.
[clears throat]
>> [crying]
>> I COULD COME BACK ANOTHER
TIME, IF THIS IS NOT A GOOD TIME
FOR YOU.
>> NO.
>> OKAY.
TODAY IS THE FIRST DAY
OF MY 13TH YEAR UP HERE.
>> OH.
>> LUCKY 13, HUH?
>> YEAH, WELL,
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY.
>> THANKS.
>> YEAH.
>> I MADE A CAKE
OUT OF BARK AND MOSS.
YOU WANT A SLICE?
>> WELL, MAYBE LATER, YOU KNOW.
HOW DO YOU--HOW DO YOU KEEP
TRACK OF THE DAYS UP HERE, GORD?
>> WELL, EVERY DAY, I'LL GET UP,
AND I'LL EAT A BOWL OF CANNED
CORN, AND THEN I'LL GO OVER AND
I'LL CARVE A NOTCH INTO MY TREE.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, IT USED TO BE A TREE,
BUT I CARVED SO MANY NOTCHES
INTO IT, IT FELL OVER.
SO I GO OVER, AND I CARVE
A NOTCH INTO MY LOG.
AND THEN, UH...
[sighs]
I DON'T KNOW.
[sniffles]
I'LL LISTEN TO MUSIC.
I LIKE MUSIC.
I'VE GOT ALL THE LATEST HITS.
I GOT SEALS AND CROFTS...
>> YEAH, A LOT OF TAPES HERE.
>> LIGHTHOUSE,
CAPTAIN & TENNILLE.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> NEIL'S THERE, I SEE.
>> NEIL'S THERE, YEAH.
>> YEAH.
>> I LIKE HIM.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
>> AND...
>> GOOD--
>> OH, YEAH!
I GOT ONE OF THESE THINGS.
THESE--THESE RUBIK'S BOXES
THINGS.
>> YEAH, RUBIK'S CUBE.
YEAH.
>> YEAH, I'VE BEEN--I'VE BEEN
WORKING ON THIS A LOT.
I'M PRETTY GOOD AT IT.
UH, YOU KNOW, I CAN SOLVE ONE OF
THESE IN JUST OVER A MONTH.
[laughs]
YOU BEAT THAT?
I BET YOU I'M THE FASTEST
ON THE FACE OF THIS EARTH.
>> WELL, ACTUALLY, GORD, THERE
ARE SOME KIDS WHO CAN--WHO CAN
DO THESE IN ABOUT TEN SECONDS.
>> OH, UNCLE RED, GREAT.
I HOPE YOU'RE IN A GOOD MOOD
THIS WEEK 'CAUSE THE LETTERS ARE
OF--CERTAINLY OF A CONTROVERSIAL
NATURE, AND I CERTAINLY DON'T
WANT YOU TO HAVE, LIKE,
A HEART ATTACK OR A STROKE
OR A BOWEL DISORDER.
>> WELL, THAT'S NOT REALLY
YOUR WORRY, HAROLD.
THAT JUST CONCERNS ME AND
THE--AND THE PEOPLE BEHIND ME.
>> OKAY, FINE.
LOOK, NO PROBLEM.
YOU'RE THE BOSS.
I'LL JUST--I'LL JUST MOVE
RIGHT ALONG.
OKAY, LETTER NUMBER ONE.
"DEAR RED THE POSSUM GREEN,"
THAT'S YOURSELF, OF COURSE.
"I'VE BEEN WATCHING YOUR SHOW
FOR TEN WEEKS NOW
AND FIND IT CHAUVINISTIC.
NOT ONE OF YOUR GUESTS
HAS BEEN A WOMAN.
WHY ARE THERE NO WOMEN
ON YOUR SHOW?"
>> [sighs]
HAROLD, WE'VE BEEN THROUGH THIS
A FEW TIMES, HAVEN'T WE?
I MEAN, WE'VE INVITED,
WHAT WOULD YOU SAY?
DOZENS OF WOMEN ON THE SHOW, AND
ALL WE'VE GOTTEN SO FAR IS A
"NO, THANK YOU."
AND WELL, I KNOW A LOT OF WOMEN
ARE NOT ALL THAT INTERESTED
IN OUTDOOR SPORTSMEN-LIKE
ACTIVITIES, BUT WE ARE
MORE THAN WILLING TO HAVE
THEM CLEANING FISH OR DOING
LAUNDRY IN THE RIVER,
AND ALL WE GET IS NEGATIVE,
NEGATIVE, NEGATIVE.
SO DON'T BLAME ME.
THAT'S NOT MY FAULT.
I'M NOT CHAUVINISTIC.
WE'VE DONE EVERYTHING IN OUR
POWER TO EXPAND THE SHOW TO
INCLUDE WOMEN.
WE DID THAT FEATURE
ON SHOPPING FOR SHOES,
BUT NOTHING'S WORKING.
I MEAN, THE WOMEN
JUST ARE NOT TUNING IN.
>> WELL, PERHAPS MAYBE IF WE DID
SOMETHING THAT WAS MORE IN SYNC
WITH WOMEN, LIKE SOMETHING WITH
WOMEN'S ISSUES INVOLVED.
PERHAPS THEN--
THEN THEY MIGHT TUNE IN.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT I THINK.
>> WELL, WHAT KIND OF ISSUES,
HAROLD?
>> WELL, OKAY.
FOR EXAMPLE, AN ISSUE MIGHT BE
EQUAL PAY FOR EQUAL WORK.
THERE'S AN ISSUE, JUST SAY.
>> WELL, YEAH.
BUT YOU CAN SAY THAT, BUT WHEN A
WOMAN TAKES A MAN'S JOB, SHE
DOES A BETTER JOB BECAUSE SHE'S,
YOU KNOW, TRYIN' TO PROVE A
POINT OR SOMETHING.
SO THAT'S NOT EQUAL WORK AT ALL.
>> OH, OKAY.
THAT'S--THAT'S VERY TRUE TOO.
OKAY.
PERHAPS THIS NEXT LETTER CAN
SHED SOME LIGHT ON--ON THIS
SITUATION, BECAUSE IT TOO
IS OF THE SAME NATURE
DUE TO THE PREPARATION WORK DONE
BY YOURS TRULY.
[laughs]
"DEAR RED GREEN,
WHAT THE HELL
DO WOMEN WANT ANYWAY?"
SIGNED, "CONFUSED."
I THINK IT'S A MAN.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, HERE AGAIN,
YOU KNOW, YOU HATE TO
GENERALIZE.
IN FACT, I NEVER GENERALIZE.
BUT I THINK THE PROBLEM STEMS
FROM WOMEN BEING NARROW-MINDED.
>> I DON'T THINK WOMEN ARE
NARROW-MINDED.
I THINK YOU'RE NARROW-MINDED.
AT LEAST THAT'S WHAT I'VE
ABSORBED FROM YOUR DISSERTATION
THUSLY FAR.
>> HAROLD, I DON'T THINK YOU
COULD CALL ME NARROW-MINDED.
I MEAN, I PRIDE MYSELF ON BEING
THE EXACT OPPOSITE OF
NARROW-MINDED.
>> FATHEADED?
I COULD BUY THAT.
I COULD LIVE WITH THAT.
>> IN KEEPING WITH SAFETY WEEK
THIS WEEK, BILL WANTED TO TALK
ABOUT FIRE SAFETY.
SO HE BUILT A LITTLE FIRE THERE.
ACTUALLY JUST, YOU KNOW, PRETEND
THAT'S A CAMPFIRE.
AND HE--HE WANTED TO DO THIS
KIND OF LIKE ONE OF THOSE FILMS
THEY SHOW IN THE SCHOOLS YOU
KNOW, TO SHOW THE KIDS WHAT NOT
TO DO AND SO ON WITHOUT BEING
REAL DANGEROUS.
SO HE--HE WANTED TO PRETEND I
WAS ASLEEP.
AND HE MADE THAT HIMSELF.
NICE JOB, BILL.
NICE. NICE.
HE THINKS THOSE ARE "S"s.
AND THEN HE BROUGHT A LITTLE
FAKE FIRE THAT HE--
GAH, SO THAT HURT.
OH.
WELL, HE WASN'T TALKIN' ABOUT
INJURY SAFETY.
HE WAS TALKIN' ABOUT
FIRE SAFETY.
AND HE WAS TRYIN' TO GET THAT
THING IN THERE, AND FINALLY JUST
ASKED ME TOLD IT BETWEEN MY
LEGS, WHICH I WASN'T REAL
EXCITED ABOUT.
AND THEN WHAT--OH, YEAH.
YEAH.
THIS IS THE FIRST THING YOU CAN
DO TO PUT OUT A FIRE.
>> YIKES!
>> OH, NO.
BILL. BILL.
>> [grunts]
>> LOT OF PRESSURE.
WE GET A LOT OF PRESSURE HERE
UP AT THE LODGE.
SO IF YOU DON'T HAVE A HOSE,
WHAT DID HE GO?
NOW WHAT WAS IT?
WHAT WAS IT?
OH, YEAH.
I REMEMBER NOW.
YEAH.
THAT WAS A BUCKET OF WATER, I
HOPE, AND THIS IS SOME OF OUR
BEACH SAND FROM POSSUM LAKE.
OH, OH, OH, BILL.
BILL.
HOLD IT, BILL.
HOLD IT.
BOY, THAT STUFF ON THE CONTACT
LENSES, LET ME TELL YOU.
SO NEXT--OH, OH, YEAH.
FIRE EX--OH, YEAH.
THESE THINGS--I THINK THIS ONE
HAD A EXTRA HEAVY CHARGE IN IT.
KIND OF GOT AWAY ON HIM
A BIT THERE.
HANG ON, BILL.
HANG ON. HANG ON.
>> WHOA!
>> I GOT IT. LOOK OUT.
SO WE WOULDN'T RECOMMEND THAT
ONE, ESPECIALLY WHEN IT'S IN
BILL'S HAND.
NOW HERE'S ANOTHER.
YOU'RE GONNA PUT THE
FIRE--YOU'RE GONNA JUMP ON IT
WITH A BLANKET.
THIS IS TO SMOTHER--SMOTHER THE
FIRE AND JUST PACK IT RIGHT DOWN
AND MAKE SURE NO OXYGEN.
UNFORTUNATELY, THE EDGE OF THE
BLANKET WAS GETTIN' INTO THE
REAL FIRE.
SO BILL WENT TO GET ANOTHER
BLANKET TO SMOTHER THAT BLANKET,
AND I THINK THIS ONE HAD BEEN
SOAKIN' IN SOMETHIN' OR OTHER.
>> WHOOPS!
>> YEAH.
YEAH, THAT WENT UP REAL GOOD.
YEAH.
AND THEN THE NEXT THING YOU
KNOW, BILL HAD A BIT OF A
SURPRISE.
>> [laughs]
>> YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH.
AND I GOT THE OTHER FIRE
EXTINGUISHER, BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT'S FUNNY?
YOU NEVER--YOU NEVER THINK ABOUT
READIN' THE INSTRUCTIONS ON
THESE THINGS UNTIL YOU
REALLY ARE PRESSED FOR TIME,
YOU KNOW?
PLUS, I HAD THE FRENCH SIDE,
I THINK.
BUT ANYWAY, WE GOT HER.
>> [yells]
[coughing]
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, I WANTED TO
DO ANYTHING TO, YOU KNOW, PUT
MYSELF OUT FOR A FRIEND, OR PUT
A FRIEND OUT FOR HIMSELF OR
WHATEVER IT WAS.
I DID NOT READ FAR ENOUGH TO SEE
HOW YOU--HOW YOU TURN THE
EXTINGUISHER OFF, SO--
[clears throat]
REALLY HAD TO USE THE WHOLE--THE
WHOLE CANISTER ON--ON BILL.
THAT WOULDN'T DO ANY DAMAGE
ANYWAY.
>> [shouts]
>> OH, OKAY.
WE'RE JUST KIBITZIN' NOW.
YOU CAN SEE THAT.
BUT I WAS REALLY JUST TRYING TO
KEEP BILL'S MIND OFF THE INJURY.
>> [moans]
>> DIDN'T WORK.
"IT IS SPRING.
ME AND THE BOYS SPEND THE ENTIRE
WEEKEND BENDING THE ELBOW,
TRYING TO PULL-START
THE DAMN LAWNMOWER."
>> ANYWAY, GLAD YOU'RE HERE, YOU
KNOW, 'CAUSE IT GETS PRETTY
LONELY, ESPECIALLY AT NIGHT.
>> OH, WELL, I MEAN--
>> CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
>> YOU CAN'T SEE ANYTHING?
>> NOPE.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE MOON,
THE STARS, AND EVERYTHING?
>> I HATE THEM.
[cries]
I HATE THEM.
YOU KNOW, THEY JUST SIT
THERE.
THEY DON'T--THEY DON'T TALK.
THEY'RE NOT LIKE HAVIN' A FRIEND
OR ANYTHING.
THEY DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
>> NO, I--I GUESS THE MOON CAN'T
TALK TO YOU LIKE A FRIEND,
COULD, EH, GORD?
>> NO.
>> THEY ONLY SPEAK GERMAN.
>> OH.
>> I TRIED TO LEARN GERMAN ONCE.
[sniffles]
I SENT AWAY FOR THESE
"LEARN GERMAN" TAPES,
AND THEY SENT THESE BACK.
WHAT THE HECK ARE THESE?
THEY DON'T FIT IN MY 8-TRACK.
>> NO.
NO, I GUESS THEY WOULDN'T.
WELL, GORD, I'M SORRY.
I'VE GOT TO GO.
BUT REALLY GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> OH, NO.
>> YOU TAKE CARE OF
YOURSELF, EH?
>> [crying] NO.
>> YEAH, I'VE GOT TO--
>> PLEASE, DON'T GO.
PLEASE. [crying]
>> WELL, I HAVE--
>> YOU'VE GOT TO SEE THE SUNSET.
THE SUNSET'S GREAT, OKAY?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> THEY SUN'LL GO DOWN, AND THEN
IF YOU YELL AND SCREAM AND BANG,
EVENTUALLY, 1,000 HOURS LATER,
IT'LL COME UP AGAIN.
YOU GOT TO SEE THAT.
[laughs]
>> WELL, I TELL YOU WHAT.
NEXT TIME,
WE'LL DO THAT FOR SURE.
>> OKAY.
>> NO PROBLEM. YEAH.
YEAH, THAT'LL BE GREAT.
>> I'M HERE SATURDAY.
WHY DON'T YOU COME BY SATURDAY,
OKAY?
WE'LL HAVE A--WE'LL HAVE A
BARBECUE AND BARBECUE UP SOME
CANNED CORN AND BEANS,
AND THEN...
>> ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
>> GO--WE'LL GO LOOK FOR MY
RUBIK'S BOX OR SOMETHING.
>> WELL, ALL RIGHT, WE'LL SEE.
WE'LL SEE.
>> GREAT, I LOOK FORWARD TO IT.
>> ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
BYE-BYE, GORD.
>> SEE YOU SATURDAY.
>> YEAH, WELL, WE'LL SEE.
>> 2:15 SOUND OKAY?
>> WELL, WE'LL--WE'LL GET BACK
TO YOU ON THAT, OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH. LOOK FORWARD TO IT.
SEE YOU.
OH, IF YOU NEED SOME TWIGS,
HELP YOURSELF, OKAY?
I GOT PLENTY OF TWIGS.
>> YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
>> TAKE AS MUCH AS YOU WANT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> HAROLD, HAS YOUR DAD HAD A
CHANCE TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT, YOU
KNOW, HOW YOUR BODY'S CHANGING?
>> OH, YEAH.
YEAH.
HE SAYS I'M A WHOLE HEAD TALLER
THAN HE WAS AT MY AGE.
>> NO, NO.
I'M--I'M TALKING ABOUT PUBERTY,
HAROLD.
>> OH. [laughs]
YEAH.
YEAH, WE LEARNED ALL ABOUT THAT
IN SCHOOL.
HOW DO YOU MEAN?
>> WELL, I, YOU KNOW, NOW THAT
YOU'RE GOIN' THROUGH PUBERTY,
YOUR--YOUR BODY--WELL, IT
CAN--IT CAN BE A LOT MORE FUN.
YOU KNOW, BUT--BUT--BUT THERE'S
A RESPONSIBILITY THAT--THAT
GOES--THAT GOES WITH THAT, YEAH.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU--YOU KNOW WHAT I'M
TALKIN' ABOUT, HAROLD?
>> NO.
>> WELL, I'M--I'M--I'M TALKIN'
ABOUT SOMETHING YOU CAN BUY
IN A DRUGSTORE.
>> OH.
CONTRACEPTIVES.
[laughs]
YEAH, WE HAVE ONE OF THOSE
MACHINES IN THE BOYS' WASHROOM
AT SCHOOL, BUT IT'S
ALWAY--ALWAYS BROKE.
IT'S FUN TO THINK ABOUT, THOUGH.
[laughs]
>> I'M TALKIN' ABOUT DEODORANT,
HAROLD.
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT PUTTIN' STUFF
UNDER YOUR ARMS SO PEOPLE'S EYES
DON'T WATER WHEN YOU WALK INTO
THE ROOM.
>> I THOUGHT YOU MEANT--
>> OR INTO THE FOREST.
>> I--YOU KNOW WHAT I THOUGHT
YOU MEANT, THOUGH.
>> YEAH, YEAH,
I KNOW WHAT YOU THOUGHT.
>> CONTRACEPTIVES, I THOUGHT
THAT'S WHAT YOU MEANT.
>> HAROLD, IF YOU SAY THAT WORD
ONE MORE TIME, WE'RE NOT HAVIN'
ANYMORE OF THESE OPEN,
HONEST DISCUSSIONS.
>> SORRY.
>> WE'RE GONNA TAKE A LITTLE
BREAK, AND THEN WE'LL BE
RIGHT BACK WITH MORE
ABOUT SAFETY WEEK.
>> DO WE NEED MORE
ABOUT SAFETY WEEK?
>> WELL, YOU DON'T WANT TO GET
INJURED, DO YOU, HAROLD?
>> WE'RE UP HERE AT JIMMY
MCVEIGH'S PLACE, AND HE'S
WORKING ON THIS BOAT HERE.
>> [humming]
>> HE'S A POSTAL WORKER, BUT
THIS IS HIS HOBBY.
HE'S JUST GONE TO BUY A
PROPELLER, AND I THINK HE'LL
BE--I THINK I SEE--I THINK I
HEAR HIM COMIN' RIGHT NOW.
JIMMY.
>> MY BOAT, MY BOAT.
>> HOW'D SHE GO?
DID YOU GET A PROPELLER
ALL RIGHT?
>> DID I GET THE PROPELLER?
>> YEAH.
>> I WENT DOWN TO THE BLOODY
MARINA TO GET THE PROPELLER, A
THING I ORDERED A WEEK AGO.
>> YEAH.
>> AND THEY HAD TO SEND
TO HONG BLOODY KONG FOR IT,
AND IT'S STILL NOT IN.
ONE WEEK.
SO WHAT DID I HAVE TO DO?
I BOUGHT THIS INSTEAD.
>> WHAT THE HELL'S THAT?
THAT'S A CEILING FAN THERE, JIM.
>> THIS IS A PROPELLER.
>> OH, NO.
>> NO, THAT'S A CEILING FAN.
>> I KNOW.
IT'S THE SAME BLOODY THING.
>> NO, NO, NO.
JIMMY, I DON'T THINK THAT'LL
TAKE THE PRESSURE, YOU KNOW,
THE--THE STRESS.
IT'S SPINNING AT THOUSANDS OF
RPM.
THAT'S--I DON'T THINK
THAT'S--THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK
OUT, IS IT?
>> OF COURSE IT'LL WORK OUT.
I MEAN--
>> WELL, JIMMY, SHE'S WOOD,
YOU KNOW.
>> ALL THE BETTER, ISN'T IT?
I MEAN, SHE'S WOOD.
THIS IS A WIZENED OLD BOAT.
I MEAN, IF YOU--IF YOU PUT A
METAL PROPELLER ON, THE BLOODY
THING COMES OFF, SHE'S GONNA
SINK LIKE A STONE.
YOU PUT THIS ON, THIS FALLS OFF,
IT'S MADE OUT OF WOOD.
SHE'S GONNA FLOAT.
I CAN PICK UP THE BEST AND FIX
IT ALL OVER AGAIN.
>> BRILLIANT, BRILLIANT.
>> NO TROUBLE AT ALL.
I WAS THINKIN' OF PATENTING
THAT, ACTUALLY.
>> WELL, I WOULDN'T GO THAT FAR,
BUT I--NOW, HOW ARE YOU
GONNA--YOU MOUNT THIS ON HERE?
ARE YOU GONNA JUST BOLT THAT
RIGHT ONTO THE BOAT OR--
>> JEEZ, I NEVER THOUGHT OF
THAT.
YOU KNOW, WHAT I'M GONNA HAVE TO
DO IS, AS I SAID BEFORE,
THAT'S MY FORTE.
>> YES.
>> I IMPROVISE.
>> OH.
>> AND WHAT I'LL PROBABLY DO
HERE IS I'LL LOOK AROUND.
>> JUST LOOK AROUND, GET SOME--
>> LOOK AROUND, SEE IF I CAN GET
A BIT OF METAL, ALL RIGHT.
>> YEAH, MM-HMM. YEAH.
>> HOLD ON A WEE MINUTE.
>> LET'S WATCH THE MASTER
BUILDER AND HOW HE CRAFTS THINGS
JUST USING HIS IMAGINATION.
HE'S WANDERIN' AROUND,
LOOKIN' AT STUFF.
AND LET'S SEE
WHAT HE'S GONNA DO.
>> WAIT, HOW 'BOUT THIS HERE?
>> WELL, THIS--
>> COME ON!
[indistinct speech]
I FIGURE I COULD GET A BIT OF A
TRIPOD SUPPORT OUT OF THIS HERE.
LOOK.
>> AH, I DON'T THINK--I DON'T
THINK THAT'S GONNA.
THAT--THAT--
[clears throat]
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> WELL, THAT'S THE CAMERAMAN,
AND THAT'S HIS TV CAMERA THERE.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO.
THAT--THAT THING UNDERNEATH THE
CAMERA, THAT THING THERE.
>> OH, THAT'S THE TRIPOD.
THAT'S A TRIPOD.
>> IS THAT MADE OUT OF METAL?
>> [clears throat]
YEAH.
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> UH, JIM, I DON'T--JIM.
WELL, NOW, THIS--THIS IS AN
EXCITING DAY, THE FIRST TIME IN
6 1/2 YEARS JIMMY MCVEIGH'S BOAT
HAS A PROPELLER.
THIS IS GREAT.
>> INDEED, INDEED.
>> YEAH.
>> WILL YOU HOLD ONTO THAT
A WEE MINUTE, RED, WILL YOU?
>> SURE, NO PROBLEM.
>> WE'RE NEARLY THERE NOW, BOY.
GIVE US A HAMMER.
>> NO, NO.
JIM, YOU BROKE THE HAMMER
ON THE TRIPOD.
>> OH, RIGHT.
WHERE'S A HAMMER?
WHAT'S THAT?
GIVE ME THAT.
>> THAT'S--
>> SO ANYWAY, BY THE TIME WE GOT
EVERYTHING INTO THE LODGE, ALL
THE SAFETY EQUIPMENT, WE DECIDED
TO HAVE A FIRE DRILL.
SEE, 'CAUSE WHAT WE'D DONE IS
WE'D GOT ONE OF THEM SMOKE
DETECTORS THAT SOUNDS LIKE 55
SEATBELT BUZZERS ALL GOIN' OFF
AT ONCE.
AND WE HAD PUT ROPE LADDERS UP
AGAINST EVERYONE'S BEDROOM
WINDOW, AND WE HAD SOME OF THEM
SAFETY LIGHTS, NON-EXPLOSIVE
THINGS, AND WE GOT SOME
AUTOMATIC SPRINKLER SYSTEM.
AND WE HOOKED THE WHOLE WORKS UP
INTO A COMPUTER THAT MOOSE
THOMPSON HAD MADE OUT OF AN OLD
CLOTHES DRYER CONTROL PANEL.
SO THEN WHAT WE DONE WAS WE ALL
WENT TO BED AND PRETENDED WE
WERE ASLEEP.
NOT THE SAME BED.
BUT, YOU KNOW, AND AFTER A
COUPLE OF MINUTES OF PRETENDING
TO BE ASLEEP, SON OF A GUN, WE
WERE ASLEEP.
AND THEN OF COURSE, THE COMPUTER
CATCHES ON FIRE, YOU KNOW, BUT
LUCKILY NOW, MOOSE HAD PUT THE
UNIT UNDER THE CUPBOARD WHERE WE
KEEP ALL THE CANS OF INSECT
REPELLANT.
SO AS THE FIRE GOT GOIN', OF
COURSE, THEY GET HOT, AND THEY
START GOIN' OFF LIKE HAND
GRENADES.
I MEAN, IT WAS--IT WAS LIKE THE
VIETNAM WAR EXCEPT IT SMELLED
BETTER AND THERE WERE NO
MOSQUITOES.
OF COURSE, THAT WOKE US ALL UP.
EVERYBODY'S RUNNIN' FOR
SAFETY, YOU KNOW.
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK BROKE HIS ARM
ON THE ROPE LADDER.
MOOSE THOMPSON SCONNED HIS HEAD
ON A SAFETY LIGHT, AND STINKY
ALMOST DROWNED FROM THE
SPRINKLER SYSTEM, AND OF COURSE,
I SLEPT THROUGH THE WHOLE THING.
BUT THE POINT IS THAT NOW WE
KNOW THE SYSTEM WORKS AND GOLLY,
WE CAN ALL--WE CAN ALL SLEEP A
LITTLE EASIER.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING RIGHT HOME AFTER THE
SHOW, AND I'LL WALK THE DOG.
>> UNCLE RED,
YOU DON'T HAVE A DOG.
>> OH, THAT--THAT'S CODE,
HAROLD.
>> OH.
>> SO ANYWAY, UNTIL NEXT TIME,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND MY DOG AND EVERYBODY ELSE
HERE AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]