IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE'S THE MAN WHO LEFT
HIS BODY TO SCIENCE,
HIS WARDROBE TO HISTORY,
AND HIS PERSONALITY TO CHANCE,
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause)
HO HO HO! BY GOLLY!
ALL RIGHT! THANK YOU!
HEY, ALL RIGHT.
SAVE YOURSELVES --
YOU'VE GOT FAMILIES.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
EVERY YEAR THIS TIME,
THE GUYS START MAKIN'
THEIR OWN BEER AND WINE.
THEY'RE TRYIN' TO GIVE
SOMETHING BACK TO THE SYSTEM.
ONE FELLA MADE
AN INTERESTING BATCH.
DOESN'T TASTE TOO BAD.
IS IT WINE
OR BEER?
KINDA HARD
TO TELL.
IT'S EITHER A SPARKLING WINE
OR A LIGHT BEER.
WHAT DOES IT SAY ON THE LABEL?
UM, "AMERICAN STANDARD".
WELL, IT'S STILL
IN THE BATHTUB.
IT'S BREWIN' AWAY RIGHT NOW.
THAT'S MY SCIENCE EXPERIMENT
FROM THE SCIENCE FAIR!
YEAH, I'M PICKLING
POLLIWOGS.
COME ON, TASTES WAY TOO GOOD
FOR THAT.
BESIDES, WHY WOULD YOU PUT
ALL THOSE OLIVES IN THERE?
THOSE ARE
THE POLLIWOGS.
(Audience laughing)
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MAIN MESSAGE BEING,
FOR GOSH SAKES,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE OUT OF THIS
PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS.
YOU DRANK MY SCIENCE EXPERIMENT
RIGHT OUT OF THE TUB.
MOOSE LICKED THE RING
AND ATE THE PLUG.
RELAX, HAROLD.
YOU CAN MAKE
SOMETHING ELSE.
IT WAS THE WHOLE ECOLOGY
OF OUR WETLAND.
NOW I GOT 12 LODGE MEMBERS
IN A BELCHING CONTEST.
WORK THAT INTO THE PROJECT.
THAT'S MARSH GAS.
I TELL YOU WHAT, HAROLD.
LET'S DO A PROJECT TOGETHER
ON TOXIC WASTE
OR THE OZONE LAYER.
WE COULD, BUT NO.
I HAD MY HEART SET ON WINNING
THIS CONTEST.
GIRLS LIKE GUYS
WHO LOOK LIKE SCIENTISTS.
YOU LOOK MORE
LIKE AN EXPERIMENT.
(Audience laughing)
I KNOW WHAT I CAN DO!
I'LL DO, LIKE, ASTRONOMY.
I'LL GRIND MY OWN LENSES,
SILVER MY MIRRORS.
I'LL ALIGN THE FOCAL PLANES
AND MAKE A TELESCOPE.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN --
I'LL GET SOME DUCT TAPE.
NO, NO, NO!
ADULTS AREN'T ALLOWED TO HELP.
YOU EITHER.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GRIND YOUR
HUBBLE TO YOUR HEART'S CONTENT.
I'M GONNA MAKE
MY OWN TELESCOPE.
ALL RIGHTY.
I COULD BE A GREAT ASTRONOMER.
HE'S GOOD AT STARING
OFF INTO SPACE.
(Audience laughing)
(Red): ONE OF
THE BIGGEST DANGERS
OF HAVING SOMETHING
ON TELEVISION
IS THAT PEOPLE SEE THINGS
AND TRY THEM,
LIKE BLOWIN' UP A VAN,
OR DOING SOMETHING ATHLETIC,
IN BILL'S CASE.
HE'S GONNA CHANGE HIS CLOTHES.
HE SAW THIS AT THE OLYMPICS,
WHERE THEY HAVE THE RINGS
AND YOU...
WHAT'S THAT?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO CHANGE
RIGHT... RIGHT...
OH! OH!
THEY DON'T NEED TO SEE THAT
AT HOME.
THAT'S YOUR PERSONAL BUSINESS
UNDER THERE, I WOULD THINK.
NO, DON'T-- OH, IT'S A SHOE.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S FINE.
THERE'S A BIT OF A PONG.
ANYWAY, NICE FIGURE.
FINE-LOOKIN' MAN,
AND UP HE GOES.
I TELL YA,
WHAT HE'S FINDING OUT
IS THAT SOME THINGS
AREN'T AS EASY AS THEY LOOK --
THINGS LIKE BEING
BILL'S FRIEND, FOR EXAMPLE.
I'LL GIVE YOU A BOOST UP.
I'M GIVING YOU--
IT'S A BOOST, BILL, A BOOST UP.
OH, MAN!
WOW! OHHH...
WELCOME TO THE POSSUM LODGE
WORD GAME!
TONIGHT'S PRIZE IS
A WEEKEND FOR TWO
AT THE SOLITAIRE CHAMPIONSHIPS.
OK, UNCLE RED,
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MIKE HAMAR
TO SAY THIS WORD.
FATHER.
AND GO.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE,
YOUR MOTHER IS MARRIED TO...
UH, HER JOB --
EXOTIC DANCING'S HER LIFE.
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT THE MAN
WHO TOOK CARE OF YOU
WHEN YOU WERE YOUNG
WAS YOUR...
TRUANT OFFICER.
OH, THIS IS
A FAMILY MEMBER, MIKE.
THE MAN WHO SLEPT
WITH YOUR MOTHER.
(Audience laughing)
COULD YOU BE MORE SPECIFIC?
GROWING UP WITH JUST A MOM,
YOU KNEW YOU HAD A...
CURFEW.
ANOTHER WORD FOR "DADDY".
LIFER.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE,
IF YOUR WIFE HAS KIDS,
YOU'LL BE...
LONG GONE.
(Audience laughing)
OH, OH, OH, OH!
JUST LIKE YOUR...
FATHER.
(Applause and cheering)
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE
A VERY COMMON JOINT
THAT YOU USE
FOR BUILDING FURNITURE,
HOUSES, EVEN WOODEN CARS.
IT'S A 90-DEGREE JOINT.
ALL'S YOU NEED IS A TABLE SAW,
OR A FRIEND WHO HAS ONE.
I'VE JUST SWITCHED
THE BLADE IN THIS,
BECAUSE THIS WAS
A SPECIAL BLADE
WHICH IS USED
FOR CUTTIN' METAL.
DOES A HECK OF A JOB,
DOESN'T IT?
(Crashing)
YOU DON'T NEED TO HORSE
THIS THING DOWN OR ANYTHING.
JUST FINGER-TIGHT IS FINE.
(Squeaking)
THEN JUST START 'ER UP.
I SHOULD HAVE USED
A STRONGER FINGER.
THERE'S A LESSON
TO YOU YOUNGSTERS.
NEVER COMPROMISE SAFETY
JUST BECAUSE YOU CAN'T FIND
THE WRENCH.
OHHH!
OH!
I WONDER IF IT'S STILL SHARP.
YEAH.
(Grunting)
(Saw squeaking)
WE'RE READY TO START CUTTIN'.
(Coughing)
HERE'S SOME ADVICE --
COUNT YOUR FINGERS
BEFORE AND AFTER EVERY CUT.
THEN YOU'LL KNOW IF YOU SHOULD
BE SIFTING THROUGH THE SAWDUST.
AND WE DO THIS CUT, HERE.
AND, UH, JUST THAT EASY,
BASICALLY.
SHE'S, UH...
ALL RIGHT, SHE DIDN'T ACTUALLY
CUT ALL THE WAY THROUGH,
SO WE'D HAVE TO SET THE BLADE
A LITTLE HIGHER
OR YOU CAN SET THE TABLE LOWER.
YOUR CHOICE, REALLY.
OH, NO, I KNOW.
(Audience laughing)
THAT OUGHT TO DO 'ER.
HERE'S SOMETHING ELSE
YOU CAN DO.
WHEN YOU WANT TO CUT
ALONG THE LENGTH,
THAT'S CALLED "RIPPING".
YOU CAN RIP THROUGH THE BOARD.
IT'S EASIER
THAN DOING IT BY HAND.
IT'S CALLED RIPPING.
IT WENT RIPPIN' OUT OF THERE.
(Laughing)
HERE'S WHAT I WANTED
TO SHOW YOU.
WHEN YOU JOIN PIECES OF WOOD
IN A 90-DEGREE ANGLE,
SOMETIMES YOU MAKE
A JOINT LIKE THAT.
THAT'S CALLED A BUTT JOINT.
FRANKLY, IT'S KIND OF
BUTT-UGLY.
I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW TO MAKE ANOTHER KIND
CALLED A MITRE JOINT.
"MITRE" -- THAT'S A FRENCH WORD
THAT MEANS "NOT BUTT".
OK?
YOU'LL STILL HAVE
YOUR 90-DEGREE ANGLE,
BUT YOU'LL DO IT WITH TWO 45's.
YOU WANT TO HAVE A RIGHT ANGLE.
ANYTHING ELSE IS A WRONG ANGLE,
WHICH I HAVE PROVEN MANY TIMES.
SET YOUR SAW TO EXACTLY
45 DEGREES.
THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT, SO, UH...
NOW WE GOT
OUR TWO 45-DEGREE ANGLES.
WE PUT THOSE TOGETHER.
PUT THAT ONE THERE
AND WHAT YOU'RE GONNA FIND
WHEN THIS GOES TOGETHER
EXACTLY RIGHT IS
YOU'VE GOT A PERFECT
90-DEGREE ANGLE.
(Audience laughing)
YEAH, UM...
(Crashing)
WE HAVEN'T GOT THE ANGLE
JUST ABSOLUTELY RIGHT ON THIS.
WE'LL GET 'ER.
BY GOLLY, SHE'S SENSITIVE.
I MAY HAVE OVER-COMPENSATED
A BIT, THERE,
AND I'M RUNNIN' OUT OF WOOD
SO I GOTTA THINK--
YOU KNOW, I NEED A TOTAL
OF 90 DEGREES
BUT IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
TWO 45's.
I'VE GOT A...
THAT'S ABOUT A 72 THERE,
SO WHAT I NEED TO MAKE 90
WOULD BE...
... SEVENTEEN, OR SOMEWHERE
IN THAT AREA.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
HAVE THE TABLE SAW
JACKED FORWARD 90 DEGREES.
A TABLE SAW'S
A HECK OF A THING.
I MEAN, THEY'RE FASTER.
THEY'RE MORE ACCURATE
THAN WHAT YOU CAN CUT YOURSELF.
THEY DON'T COST THAT MUCH
FOR WHAT YOU GET...
... AND THEY'RE PORTABLE.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
BUSTER, I'M DONE
WITH YOUR TABLE SAW.
HERE IT COMES!
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
NEED TO TALK TO YOU LADIES
TO HELP YOU UNDERSTAND
WHY WE MEN DO WHAT WE DO.
FOR EXAMPLE, NOT STOPPING
TO ASK FOR DIRECTIONS
WHEN WE'RE LOST.
OK, PRIMARILY,
IT'S A PRIDE THING.
WE'RE OUT THERE.
WE'RE DRIVING AROUND IN
OUR OWN VEHICLES, BURNING GAS.
GOT THE SUNGLASSES ON,
LOOKIN' GOOD, YOU KNOW?
PEOPLE SEE US GOIN' BY
WOULD NEVER GUESS
THAT WE HAVE NO IDEA
WHERE WE ARE.
AND WE'RE NOT REAL EXCITED
ABOUT SHARING THAT INFORMATION.
A MAN DOES NOT EMBRACE
THE CONCEPT
OF GOING UP TO TOTAL STRANGERS
AND SAYING,
"YOU MAY NOT KNOW THIS,
BUT I'M A MORON."
WHEREAS THE WOMAN
THAT HE'S WITH
IS ONLY TOO HAPPY
TO SHARE THAT INFORMATION.
I THINK IT HELPS TO EASE
HER BURDEN A LITTLE BIT.
TO A WOMAN, GETTIN' LOST
WHEN YOU'RE ON A TRIP
IS JUST A BLAMELESS
ACT OF NATURE,
BUT TO A MAN, IT'S A SIGN
OF PERSONAL FAILURE.
HE KNEW WHERE HE WAS
WHEN HE LEFT.
HE DOESN'T KNOW
WHERE HE IS NOW.
SOMEWHERE ALONG THE WAY,
HE CROSSED THE LINE
BETWEEN THE WORLD HE KNOWS
AND THE WORLD HE DOESN'T KNOW.
THAT'S HOW HE FEELS
ABOUT WHEN HE GOT MARRIED...
(Audience laughing)
... AND WHEN HE HAD KIDS.
SO IF HE ADMITS HE'S LOST
IN HIS CAR,
HE'S GONNA HAVE TO ADMIT
HE'S LOST IN THOSE OTHER AREAS
AS WELL.
THAT'S WAY TOO MUCH TO ASK.
SO JUST SIT THERE,
BITE YOUR TONGUE,
CIRCLE THE BLOCK A FEW TIMES.
MEN AREN'T LOST.
THEY JUST TAKE THE LONG WAY.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause and cheering)
WELL, HAROLD, THINK YOU'RE
GONNA WIN FIRST PRIZE
AT THE SCHOOL SCIENCE FAIR.
I'M GONNA HOOK THIS
TO THE THING.
YOU CAN'T LOSE WITH THIS.
HUH?
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
FROM AN ELEPHANT'S
PROCTOLOGIST?
HAROLD, I MADE THIS.
THIS IS YOUR TELESCOPE.
I HELPED YOU A LITTLE BIT.
LIKE,
I DID THE BUILDING PART BIT.
BUT IT WAS YOUR IDEA --
WELL, IT WAS GALILEO'S IDEA,
BUT HE'S DEAD.
YOU CAN'T HELP ME.
IT'S AGAINST SCIENCE FAIR RULES.
BESIDES, I WANT TO WIN.
HAROLD, YOU'LL WIN.
LOOK IN THE MIRROR.
THAT'S OUT OF A FORD GALAXY.
THAT'S OUT OF A COMET.
THE ONE INSIDE'S
OUT OF A SATURN.
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
OH, THAT'S AMAZING.
WHAT DOES IT SAY THERE?
"CAUTION: UNIVERSES MAY SEEM
CLOSER THAN THEY APPEAR."
NO, YOU CAN'T HELP.
I'M DOING IT BY MYSELF.
MY DAD HELPED ME WITH HOMEWORK.
THAT'S BECAUSE YOU GUYS
WERE IN THE SAME GRADE.
(Laughing)
I'M NOT DOING
A TELESCOPE ANY MORE.
I'M DOING A CRYSTAL RADIO SET.
I'VE JUST GOT
A LITTLE MORE SOLDERING TO DO.
OH, OH, OH!
SEE, SEE, SEE.
I'LL GET IT -- OOO!
YOU GET THAT.
NO, YOU GET IT.
OH, IF YOU SEE
A BIG FAT DOG
WADDLING DOWN THE ROAD
DON'T YOU BE TOO CRITICAL
OF HIS EXTRA WIDE LOAD
IF YOU'VE EVER TASTED
DOG FOOD
YOU'VE GOT TO
TIP YOUR HAT
TO AN ANIMAL WHO COULD
ACTUALLY OVEREAT
ON A DIET OF CRAP
LIKE THAT
MY NAME IS DALTON HUMPHREY,
AND I'M A MAN.
(All): HI, DALTON.
AND, UH, IT'S BEEN TWO WEEKS
SINCE I LAST ACTED LIKE A GUY.
AND THIS WEEK, UH...
THIS WEEK I DID SOMETHING
I'M PRETTY PROUD OF.
IT'S A FIRST FOR ME.
I DID LAUNDRY.
WHOA!
WOW!
WASHIN', DRYIN',
THE WHOLE NINE YARDS.
YOU KNOW, WHAT I REALIZED
IS THAT
THE PROBLEM WAS IN MY HEAD,
YOU KNOW.
IT WAS MY ATTITUDE.
IF YOU-- IF YOU--
IF YOU CHANGE YOUR ATTITUDE,
YOU CAN CHANGE THE WHOLE WORLD.
SO I DIDN'T THINK ABOUT IT
AS IF IT WAS WASHING CLOTHES.
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT LIKE IT WAS
RESTORING CLOTHES.
SEE.
REFINISHING A SHIRT.
RENOVATING A PAIR OF PANTS.
AND IT WASN'T A CHORE.
THIS WAS A PROJECT, YOU KNOW.
AND I DIDN'T EVEN CALL IT
A WASHER AND A DRYER,
BECAUSE THESE ARE MY TOOLS.
THESE ARE MY POWER TOOLS,
MY BIG POWER TOOLS.
SO I CALLED THEM
A DIRT STRIPPER,
AND A HEAT TURBINE.
"STAND BACK, KIDS!
"DAD'S USING THE HEAT TURBINE!"
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE IS NO RULE THAT SAYS
A WASHER AND A DRYER
HAVE TO BE WHITE.
WHY DON'T THEY MAKE 'EM BLACK
OR BROWN, LIKE A RADIAL ARM SAW
OR A JOINTER,
FOR HEAVEN'S SAKE?
YOU KNOW WHAT THE UP-SIDE
OF ALL THIS IS?
MY WIFE WAS THRILLED.
TWO LOADS OF LAUNDRY,
SHE'S HAPPY, SHE'S...
SHE WAS FRIENDLY.
WOW!
THAT'S RIGHT.
AND I'M GONNA SURPRISE HER.
I'M SURPRISING HER RIGHT NOW,
BY WASHING
ALL HER WOOLLEN SWEATERS.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
THE LOOK ON HER FACE
WHEN I PULL THOSE BABIES
OUT OF THE DRYER.
THAT'S GONNA BE SOMETHING.
THANK YOU.
(Red): HERE WE ARE
BACK WITH
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL".
HE'S READY TO GO.
HE'S GOT THE CHALK.
IT'S NOT CHALK --
IT'S FLOUR.
YOU DON'T NEED
A LOT OF THAT, BILL.
FOR INSTANCE,
YOU DON'T NEED THAT MUCH.
ANYWAY, I'M NOT GONNA TRY
AND BOOST HIM UP AGAIN.
HE'S GOING TO GO UP THERE
ON THE OIL DRUM.
THIS IS GOING TO TAKE
A LOT OF... A LOT OF STRENGTH.
WOW.
BOY, OH, BOY,
I'M IMPRESSED WITH THAT.
SOMETIMES I THINK BILL'S
AN IDIOT AND CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
THEN I REALIZE I'M WRONG --
HE'S JUST AN IDIOT.
THERE HE IS, UPSIDE DOWN.
LOOK AT THE POWER THERE, FOLKS.
YOU DON'T SEE THAT EVERY DAY,
AND I THINK IT'S A GOOD THING,
ESPECIALLY AROUND MEAL-TIME.
(Groaning)
WHAT ARE THOSE NOISES?
I THINK BILL'S BACK
ISN'T WHAT IT USED...
KIND OF EGYPTIAN,
KIND OF AN UPSIDE DOWN--
OH, BOY, I'M GETTING A DISPLAY
AND SO ARE YOU.
WHAT NOW, BILL?
OH, MY GOSH!
LET'S HEAR IT FOR THE BOY.
WHAT, THE OTHER ARM?
MY GOSH, HE'S AMBIRINGSTROUS.
THAT'S GOT TO BE HARD
ON THE ARM, ISN'T IT, BILL?
UH-OH -- NOW BILL
LEARNS ABOUT GRAVITY.
OH!
MY GOSH.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
I GIVE YOU...
THE LORD OF THE RINGS.
HERE'S A "RED GREEN" SIGN
SENT TO US BY A VIEWER.
GOOD NEWS, HAROLD.
THIS CRYSTAL RADIO'S
GONNA WIN YOU FIRST PRIZE.
CONGRATULATIONS
AND GOOD WORK.
GOOD WORK? --
YOU BUILT THE THING.
DON'T, DON'T, DON'T --
DON'T TOUCH IT.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW IT WORKS.
WHEN WE GET TO SCHOOL
I'LL EXPLAIN EVERYTHING.
I CANNOT ENTER SOMETHING
THAT YOU BUILT,
OR HAVE YOU NOT BEEN LISTENING
THE FIRST NINE TIMES
I SAID THAT?
I'M GONNA DO MY OWN PROJECT.
IT'S ABOUT SEX.
AWW.
OH, HAROLD, HAROLD -- SEX.
I CAN'T HELP YOU THERE.
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
OF COURSE, YOU'RE USED TO THAT,
AREN'T YA?
RIGHT?
I'M GONNA DO
A FRANK AND EXPLICIT LOOK
AT THE GERMINATION
OF SOYA BEANS,
WITHOUT THE MEDDLING
OF AN ADULT.
OK, BUT BUSTER HADFIELD
IS HELPING HIS SON
MAKE AN ATOM-SMASHING
NUCLEAR ACCELERATOR CYCLOTRON
OUT OF A T.V.
AND A WEED-WHACKER.
I DON'T CARE --
I'M GONNA DO THINGS MY WAY.
I'M GONNA ENTER
THIS CRYSTAL RADIO
IN THE SCIENCE FAIR MYSELF.
THE FAIR IS ONLY OPEN
TO HIGH-SCHOOL STUDENTS.
I NEVER GRADUATED.
IT'S TIME TO FEATURE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY.
(All): I DON'T KNOW!
OK!
TO JOIN MY UNCLE RED
IS HIS BEST FRIEND
IN THE WHOLE WIDE ROOM,
MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSY!
(Applause and cheering)
OK.
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"IS IT TRUE THAT BASKETBALL
WAS INVENTED BY A CANADIAN?"
BASKETBALL WAS INVENTED
BY A CANADIAN,
BUT HE WAS LIVING IN
THE UNITED STATES.
OH, YEAH, YEAH,
I WAS IN THE STATES
AT THE TIME,
BUT I DIDN'T GIVE UP
MY CANADIAN CITIZENSHIP.
I WAS DOWN THERE DOING SOME
HUSH-HUSH WORK FOR THE C.I.A.,
AS WAS THEN KNOWN AS
TEDDY'S ROUGHRIDERS.
THEY WANTED ME TO COME UP WITH
SOME COVER STORY
AS TO WHAT I DID FOR A LIVING.
I SAID "SPORTS INVENTOR".
AND TO MAKE THE COVER
A BIT MORE CONVINCING,
OF COURSE, WOULDN'T YOU KNOW,
I HAD TO INVENT A SPORT.
I SURE DIDN'T EXPECT
THAT DARN GAME TO CATCH ON.
HAP, YOU DON'T EXPECT US
TO BELIEVE THAT, DO YA?
WELL...
(Laughing)
YOU GOT ME THERE, RED!
NO, NO, NO, NO.
THAT WASN'T TRUE.
I SURE DID EXPECT
THAT DARN GAME TO CATCH ON.
MR. SHAUGHNESSY, OUT OF ALL
THE HISTORY BOOKS I'VE READ,
THEY SAY THE CANADIAN WAS
MR. JAMES NAISMITH.
JAMES NAISMITH, YEAH.
THAT WAS MY C.I.A. COVER NAME.
FUNNY YOU NEVER MENTIONED THAT,
HAP.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU
TO HOLD BACK.
ALL MY SPY WORK
WAS TOP SECRET, YOU KNOW.
THE ONLY REASON
I CAN MENTION THIS NOW
IS BECAUSE FRANCO IS DEAD,
AND SPAIN IS NO LONGER
A THREAT TO WORLD PEACE.
I'M FINDING THIS
HARD TO BELIEVE.
THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU'RE LISTENING.
I'M TELLING YOU,
I INVENTED BASKETBALL.
OH YEAH, OH, YEAH --
HOOP DREAMS.
NO, NO, NO,
MAYBE HAP'S RIGHT.
REMEMBER THAT TIME HE WAS UP
ON THE DRUNK AND DISORDERLY,
DRIBBLING ALL OVER THE COURT?
(Audience laughing)
(Applause)
THE SCIENCE FAIR WAS, UH,
WAS FUN.
WHOSE PROJECT EXPLODED THERE,
HAROLD?
I CAN'T HEAR YOU
OVER THE RINGING!
I'M SAYING
WHOSE PROJECT EXPLODED?
YOU MEAN THE FIRST TIME?
YEAH, YEAH.
THE ONE BESIDE US.
(Both) THIS SIDE.
YEAH, YEAH.
SORRY YOU DIDN'T WIN, HAROLD.
WELL, THAT'S OK.
I ESCAPED WITH MY LIFE.
THAT'S THE MAIN THING.
WHO WON THE FIRST PRIZE ANYWAY?
STINKY PETERSON HAS THE TROPHY.
THE DOCTORS SAY THEY CAN
GET THAT REMOVED THOUGH.
THE ACTUAL WINNER WAS
ANDREA McCLINTOCK.
THE JUDGES SAID HER ENTRY
OF FIRE EXTINGUISHERS
WAS RATHER TIMELY.
BUT, HAROLD,
I HEARD YOUR PROJECT
MADE IT TO THE FINALS
OVER IN PORT ASBESTOS.
NO!
THAT'S JUST WHERE
MOST OF THE PIECES LANDED.
(Squealing)
I DON'T HEAR IT,
BUT IT'S GOT TO BE TIME
FOR THE LODGE MEETING.
IT'S PROBABLY TIME
FOR THE LODGE MEETIN'.
WHY DON'T YOU GO AHEAD?
LODGE
MEETING!
UM...
MAYBE JUST SOME FRIES.
WHY DON'T YOU GO
TO THE LODGE MEETIN'?
I'M JUST GONNA GO
TO THE LODGE MEETING!
WELL, I COULDN'T CARE LESS
WHERE YOU GO.
LODGE MEETIN'.
LODGE MEETING!
OH, UNCLE RED.
NOW, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I LEARNED TODAY
THAT THERE ARE SOME THINGS
THAT MAN SHOULD NOT KNOW.
I'M HOPIN'
YOU'RE NOT ONE OF 'EM.
I'LL BE COMING HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AS SOON AS THE SMOULDERING
GOES DOWN IN MY PANTS.
TO THE REST OF YOU
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND --
I GUESS HE'S GONE TO
THE LODGE MEETIN' -- HAROLD,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
UNTIL NEXT TIME,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
LODGE MEETIN'.
(Possum squeal)
OK, SIT DOWN, SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, SIT DOWN.
OK, ALL RISE.