[breezy folk music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> YOU'VE PROBABLY SEEN
A LOT OF THINGS, AND ANYWAY
THAT'S PROBABLY NONE OF MY
BUSINESS, BUT I BET YOU'VE NEVER
SEEN A TELEVISION SHOW
LIKE THIS ONE.
THAT'S BECAUSE THERE'S NEVER
BEEN A TELEVISION LIKE THIS ONE.
WELL, LET'S HOPE THAT'S BECAUSE
NO ONE'S EVER THOUGHT OF IT
RATHER THAN, LIKE, SIMPLY THEY
DISMISSED THE WHOLE CONCEPT.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT'D BE WORSE?
THEY TRIED IT
AND NO ONE LIKED IT.
[murmuring]
OH, ANYWAY, WELL, HERE'S THE
STAR OF THE RED GREEN SHOW
AND, INCIDENTALLY, MY UNCLE,
RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW, AND,
OF COURSE, A SPECIAL HELLO
TO OUR GROUP OF SHUT-INS
AT LEAVENWORTH.
GOOD LUCK WITH THE PAROLE BOARD.
AND SPEAKING OF PAROLE BOARDS,
COME ON IN HERE A MINUTE,
HAROLD.
HAROLD IS THE PRODUCER AND
DIRECTOR OF THE SHOW, AND ALSO
HE HAS THIS FANCY MACHINE HERE
THAT ENABLES HIM TO MOVE INTO
OTHER SEGMENTS OF THE SHOW AND
KIND OF KEEP THE PACE UP IF,
YOU KNOW, IT'S GETTING
A BIT DRAGGY OR SLOW
OR WHAT HAVE YOU.
GIVE US A LITTLE DEMO ON THAT
UNIT THERE, WOULD YOU, HAROLD?
>> OH, SURE, NO SWEAT.
>> WELL, HAROLD,
I SAID JUST A DEMO.
I'M SUPPOSED TO TELL
MY WELL-DIGGING STORY.
>> WELL, LET'S THE HOPE
THE AUDIENCE CAN CURB
THEIR DISAPPOINTMENT.
>> WHEN LIFE GETS YOU DOWN
AND YOU CAN'T WAIT TO DIE
WHEN THE SLIGHTEST CONTUSION
BRINGS A TEAR TO YOUR EYE
HERE'S WHAT I DO
WHEN THINGS GO WRONG
I GO ON MY OWN TV SHOW
AND SING A SONG
OH, WELL, AT LEAST
I'M NOT A MOLE
>> A MOLE!
>> OH, WELL!
>> WELL!
>> AT LEAST I'M NOT A MOLE
>> MOLE
>> EITHER KIND.
WITH ONE, I'M IN A HOLE
COMPLETELY BLIND
WITH THE OTHER
I'M A BLEMISH
ON SOMEONE'S BEHIND
SO PUT A SMILE
ON THAT LONG, LONG FACE
UNLESS YOU'RE A MOLE
IN WHICH CASE I APOLOGIZE
FOR THIS INSENSITIVE SONG
OKAY, THIS WEEK
ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU
ABOUT SOME OF THE INJURIES
THAT CAN HAPPEN WITH BOATING.
NOW, YOU GOT TO BE CAREFUL.
YOU GOT TO WEAR A HARD HAT WHEN
YOU'RE FIGHTING DINGHIES,
YOU KNOW, OR YOU GOT TO BE
CAREFUL TOBOGGANING
IN CANOES AND STUFF.
AND, OF COURSE, UP AT THE LODGE
NOW, YOU CAN GET INJURED
JUST STRADDLING A BOAT.
WE GET--WE GET A LOT OF
STRADDLING INJURIES UP THERE.
BUT ONE OF THE THINGS THAT
PEOPLE DON'T TALK ABOUT
ALL THAT MUCH
IS THE TYPE OF INJURY YOU GET
WHEN YOU'RE WINCHING
A LARGE BOAT OUT OF THE WATER.
SO I THOUGHT I'D JUST SHOW YOU
TODAY IN THE HANDYMAN CORNER--
LET'S JUST PRETEND NOW
THAT THIS IS THE LAKE.
IT'S THE SAME COLOR AS THE LAKE.
AND WE'LL PRETEND THAT THIS
CANOE HERE IS A--
IS A LARGE BOAT.
FIRST THING YOU DO IS, YOU--
YOU FIND THE BOW OF THE BOAT,
WHICH IS THE FRONT.
THEY CALL IT THE BOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
BUT THERE'LL BE A RING THERE.
NO, THAT'S--
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS--THIS IS THE BOW HERE.
YOU CAN SEE THE RING.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S THE--THAT'S
THE TROUBLE WITH CANOES;
THEY LOOK THE SAME WAY
FROM BOTH ENDS.
I HAD AN AUNT LIKE THAT.
THIS IS OUR TRAILER,
AND WHAT IT'S GOT UP HERE IS,
THIS IS CALLED THE TONGUE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
YOU KNOW, IT'S SLIPPERY.
IT'S UNDERWATER
MOST OF THE TIME.
MAYBE THAT'S IT; I DON'T KNOW.
AND THIS, THIS IS WHAT I WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
THIS IS CALLED THE WINCH.
THIS IS HOW WE GET THE BOAT
UP ON TRAILER, BUT THERE'S
A LOT OF WORK INVOLVED,
AND IT'S VERY DANGEROUS,
BECAUSE THE THING CAN BREAK,
OR YOU CAN HURT YOUR ARM,
OR YOU CAN JUST GET BORED.
SO I'VE GOT A BETTER WAY,
A DIFFERENT WAY TO GET
THAT BOAT UP ON THE TRAILER.
ALL RIGHT, WHAT I'VE DONE IS
INSTALLED A ONE-TON POWER WINCH
INTO THE FRONT SEAT OF THE VAN.
IT'S AN ATTRACTIVE INSTALLATION,
I THINK.
BUT THE IMPORTANT THING HERE
IS THAT IT'S WIRED INTO
THE ALTERNATOR OF THE VAN
AND VERY, VERY SAFE.
YOU'RE A LONG WAY
FROM THE ACTION BACK THERE,
AND THERE'S NO EFFORT INVOLVED.
YOU RIG THIS AS A CONTROL BOX,
YOU PUSH THE BUTTON, AND YOU
WINCH THE BOAT UP THERE
JUST AS SAFE AND SOUND
AS YOU PLEASE.
[winch rattling]
HELLO.
WELL, OF COURSE NONE OF THIS
WOULD HAVE HAPPENED
IF I'D HAD A SPOTTER.
ANYWAY, REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY
SHOULD AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
HAROLD!
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH MORE OF
THE WELL-DIGGING ADVENTURE
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO ENJOY
MY STORIES.
>> OH, I DIDN'T KNOW
YOUR WIFE WAS WATCHING.
HI, AUNT BERNICE.
>> "IT IS AUTUMN.
500 GEESE ARE FLYING SOUTH
IN A GIANT WEDGE FORMATION
LIKE A HUGE PIECE OF PIZZA,
SHADES OF MUSHROOM AND PEPPERONI
AND ANCHOVIES.
AND AS THEY TRAVEL,
THEY DROP THE TOPPINGS
THAT THEY DON'T LIKE."
WELL, AS I NEVER GOT A CHANCE
TO MENTION EARLIER, WE HAD
A LITTLE PROBLEM WITH THE WELL
UP AT THE LODGE YESTERDAY.
SHE WASN'T ANY PUMPING ANY
WATER, AND RATHER THAN HAVE TO
GO DOWN THERE AND FIX THE WASHER
ON THE FOOT VALVE, WE FIGURED
IT'D BE EASIER
JUST TO DIG ANOTHER WELL.
WE WERE GONNA DO IT BY HAND,
BUT THEN WE FOUND THE SHOVEL.
WE FIGURED
WE'D GET STINKY PETERSON
TO DIG THE WELL, 'CAUSE HE'S
THE SKINNIEST, AND THAT WAY
THERE'D BE A LOT LESS
OF A HOLE TO WORK ON.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
MAKE IT EASIER ON EVERYBODY.
STINKY HAD A PROBLEM SEEING
THE LOGIC, BUT HE'S LIKE THAT.
SO WE DID WHAT THE--WHAT THE
PROFESSIONAL WORK CREWS DO.
WE JUST KIND OF SAT IN A RING
AROUND STINKY
AND WATCHED HIM WORK.
HE SEEMED TO ENJOY
THE ENCOURAGEMENT AND GAVE HIM
SOMETHING TO THROW THE DIRT AT.
>> UNCLE RED, UNCLE RED.
THIS IS SUCH, LIKE,
A GREAT STORY, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, WHAT I SUGGEST IS THAT
WE COME BACK TO IT LATER.
THAT WAY, THE VIEWER
WON'T TURN US OFF
AS SOON YOU'RE FINISHED
OR, EVEN WORSE,
BEFORE YOU'RE FINISHED, RIGHT?
SO LET'S JUST GO
TO ANOTHER SEGMENT.
>> NO, THANKS, HAROLD.
I'D RATHER JUST KIND OF CARRY ON
WITH THE STORY NOW.
>> [laughs]
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
>> BOB.
>> OH, HI, RED.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> YEAH, I FIGURED YOU'D BE
OUT HERE, YOU KNOW,
OUT IN THE FAIRWAY.
>> ANOTHER DAY, ANOTHER DOLLAR,
YOU KNOW.
>> WELL, THAT'S NOT
THE GREEN FEE, IS IT?
>> NO, NO, RED.
NO, I'M WORKING
FOR THE DEPARTMENT TODAY.
UM...
STUDYING CLOUD PATTERNS,
YOU KNOW.
SEE THOSE STRATO-NIMBULUS
OVER THERE?
THAT'S SOME HIGH PRESSURE
MOVING IN.
>> YEAH, WELL, ANYWAY,
BOB, WE'RE THINKING ABOUT
PUTTING INDOOR PLUMBING
INTO THE LODGE?
>> HMM.
>> AND WE GOT TO PUT
A SEPTIC THING.
WE GOT THE FORM HERE,
AND THERE'S A LOT OF PAPERWORK
TO IT, AND I THOUGHT,
YOU KNOW, SINCE YOU'RE A MEMBER
AND YOU BELONG TO THE
DEPARTMENT OF NATURAL RESOURCES,
I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU COULD
HELP ME OUT WITH THIS.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW, RED.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT REALLY INTO
THE OL' SEPTIC TANK
APPROVAL THING, YOU KNOW.
OH, THANKS.
NO, MY DEPARTMENT IS WILDLIFE
AND FOLIA--FOLI--FOL--
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING.
>> YEAH, WELL, AND WEATHER TOO,
I GUESS.
>> HMM?
>> WEATHER.
>> OH, YEAH, WEATHER
AND WEATHER STUFF.
YEAH, AS YOU SAY, YEAH.
>> AND GOLF, I GUESS.
>> AND GOLF?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NOT GOLF.
I DO THAT JUST FOR FUN.
YEAH, I'M OUT HERE NOW AND THEN.
>> WELL, IT'S ABOUT SEVEN DAYS
A WEEK, I THINK.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THAT.
NO, NOT SEVEN DAYS.
THERE'S SOME DAYS
I COME OUT HERE, I DON'T PLAY.
>> WHAT DAY?
>> IT'S IN FEBRUARY.
THE 30TH, I THINK.
>> HMM.
>> OH, HEY.
SEE OVER THERE, RED?
STORM CLOUDS BREWING
OVER THE NINTH HOLE?
HEY, WHAT DO YOU SAY YOU AND I
PLAY OVER TO THE NINTH HOLE,
COUPLE OF ROUNDS,
SEE IF THERE'S A STORM BREWING
OR SOMETHING?
>> NO, I CAN'T DO THAT, BOB.
I'VE ALREADY RENTED THE BACKHOE
AND, YOU KNOW, WAITING TO PUT
THE SEPTIC IN, AND IT'S ACTUALLY
COSTING ME MONEY
JUST STANDING HERE
TALKING TO YOU RIGHT NOW.
>> WELL, NINE HOLES.
50 MINUTES.
>> WELL, I DON'T HAVE
50 MINUTES, BOB.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE ANY CLUBS.
>> WELL, LOOK.
I HAVE TWO SETS OF CLUBS
RIGHT HERE.
YEAH, TWO SETS OF CLUBS,
BAG OF BALLS, BAG OF TEES,
MICKEY OF BOOZE.
COMPLETE GOLF SET.
>> SOME OTHER TIME, BOB.
>> YEAH.
YEAH, SURE, RED.
YEP, ALWAYS SOME OTHER TIME.
ALWAYS ANOTHER TIME
TO DO THIS, EH?
[chuckles]
YUP.
FORE!
OH!
LOOK AT THAT!
TOO MUCH TOPSPIN!
I CAN'T EVEN PLAY THAT.
>> SO WHAT ABOUT THIS FORM, BOB?
CAN YOU HELP ME OUT
WITH THE FORM AT ALL?
>> OH, RIGHT, YEAH.
LOOK AT THAT.
WELL, RED, THIS IS
PRETTY COMPLICATED, YOU KNOW--
>> WELL, YEAH, I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY--
>> WELL, THIS'LL TAKE ME
ABOUT--ABOUT 50 MINUTES.
>> 50?
>> I DON'T KNOW; WITH PULLING
THOSE TWO GOLF CLUBS AROUND
AND THE WEATHER REPORT
I GOT TO FILL OUT,
MIGHT TAKE ME ALL DAY.
>> I GOT AN IDEA HERE.
>> HMM?
>> MAYBE IT IS A GREAT DAY
FOR GOLF, HUH?
>> IT SURE IS, RED.
THAT'S WONDERFUL!
THE DEPARTMENT OF NATURAL
RESOURCES IS REALLY GONNA
APPRECIATE THIS.
>> OH, AND TELL YOU WHAT.
LET'S NOT COUNT THAT ONE.
>> HEY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> YOU JUST GO AHEAD.
I'LL HANG ONTO THAT.
>> YEAH, YOU HANG ON.
>> WE'LL DO THIS, THOUGH, RIGHT?
>> OH, YEAH, WE'LL GET TO THAT.
I WOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT THAT
AT ALL.
NO, SIR.
>> OKAY, WATCH THE TOP SPIN, EH?
>> TOP SPIN, YEAH,
I GOT TO WATCH THAT.
KEEP MY HEAD DOWN.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH.
>> THAT'S THE KEY, YOU KNOW.
>> YEAH.
>> AH, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
A GOOD TIME.
I'LL SHOW YOU WHAT I KNOW TOO,
RED.
>> ALL RIGHT.
50 MINUTES, HUH?
>> YEAH, 50 MINUTES.
FORE!
OH!
[water splashes]
DARN!
LOOK AT THAT.
I MEAN, THAT'S NO BETTER
THAN THAT ONE.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, I THINK
YOU MAY HAVE OVERCLEANED
THAT BALL.
>> OH, I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S PROBABLY IT.
>> YEAH.
LET ME GIVE HER A GO HERE.
>> JUST CLEAN THOSE BALLS WAY
TOO MUCH SOMETIME, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> NOW, KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN.
>> YEAH, YOU MIGHT WANT TO KEEP
YOURS DOWN TOO THERE, BOB.
>> OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
OF COURSE.
>> WELL, LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S VERY NICE, RED.
VERY, VERY NICE.
>> OH, BOB.
I HIT THAT LITTLE FLAGPOLE
ON THE GREEN.
IS THERE A PENALTY FOR THAT?
>> NO, WE'LL BEND THE RULES
JUST A LITTLE BIT, RED.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S GONNA RAIN.
MIGHT HAVE TO CUT THE GAME
SHORT, YOU KNOW.
>> WELL, WHATEVER.
>> MY LEG'S ACTING UP TOO.
>> IF I HAVE
A BIG, IMPORTANT JOB TO DO
THE KIND OF JOB
I'D RATHER NOT DO
I HAVE A LITTLE TRICK
AND I'LL TEACH IT TO YOU
TO MAKE THE JOB GO
BOPPITY BOO
WALK AWAY, WALK AWAY
LEAVE THE DAMN JOB
FOR ANOTHER DAY
CUT YOURSELF SOME SLACK
HAVE A COLD ONE, HAVE A NAP
ANY JOB THAT'S URGENT
WILL BE THERE
WHEN YOU GET BACK
JUST TELL YOUR BOSS YOU'RE
NOT SUFFICIENTLY MOTIVATED
TO ACCEPT
THIS PARTICULAR CHALLENGE
ANYWAY, IF IT WAS A GOOD JOB
THERE WOULDN'T BE ANY WORK
CONNECTED TO IT
WOULD THERE?
>> OOH!
>> YOU CAN ALWAYS TELL
WHEN BILL DROPS BY,
BECAUSE YOU'RE USUALLY
IN A LOT OF PAIN.
YOU ALWAYS HURT
THE ONE YOU LOVE, AND BILL
MUST BE CRAZY ABOUT ME.
ANYWAY, WHAT HAPPENED WAS,
HIS ROPE WAS HOOKED
ON A TREE THERE.
WHAT HE WAS GOING TO SHOW US
TODAY WAS SOMETHING ABOUT TRAPS
AND SNARES AND EVERYTHING.
THIS IS ACTUALLY
AN OFFICIAL TRAP.
I THINK THIS IS FOR RACCOONS
OR WHATEVER.
YOU OPEN THE ONE END, AND
I THINK THE ANIMAL GOES IN,
AND THEN WHEN HE GOES IN IT--
BUT BILL'S GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
YOU CAN MAKE YOUR OWN TRAPS.
FIRST OF ALL, HE'S LOOKING
FOR TRACKS OF ANIMALS.
UH, HE FOUND SOMETHING.
YEP, YEP.
ANIMALS HAVE BEEN HERE.
SO THIS IS A GOOD PLACE
TO BUILD A TRAP.
NOW HE STICKS THREE LITTLE
STICKS IN THE GROUND, AND HE
WRAPS THIS LITTLE--LITTLE LINE
AROUND THEM.
I DON'T KNOW WHETHER
THIS IS MAYBE
TO HOOK ONTO THEIR LEG OR--
I WASN'T QUITE SURE.
HE DIDN'T EXPLAIN.
DIDN'T TIE THAT KNOT REAL WELL,
EITHER.
AND THEN HE PULLS THIS DOWN
AND--
>> OOH!
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL,
WHAT HE NEEDS IS A TREE
THAT MAYBE HAS A LITTLE MORE--
A LITTLE MORE SPRING TO IT
THAN THAT.
WELL, I GUESS--HE PICKED ONE.
YEAH, MM-HMM, MM-HMM.
SO HE PULLS THIS TREE DOWN.
WE'RE GONNA USE THIS,
AND THIS IS GOING TO BE LIKE
THE SPRING TO MAKE THE--
AND THIS THING REALLY--
THERE WAS A LOT OF PULL TO THEM
AND TOOK BOTH OF US
WITH BOTH HANDS GOING.
AND THEN HE WANTED ME
TO TIE THE ROPE ON,
BUT, YOU KNOW, TO TIE
THE ROPE ON, I HAD TO--I HAD
TO LET GO OF THE BRANCH,
WHICH MEANT I WASN'T HOLDING
THE BRANCH DOWN,
AND THEN IT WAS JUST--
>> [yelling]
>> WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
OH!
>> [crying]
>> SO I THOUGHT MAYBE HE WANTED
TO USE THIS TREE NOW.
HE'LL NEVER GET THAT ONE
BENT DOWN.
BUT, NO, HE HAD--
NO, HE HAD SOMETHING--
GONNA TRY SOMETHING ELSE,
GONNA TRY SOMETHING ELSE.
YEAH, YEAH.
NOW, THIS ONE WAS REALLY
SOMETHING.
HE PUT A LITTLE KNIFE IN THERE,
AND THAT BECOMES, I THINK--
I BELIEVE THEY CALL THAT
THE FULCRUM.
AND THEN HE HOOKED THAT
ONTO A LITTLE TWIG--
OR MAYBE THERE WAS A NAIL
IN THAT TREE FROM SOME SORT OF
A PREVIOUS PARTY WE'D HAD--
AND THEN UP TO--I THINK
HE CALLED THAT THE TRIGGER.
I WAS GETTING A LITTLE CONFUSED
AT THIS POINT.
HE HAD A LOOP TIED IN THE ROPE.
THEN HE GOT ME TO PICK UP
THIS LOG.
I BELIEVE IT WEIGHED 250 POUND
OR SO, 'CAUSE IT WAS FULL OF
WATER AND STUFF.
NOW, BILL WENT DOWN TO HOOK UP
THE LEG PART, AND I WAS TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT
HOW THIS WOULD WORK.
YOU KNOW, I GUESS THE IDEA IS
THAT THE ANIMAL IS SUPPOSED TO
TRIGGER IN THAT LOCK,
'CAUSE I COULDN'T FIGURE OUT
HOW THE LOG WOULD DO IT
AND FALL, BUT...
>> OOH!
>> IT WORKED.
SO THEN WHAT HE WANTED TO DO
WAS THIS--THIS IS--THIS ONE
I SAW WAS REALLY TERRIFIC.
HE KNOCKED OFF ALL THE LITTLE
BRANCHES AND TWIGS ON THIS
BRANCH THAT WAS STICKING OUT.
AND THEN WHAT HE DID WAS,
HE TOOK HIS KNIFE,
WHICH IS A PRETTY SERIOUS
INSTRUMENT THERE,
AND HE TIED THAT AROUND
THE END OF THE BRANCH,
AND HE TIED HER ON PRETTY GOOD.
MAYBE NOT QUITE AS GOOD AS MAYBE
HE SHOULD HAVE,
BUT HE HAD THAT ON THERE.
AND THEN WHAT HE DOES IS,
HE BACKS THAT UP.
AND AGAIN THE SPRING
IN THESE TREES IS UNBELIEVABLE.
IT WAS A GREEN TREE
AND LOT OF FORCE THERE.
HE WAS TRYING TO HOOK IT ONTO
SOMETHING, YOU KNOW,
WITH HIS FOOT THEN SLIPPED
AND THEN--
LOOK OUT. LOOK OUT. LOOK OUT.
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
I WASN'T REAL HAPPY WITH THAT,
SO I DECIDED TO MAKE KIND OF
A TRAP ALL OF MY OWN.
I ASKED BILL JUST TO STAND THERE
BY THE TREE
AND KIND OF LOOK LIKE BAIT.
AND THEN I WOULD--
THIS IS KIND OF THE MAYPOLE
STYLE OF ANIMAL TRAP.
AND THE BEAUTY OF THIS IS THAT
YOU DON'T HAVE TO COME BACK
AND CHECK IT.
SEE YOU LATER, BILL.
"IT IS WINTER.
TOES ARE NUMB FROM THE COLD,
LIKE A FAMILY OF ICE CUBES
SHIVERING BESIDE
THEIR BIG FAT MOTHER.
FROZEN TOES SCREAMING
IN QUIET PAIN, BUT NO MATTER
HOW SORE THEY GET,
I'M NOT PUTTING THEM
IN MY MOUTH."
WELL, HAROLD, I GUESS BY NOW
YOU'VE DISCOVERED GIRLS, HUH?
>> NO, I DIDN'T DISCOVER THEM.
THEY BEEN AROUND A LONG TIME
BEFORE ME.
>> NO, I MEAN--I MEAN, YOU'RE
STARTING TO GET INTERESTED
IN GIRLS.
>> OH, YEAH.
[laughs]
THAT'S PUTTING IT MILDLY.
I'M SWIMMING IN HORMONES.
I'M SWIMMING IN THEM, UNCLE RED.
I'M DROWNING IN THEM, AND
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> WEAR A SNORKEL.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> I'M NOT REALLY SURE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, HAROLD,
YOU KNOW.
THERE'S GONNA COME A TIME
PRETTY SOON
WHEN YOU'RE GONNA REALIZE
THERE'S A LOT MORE TO LIFE
THAN THINKING ABOUT SEX.
>> OH, GOOD.
WHEN DOES THAT TIME COME,
UNCLE RED?
>> WELL, I'M TOLD
IT'S JUST IN THOSE FEW MINUTES
BEFORE YOU DIE.
NO ONE REALLY KNOWS.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK
TO END THE WELL-DIGGING SAGA.
>> AND I'LL BE HERE
TO PROTECT YOUR INTERESTS.
REST EASY, COMPADRES.
>> WE'RE OUT HERE WITH
MY GOOD BUDDY DOUGIE FRANKLIN
AND WHAT HAS TO BE
ONE OF THE LARGEST
FOUR-WHEELED VEHICLES
IN THIS COUNTRY, I BELIEVE.
>> WELL, THAT MEANS A LOT
COMING FROM YOU, RED.
IT REALLY DOES.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, SHE'S MORE
THAN A TRUCK TO ME.
SHE'S--SHE'S A WIFE.
SHE'S A WIFE AND KIDS.
A WIFE, KIDS, AND FAMILY,
AS WELL AS A JOB.
SHE'S A WIFE, KID, FAMILY,
A JOB, AND FRIENDS.
SHE'S MY FRIEND.
THIS TRUCK'S MY LIFE.
>> I COULDN'T HELP BUT NOTICE
THAT YOU CALLED HER "SHE," DOUG.
WHY IS THAT?
>> WELL, ACTUALLY, RED, THAT'S--
THAT'D BE ONE OF YOUR OLD
NAVY-TYPE TERMS, AND I WAS
IN THE NAVY THERE FOR ABOUT--
WELL, WELL, IT WASN'T REALLY
THE NAVY.
IT WAS NAVAL RESERVE.
I WAS IN THERE
FOR ABOUT THREE WEEKS.
WELL, IT WAS TWO AND A HALF.
I JUST ROUNDED HER OFF SOME.
ANYWAY, I'M THINKING ON CHANGING
THE OIL RIGHT ABOUT NOW,
IF YOU WANT TO STICK AROUND.
>> I SAW YOU HAD THE--I SAW
YOU HAD THE--SAW YOU HAD
THE HOOD OFF.
>> YEAH, YEAH, I DID.
WELL, YOU GOT TO DO THAT
TO CHANGE THE OIL.
>> YEAH.
>> IF YOU COULD JUST GET--HELP
GIVE ME A BOOST UP THERE, I'M
NOT AS AGILE AS I USED TO BE.
JUST HOLD YOUR HAND LIKE THAT,
AND I'LL JUST USE THAT
AS, LIKE, A STEPPING THING.
THERE YOU GO.
JUST WIPE YOUR HANDS OFF.
DON'T WANT TO GRIND ANYTHING
INTO HER.
OKAY, YOU READY?
>> UP YOU GO.
OH, SORRY.
YEAH, YOU GOT HER?
>> BOY, YOU'RE--YOU BEEN
WORKING OUT THERE, RED?
OKAY.
NOW LET'S JUST HAVE A LOOK.
>> SHE--SHE BURN A LOT OF OIL
THERE, DOUGIE?
>> WELL, RED, NO, BUT, YOU KNOW,
SHE LEAKS A BIT.
FOUND THAT OUT THE OTHER NIGHT
WHEN I SLEPT UNDER HER.
>> DO YOU GET A LOT OF
NOSEBLEEDS SITTING UP THAT HIGH
THERE, DOUG?
YOU'RE UP THERE.
[laughs]
>> NO, I DON'T.
WHY WOULD YOU ASK THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WELL, LOOK, DO YOU WANT
TO PASS ME THAT OIL CAN?
I'M LOOKING HERE, AND I THINK
SHE'S DOWN A BIT.
SHE'S GOT A BIT OF A THIRST
ON HER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
YOU GONNA TOP HER UP, HUH?
>> YEAH, SURE, YOU KNOW.
TO STAY ON TOP OF THIS,
IT'S A FULL-TIME JOB.
KEEP HER IN A-1 CONDITION.
IT'S LIKE THEM FELLERS YOU SEE
THAT--THAT PAINT THAT
GOLDEN GATE BRIDGE, YOU KNOW.
THEY'RE NO SOONER DONE
PAINTING HER
THEN THEY GOT TO START
ALL OVER AGAIN, YOU KNOW?
BUT OH!
THAT LAST BIG EARTHQUAKE,
SHE'S STILL STANDING,
SO IF YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT I'M SAYING...
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> GOOD.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, WE'RE JUST GONNA
TOP HER OFF.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
FILL HER UP THERE.
>> YOU GOT TO BE CAREFUL,
YOU KNOW.
YOU GET OIL ON HERE, AND BEFORE
YOU KNOW IT, YOU GOT A FIRE,
WHICH IS WHAT WE GOT IN
CASTORVILLE THERE THAT ONE TIME.
>> YEAH, I--I READ ABOUT THAT.
WELL, DOUG,
HEY, BEST OF LUCK TO YOU.
AND, GOSH, SHE'S LOOKING GREAT
HERE.
>> YEP, NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
SHE IS LOOKING GOOD.
>> LOOKING REAL GOOD.
LOOKING REAL GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S DOUGIE FRANKLIN THERE
AND HIS BIG, BIG, BIG, BIG, BIG,
BIG, BIG, BIG, BIG TRUCK.
YOU GOT A NAME FOR HER, DOUGIE?
>> YEAH, WE CALL HER IMELDA.
>> IMELDA?
GOD, THAT'S PERFECT, ISN'T IT?
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
MAKE ME SICK.
POOR OLD STINKY WAS OUT THERE
DIGGING THE WELL, JUST DIGGING
AND DIGGING AND DIGGING
A LONG TIME.
I MEAN, HE CUT THROUGH
HYDRO LINES,
HE CUT THROUGH GAS LINES,
AND THEN HE COME UP WITH A ROCK
THERE THAT WAS ABOUT THE SIZE
OF MOOSE THOMPSON'S HEAD
AND ABOUT THE SAME WEIGHT
AND VERY SIMILAR IN COMPLEXION.
THEN AFTER ABOUT 12 HOURS,
HE SAYS HE THOUGHT HE WAS GONNA
STRIKE WATER AT ANY MOMENT,
WHICH IS A REAL DUMB THING
TO SAY AROUND MEN WHO'VE BEEN
DRINKING BEER ALL DAY.
LUCKILY, THEIR AIM WAS OFF.
BUT AROUND 3:00 IN THE MORNING,
I GUESS IT WAS, STINKY FINALLY
HIT WATER, BUT WHEN WE SHONE
THE FLASHLIGHT DOWN,
WHAT HAD HAPPENED WAS,
HE'D GONE SO FAR OFF COURSE
THAT HE HAD GONE
INTO THE OLD WELL SHAFT.
SO WE JUST THREW DOWN
A REPLACEMENT WASHER,
AND HE FIXED THE FOOT VALVE.
EVERYTHING WAS PERFECT, SO IT
WORKED OUT GREAT, BUT--STINKY
WASN'T ALL THAT PLEASED,
BUT, YOU KNOW, HE HAS
THAT LOGIC PROBLEM THING.
ANYWAY, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME,
BUT THE BRIDGE IS OUT
ON THE NUMBER TWO SIDE ROAD,
SO I MAY BE A LITTLE BIT
LATER, 'CAUSE I HAVE TO TAKE
THE EXPRESSWAY.
ANYWAY,
THANKS AGAIN FOR WATCHING,
AND ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT THE LODGE,
UNTIL NEXT TIME,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.