(Tires screeching)
(Motor revving)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE HE IS, A SELF-EDUCATED MAN
WHO'S A LIVING TESTIMONIAL TO
WHY YOU SHOULD STAY IN SCHOOL,
MY UNCLE, YOUR HERO, RED GREEN!
(Laughing)
(Applause)
(Cheering)
(Whistling)
HOW YOU DOING, HAROLD?
THANK YOU.
I WAS WALKING AROUND DOWNTOWN.
RALPHIE'S GAS STATION IS GONE. OKAY?
IT'S BEEN REPLACED
BY A CONVENIENCE STORE/
BANKING MACHINE/VIDEO OUTLET.
RALPHIE COULDN'T MAKE MONEY
IN THE GASOLINE BUSINESS.
WOW, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE,
UNCLE RED.
EVERYTHING AROUND HERE
RUNS ON GAS,
INCLUDING MOST
OF THE LODGE MEMBERS.
BOY, HE SOLD HUNDREDS OF
GALLONS TO YOU GUYS EVERY WEEK.
TO BE HONEST, A LOT OF GUYS
WERE TAKING GAS
FROM THE SELF-SERVE
AND NOT PAYING FOR IT.
RALPHIE'S PUMPS
AREN'T SELF-SERVE.
THEY ARE
AT 3:00
IN THE MORNING.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): RANGER GORD IS WOUND UP
JUST A LITTLE TOO TIGHT,
I'LL GRIND A BIG HOLE
IN THE POSSUM VAN,
GARTH HARBLE'S GOT SOMETHING
IN THE ATTIC,
BUT IT'S NOT WORTH MUCH,
AND WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
GOES ON AND ON AND ON...
WATCH YOUR ALLERGIES, HAROLD.
I MIGHT HAVE SPILLED GASOLINE
ON MYSELF.
DON'T COME NEAR ME!
OR THE STOVE.
I'M PARTICULARLY ALLERGIC
TO HUMAN TORCHES.
YOU TRY SOMETHING,
WHERE DOES IT GET YOU?
WE WANTED TO RUN A PIPELINE
FROM THE GAS STATION
IN PORT ASBESTOS TO THE LODGE.
IT'S DOWNHILL ALL THE WAY.
THE GOVERNMENT STEPS IN.
SAYS IT'S ILLEGAL TO RUN
GASOLINE THROUGH EAVESTROUGHS.
I'M NOT SURE HOW LONG THE DUCT
TAPE WOULD HAVE HELD, ANYWAY.
WELL, MAYBE
I'M GLAD
WE HAVE A GOVERNMENT.
(Audience laughing)
I KNOW I'M GLAD
WE HAVE A FIRE DEPARTMENT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU HEARD,
BUT THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
THOSE BATHTUBS
WERE PORCELAIN.
THERE WASN'T A LEAKY ONE
IN THE BUNCH.
WHOA! WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
OH, WELL, WE HAD A BUNCH
OF BATHTUBS ON A FLAT-BED
UP TO PORT ASBESTOS AND
WE FILLED THEM WITH GAS AND...
IT DIDN'T GO REAL WELL.
PERHAPS THEY WERE
A LITTLE *TOO* FULL?
NOT AFTER THE FIRST CORNER.
THE REAL PROBLEM HIT
WHEN JUNIOR SINGLETON
FLICKED HIS FLAMING BUTT
OUT THE WINDOW...
AND THEN HIS LIT CIGARETTE OUT.
NO, NO, NO, I GOT THOSE
IN THE WRONG ORDER.
(Applause)
(Red): BILL'S SOLUTION
TO BEING OUT OF GAS
IS TO FIND ANOTHER MODE
OF TRANSPORTATION.
HE'S GOING BACK TO
THE OLD WEST, THE OLD COWBOY.
THAT'S A REAL
LOVELY HORSE, BILL,
BUT HE'S NOT A QUALITY--
HE'S GOT A CHAW OF TOBACCO--
OH, HE'S GONNA DO
THE SPITTOON THING.
OH, BY GOLLY.
THIS IS-- YOU KNOW, BILL--
OH, CAREFUL, THERE.
OH, YOU'RE FINE.
(Laughing)
SPRING CAME EARLY THIS YEAR.
AND HE'S GONNA FIRE THAT
INTO THE PAIL.
OK, BILL, GET A BIG CHAW.
GET A MAN-SIZED--
OH.
OH, BY GOLLY.
UH, BILL?
NO, NO, YOU MISSED ON THAT.
YOU'LL FIND IT OVER...
IT'S OVER IN THAT AREA.
IT'S FUNNY, EH?
HE'LL BE BACK LATER.
SHE SCRIMPED AND SAVED
FOR TWO YEARS TO BUY THAT CAR.
SHE DID NOT GIVE YOU PERMISSION
TO DRIVE IT,
BUT YOU HAD TO GO BEHIND HER
BACK AND TAKE IT FOR A DRIVE.
YOU HAD TO GO
TO THE LUMBER YARD
AND YOU HAD TO BUY
TWO SHEETS OF DRYWALL
AND YOU HAD TO CRAM THEM
INTO THAT TINY HATCHBAC.
AND YOU HAD TO RIP
THE UPHOLSTERY IN THE ROOF.
NOW WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA TELL HER?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TELL HER
ANYTHING, NOT YET.
FIRST, YOU'RE GONNA DITCH
THAT DRYWALL.
YOU GET BACK IN THAT CAR,
DRIVE OVER TO HER NEPHEWS'.
YOU KNOW THE ONES.
THOSE ROTTEN LITTLE CHILDREN
OF SATAN.
YOU'RE GONNA TAKE THEM OUT
AND BUY THEM ICE CREAM
AND CHOCOLATE AND POP.
ESPECIALLY CHOCOLATE.
AND MAKE SURE THEY SPEND
AT LEAST AN HOUR
INSIDE THE CAR.
WHEN THOSE THREE HYENAS
ARE DONE,
YOUR RIP IN THE ROOF'S GONNA
LOOK LIKE AN AFTERTHOUGHT.
YOU'RE OFF THE HOOK.
HOW CAN SHE BLAME YOU?
YOU WERE TRYING TO BE NICE
TO
HER
NEPHEWS.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT
THEY'RE ROTTEN,
DESTRUCTIVE SOCIOPATHS.
THEY'RE FAMILY.
RIGHT!
(Applause)
(Strums acoustic guitar)
LYING ON THE BOATHOUSE,
STARIN' AT THE STARS
NO NOISE, NO HORN,
NO EXHAUST
AT LEAST, NONE OF IT
FROM CARS, RIGHT?
I DON'T LET ANYONE
UP HERE
IT'S MY OWN
PRIVATE LITTLE NEST
BUT NOW THAT
I'VE THROWN MY BACK OUT
AND I'M PRETTY MUCH
PARALYSED
FROM THE EYEBROWS DOWN
I'M VALUING PRIVACY
LESS AND LESS
OH!
DON'T BELIEVE WHAT YOU READ
IN THE NEWSPAPERS.
THE REASON WE HAVE
A FUEL SHORTAGE IS
BECAUSE OUR GAS TANKS
AREN'T BIG ENOUGH.
THIS WEEK IN "HANDYMAN CORNER",
I'M GONNA PUT A MAN-SIZE
GAS TANK INTO THE POSSUM VAN.
ORIGINALLY, I WAS THINKING
I'D POP IN THIS UNIT,
BUT I DON'T THINK
THIS WILL DO THE JOB.
IT WON'T HOLD ENOUGH GAS
TO COVER OFF
THE GAS MILEAGE PROBLEM
I HAVE WITH THE VAN.
I COULD CHANGE THE PLUGS
AND POINTS,
BUT I DON'T WANT
TO GET INTO THAT.
INSTEAD, WHAT I NEED IS
A GAS TANK THE SAME SIZE
AS THE WHOLE VAN.
ONCE I FILL THIS UNIT UP
WITH GASOLINE,
I NEED SOME WAY TO GET GAS
INTO THE REAL GAS TANK
TO GO UP INTO THE ENGINE.
NO PROBLEM --
HACK A HOLE IN THE FLOOR
AND LET GRAVITY DO THE WORK.
NOW, BEFORE WE START THROWING
A COUPLE OF THOUSAND GALLONS
INTO THIS UNIT,
YOU WANT TO PLUG UP ANYWHERE
THAT GASOLINE MIGHT SEEP OUT.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE DRIVING
WITH THE GAS
ROARING OUT OF HER...
NOT AT TODAY'S PRICES.
I'VE GONE DOWN THE DASHBOARD,
COVERED UP WHEREVER I THOUGHT
GASOLINE MIGHT LEAK --
THE HEADLIGHTS SWITCH,
THE WINDSHIELD WASHERS.
I'VE GOT THE HEATER VENT
CLOSED UP.
DO EXTRA DUCT TAPE
AROUND THE DIMMER SWITCH.
I KNOW THE FLOOR'S
KIND OF RUSTY THERE.
BUT THAT SHOULD HOLD HER,
AND DO IT PROPERLY.
YOU KNOW, THAT WILL TAKE YOU
MAYBE 10 TO 15 MINUTES
TO DO IT RIGHT, YOU KNOW?
ONCE YOU'VE DONE THAT,
YOU'VE GOTTA DO THE WINDOWS
AND THE DOORS
AND ALL THE RUST HOLES.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT IS ONE TIGHT-SEALED VAN.
ALL'S I HAVE TO DO IS GO
TO THE FILL-UP STATION
AND LOAD 'ER UP
WITH A YEAR-AND-A-HALF'S SUPPLY
OF GASOLINE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND--
OH, GOLLY.
ALL RIGHT, OK, RE-THINK.
THE MARK OF A TRUE HANDYMAN IS
HIS ABILITY TO ADAPT
TO CHANGING CONDITIONS.
SAFETY REGULATIONS,
THAT KIND OF THING.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO HERE?
MAYBE A SNORKEL UNIT
OF SOME KIND OR...
MAYBE RADIO CONTROL...
I KNOW!
YOU KNOW THE FLYING BRIDGE,
LIKE THEY HAVE
ON CABIN CRUISERS?
YEAH, I'LL MOVE
THE WHOLE DASHBOARD UNIT
UP ONTO THE ROOF AND...
OK, NO, NO, NO.
GONNA NEED A WHOLE NEW
DASHBOARD UNIT.
OH, OH, OH, OH!
THIS HAS TO BE GOOD NEWS
FOR ALL YOU SMALL-CAR OWNERS
OUT THERE.
I'VE HOOKED EVERYTHING UP
TO RUN THE UNIT.
I DUCT-TAPED HER ON.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO WELD IT.
I'D SUGGEST YOU DO YOUR WELDING
BEFORE YOU FILL THE VAN
WITH GASOLINE.
KEEP AN EYE OUT
FOR THE MAXIMUM HEIGHT
ON THE LOW BRIDGES AND SO ON.
(Starting engine)
LET'S GIVE HER A TEST DRIVE.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
(Honking "Shave And A Haircut,
Two Bits")
(Red): STAY TUNED FOR RANGER GORD
PRETENDING HE'S A TREE.
HE'S GOT TO EXAGGERATE
HIS I.Q.
ANY DAY NOW,
YOU'LL BE SHAVING
OR SCRAPING PIZZA CHUNKS
OFF YOUR FOREHEAD.
YOU'LL LOOK IN THE MIRROR
AND SEE THAT YOUR FACE
IS COVERED WITH WRINKLES.
ALL AROUND YOUR MOUTH,
YOUR EYES, UP OVER YOUR EARS.
WHEN YOU FURROW YOUR BROW,
LOOKS LIKE A RUMP ROAST
MADE OUT OF CORDUROY.
(Audience laughing)
WRINKLES IS CAUSED
BY ONE THING ONLY.
YOU GOT TOO MUCH SKIN.
YOU GO TO A COSMETIC SURGEON,
THEY'RE HAPPY
TO CUT THE SKIN OFF FOR YOU,
OR IF YOU'RE ON A BUDGET,
I GUESS YOU COULD
DUCT-TAPE WIRES TO THE SKIN
AND THEN TIGHTEN IT
WITH A LITTLE WINCH
HIDDEN IN YOUR HAT.
HERE'S A SIMPLE WAY TO GET RID
OF WRINKLES -- PUT ON WEIGHT.
(Audience laughing)
OH, YEAH, YOU JUST EAT
AND EAT AND EAT
UNTIL YOU FILL UP
ALL THAT EXTRA SKIN.
YOU SEE, MOTHER NATURE
GAVE YOU THAT SKIN,
THINKING YOU'D BE
A LOT FATTER BY NOW.
DON'T LET HER DOWN.
IT'S JUST THAT SIMPLE.
FAT IS THE SAFEST
AND SIMPLEST CURE FOR WRINKLES.
YOU EVER SEE A WRINKLED PIG?
NO, SIR.
FILL YOUR FACE EVERY DAY,
AND ONE DAY,
WHEN YOUR HEART EXPLODES,
AND YOUR FRIENDS ARE LEANING
OVER YOUR EXTRA-WIDE COFFIN,
THEY'LL COMMENT
ON HOW YOUNG YOU LOOK.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause and cheering)
RANGER GORD IS GONNA TEACH US
HOW TO AVOID BEING ATTACKED
BY GRIZZLY BEARS.
THAT'S RIGHT, RED.
IN THE 16 YEARS I'VE BEEN
MANNING FIREWATCH TOWER 13,
I'VE NEVER ONCE BEEN MAULED
BY A BEAR.
I'VE BEEN ATTACKED BY FOXES
AND WOLVES AND DEER
AND ELK AND BADGERS
AND SQUIRRELS.
A HUMMINGBIRD
WILL GIVE A GOOD NIP.
OH, AND THAT CHIPMUNK SCAR
IS JUST STARTING TO HEAL.
NO, WE DON'T NEED TO SEE THAT.
I'VE NEVER ONCE -- NOT ONCE --
BEEN MAULED BY A BEAR.
WHY DO YOU THINK THAT IS?
GOOD SENSE, I WOULD SAY.
NO.
NO WAY.
NO, CAMOUFLAGE, OK?
NOW, BEARS LIKE TO EAT FISH
AND GRUB,
SO I NEVER EVER DRESS UP
LIKE A FISH OR A GRUB, OK?
AS MUCH AS I'D LIKE TO
SOMETIMES, I AVOID IT.
I DRESS UP LIKE A TREE.
NOW, THESE ARE ASH BRANCHES,
AND AN ASH LOOKS LIKE THIS.
SEE THAT?
YEAH.
I'M AN ASH.
TOOK THE WORDS
RIGHT OUT OF MY MOUTH.
YOU HOLD THE BRANCHES
LIKE THIS, LIKE THIS,
OR EVEN AS MUCH AS THIS,
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO FOOL
A RABBIT, LET ALONE A BEAR.
THE KEY TO DRESSING UP
LIKE A TREE IS THE SHAPE.
ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU, GORD.
NO, WAIT.
I HAVE ANOTHER ONE.
THIS IS MY FAVOURITE,
SO IF YOU'D HOLD THAT...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
HOLD IT IN YOUR FINGERS.
HERE WE GO -- WATCH THIS.
OK, OK, OH, YEAH.
ISN'T THIS FUN?
OH, MY GOSH!
WATCH THIS.
THIS MUST BE MY FAVOURITE.
IT MUST BE.
THERE, OK?
YEAH.
WHAT AM I?
DON'T ASK ME QUESTIONS
LIKE THAT, GORD.
I'M A WHITE BIRCHBARK.
YOU SEE THAT?
YOU DIDN'T RECOGNIZE ME.
NO.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
ABOUT THE SAME AS ALWAYS.
OH, YEAH?
GAS FUMES GETTING TO YOU,
ARE THEY, HAROLD?
WELL... THAT WAS CLEAN
WHEN I PUT IT ON.
THE WHOLE TOWN'S GOING
THAT WAY.
PEOPLE WEARING DISGUISES
SO THEY CAN STEAL GAS
FROM EACH OTHER,
AND PEOPLE HOARDING
THEIR GAS SUPPLY.
A GALLON OF PREMIUM UNLEADED IS
30 BUCKS ON THE BLACK MARKET.
IF YOU BUY 10 GALLONS, YOU GET
A FREE BLACK-MARKET CAR WASH.
WE GOT A REAL ENERGY CRISIS.
IT'S LIKE THE '70's,
BUT WE DON'T GET THE FUN
OF BLAMING FOREIGNERS.
ONE GUY ORDERED A PIZZA.
WHEN THE DRIVER WENT
TO GET THE MONEY,
SOMEONE SIPHONED GAS
FROM HIS CAR.
(Audience laughing)
REALLY?
BOY, THAT'S BAD.
PEOPLE ARE PUTTING
LOCKING GAS CAPS
ON THEIR LAWN MOWERS.
I BOUGHT FIVE GALLONS OF GAS
FROM FLINTY McCLINTOCK.
TURNED OUT TO BE APPLE CIDER.
MIND YOU, THE VAN
STILL RAN PRETTY GOOD.
THE EXHAUST SMELLED
LIKE A WALDORF SALAD.
(Audience laughing)
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION.
THIS WEEK, WE HAVE TWO EXPERTS:
MY UNCLE RED
AND WINSTON ROTHSCHILD!
(Applause and cheering)
HERE'S OUR FIRST LETTER
AND IT GOES AS FOLLOWS:
"DEAR EXPERTS, MY DAD SAYS
I SHOULD STAY IN SCHOOL
"AND GET AN EDUCATION.
"I WANT TO GET OUT
AND GET MY DREAM JOB
NOW.
"WHAT DO YOU THINK?"
THAT'S NO CONTEST --
GET OUT AND GET THE JOB.
A DEGREE'S JUST
A PIECE OF PAPER.
JUST A SECOND, NOW.
THE ROAD TO A HIGHER EDUCATION
IS NOT A ONE-WAY STREET.
TAKE ME, FOR EXAMPLE.
I TOOK AN ALTERNATIVE ROUTE.
AFTER I QUIT HIGH SCHOOL
AND STARTED ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES,
IT WAS AFTER THAT
THAT I GOT MY COLLEGE DEGREES,
IN MY SPARE TIME.
THERE ARE A NUMBER OF GREAT
LEARNING INSTITUTIONS
FOR ANYBODY
WHO CAN READ A MATCHBOOK COVER.
(Audience laughing)
RIGHT NOW,
I'M WORKING ON A DEGREE
FROM M.I.T.
NOT THE MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE
OF TECHNOLOGY.
NO, MURRAY'S SCHOOL OF TENNIS.
THE WAY
I SEE IT,
IF I GET MY, UH, Ph.B.
FROM MURRAY'S,
THAT WILL BE NINE IN TOTAL.
OH, YEAH --
NINE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD, Ph.B.,
LL.X., S.O.L., I.O.U.,
D.O.A., V.C.R., P.D.Q., Q.T.,
AND, OF COURSE, T. & A.
(Audience laughing)
LOOK WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YOU'RE RUNNING
A SEWAGE BUSINESS.
EDUCATION'S NOT WORTH IT --
JUST GO FOR THE JOB.
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY EDUCATION.
ALL YOU'RE DOING
IS HOSTING THIS SHOW.
YOU'RE NO BETTER THAN ME.
YOU'RE SAYING WE'RE BOTH
IN THE SEWAGE BUSINESS?
(Audience laughing)
WELL, YEAH,
BUT I TAKE IT AWAY.
(Laughing and applause)
(Cheering)
(Red): MEANWHILE, BACK
WITH BUFFALO BILL...
I MEAN...
OW, OW.
... "BUFFALO" IN THE SENSE OF
HE'S GONNA NEED WINGS
AT SOME POINT.
BILL'S GOT--
LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT.
OH, BOY.
ONE THING ABOUT GOING
TO A PLAYGROUND
WITH A FELLOW LIKE BILL,
YOU DON'T NEED TO GET INVOLVED.
KIDS, YOU STAY WELL BACK,
YOU SEE A MAN LIKE THIS.
OH, BOY.
OH, FOR GOSH--
I'M STANDING THERE,
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT HE HAS IN MIND,
THINKING THAT
IT MUST BE SOMETHING.
WHAT IS IT?
OH, YEAH, TEETER-TOTTER.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, FUNNY --
THAT'S VERY FUNNY.
I GET, AS USUAL, THE SHORT END
OF THE STICK.
I'LL SHOW YOU
WHO'S GOT THE SHORT END
OF THE WHATEVER -- OH!
SORRY, BILL -- I FEEL TERRIBLE.
(Laughing)
OH, OH, OH!
OH, OOOH, THAT SMARTS,
YOU KNOW?
HE GETS OFF IT.
(Laughing)
ALL RIGHT.
OHHH!
THESE PLAYGROUNDS ARE FUN,
AREN'T THEY?
WE GOT THAT UNIT APART
AND I GOT BILL'S HORSE.
HE MOUNTS THE WHOLE UNIT
ON THE OLD WAGON WE HAD.
STOLE SOMETHING FROM
THE HANDYMAN WORK BENCH, BILL?
WHAT ARE WE DOING HERE?
HOW'S THIS WORK, BILL?
YOU'RE GONNA SIT ON...
ALL RIGHT, HE'S GONNA SIT
ON THAT END.
THE SPRING'S ATTACHED THERE,
SO... YEAH, OK.
THE PIPE GOES DOWN HERE AND...
OH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
THE OLD RAILROAD CAR THING.
IF YOU CAN GET THIS PUMPING,
YOU DON'T NEED GAS.
YOU CAN JUST PUMP UP AND DOWN
AND THAT WILL DRIVE
THE CAR FORWARD, BUT...
IT'S GONNA BE HARD
TO GET HER STARTED, BILL.
YOU CAN'T JUST... WHAT?
OH, I'LL GIVE IT A PUSH.
ALL RIGHT, FAIR ENOUGH.
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES.
THESE KIDS THAT DON'T
CLEAN UP THEIR ROOM.
OH, IT'S THE HORSE.
THE HORSE CAN DRIVE.
BACK I GO AND GIVE HER
A LITTLE PUSH.
HE'LL BE ABLE TO...
(Squeaking)
SOME GREASE MIGHT HAVE BEEN
AN IDEA.
SLOWLY UP AND DOWN.
THIS ISN'T GONNA GET
LOTS OF SPEED,
BUT THERE YOU GO.
THERE YOU ARE, THAT'S WORKING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HE DOES
AT A HILL, BUT YOU KNOW,
WE LEFT THE KEY TURNED ON
AND BY GOLLY
IF SHE DIDN'T START UP.
(Laughing)
THAT PICKED THINGS UP
A LITTLE BIT.
WITH THE BOUNCING, THE HORSE
FELL ON THE GAS PEDAL
AND THAT REALLY
PICKED THINGS UP, RIGHT, BILL?
OH, BOY, OH, BOY!
WE LOST ONE!
MAN OVERBOARD!
BILL, THE CAR, THE CAR--
BILL, THE CAR.
OH, OH, OH... OOOOH!
WOW! OHHH!
BOY!
HE LOOKS GOOD
WITH A PIPE, DOESN'T HE?
YOU ALL RIGHT, BILL?
WOW.
STAY TUNED FOR GARTH.
HE'S BEEN ATTACKED
BY A PORCUPINE.
I LIKE THE WAY GUYS ARE DEALING
WITH THE GASOLINE SHORTAGE.
WE'RE MAKING VEHICLES BURN
LESS GAS.
TAKING THE PASSENGER SEAT
WON'T SAVE ANY WEIGHT.
NO PASSENGER SEAT
MEANS NO PASSENGER.
WITHOUT YOU THERE BESIDE ME,
NOT ONLY WILL I GET
WHERE I'M GOING,
I'LL ARRIVE IN A BETTER MOOD.
(Audience laughing)
THAT WOULD MAKE
A DANDY RECLINER
ONCE I WASH THE DR. PEPPER OUT.
IT'S GOOD YOU GUYS ARE USING
LESS FOSSIL FUEL.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE THE EXTRA
WEIGHT YOU WERE CARRYING.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
OH!
I MEANT YOUR VEHICLE.
YEAH... OH!
YOU KNOW, THE BUNCH OF US
HAVE MADE A WAGER
TO SEE WHO CAN GO THE FARTHEST
ON THE LEAST GAS,
SO WE'RE CUTTING THE WEIGHT
DOWN ON OUR VEHICLES.
JUST TAKE OUT THE DUPLICATION.
ALL'S YOU NEED ON ANY CAR
IS ONE HEADLIGHT,
ONE MIRROR, ONE WINDOW,
ONE SEAT, ONE DOOR...
ONE ACCIDENT.
(Audience laughing)
HEY, HANDYMAN, HERE'S A TIP.
YOU KNOW ALL THE DIFFERENT
GLUES ON THE MARKET?
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT KIND YOU USE.
IF YOU SPILL IT, MAKE SURE
YOU CLEAN IT UP RIGHT AWAY,
EVEN IF IT DOESN'T SAY
"QUICK-DRYING" ON THE CAN.
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL,
WITH ANOTHER IMPORTANT TIP
ON HOW YOU CAN CONTROL
YOUR ANIMALS.
COME ON IN HERE, RED.
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR ARM?
THERE YOU GO, RED.
YOU HAVE TO POINT IT OUT.
NO ONE WOULD NOTICE IF YOU
DIDN'T MAKE A THING ABOUT IT.
I THINK THEY'D NOTICE.
WHAT IS IT, ANYWAY?
WELL, PORCUPINE.
I DIDN'T THINK A PORCUPINE
COULD THROW HIS QUILLS.
HE CAN'T --
A BEAR CAN THROW A PORCUPINE.
YES, WELL...
KIDS, IF YOU LOVE ANIMALS,
AND YOU WANT TO MAKE
A LIVING AT IT,
MAKE SURE YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT ANYTHING AT ALL.
THEN GO TO
THE ANIMAL CONTROL CENTRE
AND THEY'LL MAKE YOU A BOSS.
TRY TO AVOID HAVING
ANY PERSONALITY WHATSOEVER.
GARTH, YOU HAVE
A FEATURE FOR US ON SQUIRRELS?
HUH?
SOMETHING ABOUT SQUIRRELS.
WHAT?
SQUIRRELS.
OH, YEAH, YES, SQUIRRELS.
IF YOU'RE GONNA TRY
TO CATCH SQUIRRELS, MAKE SURE
YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING EDIBLE
IN YOUR POCKETS.
DON'T ASK HOW I KNOW THAT.
GOT ANOTHER TIP
ABOUT SQUIRRELS.
DON'T TRY TO CATCH THEM AT ALL.
THEY'RE NOT NICE ANIMALS.
THEY'RE JUST RATS
WITH A HAIRDO.
I GOT A NEST OF SQUIRRELS
IN MY ATTIC,
SO WHAT I'VE DONE IS
I'VE STUFFED
ALL THE ATTIC HOLES
WITH THIS SCREEN RIGHT HERE,
SO THAT SHOULD TAKE CARE
OF THE PROBLEM.
HOW DID YOU CHASE
THE SQUIRRELS OUT
BEFORE YOU PUT THE SCREEN UP?
HOW DO YOU MEAN?
OH, BOY.
YOU'VE PROBABLY TRAPPED
THOSE SQUIRRELS IN THERE.
(Squirrels chittering)
I'LL TAKE THE SCREEN DOWN
FOR YOU.
YEAH, OK, WELL, MAKE SURE
YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING EDIBLE
IN YOUR POCKETS.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, ANOTHER SUPER DAY.
SORRY.
I HOPE THAT WAS A COIN
OR SOMETHING.
NICE WORK, HAROLD.
WELL, GOOD NIGHT,
EVERYBODY.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, SIR.
WE'RE GONNA TELL 'EM
WHAT HAPPENED.
OUR MOST-FUEL-EFFICIENT
VEHICLE THING, THAT WENT FINE.
THEN MR. CONSCIENCE FIGURES
HE'LL STICK HIS NOSE IN.
I ONLY SAID
HONESTY'S THE BEST POLICY.
YOU FORCED US TO GO
TO RALPHIE'S
AND ADMIT
WE'D BEEN STEALING GAS
AND OFFER TO PAY WHAT WE OWED
IF HE WENT BACK TO BEING
A GAS STATION.
A SUGGESTION,
THAT'S ALL IT WAS.
WELL, HERE'S THE KICKER.
HE'D NEVER NOT BEEN
A GAS STATION.
HE EXPANDED TO BE
A CONVENIENCE STORE, TOO.
THE GAS PUMPS WERE THERE,
BEHIND THE CHIPS, MAPS,
KEY FOBS, AND CARPETING.
HOW COME GAS STATIONS
HAVE TO BE DEPARTMENT STORES?
YOU SHOULD BE HAPPY
THAT THE GAS SHORTAGE IS OVER.
YOU MADE US TELL THE TRUTH
FOR NOTHING.
THAT'S A CARDINAL SIN.
YOU'D UNDERSTAND
IF YOU WERE MARRIED.
(Possum squeal)
IT'S MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
THE MEN ARE WAITING FOR YOU.
OH, OK.
OHHHH!
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I'LL GAS UP THE WEED-WHACKER.
YOU'LL SEE OUT
THE WINDOWS AGAIN.
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): ALL RISE!
ALL RISE!
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN.
EXCUSE ME FOR INTERRUPTING.
WHO RAN OVER MY HAT?
NEXT TIME, WAIT
TILL I'M OUT OF IT!