All the great chefs in
the world are men
There's the guy
with the hat
and the "Bam" guy
and the funny guy.
So I would think that most
men would like to cook.
I mean, you get
to use lots of tools
and you can eat your mistakes
or at least your dog can
and you don't have to buy
any of those fancy
kitchen gadgets,
you can use the equipment
you already have.
Like why would
you need a mixer
if you already
have a drill?
You reload your nail gun
with toothpicks...
you're ready to make
hors d'oeuvres.
Where are you going,
you weiner?
And here's a dandy,
you know they advertise
these home vacuum-packing
systems for food on T.V.
and the salesman says if you
don't get one of these
for your wife,
you're almost like a --
like a war criminal.
But hey, I already have
a vacuum cleaner.
All I got to do
is suck the air out
of the bag.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Thank you.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
No, no.
I appreciate that.
Thank you very much.
You know what this is?
These are called
Yorkshire Puddings.
I made these.
Don't worry, I haven't
crossed over or anything.
Just a little business
deal I'm working on.
Bernice and I were out at
a seafood restaurant
the other night
and wouldn't you know it,
they're out of steak.
So I got to take a walk
on the wild side
and order roast beef
and it comes with
one of these Yorkshire
Pudding deals on the side.
I thought a wasp nest had
dropped off of one of
the ceiling tiles.
You know, it's kind
of doughy on the outside,
nothing on the inside
sort of like
a lodge member.
So that's when my
entrepreneurial mind kicks in.
You know, in our town,
we got four doughnut shops,
three muffin outlets
and a bagel factory,
but so far nobody's had
the smarts to open up
a Yorkshire Pudding
drive thru.
Uncle Red?
Yeah?
Did you want
to see me?
Yeah, I need your
brain for something.
Ahh... thank you
very much.
I figure you're
not using it so...
Harold, do you know
what that is?
Oh yeah, yeah.
I've been
to a horse farm.
Harold, I made
these myself.
You must eat
a lot of oats.
It's a Yorkshire Pudding,
Harold, okay?
This is the next
big thing for me.
I've already got a retired
athlete as a spokesperson.
Oh, let me guess...
Seabiscuit?
Harold, I got
"Gump" Gorbachek.
Wow.
Wow, who's he?
He's a hockey --
He's a great
hockey player, Harold.
He's the best left-handed,
one-legged defenseman
that ever played for the
Port Asbestos Aspirators,
that's who he is.
Okay, I just thought
that a celebrity
was supposed
to be famous.
I never heard
of "Gump" Gorbachek.
Well, you probably
know him as Bob.
They call him Bob but
his real name's "Gump."
Bob?
I know that guy.
I know him.
Oh yeah, he's a big
hairy guy, no front teeth.
Yeah, they call
him "puckface."
Well, close enough
and the missing
front teeth
is one of the things
I like about him
because his smile
makes it look like
our Yorkshire Puddings
are easy to chew.
Uncle Red, you know
nothing about creating
a restaurant franchise.
I have a plan.
Oh really, and
what might that be?
My plan is to think
of something brilliant.
Never happen.
[ APPLAUSE ]
It's time for the
Possum Lodge word game!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Tonight's winner receives
this coupon for a free jar
of Farmer Dan's
Moisturizing Cream
made entirely
out of pig fat.
For women who want
their face
to be as smooth
as a football.
All right, Mike,
cover your ears.
Red, you've got 30 seconds
to get Mike Hamar
to say this word...
All right, Winston.
And go!
Okay Mike, when
you were a kid
your grandma
always needed a...
Breath mint.
Okay.
This is something
that your mother
would give you
to make you
feel better...
Rye.
Okay, no.
Okay.
What's it called when
one person wraps their arms
around another person
and holds on tight?
A citizen's arrest.
No, okay.
This is something a lot
of men would like to exchange,
but they feel
they just can't.
Wives?
All right.
Say one night you're
feeling romantic
and to get things started
you give your girlfriend a...
Twenty.
Almost out
of time here, Red.
Okay, okay Mike.
If you ever meet
your real dad,
you'll probably want
to give him one of these...
Oh, a paternity test.
Well you know,
just to be sure.
I mean the last
time I saw him
I was still
in Huggies.
Yes!
You know, if you want
to invite friends
over to your house
but it's too small
or your friends
are too large,
you've got two options.
Move to a bigger place
or put an addition
on your current one.
Now, I don't know a lot
about buying real estate...
but I do have an idea for an
addition that's fast, easy,
and best of all,
requires no construction.
That's right,
we're talking "pre-fab."
Now, "pre-fab" comes
from the Latin phrase,
"prefabricatamus."
"Pre" means "before"
and I believe "fabricatamus"
means "think things through."
So before you
think things through,
get yourself a few
rolls of duct tape
and a little imagination.
Oh yeah and a bus.
Hope you're not thinking
things through,
remember, "pre-fab."
Now, this is probably not
the ideal seating
configuration for
your guests
unless it's the playoffs
so we're going to just
rearrange the seats.
Heads up!
Glad that
wasn't my chain saw.
Fore!
Okay, after you carefully
remove the bolts
you can start
rearranging the seats.
For example, if your guests
want to stay overnight,
you need to give them
somewhere to sleep.
Oh sure, they could just
sleep on the seats,
but with a touch
of creativity,
we can give them something
a little more comfortable.
And the built-in bedsides
prevent them from falling out
and prevent you
from seeing something
you're not supposed to.
And of course, this unit
has an ensuite bathroom.
But here again
a couple of seats
placed just right
are going to give your
guests a little privacy
and prevent you
from seeing something
you really
don't want to.
Okay, as you can see,
I've put up some
classical pieces of art here,
instead of all the ads
'cause you don't
need people selling you
stuff in your own home.
Unless it's on TV,
which I fully support.
I also recommend you keep
a couple of these chrome poles
just in case an
exotic dancer drops by.
Who am I kidding?
Turn them into pole lamps.
Of course, the key
to the whole design
is to have the bus door
line up with the house door.
It makes them
separate yet together,
kind of like
Canada and Quebec.
I guess that makes
these French doors.
Oh, here's
another bonus...
Your dog can
let himself out.
And the dining area
is really spectacular.
Well, maybe not spectacular,
rectangular probably
a better word.
Here again, we just move
a bus seat here or there
line them up just so,
throw a folding table into
the centre of the configuration
and suddenly, it's not
just a dining table,
it's a booth.
And the nice thing about
eating here
is you don't have to shout
yourself hoarse calling
everybody to dinner.
Next stop, supper.
But you got to admit
this "pre-fab" addition
has a lot of
attractive features.
So remember, if the women
don't find you handsome,
they should at least
find you handy.
And here's the best part,
if you have guests arrive
who aren't particularly welcome,
you just hit the gas
and turn this addition
into a subtraction.
[ APPLAUSE ]
There's a poker craze
going on TV right now
that brings out
mixed emotions for me.
On the one hand, knowing
that millions of people
are willing to watch
six ugly, fat guys
play cards for an hour
gives me renewed hope
for the success of our show.
On the other hand,
a lot of these people
who are watching are women
and they're getting to see
something very dangerous,
men bluffing.
Pretty soon they'll
become experts
because that's
what women do.
They'll become experts
on figuring out when
men are bluffing.
And not just any man,
I'm talking about you and me.
Once our women can spot
when we're bluffing,
life as we know it
will be over.
They'll know stuff like
when we're right we
just quiet down
and let them talk themselves
into our little trap
but when we have nothing,
that's when we come out
with guns blazing.
And you can forget the tricks
you see on those poker shows.
Pulling your cowboy hat
down over your face
or wearing glasses with
eyeballs painted on them
isn't going to fool
that certain lady.
She'll read you
like a book
and book you
like a repeat offender.
Women have no sympathy
for a bluffer, so don't bluff.
I suggest you fold 'em
or you'll never
get to hold 'em.
Remember,
I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Think you're too busy
to have your septic
system serviced?
Maybe it's time to stop...
[ SNIFFS ]
and smell the hoses.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho...
Ha!
Hey, don't eat any more
of those Yorkshire
Puddings, Harold!
Deal.
They're not ready yet.
I've got to put the
chocolate glaze on them.
Oh, okay.
So how did the
press conference go?
Not real well.
That Gump sure
swears a lot.
Mind you, you know,
with the teeth missing
it's hard to tell.
But it gut so bad I had
to use the "F" word
on him.
Fired.
Well, that's too bad.
Oh boy because Gump's
Yorkshire Puddings
had such a natural ring
to it, too, didn't it?
I can see --
I can just see the logo, too.
It'd be like Gump's
big scar-ridden face
with a Yorkshire Pudding
jammed in the gap
of his smile.
Well, Harold, we got
something even better now.
You know, how they
have New York Fries,
New York Sirloin?
How about New Yorkshire
Puddings, huh?
Gives the product kind
of a New York, New York
kind of feel.
Oh yeah, if you
can eat 'em here,
you can eat
'em anywhere.
Red, Red, there's
a real bad smell
coming from the lodge.
It's like
hot sneakers or...
Well, you're right
about the hot part.
It's my new chocolate-glazed
Yorkshire Puddings.
Do you want
to try one?
Huh? Huh?
Yeah, no, yeah!
Here let me put a little
more chocolate on
that for you.
There you go,
try that?
Mmm? Yeah?
Not bad 'eh?
Not bad.
The boys have decided
to do a little
bird watching
out in the...
oh, easy, easy, easy.
Tripods and Bill are
not compatible.
So Bill and Winston had
the fancy camera gear
and Ed was a little
more lowbrow.
So they start assembling
their camera.
They're going to go off
and find the --
Ed just wanted to stay --
Let's just stay here
and let the birds come to us
but no, that
wasn't in the works.
So, yeah, go, go.
So he gets over there
and by now Bill and Winston
are starting to
assemble these telescopic
telephoto lens-type things
and Ed is, I say, going
a little lower-end on his
and they start making fun
of his but of course,
you know,
he has the flash.
So the two pros head off
into the woods
and mister amateur
falls along behind
with his disposable --
and also with his camera.
He can't see
where they're --
The trouble is they're
looking through the cameras.
They can't always see
where they're going.
Look down,
look down, Ed.
And they went right over
the edge of the cliff.
Now, Ed is planning
to help them but first,
this is a Kodak
moment, is it not?
So later that day,
Bill and Winston
are working hard and
choreographing all their moves
and all of a sudden both
of them together spot
the same bird.
Which, at this point, I
guess is a spotted owl
would it not be?
Yes, indeed.
Oh, they were pretty close.
And it's rarely seen
except for K-Mart.
So now they got a big
laugh out of it
and try the bird calls.
And he's --
No, he's getting an answer.
He's getting an --
What is that, ohhh...
Gosh.
Oh I see where
the answer is --
You're talking
to each other, bird boys.
Yeah,
that's the problem.
Meanwhile, Ed goes
back to plan A.
He just drops the
birdseed down there.
Might as well
give her the --
Yeah, go for it.
And he's got
the binoculars.
He's just gonna stay focused
on where he expects to
see some birds.
So now, they're
trying the duck calls
and they're getting
a response from --
It's like a Mallard
or something.
Oh no, it's just
another duck decoy.
Meanwhile, Ed has been gazing
in the sun too long.
He's asleep and they
spend the whole day
and do not see
one bird.
You know, one of
the downsides of the
Home Shopping Channel
is that a lot of people
are baking their own
bread these days.
Oh sure, the bread machines
can knead the dough
and bake the bread,
but can they slice it?
No.
And just ripping
the loaf in half
or biting the end off
is not acceptable if
you have company.
So what do you do?
Well, I say
don't have company,
but Bernice says otherwise.
So you do what
your ancestors did...
You get out your autoharp.
Now, the autoharp is
a traditional instrument,
very popular for the first
two weeks of August in 1963.
It looks like somebody mated
a banjo and a washboard
but it sounds like they
mated a couple of cats.
Okay, for my purposes,
I hacked the back out
of this unit.
You might wonder how I could do
that to a valuable instrument
but hey, it's Harold's.
Anyway, we don't
need an instrument,
we need a tool.
You might say this is the
greatest thing since...
Man, don't you hate
when that happens?
And for my next number,
here's a little
thing by bread.
If the women don't
find you handsome
they should at least
find you handy
Well, that's it
for today's show.
Oh no you don't!
No, no, no!
You explain to them
what happened!
You tell them.
Go, go, go!
Nobody cares, Harold.
No, of course not but no,
I think you have to go
through the experience
of confessing --
well, explaining
what went wrong
so we can all learn
from your mistakes.
Okay, well maybe not all.
I mean everybody but you.
All right, the New
Yorkshire Puddings
were not a hit.
Okay, even though we
had a great slogan,
"A Taste of New York."
Which was true, you know,
if you include the East River.
He made like
a thousand of these.
I said that was too
much for a test run.
Well, you got to prepare
for success, Harold.
Not around here,
you don't.
So, you know,
by four o'clock
we'd roughly sold...
none.
So we went
to "Plan B."
Tell them what "Plan B" was.
We sold them
as animal feed.
To what kind
of animals?
Horses.
Horses, yes!
And how did that go?
Not great.
No.
The problem was
a pile of fresh ones
look identical to
a pile of eaten ones.
This is not
helping, Harold.
It's helping me.
Anyway, we're just getting
to the good part --
Getting to the good part.
The good part?
We dumped them all
into the Possum Lake.
Yeah... And?
And they floated?
Yes!
Well, don't be shy.
The Yorkshire Puddings,
they absorbed the dangerous
layer of toxins
that have been forming
atop of Possum Lake
since shortly after
the lodge opened.
Really?
I mean, yeah?
You know what,
yeah, of course,
that was my plan,
always my plan.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Well, see your greedy little
plan to make yourself rich
resulted in you helping
clean up the environment.
That's right, Harold
and you got nothing
to be critical about.
I see nothing
to criticize.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Meeting time, Harold.
Meeting time.
Away you go.
Okay, if my
wife is watching,
I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting
and I keep getting the same
lesson over and over
in my life...
I look for the fast
and the easy
and I end up coming
home to you.
And to the rest of you,
thanks for watching.
On behalf of
myself and Harold
and the whole gang up
here at Possum Lodge,
keep your stick on the ice.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Okay guys,
everybody c'mon in.
Sit down.
Everybody sit down.
C'mon guys, take your seats.
Sit down in the back there.
Sit down.
All rise.
Quando omni flunkus moritati.
RED: Sit down.
Bow your heads
for the Man's Prayer.
I'm a man
but I can change
if I have to
I guess.
All right, men, due to some
recent developments
I am now selling my New
Yorkshire Puddings
as an environmental
cleanup initiative.
You just buy 'em
and you thrown them out.
They're only $4.95 a dozen
and I'm urging you
to think green.
I know I am.