IF YOU'VE EVER DRIVEN
OFF THE MAIN ROAD
TO AVOID COPS,
OR WHATEVER,
THEN YOU'VE PROBABLY GONE BY
SOME OLD FARMHOUSE
AND HAD SOME FRANTIC DOG COME
CHASIN' AFTER YOUR VEHICLE.
THEN YOU START SLOWING DOWN
OR SWERVING ALL OVER THE PLACE.
THAT JUST GIVES
THE DOG CONFIDENCE.
HE THINKS HE'S WINNING.
WELL, HERE'S A SIMPLE TRICK TO
HELP YOU AVOID THE WHOLE
SITUATION.
JUST TAKE A PIECE
OF COPPER PIPE,
STICK IT INTO A TOY DOG
OUT THE BACK OF YOUR VEHICLE.
IT'S THAT SIMPLE.
JUST MAKE SURE THAT YOU STICK IT
INTO THE RIGHT END.
WHEN OTHER DOGS SEE THAT
FAKE DOG BOUNCIN' ALONG
BEHIND YOUR VEHICLE,
THEY'LL THINK,
OH, BOY.
I CAN RELAX FOR A CHANGE.
THIS ONE'S COVERED.
[ APPLAUSE AND CHEERS ]
ALL RIGHT, YEAH.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
ACTUALLY, JUST HAD A
BRUSH WITH DEATH.
AND I DON'T MEAN MY WIFE FINDING
OUT HOW MUCH I SPEND ON
FISHING GEAR EITHER.
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT
THE REAL THING.
DALTON AND I PULL INTO
THE PARKING LOT,
AND I HEAR
THIS LOUD CRACK.
AND I JUMP OUT
JUST A MAPLE TREE
CRASHES RIGHT THROUGH THE ROOF
OF THE POSSUM VAN.
OH, BOY.
I'M TELLIN'
YOU, RED,
SOMEBODY UP THERE
WAS LOOKIN' OUT FOR YOU.
WELL, WHOEVER'S LOOKIN'
OUT FOR YOU NEEDS
GLASSES, DALTON.
DALTON WAS BENT OVER
TRYING TO PICK A NICKEL
UP OFF THE FLOOR.
HOW ARE YOU DOIN'?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH, EVERYTHING'S
COPACETIC.
AND I FOUND IT.
I MUST HAVE AN
ANGEL TOO, HUH?
WHAT DO MEAN "TOO"?
I DON'T BELIEVE IN
THAT STUFF.
REALLY?
NO.
YOU DON'T BELIEVE
THAT THERE ARE BEINGS
KEEPIN' AN EYE ON WHERE
WE ARE AND WHAT WE'RE DOIN'
AND KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT WE'RE THINKIN'?
YEAH, BUT THEY'RE
CALLED
WIVES.
SO YOU'RE
TELLIN' ME
THAT YOU DON'T BELIEVE
IN THE SUPERNATURAL?
NO, I DON'T.
NO, NO.
NO HOROSCOPES OR GHOSTS
OR OUIJA BOARDS --
WHAT'S THAT OTHER
THING I'M THINKIN' OF?
E.S.P.?
THAT'S IT.
NO. NO. NO.
WHAT ABOUT
TELEKINESIS,
YOU KNOW, MOVING THINGS
WITH YOUR MIND?
WELL, NOW,
THAT ONE, YEAH,
'CAUSE ONE TIME I SAW
BUSTER HATFIELD LAY
ON HIS COUCH
AND MADE HIS WIFE
MOVE TO PORT ASBESTOS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT'S TIME TO PLAY
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YES, SIR.
AND TODAY'S PRIZE IS AN R.V.
WOW!
IN THIS CASE R.V.
MEANS RED'S VAN.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU CAN'T GIVE
AWAY MY VAN.
JUST FOR A DAY, RED.
ALL RIGHT.
IT'LL NEED GAS.
PLAYIN' FOR TODAY'S PRIZE
IS MIKE HAMAR.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET MIKE TO SAY THIS WORD...
ALL RIGHT,
DALTON.
AND GO!
MIKE, SOMBODY'S
CHASIN' YOU,
SO YOU'RE IN A...
STOLEN CAR?
UM, OKAY,
YOU'RE IN A CAR,
GOIN' A LITTLE FASTER
THAN YOU SHOULD,
AND THE COPS
PULL YOU OVER,
AND THEY SAY,
HEY, WHAT'S THE BIG...
AUTOMATIC WEAPON.
NO, LET'S GO BACK
TO YOUR CHILDHOOD.
REMEMBER YOU MOM WOULD SAY,
DON'T EAT SO FAST.
THERE'S NO...
SECONDS.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS AN EXPRESSION.
YOU'RE IN A LONG,
SLOW LINE AT THE BANK,
AND IT'S NO MOVING
AS FAST AS IT SHOULD BE
'CAUSE THE TELLER'S
MOVING KINDA SLOW,
SO YOU YELL,
SOMETHING UP!
STICK 'EM.
NO.
TIME'S ALMOST UP, RED.
COME ON, MIKE.
YOU GOTTA DO THIS,
OR YOU WON'T WIN THE GAME.
CHEAT?
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NOT CHEAT, NO.
YOU GOTTA BE QUICKER,
OR YOU WON'T GET TO
DRIVE MY VAN.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
I'D RATHER WALK.
SEE, I'M KINDA
IN A HURRY.
THERE WE GO!
[ BELL RINGING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
HERE'S THE KEYS.
HAROLD.
HEY, UNCLE RED!
HOW YOU DOIN'?
GOOD. GOOD.
I'M ON A BREAK.
GREAT, GIVE YOU A COUPLE OF
MINUTES TO TAKE A LOOK AT SOME
OF THE STUFF I BROUGHT YOU
FOR YOUR WORK SPACE, HERE.
STUFF?
YOU BROUGHT STUFF?
YEAH, YOU KNOW,
JUST A FEW MOMENTOS
FROM THE LODGE.
OH, WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE I'M
NEVER COMIN' BACK UP TO
THE LODGE, OR ANYTHING.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BRING
STUFF DOWN TO ME 'CAUSE --
THAT'S A BIG PICTURE,
ISN'T IT?
THAT'S BIG ONE, EH?
YEAH!
ISN'T THAT A BEAUTY?
THAT'S OF ME AND YOU
IN OUR LODGE CLOTHING.
LODGE CLOTHING, YEAH.
UP AT THE LODGE.
SURROUNDED BY
LODGE STUFF.
WORTH A THOUSAND WORDS,
ISN'T IT?
YEAH.
COUPLE ARE COMIN'
TO MIND RIGHT NOW.
GOOD.
YOU KNOW,
THE PROBLEM IS --
OH, I DO NOT HAVE
A WALL TO HANG THIS ON.
NO PROBLEM, HAROLD.
LOOK AT THIS.
SEE?
GOT A STAND ON IT.
LET'S HER STAND
RIGHT UP ALL
ON HER OWN.
OH, THAT'S --
THAT'S --
THAT'S IN MY
STAPLE ZONE!
THAT'S WHERE I DO
ALL THE STAPLING.
THAT'S --
HIGH BUSINESS STAPLING
I DO THERE.
I GOT AN IDEA.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHERE
I CAN STUFF THIS.
REALLY?
YEAH.
INTO MY SCANNER,
YOU SEE.
AND THEN I'LL
SCAN THE IMAGE.
IT'LL GO INTO MY COMPUTER AND
I'LL USE THAT AS A SCREEN SAVER.
THIS IS WHERE IT'LL BE.
BUT, HAROLD,
THEN YOU'LL ONLY BE ABLE TO
SEE IT WHEN YOU'RE NOT WORKING.
WELL, I DON'T
DO MUCH WORK.
I DO SO LITTLE WORK,
IT'S SCARY.
OH, I GET IT, HAROLD.
YOU'RE ASHAMED
OF THE LODGE.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS,
ISN'T IT?
NO.
NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO.
NO, IT'S JUST THAT --
NO, WHAT IS IS THAT IF I LOOK
AT THIS PICTURE ALL DAY LONG,
I'M GONNA START
DAY DREAMING.
I'LL BE FANTASIZING
ABOUT, YOU KNOW,
MAYBE IF FISH COULD
SWIM IN POSSUM LAKE.
YOU KNOW, I'LL NEVER
GET ANY WORK DONE.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
I SEE WHERE YOU'RE
COMIN' FROM.
YEAH. YEAH.
OKAY. OKAY.
I GUESS THIS HERE IS OUT
OF THE QUESTION, IS IT?
YES, YES, IT WOULD.
ALL RIGHT.
MY WIFE, BERNICE, TELLS ME
IT WOULD BE REAL NICE
TO HAVE HEAT IN THE UPPER
LEVEL OF THE SHED, HERE.
AND WHEN YOU'VE BEEN MARRIED
AS LONG AS I HAVE,
YOU ACCEPT THAT YOUR WIFE'S
DECISIONS ARE NOT ONLY FINAL,
THEY'RE ALSO RELENTLESS.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS
I GOTTA FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO GET THIS CAST-IRON WOOD STOVE
UP TO THE SECOND FLOOR.
I SUPPOSE I COULD HORSE
THE UNIT UP ONTO MY BACK
AND THEN CARRY IT
UP THIS LADDER HERE.
BUT THAT WOULD BE THE EQUIVALENT
OF PUTTIN' ALL MY VITAL ORGANS
INTO A BLENDER.
BEIN' ON A LADDER WITH AN EXTRA
150 POUNDS ON MY BACK
IS THE REASON MIDDLE-AGED
GUYS DON'T ELOPE.
BUT AN EXTENSION LADDER IS
STILL A BIG PART OF MY PLAN.
SEE HOW IT GOES UP WHEN I PULL
ON THIS ROPE, HERE?
REMEMBER THAT.
IT'S A HINT.
ALL RIGHT, HERE'S ANOTHER
PIECE OF THE PUZZLE.
CROSS-COUNTRY SKIS.
EVERY COUPLE OF YEARS,
SOME HEALTH FREAK GIVES ME
A PAIR OF THESE.
CROSS-COUNTRY SKIING IS
KINDA LIKE DOWNHILL,
BUT WITH THE FUN REMOVED.
I'LL TELL YOU,
IF I START CROSS-COUNTRY SKIING,
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE I'M EATIN' BROCCOLI
AND WATCHIN'
THE LEARNING CHANNEL.
OH, DARN,
THEY'RE BROKEN.
OH, HERE'S A KEY COMPONENT
YOU'RE GONNA NEED TOO.
A POWER WINCH, EH.
YOU GOT ONE OF THESE ON THE
FRONT OF YOUR VEHICLE?
I TELL YOU, IF I HAD A NICKEL
FOR EVERY DRAINAGE DITCH,
SAND TRAP, OR SWIMMING POOL
THIS UNIT HAS PULLED ME OUT OF,
THOSE DARNED LAWSUITS WOULD
TAKE CARE OF THEMSELVES.
ALL RIGHT, THESE ARE
FOR PULLIN' STUFF OUT,
BUT THEY CAN ALSO BE USED
FOR PULLIN' STUFF UP.
CAN YOU SAY FORKLIFT?
NOW ALL I GOTTA DO IS HOOK THE
WINCH HERE ON TO THE LADDER,
AND WHEN I HIT THE POWER,
UP SHE GOES.
LET'S GIVER 'ER A GO.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
GONNA NEED SOME BALLAST.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S GOT IT.
THIS IS SO MUCH EASIER THAN
CARRYING THE STOVE UP THERE.
SO REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I WANNA TALK TO YOU MIDDLE-AGED
GUYS OUT THERE FOR A MINUTE.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S
AN EXPRESSION,
THE APPLE DOESN'T FALL
TOO FAR FROM THE TREE.
IN HUMAN TERMS
THAT MEANS,
LIKE FATHER,
LIKE SON.
AND IN MOST CASES,
THAT'S A PRETTY SCARY THOUGHT.
ESPECIALLY AS YOU
HEAD TOWARD RETIREMENT
AND THAT INEVITABLE MOMENT
WHEN YOUR OFFSPRING NOT
ONLY LOOK LIKE YOU,
THEY START LOOKIN' AFTER YOU.
YOU DON'T WANT THEM TO
BE LIKE YOU, BELIEVE ME.
YOU GOTTA START SETTIN'
A BETTER EXAMPLE RIGHT NOW.
NOW, I'M NOT SAYIN'
YOU HAVE TO QUIT BEIN'
THAT LAZY APATHETIC GUY YOU'VE
WORKED SO HARD TO BECOME,
JUST NOT IN FRONT
OF THE KIDS,
OR AS I CALL THEM,
YOUR FUTURE CARE GIVERS.
YOU NEED TO COME UP
WITH A FEW MOMENTS OF
HARD WORK AND
RESPONSIBLE BEHAVIOUR
'CAUSE YOU WANT THEM
TO BE MORE RESPONSIBLE,
AND YOU'RE
RUNNIN' OUTTA TIME.
THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU DON'T WANT ANYONE LIKE YOU
MAKIN' YOUR MEALS,
DRIVIN' YOU AROUND,
AND SUPERVISING YOUR MEDICATION.
SO YOU WANT THAT
APPLE TO FALL
AS FAR AWAY FROM
THE TREE AS POSSIBLE,
MAYBE EVEN ROLL
DOWN A HILL.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLIN'
FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
C'MON IN, RED.
I AM GONNA
CONVINCE YOU
THAT THERE IS SUCH A
THING AS PSYCHIC POWER,
AND I'M GONNA DO IT
IN FRONT OF WITNESSES.
IF YOU COULD READ
MY MIND, DALTON,
YOU WOULDN'T EVEN
TRY THIS, YOU KNOW.
PICK A CARD.
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL PICK A CARD.
OKAY,
NOW STARE AT IT.
CONCENTRATE.
SEND A MENTAL PICTURE
OF THAT CARD TO ME.
ARE YOU THINKIN'
OF NAKED WOMEN?
NO.
OH, THAT MUST BE ME.
OKAY, CONCENTRATE
ON THAT CARD.
IS IT THE
THREE OF CLUBS?
NO.
THE FOUR OF CLUBS?
IT'S A CLUB, THOUGH.
NO.
IT'S A BLACK CARD,
IS WHAT I MEAN.
NO, IT'S NOT.
OH, LET ME
SEE THAT!
OH, THERE IT IS.
THE TROUBLE IS, RED,
THAT YOU DON'T BELIEVE IN IT.
NO, NO, NO.
I DON'T BELIEVE IN IT
BECAUSE IT DOESN'T WORK.
DID YOU WANNA
SEE ME, Mr. HUMPHREY?
YEAH, MIKE.
I'M TRYING TO CONVINCE RED
HERE THE POWER OF THE MIND,
AND THINK YOU
CAN HELP ME
'CAUSE MOOSE THOMPSON SAID
THAT YOU BELIEVE IN ANGELS.
NO, NO, NO.
MIKE BELIEVES IN ANGLES.
NO. NO. NO.
I HAVE AN ANGEL.
HE LOOKS OUT FOR ME.
KINDA KEEPS
ME OUTTA TROUBLE.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU SEE?
THAT'S WHAT
I MEAN.
YEAH, HE LIVES
UP BACK OF MY PLACE.
OKAY, MIKE,
LET'S NOT GO TOO FAR.
THE ANGEL LIVES
BEHIND YOUR HOUSE?
YES, SIR.
DOES HE HAVE WINGS?
YEP.
MIKE, I KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TRYING TO DO,
BUT LET'S THINK ABOUT
WHAT WE'RE SAYIN' HERE.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I'M ALMOST CONVINCED.
YOU KNOW, WHAT WOULD
MAKE IT WORK GREAT,
THOUGH?
IF YOU COULD BRING THAT
ANGEL OVER WHERE I
COULD MEET HIM.
THAT WOULD BE
THE CLINCHER.
UH, SORRY.
NO. NO.
UM, SEE, HE'S REAL SHY.
OH, OH, OH.
THAT'S A SHAME
BECAUSE YOU WERE
SO CLOSE TO A
BREAKTHROUGH.
WELL, MAYBE I CAN CONVINCE HIM
TO COME DOWN TO THE LODGE
MEETING TONIGHT,
IF YOU'RE THAT CONVINCED
YOU WANNA MEET HIM.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT
A BETTING MAN,
BUT I'D BE WILLING
TO PUT UP, SAY,
TEN BUCKS
THAT SAYS MIKE CAN'T GET
HIS ANGEL TO SHOW UP AT
THE LODGE MEETING.
ALL RIGHT, Mr. GREEN,
I'LL TAKE THAT BET,
ON ONE CONDITION.
THAT YOU MAKE THE SAME
BET WITH Mr. HUMPHREY.
THAT WAY, WHEN I BRING
MY ANGEL IN,
YOU'LL HAVE TO PAY US
EACH TEN BUCKS.
OH, NO,
THAT'S OKAY, MIKE.
NO, NO, Mr. HUMPHREY,
YOU DESERVE IT.
YOU STUCK BY ME WHEN
Mr. GREEN WOULDN'T,
AND I THINK THAT YOU
DESERVE THAT OPPORTUNITY
TO MAKE SOME
EASY CASH.
YEAH, I DO TOO,
DALTON.
OKAY, GENTLEMEN,
LET'S SEE
YOUR MONEY.
UH, CAN YOU LEND
ME TEN BUCKS?
RED GREEN!
THIS IS AMAZING.
I WAS JUST
THINKING ABOUT YOU.
WELL, I WAVED AT YOU
BEFORE I COME UP, GORD.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
RIGHT.
SO WHAT BRINGS
YOU HERE?
WELL, YOU GAVE ME A ROLL
OF FILM TO GET DEVELOPED.
YEAH, BUT THAT WAS ONLY
ABOUT 20 MINUTES AGO.
THAT WAS
LAST MONTH, GORD.
REALLY?
YEAH.
TIME FLIES.
DO YOU WANT THESE
PICTURES OR NOT?
OH, YEAH,
GREAT, THANKS.
DID YOU LOOK
AT THEM?
NO,
I WAS AFRAID TO.
OH, LOOK.
THESE ARE GREAT.
OOPS.
WHAT'S THAT BY
THE TREE, THERE, GORD?
IS THAT A BEAR?
WHAT IS THAT?
NO, THAT'S ONE OF
THOSE TALL HAIRY MEN,
THE, UH --
OH, YOU MEAN
BIGFOOT?
UH, NO,
BIGFEET, ACTUALLY.
BOTH OF 'EM,
HUGE.
YEAH, HE JUST TRAMPLED THE NEW
FLOWER BED I JUST MADE,
CRAZY RASCAL.
WELL, HOW DO YOU KNOW
IT'S A "HE" AND NOT A "SHE"?
YEAH, THERE'S
A BETTER PICTURE.
OH, YEAH,
THAT'S A HE.
YEAH, I CALL HIM FUZZY,
BUT HIS REAL NAME IS
[ GROWLING ]
YOU KNOW, GORD,
THESE PICTURES COULD BE WORTH
A LOT OF MONEY, YOU KNOW.
NAH, NAH.
FUZZY DOESN'T HAVE ANY MONEY.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I MEAN C.N.N.
THEY'D PAY MONEY
FOR THESE
'CAUSE YOU'VE GOT PROOF THAT
THE ABOMINABLE SNOWMAN EXISTS.
I WOULDN'T CALL
HIM ABOMINABLE.
HE'S MORE
TOUGH BUT FAIR.
NO, NO, NO, GORD.
I'M SAYING IF YOU LET ME
TAKE THESE PICTURES, OKAY,
AND I'LL PRESENT THEM
TO THE RIGHT PEOPLE,
AND WE WOULD BE LOOKIN' AT
A FAIR MAJOR AMOUNT OF
COIN TO SHARE.
REALLY?
YOU KNOW,
IF WE DO THAT,
I SHOULD BE THE ONE TO ALL
THE TALKING, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE I AM A
PROFESSIONAL FOREST RANGER.
JUST TO MAINTAIN
CREDIBILITY.
UH, THESE PICTURES
AREN'T THAT GOOD.
NAH.
Red:
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
MIKE HAD A DATE.
MY MIND IS AGOG.
AND HE'S HAVIN' A GOOD
TIME DRIVING ALONG,
AND I GUESS THIS GIRL
DIDN'T KNOW HIM.
SUDDENLY HE STARTS
TO RUN OUT OF GAS.
AND SO DOES THE CAR.
NOW HE HAS TO DO WHAT
ALL MEN HATE TO DO,
NO, NOT THAT.
HE HAS TO LOOK
AT THE GAS GAUGE.
YEAH, IT LOOKS
A LITTLE DRY THERE.
BUT LOOK,
THIS GIRL KNOWS MIKE.
NOW HE COMES UP
TO HIS NEXT OBSTACLE.
THIS CAR, TECHNICALLY,
ISN'T A CAR HE'S HAD
MORE THAN FIVE MINUTES,
SO HE DOESN'T KNOW
WHERE THE GAS FILLER IS.
THIS IS KIND OF A TIP-OFF.
TRY THE OTHER SIDE,
THERE, MIKE.
NO, I THINK IT'S BEHIND
THE LICENSE PLATE.
TRY THE LICENSE PLATE THERE.
I DOUBT IF IT WOULD BE --
I DOUBT IT.
WHAT THE --
OH, OH, OH.
THIS IS A MAGNETIC HILL
IN THE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
I DON'T THINK MIKE'S
FAMILIAR WITH THAT.
AND HE'S ALL --
MIKE, IT'S AN OPTICAL ILLUSION
IT'S A MAGNETIC HILL.
NO, IT'S AN OPTICAL --
WATCH.
THERE'S NOTHIN' TO IT.
SEE?
THAT'S ALL THERE
IS TO THAT.
BUT YOU KNOW YOU CAN HAVE
A LOT OF FUN WITH IT, YEP.
NO, NO, NO.
YOU CAN HAVE A LOT OF FUN.
COME ON.
FIRST OF ALL,
WE DON'T WANT THE POSSUM VAN
TO GO UP THERE.
GET A LITTLE ROCK THERE.
PUT THAT IN FRONT
OF THE WHEELS.
OKAY, NOTHIN'
TO WORRY ABOUT.
NOW WE CAN HAVE SOME FUN.
COME HERE.
ANYTHING I GOT THAT
I WANNA ROLL UP THAT HILL?
HOW ABOUT --
TRY THE SPARE.
THIS IS GREAT.
LET 'ER GO.
[ LAUGHING ]
WASN'T THAT GREAT?
UP SHE GOES.
THERE WE GO.
WHAT ELSE I GOT IN HERE?
I GOT MORE OF
THOSE BIG BALLS.
YOU KNOW THOSE
BEACH BALL-TYPE THINGS?
LET'S TRY A FEW OF THOSE.
DUMP A FEW IN THERE.
DUMP A FEW IN.
WATCH THIS, MIKE, EH?
LET 'EM GO.
YOU GOT THREE OF THEM.
LET 'ER RIP.
LOOK AT THIS.
THERE GOES ONE.
THERE GOES TWO.
AND NUMBER THREE.
OH, MY GOLLY.
YOU KNOW --
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
LET'S DO THE BIG ONE, EH?
LET'S FIRE THE WHOLE
VAN UP THERE.
GET THE OTHER ROCK.
TAKE THE OTHER ROCK OUT.
WATCH OUT.
SHE'LL CREEP ON YOU.
SHE'LL CREEP.
GET AWAY.
I'LL GET MINE.
STAND BACK.
OKAY, HERE SHE GOES.
HERE SHE GOES.
WATCH THIS.
AH! AH! AH!
OH, HEY.
HOW ARE YOU?
OH, RIGHT!
IT'S TIME FOR
MIKE'S TEEN TALK.
OKAY.
SO I KNOW A LOT OF YOU
YOUNG PEOPLE HAVE TROUBLE
TELLING THE TRUTH.
WELL, THE PROBLEM IS THAT THE
TRUTH ISN'T ALWAYS THAT SIMPLE.
'CAUSE WHAT MIGHT
BE TRUE FOR ONE GUY,
LIKE, SAY, YOU OR ME,
MIGHT NOT BE TRUE
FOR SOME OTHER GUY;
LIKE, THE POLICE.
AND ALSO, YOU MIGHT BE SO BUSY
MAKING UP YOUR STORY
AND REHEARSING IT FOR SO LONG
AND WORKING AND
WORKING ON IT
THAT YOU THINK IT'S
REALLY THE TRUTH, RIGHT?
AND IT COMES AS A COMPLETE SHOCK
WHEN SOME EYE WITNESS
TELLS YOU YOU'RE LYIN'.
THIS HAPPENS TO ME A LOT.
SO I LIKE TO LOOK FOR
THE DANGER SIGNS
THAT'LL SHOW ME IF I MIGHT
BE TELLING THE TRUTH.
LIKE, IF MY STORY
IS GONNA CAUSE A HASSLE,
OR IF IT'S GONNA
GET PEOPLE IRRITATED,
OR -- AND HERE'S
THE BIG GIVEAWAY,
IF IT SEEMS A LOT MORE UNLIKELY
THAN THE LIE I WAS GONNA TELL,
THEN IT'S PROBABLY THE TRUTH.
SO I'D SAY THAT IF YOU WANNA GET
YOURSELF INTO A LOT OF TROUBLE
AND HAVE PEOPLE MAD AT YOU
AND CALLIN' YOU A LIAR AND ALL
THAT KIND OF STUFF,
THEN, SURE,
TELL THE TRUTH;
OTHERWISE, I'D JUST SORT OF USE
THE TRUTH AS A LAST RESORT.
LIKE THEY DO IN POLITICS.
OH, THAT'S IT.
SO WHAT ARE YOU
LEARNIN' IN SCHOOL
THESE DAYS, DALE?
WELL, MY ECONOMICS
CLASS IS KIND OF
INTERESTING.
WE'RE DOING A
COMPARISON BETWEEN
GUNS AND BUTTER.
OH, YEAH.
IS THAT WHAT THE
EDUCATIONAL SYSTEM
HAS COME TO NOW?
YOU GOTTA GO TO COLLEGE
TO BE ABLE TO TELL
GUNS FROM BUTTER?
WELL, YOU COULD LEARN
ABOUT IT TOO, Mr. GREEN.
I MEAN, THEY'VE GOT
ADULT CLASSES AT NIGHT,
IF YOU'RE INTERESTED.
I'M NOT INTERESTED.
I'M JUST TRYING TO
DISTRACT YOU,
SO YOU'LL PUT MORE GAS IN
THAN THE FIVE BUCKS
I'M PAYIN' FOR.
THAT'LL BE $5,
Mr. GREEN.
THERE YOU GO,
DALE.
SEE YOU
NEXT TIME.
OH, WAIT A SECOND.
YOU FORGOT YOUR COUPONS.
WHAT?
IT'S A PROMOTION
WE'RE DOIN' HERE
AT THE STATION.
IT'S LIKE MONEY,
BUT YOU GOTTA
SPEND IT HERE.
SO HOW MUCH ARE
THESE COUPONS WORTH,
QUARTER OF A TANK
OF GAS OR SOMETHING?
NINE CENTS.
NINE CENTS?
WELL, YOU COLLECT 'EM.
IT ADDS UP.
WELL, CAN YOU GET
ME AN ELASTIC BAND,
SO I CAN KEEP 'EM
TOGETHER AT LEAST?
I DON'T HAVE AN
ELASTIC ON ME.
THE CONVENIENCE STORE
SELLS ELASTICS.
YOU GOTTA BUY 'EM A BAG
AT A TIME, THOUGH.
AND HOW MUCH DOES A BAG
OF ELASTICS COST?
I DUNNO.
TWO BUCKS?
DALE, I'M NOT GONNA SPEND
TWO BUCKS TO HOLD NINE
CENTS TOGETHER.
HERE, YOU TAKE
'EM BACK.
NO, I CAN'T
TAKE 'EM.
I HOPE YOU DON'T THINK
I'M GONNA GET OUTTA THE
VAN TO PICK THOSE UP.
I DON'T BEND OVER
TO PICK UP A DIME.
AND NEITHER
SHOULD YOU, DALE.
WHAT ARE YOU MAKIN'?
EIGHT BUCKS AN HOUR?
OKAY, THAT'S
13 CENTS A MINUTE.
YOU TAKE THE TIME TO
PICK UP THOSE COUPONS,
YOU'RE LOSIN' MONEY.
THERE'S YOUR
ECONOMICS.
AND DROP BY THE LODGE
AND BRING A BAKED POTATO,
AND I'LL ALSO SHOW YOU THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN GUNS
AND BUTTER.
WELL, MIKE'S RUNNIN'
A BIT LATE, IF HE'S
COMIN' AT ALL.
YOU DON'T SUPPOSE HIS
ANGEL WHISKED HIM OFF
TO HEAVEN, DO YOU?
IF MIKE COULD
GET INTO HEAVEN,
THAT'S GOOD NEWS FOR ALL
OF US, ISN'T IT?
WELL, I GOT THINGS
TO DO, DALTON,
SO IF YOU DON'T MIND,
I'LL JUST KINDA --
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE,
Mr. GREEN.
THAT MONEY ISN'T
YOUR'S YET.
MIKE, DID YOU
COME ALONE,
OR IS THERE AN INVISIBLE
SPIRIT KINDA HOVERING
AROUND YOU?
PROBABLY SOME
ON HIS BREATH.
NO.
NO, IT TOOK A
LOT OF COAXING,
BUT MY ANGEL FINALLY
AGREED TO DROP BY.
SO IF YOU DON'T MIND
HANDING OVER THE MONEY.
FOR WHAT?
SOME INVISIBLE ANGEL
NOBODY CAN SEE OR HEAR?
HEY, ANGEL,
IF YOU'RE HERE,
SMITE ME, HUH.
SMITE ME DOWN.
SMITE ME GOOD.
C'MON IN,
FRANCO.
UM, THIS
IS FRANCO.
HE'S A VOLUNTEER WITH THE
POSSUM LAKE GUARDIAN
ANGEL SOCIETY.
THEY HELP GUYS
LIKE ME.
PLEASED TO
MEET YOU, FRANCO.
I LOOK OUT
FOR MIKE.
WE DON'T WANT ANYTHING
TO MESS UP HIS PAROLE.
THIS IS Mr. GREEN.
HE WANTED YOU
TO SMITE HIM.
NO, NO, NO.
JUST KIDDIN'.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT
IN THE TAKE OUT
FOOD BOX?
MY WINGS.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
I THINK SOMEBODY OWES Mr.
HUMPHREY AND ME TEN BUCKS.
HEY, HEY.
THIS GUY ISN'T
TECHNICALLY AN ANGEL.
WHAT!
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
I GUESS THOSE ARE
SUICIDE WINGS.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
YOU GUYS GOTTA GO.
AWAY YOU GO.
OH, YEAH.
RIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU
GUYS LATER.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
I'LL BE COMIN' STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING,
AND I THINK I'M GONNA NEED A
CHANGE OF CLOTHES
BECAUSE I'VE JUST BEEN
TOUCHED BY AN ANGEL.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND MY BEST PAL, FRANCO,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
closed captioning performed
by INTERCAPTION CANADA
www.intercaption.com
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
TAKE A SEAT.
EVERYBODY SIT.
SIT DOWN, EVERYONE.
OKAY, EVERYONE SIT.
SIT.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
OKAY, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE
IF I HAVE TO
I GUESS.