WE'VE ALL SEEN
THE BIG AIRPORTS
WITH THOSE FANCY
REMOTE CONTROL HALLWAYS
THAT COME OUT AND SIT
AGAINST THE DOOR OF THE PLANE
SO YOU CAN
GET IN AND OUT
WITH OUT THE RAIN
SOAKING YOUR FREE PRETZELS.
WELL, HEY, I'M THINKIN'
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT TO HAVE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT AT HOME?
SO I'VE ATTACHED THIS
SEWER PIPE TO MY PORCH HERE
AND IT CAN SWING AROUND,
THANKS TO THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET HINGE.
BUT WHEN IT'S NOT IN USE,
THESE BUNGIES WILL HOLD
HER OFF TO THE SIDE
SO THAT THE LOCAL RESIDENTS
CAN GET ACCESS TO THE
FRONT DOOR.
SEE, I DON'T DO
MUCH AIR TRAVEL,
SO IT'S THE
ONLY CHANCE I GET.
IT'S NOT THAT I'M AFRAID OF
TAKING AN AIRPLANE,
IT'S MORE THAT THE TRAVEL AGENT
IS AFRAID OF TAKING MY CHEQUE.
BUT WHEN IT GETS
TO BE QUITTIN' TIME
AND THE WEARY TRAVELLER
RETURNS HOME OF ANOTHER DAY
OF SEEKING
GAINFUL EMPLOYMENT,
HIS VEHICLE WILL PUSH
AGAINST THIS CANADARM,
WHICH WILL SIMULTANEOUSLY
ACTIVATE THE REMOTE CONTROL
ENTRANCEWAY.
SOMETHING LIKE THIS...
MAKE SURE YOU USE
A BRAND NEW SEWER PIPE,
BECAUSE A USED ONE
IS JUST WAY TOO SLIPPERY.
NOW IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I'VE GOT A MEAL TO CATCH.
OH, BOY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
WELL, AFTER 30 YEARS OF
GIVING IT A REAL GOOD TRY,
I'M FINALLY PREPARED TO ADMIT
THAT IT IS IMPOSSIBLE
FOR A NORMAL GUY
WITH LIMITED RESOURCES
TO MAKE AN
AFFORDABLE SUBMARINE.
COINCIDENTALLY, I AM NOW
SELLING A 1974 CHEVY VAN.
SHE'S ONLY TEN BUCKS.
IF YOU WANT A TEST DRIVE,
YOU BETTER BRING YOUR
SCUBA GEAR.
UNCLE RED! UNCLE RED!
THIS IS SO GREAT!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I GOT THIS LETTER HERE.
A MAJOR CORPORATION WANTS
YOU TO DO ADS FOR THEM.
OH!
YEAH!
YOU MEAN LIKE
BE A SPOKESMAN.
SPOKES PERSON.
GET WITH THE TIMES,
UNCLE RED.
YOU SHOULD NEVER IDENTIFY
ANYBODY BY THEIR SEX.
WELL, YOU'VE
PROVEN THAT, HAROLD.
ANYWAY...
WE'VE GOT ENDORSEMENT FEES
AND FREE SAMPLES.
IT'S A VERY HIGH PROFILE
LINE OF PRODUCTS.
YOU COULD BE LIKE
THE NEXT MARTHA STEWART.
BUT WITH DIGNITY.
YEAH, AND MORE LIKE
RONALD McDONALD.
YEAH, AND I CAN'T TELL YOU
WHAT THE LINE OF PRODUCTS ARE
BECAUSE THIS DEAL
HASN'T BEEN SIGNED YET,
SO I CAN'T TELL
YOU THE COMPANY, OKAY,
SO DON'T TRY AND GET
IT OUT OF ME,
BECAUSE I CAN'T DO THAT.
THAT WOULD BE UNETHICAL
FOR ME TO DO THAT,
SO DON'T.
OH, YOU'RE SO GOOD!
OKAY, I'LL TELL YOU.
AH, HAROLD! HAROLD!
CAN YOU BACK OFF
ON THE SALIVA?
I'M GETTING
SWIMMER'S EAR HERE.
TRY AGAIN.
OH, I DRIVE ONE!
DON'T!
STOP IT!
YOU'RE GONNA
RUIN EVERYTHING.
THE DEAL HASN'T
BEEN SIGNED YET.
YOU'LL JUST KILL IT
RIGHT OFF BY DOING THAT.
DON'T EVEN.
BOY, THEY WANT YOU
TO DO COMMERCIALS TOO.
AH, GEEZ, HAROLD.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
ALL YOU HAVE
TO DO IS SMILE.
SEE, THERE'S
ALWAYS A CATCH.
NO, THE AD FEATURES YOU
IN A HOT TUB WITH
SIX MODELS.
YOU DON'T MEAN LIKE YOUR
MODEL AIRPLANES, DO YOU?
NO, NO, I DON'T.
FASHION MODELS,
HIRED FOR THEIR LOOKS.
MALE MODELS?
NO!
FEMALE MODELS.
FEMALE, HUMAN MODELS?
YES!
TRUST ME ON THIS.
WHEN YOU SEE THESE SIX HEALTHY,
YOUNG, 20-SOMETHING MODELS
YOU KNOW, IN THEIR
THONG BIKINIS...
YOU'RE GONNA KNOW
THEY'RE WOMEN.
W-W-WOMEN.
AND ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS SMILE, IS WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING?
WELL, YOU MIGHT
HAVE TO SHAVE TOO.
OH, NO, NO.
THE BEARD STAYS ON,
HAROLD.
I MEANT YOUR BACK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S PRIZE IS A COUPON
FROM BETTY'S PLEASURES
AND CRAFTS
AND PLEASURE CRAFTS.
OH, IT'S A GOOD ONE TOO.
A ONE-YEAR SUPPLY
OF CALENDARS.
OKAY, DALTON,
COVER YOUR EARS.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON TO SAY
THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
WINSTON.
AND... GO!
OKAY, DALTON, UM,
THE OPPOSITE OF MARRIED.
HAPPY.
OKAY, NOW, JUST SAY THE FIRST
THING THAT COMES INTO
YOUR MIND, OKAY?
A GUY IS NO
LONGER MARRIED...
CONGRATULATIONS!
YOU KNOW, LIKE,
THE MARRIAGE IS OVER.
HE'S NOT MARRIED ANYMORE,
SO NOW HE'S...
BROKE.
NO, WHEN SOMEONE'S MARRIAGE
IS FINALLY, FINALLY OVER --
SOMETIMES IT TAKES YEARS,
BUT IT'S ALL OVER.
THAT MEANS YOU
ARE NOW LEGALLY...
INSANE.
YOUR SISTER-IN-LAW
AND HER HUSBAND,
THEY WERE MARRIED
UNTIL THEY GOT...
OH, THE RESULTS
OF THE PATERNITY TEST.
ALMOST OUT OF TIME, RED.
YEAH, OKAY.
OH, I KNOW, DALTON.
REMEMBER THAT WAITRESS,
LUCY, DOWN AT THE TAVERN?
SHE GOT...
CAUGHT, YEAH!
AND EVERY ONE OF
THOSE GUYS IS DIVORCED.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERTS
PORTION OF THE PROGRAMME,
WHERE WE ADDRESS
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW.
OKAY, HERE'S
TODAY'S LETTER...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"I'M THINKING OF HAVING
MY BODY CRYOGENICALLY FROZEN
"AT MY DEATH SO THAT
I MIGHT BE REVIVED
"IN THE EXCITING
WORLD OF THE FUTURE.
"WHAT DO YOU THINK?"
OH, DON'T DO IT.
YOU'RE GOING TO WAKE UP
WITH AN ICE CREAM HEADACHE
THAT'D KNOCK
YOUR SOCKS OFF.
AH, IT'S NOT
THAT BAD.
YOU'VE HAD YOUR
HEAD FROZEN, HAP?
YOU KNOW, THAT WOULD
EXPLAIN A LOT.
NO, WE DABBLED IN CRYOGENICS
WHEN I WAS AT HARVARD.
HAP, IF YOU WENT TO HARVARD,
I WENT TO YALE.
SO DID I!
I SAID "YALE"
NOT "JAIL."
I DIDN'T GO TO HARVARD.
I WAS THERE AS A
CONSULTANT ON CRYOGENICS.
WALT DISNEY WAS
FUNDING THE PROJECT.
HE WANTED ME IN ON IT.
HAP, ARE YOU TELLIN' US THAT
WALT DISNEY WAS A PERSONAL
FRIEND OF YOURS?
MORE LIKE A
BUSINESS PARTNER.
I WAS THE ONE WHO CONVINCED
HIM TO GO TO FOUR FINGERS
INSTEAD OF FIVE
ON ALL OF HIS
CARTOON CHARACTERS.
CUT HIS COSTS BY 20%.
WALT WAS ONE OF THE
FIRST TO TRY CRYOGENICS.
NOBODY KNOWS WHERE
THE BODY IS.
OH, YEAH, HE'S AT
PORT ASBESTOS ARENA,
DISNEY ON ICE.
UM, I'M NOT SURE IF
I UNDERSTAND WHAT
CRYOGENICS IS.
OH, DON'T ENCOURAGE
HIM, MIKE.
THEY STOP YOUR HEART,
AND THEN THEY IMMERSE YOU
IN LIQUID NITROGEN
AND THEN IN THE FUTURE
THEY BRING YOU BACK TO LIFE
AND FIX WHATEVER'S
WRONG WITH YOU.
YEAH, LIKE, SAY,
FREEZER BURN.
SO, UH, WOULD YOU ADVISE THAT
IT WOULD BE A GOOD THING
FOR THIS VIEWER?
WELL, NOBODY'S EVER DONE IT,
SO WE DON'T HAVE ANY RESULTS.
COULD BE RISKY.
OH, FOR SURE.
A COUPLE YEARS AGO OLD MAN
SEDGWICK HAD HIS
ASSETS FROZEN.
NOW HE WALKS WITH A LIMP.
SO I WOULD ADVISE THAT THIS
VIEWER SHOULD PROCEED
WITH EXTREME CAUTION.
OH, YOU'RE
RIGHT THERE, MIKE.
IT'S ALSO BEST TO
LET SOME THINGS LIE.
THAT'S WHAT
WE DO WITH HAP.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU EVER SEE THESE
AUTOMATIC COFFEE MAKERS
THAT HAVE THE TIMER SO YOU
CAN WAKE UP TO THE SMELL
OF FRESH COFFEE?
YOU KNOW WHAT I CALL THAT?
NICE TRY.
COFFEE'S NOT ENOUGH.
YOU CAN'T JUST HAVE
COFFEE FOR BREAKFAST.
IT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT
MEAL OF THE DAY.
FOR A LOT PEOPLE,
IT'S THE LAST DECENT MEAL
THEY'LL HAVE UNTIL LUNCH.
WOULDN'T IT BE BETTER IF YOU
COULD USE THE TECHNOLOGY
OF CLOCKS AND TIMERS
TO HAVE YOUR WHOLE BREAKFAST
PREPARED BEFORE
YOU'RE EVEN AWAKE?
WELL, IF YOU
DIDN'T THINK SO,
YOU PROBABLY WOULDN'T BE
WATCHING THIS SHOW.
OKAY, THE FIRST
THING YOU WANNA GET
IS ANOTHER COFFEE MAKER.
I WOULD SUGGEST
YOU GO SECOND HAND.
IT'S CHEAPER AND WE'RE GONNA
PRETTY MUCH VOID THE
WARRANTY ANYWAY.
TAKE THE COFFEE POT
OUTTA THERE.
AND REPLACE IT
WITH A SMALL FRY PAN.
SET IT RIGHT DOWN
ON THE HEATING ELEMENT,
'CAUSE THAT'S WHERE WE'RE
GONNA DO ALL OUR COOKIN'.
BUT WE NEED THE FOOD TO GET
THERE AT THE RIGHT TIME.
HOW ARE WE GONNA DO THAT?
LIKE CLOCKWORK.
YOU CAN GET RID
OF THE EXTRA COFFEE POT.
WE DON'T NEED
THAT ANYMORE.
TOO STRONG FOR YOU?
I HAD TO RE-JIG THE
ALARM CLOCK A LITTLE BIT.
SO INSTEAD OF THE HAMMERS
RINGING THOSE BELLS
THAT'S THE CAUSE OF SO MANY
BROKEN BEDROOM WINDOWS,
I TOOK THE BELLS
RIGHT OUTTA THERE
AND REPLACED THEM
WITH A COUPLE OF EGGS.
THIS HERE IS JUST
AN OLD SCHOOL RULER
THAT I WAS SUPPOSED
TO USE IN GEOMETRY,
BUT INSTEAD MY TEACHER
USED IT ON MY BACKSIDE.
AND NOW IT BECOMES
THE SAUSAGE FEEDER
FOR MY AUTOMATIC
BREAKFAST MACHINE.
JUST GOTTA PUT A
COUNTERWEIGHT ON THIS END,
WHICH WILL START THE TOASTER
ONCE THE SAUSAGES ARE
IN THE PAN.
A LOT OF COORDINATION
NEEDED HERE,
BUT I THINK
WE'RE GOOD TO GO.
I SET THE COFFEE MAKER AND THE
ALARM CLOCK FOR 7:00 a.m.,
AND I CUSTOMIZED
THE CUCKOO CLOCK,
SO NOW IT'LL ONLY
GO OFF AT 7:00.
NOW I JUST NEED TO MOVE THE
WHOLE UNIT TO THE KITCHEN.
YOU'RE PROBABLY WONDERING WHY
I DIDN'T JUST BUILD
THE THING IN THE KITCHEN.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU DON'T KNOW MY WIFE.
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO DO
PROJECTS INSIDE THE HOUSE
EVER SINCE I DID
THAT VALVE JOB ON THE
DINING ROOM TABLE...
DURING DINNER.
[ CLOCK TICKING ]
[ SIZZLING ]
[ ALARM RINGING ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
I WAS LISTENING
TO THE RADIO THE OTHER DAY,
AND THEY PLAYED OUR SONG,
THE SONG THEY WERE PLAYING
WHEN BERNICE AND I MET.
IT'S FUNNY
HOW SOMETIMES A SONG
CAN DEFINE
A RELATIONSHIP.
LIKE HAROLD'S SONG
IS "ALONE AGAIN."
AND DALTON AND ANNE MARIE'S
SONG IS, I BELIEVE,
"WHO'S SORRY NOW?"
BUT FOR
BERNICE AND I,
IT'S "BLUEBIRDS OVER
THE MOUNTAIN" BY THE KING,
THAT'S RIGHT,
URSEL HICKEY.
REMEMBER URSEL HICKEY?
BOY, OH, BOY, OH, BOY.
BUT THE ONE THEY PLAYED
ON THE RADIO JUST NOW
WAS LIKE BY
SOME COVER BAND.
I MEAN,
WHAT IS WITH THAT?
IT WASN'T
URSEL HICKEY AT ALL.
IT WAS A NO NAME.
HOLY COW.
I MEAN, BERNICE AND I,
WE WANT THE REAL THING,
ESPECIALLY WHEN
IT COMES TO HICKEYS.
WHAT WAS WITH
THESE GUYS?
WHY WOULD THEY RE-DO
A PERFECTLY GOOD SONG
AND DO IT BADLY?
I MEAN, I SOMETIMES
DO MY OWN VERSION OF STUFF.
I MIGHT TAKE A COUPLE
OF PING PONG BATS
AND A WEED-WACKER AND MAKE
A CEILING FAN OUT OF THEM
BUT BY GOLLY,
I WOULD NEVER DISRESPECT
A CLASSIC MUSICAL RENDITION
LIKE URSEL HICKEY DID
OF "BLUEBIRDS
OVER THE MOUNTAINS."
SO IF THERE ARE
ANY MUSICIANS OUT THERE,
FOR HEAVEN SAKES,
THERE WILL NEVER BE
ANOTHER URSEL HICKEY
GET OVER IT.
START MAKING
YOUR OWN NOSTALGIA
AND KEEP YOUR
COTTON-PICKING HANDS OFF MINE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
CALL ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES
'CAUSE ONE IN THE CAN
IS WORTH TWO IN THE BUSH.
WELL, I SPOKE
TO MY WIFE, BERNICE,
ABOUT THE HOT TUB
PHOTO WITH THE MODELS.
SHE'S OKAY WITH IT,
AS LONG AS I KEEP
MY CLOTHES ON.
I SAID YEAH,
BUT YOU KNOW,
I CAN'T CONTROL
WHAT THE WOMEN WEAR
OR CHOOSE
NOT TO WEAR.
IF THEY DECIDE
TO GO AL FRESCO ON THIS THING
I MIGHT SEE
SOMETHING THAT, MAYBE,
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO SEE.
SHE SAID, "NO PROBLEM."
BUT SHE KEPT MY GLASSES.
I'M NOT
WORRIED ABOUT THAT.
I'VE STILL GOT
A 20/20 IMAGINATION.
OKAY, ALL SET HERE,
UNCLE RED.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
LET'S DO THIS.
WHERE DO YOU
WANT ME, HAROLD?
RIGHT THERE
ON THAT STOOL.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
NOW JUST LOOK THE
CAMERA AND SMILE NATURALLY,
IF YOU COULD
DO THAT FOR ME.
BUT WHERE ARE THE --
OKAY. GOOD.
ALL DONE.
ALL DONE?
WHERE'S THE HOT TUB
FULL OF HONEYS, HAROLD?
IN COLORADO.
WE'RE ALL GOOD,
IT'S ALL DIGITAL NOW.
GET WITH THE TIMES.
EVERYTHING'S RIGHT
HERE IN MY COMPUTER.
WHAT?
YUP.
LOOK AT THIS.
JUST TO MOVE YOU HERE...
THERE YOU ARE.
HEY, HEY,
HEY, HEY, HEY.
WOW!
HEY, CAN I DO SOMETHING
LIKE THAT WITH YOUR HEAD?
YEAH. YEAH.
GO. GO. GO. GO.
OKAY, I'M GOING TO NEED
A STOCK PICTURE OF A
HORSE, THOUGH.
REAR VIEW.
HEY!
Red: A BUNCH OF US GOING
ON A CAMPING TRIP THERE.
HAD THE TENT TRAILER.
AND UH, JUST --
I GUESS WE'LL TAKE THIS SPOT.
BUT WE NOTICED ALMOST
IMMEDIATELY THAT THE TENT
TRAILER SEEMED TO BE MISSING.
AND THERE'S WALTER,
BUT I DON'T THINK HE'S GOT IT.
AND BIG ARGUMENT AS TO WHO
DIDN'T HOOK IT UP PROPERLY.
J-JUST RELAX.
GOOD NEWS, GUYS.
IT FOLLOWED US.
OKAY, SEEMED TO PICK UP A FEW
CLOTHES AND CLOTHESLINES
ON THE WAY,
BUT THAT'S A GOOD
SPOT OVER THERE,
SO WE'LL GO OVER THERE AND
JUST SET HER UP RIGHT
WHERE SHE IS.
JUST GET THE CLOTHES --
THAT'S KINDA NEAT.
OH, AND WALTER FOUND ONE
OF THOSE GARDEN GNOMES.
HE LIKES THOSE.
OF COURSE, MIKE AND DALTON
ARE ANXIOUS TO GET AT
THE FOOD, YOU KNOW.
WE'VE BEEN TRAVELING
FOR OVER TEN MINUTES NOW,
AND SO DALTON'S HELPING
MIKE INTO THE UNIT.
THEN HE LEANS BACK,
AND OF COURSE,
I FOUND THAT --
[ CHUCKLING ]
I FOUND THAT -- I DIDN'T
FIND THAT FUNNY, THOUGH.
SO I SAY,
GET THE HECK OUTTA THERE.
IT'S NOT HOW
IT WORKS, GUYS.
EVERYBODY GO TO A CORNER
BECAUSE THERE'S A LEG ON
EACH CORNER OF THESE UNITS,
AND THEY PULL OUT
AND THEY SNAP DOWN
AND THEY KINDA
TELESCOPE OUT
AND THEY HOLD THE
THING TOTALLY LEVEL.
NOW DO THAT
WITH ALL FOUR.
DO THAT WITH YOURS
THERE, DALTON.
WELL, HIS WAS KIND OF
RUSTED SOLID THERE,
SO HE GAVE HER JUST A
LITTLE TOO MUCH FOOT ENERGY.
OKAY. GREAT.
YEAH, LUCKILY,
DALTON ALWAYS HAS A PLAN.
NOW, MIKE'S WAS
REALLY WEDGED ON THERE,
AND IT WASN'T EVEN
MOVING WITH THE HAMMER,
BUT HE FIGURES, WE'RE NOT
GONNA USE THAT HAMMER THAT
MUCH THIS WEEKEND...
AND IN WALTER'S CORNER,
THERE'S NOTHING THERE AT ALL,
BUT, UH, THEN HE
SPOTTED THAT OTHER --
I ALWAYS WONDERED WHAT
THOSE THINGS WERE FOR.
THERE WE GO.
PERFECT.
OKAY. NOW, GET ALL
THE CLOTHES OFF THERE.
THIS IS ONE OF THESE
HI-LO TENT TRAILERS.
YOU JUST TURN THE CRANK,
AND UP COMES THE WHOLE UNIT.
SO JUST STAND BACK, GUYS,
AND JUST WATCH THIS.
SO I START CRANKING.
AND, UH -- NO, JUST WAIT.
JUST BE PATIENT.
SHE GOES UP PRETTY GOOD.
AND THEY'RE TRYING TO WAIT,
BUT IT'S JUST KILLING THEM.
THEY JUST WANNA GET AT THOSE
SANDWICHES AND WHAT HAVE YOU.
AND THEY JUST CAN'T
WAIT THE WHOLE TIME,
SO THEY JUST START CLIMBING IN
BEFORE SHE'S GONE TO HER
FULL ELEVATION.
AND OF COURSE WHAT HAPPENS
IS SHE GETS A LITTLE TIGHTER
AS SHE GETS TO THE TOP.
SHE SNAPS OFF
RIGHT IN MY HAND,
AND THE WHOLE
THING COLLAPSES.
WELL, NOW THE THREE OF
THEM ARE TRAPPED IN THERE,
BUT FIRST OF ALL, I CHECK TO
MAKE SURE THEY'RE ALL OKAY.
YEAH, THEY'RE FINE.
AND I FIGURE, IF I COULD
JUST GET MIKE OUT,
THE OTHERS WOULD PROBABLY
HAVE ROOM TO WIGGLE THERE.
NO, HE'S NOT -- NO,
HE'S KINDA LOCKED IN THERE.
THEN I THINK,
BOY, I THINK --
YEAH, I GOT A
CORDLESS DRILL IN THE VAN.
I COULD HOOK THAT UP.
I SHOW THE GUYS.
THEY DON'T CARE
HOW I DO IT.
JUST DO IT.
SO I HOOK HER
UP TO THE AXLE.
AND THAT'S GONNA -- THEN I
HAD HER GOIN' THE WRONG WAY.
THEN I JUST REVERSED THAT.
THEN AWAY WE GO.
OH, AND DALTON
GOT OUT NO PROBLEM.
AND THEN MIKE
GOT OUT OF THERE OKAY.
BUT WALTER WAS
A LITTLE SLOW
AND THEN SHE COMES UP
AND THEN SHE CAME DOWN HARD.
I THOUGHT I COULD WEDGE,
LIKE, A PADDLE IN THERE,
IT WOULD STOP DRILL.
AND THAT GOT IT UP.
AND THEN WE HAD A PROBLEM
AND I'VE NEVER SEEN A TENT
TRAILER COMPRESS THIS FAR.
IT WAS JUST, I --
BUT LUCKILY,
THE COOLER SEEMED ALL RIGHT.
WE JUST HAD TO
CHECK THE SANDWICHES,
AND THIS IS --
YEAH, LOOKS GOOD.
LOOKS GOOD.
WE'RE GOOD.
OH, YEAH, WALTER.
HERE, HAVE A SANDWICH.
HAPPY CAMPING.
[ APPLAUSE ]
GOT A BIT OF
A CROOKED FLOOR HERE
AND IT'S MAKIN' THE GAME
OF POOL A REAL CHALLENGE.
SO I'M TRYING TO LEVEL IT
WITH THIS SPIRIT LEVEL
AND THE DO-IT-YOURSELFER'S
GUIDE TO HOME IMPROVEMENT.
OKAY, NOW WE GOT
TWO OPTIONS...
EITHER GET ANOTHER
COPY OF THE BOOK,
OR GET CREATIVE.
LET'S SEE WHAT
A REAL MAN DOES.
[ WATER SPRAYING ]
A TRUE HANDYMAN
IS LIKE WATER...
HE FINDS HIS OWN LEVEL.
WELL, NOW THAT THE
WHOLE PHOTO SESSION IS DONE,
I'M OKAY TO TALK
ABOUT THE DEAL.
I AM NOW THE
OFFICIAL SPOKESMAN --
PERSON -- THING -- WHATEVER
THEY CALL IT -- FOR DODGE,
WHICH MEANS I'M LOOKIN'
AT A NEW TRUCK.
AND IT BETTER
NOT BE DIGITAL.
UNCLE RED.
UNCLE RED,
THE PROOFS ARE HERE,
WHICH IS ADVERTISING
TALK FOR SAMPLES.
OH, YEAH.
I KNOW.
IS IT A SHOT OF ME
DRIVING A SHINY NEW VAN?
NO, NO, IT'S JUST YOU AND
THE GIRLS IN THE HOT TUB.
WOW!
ARE THOSE REAL,
DO YOU THINK?
AH, NO!
THOSE TEETH ARE CAPPED.
I DON'T SEE
ANY PRODUCT.
WHERE'S THE PRODUCT?
WELL, IT'S INFERRED.
IT'S UNDER THE WATER.
THERE'S A TRUCK
IN THE HOT TUB?
A T-T-TRUCK?
WHY WOULD THERE BE A TRUCK?
OH! I SEE
YOUR CONFUSION.
YEAH, THE COMPANY'S
PRONOUNCED "DODGE,"
BUT IT'S SPELLED
D-O-J.
THEY'RE SWEDISH.
SO THEY DON'T
MAKE TRUCKS?
NO, THEY MAKE
ADULT DIAPERS.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME!
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD,
HAROLD.
BUT NOBODY'S TO FIND OUT
ABOUT THIS, OKAY?
ABSOLUTELY.
ALL RIGHT. GREAT.
OKAY, UH,
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
UH, I HAVE GREAT NEWS.
UM, THE NEXT TIME
WE GO TO THE MOVIES,
I'LL BE ABLE TO WATCH
THE WHOLE THING.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN.
HAVE A SEAT.
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN, GUYS.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN, THERE'S PROBABLY
BEEN SOME MISINFORMATION
BEEN GOING ON
ABOUT WHAT WE
HAVE IN THESE BOXES.
IT'S ACTUALLY
A SPECIAL NEW PRODUCT
FROM, UH, SWEDEN.
AND IT'S FOR VERY
QUICK BOAT REPAIRS.
OKAY?
HIDES LEAKS.