ONCE IN A WHILE YOU READ ABOUT
SOMEBODY WITH AN EXOTIC PET
LIKE A FERRET OR
A RHINO OR SOMETHING.
TO WOMAN, YOU KNOW,
AN EXOTIC PET MIGHT BE
A STRANGE KIND OF CAT,
YOU KNOW, ORANGE EYES,
NO FUR,
EARS LIKE MR. SPOCK.
BUT THE KIND OF EXOTIC PETS
THAT APPEAL TO MEN,
WELL, THESE WOULD BE
TIGERS, FALCONS, COBRAS.
THESE ANIMALS ARE
LIVING WEAPONS.
YOU DON'T GO PLAY IN A
PARK WITH THESE BABIES.
YOU DON'T DRESS THEM UP
IN LITTLE OUTFITS.
YOU DON'T LET THEM SIT IN YOUR
LAP WHILE YOU WATCH RESCUE 911,
UNLESS YOU WANT
TO BE ON IT.
IT'S NOT SMART OR CORRECT,
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT MAKES US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red: STAY TUNED FOR TIPS ON
APPLIANCE REPAIR,
AND BILL AND I UNFORTUNATELY
WENT OUT SKEET SHOOTING
AND HAD A LITTLE
ACCIDENT... OH BOY.
HAROLD IS VERY UPSET
TO HEAR ABOUT THAT.
AND EDGAR MONTROSE
IS HERE TO SHOW US
SOME OF THE DELICACIES
OF WORKING WITH DYNAMITE.
AND NOW HERE IS THE
BIG KAHUNA OF POSSUM LODGE,
THE REASON GOD CREATED
THE WORD APOLOGIZE,
MY UNCLE RED GREEN!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Red: THANK YOU.
AND HERE IS THE MAIN REASON
I HAVE TO APOLOGIZE,
MY NEPHEW HAROLD.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
BIT OF A MAJOR CRIME SPREE
OVER AT BUSTER HADFIELD'S
HOUSE THIS WEEK.
ALL OF HIS LAWN ORNAMENTS
WERE STOLEN.
ALL OF THEM?
THE FAT LADY BENT OVER,
SNOW WHITE AND THE 7
PINK FLAMINGOES,
THE GOAT, THE COW
AND BAMBI WITH
THE EAR SHOT OFF?
YEAH, AND THE
OVERSIZED MUSHROOMS
AND THE FIBERGLASS
FLUORESCENT SANTA CLAUS
AND THE MOTORIZED SHEEP
AND EVEN THE BIG
UNITED WAY THERMOMETER.
WOW!
MARY AND HER
LITTLE PLYWOOD LAMB,
THE NEON JAMES DEAN,
THE ENTIRE CAST OF
THE WIZARD OF OZ?
YEAH, ALL THE STUFF UP
ON THE WALLS OF THE
HOUSE TOO, HAROLD.
THE BUTTERFLIES,
THE HALLOWEEN PUMPKINS
AND THAT NATIVITY SCENE
WITH THE THREE
WISE SMURFS.
SO WHAT'S BUSTER
GOING TO DO NOW?
WELL, HE'S GOING TO
NEED A NEW LAWN
FOR STARTERS.
HE'S GOT NOTHING BUT
HOLES THERE NOW.
HE OUGHT TO TURN IT INTO A
MINIATURE GOLF COURSE.
THAT'S WHAT PEOPLE ALREADY
THOUGHT IT WAS.
NO, HAROLD, HE'S GOING
TO RENT A GUARD DOG.
THAT'S THE MAN'S WAY,
REVENGE FIRST,
SOLUTIONS LATER.
YOU GET ONE OF THEM
DOBERMAN PINSCHERS,
YOU KNOW THE KIND THAT
PINCE A BURGLAR RIGHT
IN THE DOBERMAN.
OH, I DON'T
LIKE THAT IDEA.
OH, THEY SCARE
ME THOSE DOGS.
THEY GOT BIG FEROCIOUS TEETH
AND LITTLE SHORT HAIR,
AND THEY LOOK
WEIRD AS ANYTHING.
GRRR. GRRR. GRRR!
PEOPLE IN GLASS
HOUSES, HAROLD.
OH I OFTEN CAN GUESS
HOW LONG
THEY'VE BEEN WITH
BY THE VOLUME AT
WHICH THEY YELL
THE ARGUMENT NOISE LEVEL
GOES UP EVERY YEAR
AFTER TEN YEARS YOU
REALLY CAN TELL
HE GRUNTS AND COMPLAINS
AND STARTS TO FIGHT
HE BELLOWS AND
ROARS LIKE A BEAR
AND LIKELY AS NOT SHE'LL
SNEAK OFF IN THE NIGHT
TO GO HAVE A
QUIET AFFAIR
THIS WEEK ON MEET
YOUR MEMBER,
WE'RE GOING TO FIND OUT
A LITTLE BIT MORE ABOUT
EXPLOSIVE EXPERT,
EDGAR K.B.
MONTROSE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, RED, IF WE'RE GOING
TO MEET OUR MEMBERS,
AND IT SOUNDED
LIKE WE WERE,
WELL, I JUST WANTED TO SAY
THAT I'M NOT REALLY AN
EXPLOSIVES EXPERT,
I JUST WATCH A LOT OF
ROAD RUNNER CARTOONS.
ALL RIGHT, THEN, MAYBE WE'LL
TALK A LITTLE BIT MORE
PERSONALLY,
YOU KNOW, YOUR GROWING UP,
YOUR FAMILY LIFE,
THAT TYPE OF THING.
OKAY, SURE, RED.
OKAY.
WELL, I WAS BORN
IN SASKATCHEWAN UP
NEAR SANTA BOYA.
BUT I DIDN'T REALLY FIT IN
WITH THOSE NARROW MINDED
NITPICKERS.
YOU KNOW THEY WERE ALWAYS
SAYING THINGS LIKE,
SHOULDN'T YOU HAVE A LICENSE
TO HANDLE EXPLOSIVES?
OR SHOULDN'T YOU BE
USING A LONGER WICK?
OR WHERE DID THE
SCHOOLHOUSE GO?
YOU KNOW,
THAT SORT OF THING.
THAT'S A SECRET, RED,
KNOWING WHERE TO
PLACE YOUR CHARGES.
WELL, I'M NOT GREAT
AT PAYING MY BILLS,
BUT I DEFINITELY WOULD
NOT STIFF THE GUY WITH
THE DYNAMITE.
YEAH. YEAH.
LIKE YOU SAID,
I GOT FED UP.
SO I LEFT CIVILIAN LIFE
AND I JOINED THE MILITARY
BUT THAT ONLY LASTED
THREE WEEKS.
DISHONOURABLE DISCHARGE?
DISCHARGE, I'LL SAY SO,
YOU COULD HEAR IT AND SEE
IT FOR 20 MILES AND ALL
THE WAY AROUND.
BLEW UP THE
OFFICERS' MESS.
TURNS OUT THEY WERE JUST
THINKING ABOUT BUILDING
A NEW ONE.
WELL, YOU KNOW, EDGAR,
IT SOUNDS TO ME LIKE
YOU HAVE TROUBLE MAKING
FRIENDSHIPS AND RELATIONSHIPS
LAST ANY LENGTH OF TIME.
WELL, YEAH, RED, I DON'T
REALLY HAVE ANY FRIENDS
AND I'VE YET TO MEET
THE KIND OF WOMAN
WHO ENJOYS SITTING ON THE BACK
PORCH ON A SATURDAY NIGHT
WHILE I BLOW A
FULL-GROWN DOUGLAS FIR
RIGHT CLEAN
ACROSS THE LAKE.
YOU KNOW WITH BUSTER HADFIELD
BEING ROBBED AND ALL,
I THOUGHT I WOULD TAKE THIS
WEEK'S HANDYMAN CORNER
AND SHOW YOU HOW YOU CAN
MAKE YOUR VERY OWN HOME
SECURITY SYSTEM
USING COMMON
HOUSEHOLD APPLIANCES.
I'M GUESSING YOU PROBABLY
DON'T HAVE AN INFRARED
MOTION SENSOR
AND A SILENT ALARM SITTING
THERE IN YOUR SOCK DRAWER,
BUT I BET A BUNCH OF
YOU HAVE, SAY, A TOASTER
AND POSSIBLY EVEN ONE OF
THESE DART BOARD UNITS,
AND YOU CAN
COMBINE THESE THINGS
TO MAKE A FOOT ACTIVATED
ANTI-THEFT PAIN DEVICE.
A BURGLAR STEPS ON THIS...
HE'S TOAST.
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS BERNICE
AND I ARE SUCH HEAVY SLEEPERS
THAT A BURGLAR IS GOING TO
HAVE TO COME ACTUALLY RIGHT
UP INTO THE BEDROOM
AND TAKE OUR PILLOWCASES
OR OUR PYJAMAS OR OUR SHEETS
OR SOME OF THOSE DEVICES
THAT BERNICE KEEPS IN
THE END TABLE
BEFORE WE'LL EVER
NOTICE THAT HE'S THERE.
SO I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW
TO MAKE AN ANTI-THEFT
ALARM DEVICE
THAT WILL BE TRIGGERED ANY
TIME A BURGLAR JIMMIES
OPEN A DOOR
OR EVEN A WINDOW.
BUT TO DO THAT YOU'RE GOING
TO NEED SOME OF THE LARGER
HOUSEHOLD APPLIANCES...
A STOVE, A FRIDGE
AND A TELEVISION SET.
ALL RIGHT, FIRST OF ALL,
FROM THE STOVE WE NEED THIS,
[ BUZZING THEN RINGS ]
A BUZZER FROM
THE CAKE TIMER.
NOW, THAT'S NOT LOUD ENOUGH
YET TO SCARE A BURGLAR
BUT IT WILL BE
ONCE WE HOOK IT UP TO
THE SPEAKER FROM THE
TELEVISION SET.
AND FROM THE REFRIGERATOR
WE NEED THIS,
THE PRESSURE SENSITIVE LIGHT
SWITCH THAT ACTIVATES
THE LIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, NOW YOU WANT TO
REMOVE EACH OF THOSE THINGS
FROM EACH OF THE
THREE APPLIANCES.
ALL RIGHT, GETTING THESE PARTS
OUT IS GOING TO TAKE A LITTLE
LONGER THAN I THOUGHT,
SO WHY DON'T YOU GET
BACK TO THE SHOW
AND I'LL JUST KIND OF
GET THEM OUT OF HERE.
Red: STAY TUNED AS BILL AND
I GO SKEET... SHOOTING, HMM.
AND RANGER GORD PRETENDS
TO BE IN BETTER SHAPE
THAN I'M IN.
LAST WEEK MY WIFE FOUND SOME
PICTURES OF ME WHEN I
WAS A TEENAGER.
YES, THEY HAD
PHOTOGRAPHY BACK THEN.
SHOULD HAVE SEEN
THE WAY I DRESSED,
THE WAY I COMBED MY
HAIR AND MY SHOES.
PRETTY SCARY STUFF.
I DIDN'T LOOK NEARLY SHARP
AS I DO NOW, OF COURSE.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT MADE
ME FEEL BETTER
WAS THINKING ABOUT THE
TEENAGERS OF TODAY
AND HOW THEY'RE GOING TO BE
HUMILIATED LOOKING BACK
AT HOW THEY LOOKED 15 OR 20
YEARS DOWN THE ROAD, YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, IMAGINE SOME FUTURE
VICE PRESIDENT OF I.B.M.
PASSING AROUND PICTURES OF
HIMSELF WITH A PURPLE MOHAWK,
CUTLERY FOR EARRINGS,
A DRAGON TATTOOED ON
HIS EXPOSED STOMACH
AND JEANS SO BAGGY
IN THE CROTCH
YOU GOT ROOM FOR
A FAMILY OF GROUNDHOGS.
SO IF YOU GOT A KID AT HOME
WHO LOOKS LIKE AN EXTRA
FROM "ROAD WARRIOR,"
TAKE LOTS OF
PICTURE OF HIM NOW,
THEN WHEN HE WISES UP
AND GETS RESPECTABLE,
YOU CAN SELL
THEM BACK TO HIM
ONE PICTURE AT A TIME.
SURE BEATS SAVING YOUR OWN
MONEY FOR RETIREMENT,
DOESN'T IT?
WELL, WE'VE HAD A COUPLE OF
PROBLEMS WITH BUSTER'S
GUARD DOG BRUTUS.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE HE
SHOULDN'T HAVE RENTED
THE MOST FEROCIOUS
DOG IN THE KENNEL.
THE ATTACK DOG GOT AWAY?
BRUTUS IS ON THE LOOSE?
UNCLE RED,
THEY CAN SMELL FEAR!
NOW, DON'T WORRY,
HAROLD.
BRUTUS IS FREE TO GO
ANYWHERE HE WANTS,
BUT FOR SOME REASON
HE'S JUST STAYING THERE
PATROLLING
BUSTER'S FRONT LAWN.
WELL, BUSTER WON'T
BE GETTING ANY MAIL
OR ANY VISITORS.
YEAH, THAT'S THE UPSIDE.
THE DOWNSIDE BEING THAT
BUSTER IS ACTUALLY TRAPPED
IN HIS OWN HOUSE.
TRAPPED, OH NO,
IMAGINE THE IRONY,
HIRING AN ANIMAL TO
PROTECT YOUR INTERESTS
AND THEN
HE TURNS ON YOU.
YEAH, I CAN IMAGINE THAT
MR. PRODUCER/DIRECTOR.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
GOING TO DO?
WELL, WE'VE COME UP
WITH A PLAN THAT
WE CALL
COWERING INDOORS.
OTHER THAN THAT WE'RE
GOING TO RUN BACK AND
FORTH BETWEEN OUR VEHICLES
THROWING WIENIES OVER
OUR SHOULDERS TO
DISTRACT BRUTUS.
WELL, THERE IS A LESSON TO BE
LEARNED HERE, UNCLE RED.
BUSTER SHOULD HAVE
PHONED THE POLICE
AS SOON AS HIS LAWN
ORNAMENTS WERE STOLEN,
BUT INSTEAD HE CHOSE
THE ROUTE OF REVENGE,
AND NOW,
LIKE A PRISONER,
HE IS TRAPPED IN HIS
OWN HOME, HA HA!
I HOPE YOU ARE LEARNING
FROM HIS MISTAKE.
YES, WE ARE,
HAROLD.
WE'RE ALL GOING
TO GET GUARD DOGS
'CAUSE THAT GUARD DOG
IS ON THE LOOSE AND
OUR GUARD DOGS
WILL PROTECT US FROM
THAT GUARD DOG.
EVERYONE AT POSSUM LAKE
IS GETTING A GUARD DOG?
YES, SIR.
NOT EVERYBODY IS GETTING
A DOBERMAN THOUGH.
STINKY'S GOT A COUGAR
IN HIS FRONT LAWN.
A LIVE COUGAR?
WELL, IT RUNS.
IT'S A '74.
GOT THE PLYWOOD SPOILER
ON THERE, THE MOON RIMS.
HE PAINTED HER UP
LIKE A RAINBOW TROUT.
OKAY, YEAH,
THAT IS SCARY.
HEY, NOBODY HAS EVER STOLEN
ANYTHING FROM STINKY.
NO, TOO EASY
TO TRACE.
NOPE.
ROLLING THERE,
HAROLD?
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE UP HERE
AT FIRE TOWER 13 WITH
RANGER GORD.
YOU'RE GOING TO TELL US
ALL ABOUT OUTDOOR SECURITY.
THANK, RED.
LET ME SHOW YOU MY
SECURITY SYSTEM.
NOW, I DON'T ACTUALLY
HAVE ELECTRICITY FOR
AN ALARM
AND I USED TO HAVE
A GUARD DOG,
BUT HE COULDN'T
TAKE THE LONELINESS.
SO YOU HAVE NO SECURITY
SYSTEM AT ALL GORD?
WELL, THAT'S NOT
ENTIRELY TRUE, RED.
YOU SEE, I LIVE
IN THIS 100-FOOT TOWER
ATOP A 200 FOOT HILL.
NOW, I DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT THE CRIMINAL MIND,
OF COURSE,
BUT THE CRIMINAL BODY
TENDS NOT TO BE
IN THE BEST PHYSICAL
CONDITION.
SO THE FACT IS, RED,
THAT NOT A LOT OF
CRIMINALS CAN MAKE IT
TO THE TOP OF MY TOWER
TO STEAL MY STUFF.
YOU DON'T HAVE ALL THAT
MUCH STUFF THAT'S WORTH
STEALING, DO YOU GORD?
OH, THAT'S NOT ALL
ENTIRELY TRUE
EITHER, RED.
YOU SEE, I'VE GOT ALL
SORTS OF THINGS UP HERE.
IN FACT, WELL, THERE'S
MY GRANDMOTHER'S
SILVERWARE SET
RIGHT OVER BY YOUR
FOOT, HAROLD.
BE CAREFUL.
HAROLD, BE CAREFUL.
[ CUTLERY CLATTERING ]
NO!
Red:
WAS THAT THE CAMERA?
NO, THAT'S NEXT.
NO.
Red: SOMETHING A LITTLE MORE
SOPHISTICATED THIS WEEK
ON ADVENTURES WITH BILL,
SOME SKEET SHOOTING.
I WAS A LATE ARRIVING,
I DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING TO WEAR.
BILL APPARENTLY
STARTED WITHOUT ME.
AND HE FOLLOWS THE SKEET...
THERE IT IS THERE.
NOW, BILL, BILL,
BILL, BILL, BILL...
THANK YOU, BILL.
YEAH, YEAH, YOU GOT IT.
YOU SHOULD BE DARN
PROUD OF YOURSELF.
ANYWAY, THIS IS A KIND
OF NEAT LITTLE RIG,
KIND OF A SKEET THROWER.
AND, YEAH,
I WASN'T -- SORRY.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
SO WHAT IT DOES IS HE MOUNTS
THE LITTLE CLAY SKEETS --
CLAY SKEETS, GOOD NAME FOR
A COUNTRY WESTERN SINGER,
HE MOUNTS THEM INTO
THE SKEET THROWER
AND THEN THE IDEA IS THAT
THERE'S APPARENTLY A TRIGGER
THING WHICH I -- OH.
I SEE HOW THAT WORKS.
YOU ALL RIGHT
THERE, BILL?
I REMEMBER BILL
AS BEING TALLER.
BUT I CAN GET THE SKEET.
THAT'S 100 POINTS,
I BELIEVE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, I WAS GOING TO
TAKE A CHANCE AT THIS MYSELF.
I'VE NEVER DONE
ANY SKEET SHOOTING,
BUT I REALLY FELT THAT
GARBAGE CAN WAS KIND OF --
HE WOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO PULL BACK --
AND HE WAS GOING TO WALK
INTO THAT WHEN HE HITS IT.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY HE JUST
ANCHORED HER ON THE ONE SIDE,
SO AS HE'S MOVING HE'S
KIND OF CHANGING THE --
I DON'T REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED
OVER THE NEXT FEW MINUTES.
I DON'T KNOW
WHY THAT IS.
AND THEN SUDDENLY, YOU KNOW,
ALL OF A SUDDEN
I WAS KIND OF AWARE
I WAS SKEET SHOOTING
WITH BILL.
AND WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
ALL RIGHT, WELL, HE MUST
HAVE BLANKED OUT THERE.
ALL RIGHT, SO WE'RE GOING TO
GIVE HER ANOTHER TRY HERE.
SO HE SETS IT UP.
AND I'M JUST
WAITING TO SHOOT.
AND I JUST --
I DON'T WANT --
I DON'T WANT TO TAKE MY
EYE OFF HIM BUT APPARENTLY
HE'S FORGOTTEN TO COCK
THE SKEET THROWER.
THERE HE GOES.
SO THEN HE NOTICES HIS
SHOE LACE WAS UNDONE,
WHICH IS ALWAYS
DANGEROUS KIDS.
FOR YOU KIDS OUT THERE,
NEVER GO OUT INTO THE WOODS
WITH A SKEET SHOOTER AND A
LOADED RIFLE WITH YOUR
SHOE LACES -- WHOOPS.
BLACKED OUT AGAIN.
FUNNY HOW THAT HAPPENS.
MAYBE'M GETTING OLDER.
[ GUNSHOT ]
I MISSED HIM.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE ALL SET.
THERE WE GO.
I'M A LITTLE FED UP NOW
AND I'M STARTING TO REALIZE
THE BEST FUTURE FOR ME IN
SKEET SHOOTING IS RIGHT HERE.
[ GUNSHOT ]
THERE WE GO, DEAD.
SEE YOU LATER, BILL.
THERE'S YOUR GUN BACK.
OH AND HERE'S YOUR SKEET!
Red: COMING UP,
WE'RE GOING TO VISIT
DALTON'S STORE/LANDFILL SITE
AND HAROLD DECIDES TO FACE
THE GUARD DOG LIKE A MAN.
WELL, AS SO OFTEN HAPPENS
UP HERE AT THE LODGE,
THIS GUARD DOG THING HAS GOTTEN
INTO A BIT OF A COMPETITION.
FLINTY McCLINTOCK GOT
HIMSELF A GERMAN SHEPHERD,
EAST GERMAN I THINK,
ARTIE KAY WENT
WITH THE GREAT DANE,
OLD MAN SEDGWICK GOT A
CHIHUAHUA BUT HE'S GOT
HER ON STEROIDS.
AND, NOW, JUNIOR SINGLETON
WENT THE OTHER WAY,
HE GOT HIMSELF A CAT.
YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY,
THAT'S NOT SO UNUSUAL.
THE CHINESE USED TO USE
SIAMESE CATS TO PROTECT
THEIR PALACES.
THIS IS A MOUNTAIN
LION, HAROLD.
YEAH, IT ESCAPED
FROM THE LION SAFARI
OR AT LEAST THAT'S
WHAT JUNIOR'S GOING
TO TELL THEM
WHEN THEY NOTICE
IT'S MISSING.
YOU GUYS BETTER BE CAREFUL
WITH AN ANIMAL LIKE THAT!
THEY'RE NOT USED TO
SEEING PEOPLE, YOU KNOW,
UNLESS THEY'RE IN CARS, YOU
KNOW, SNAPPING PICTURES
AND TRYING TO SNEAK SNACK
FOOD OUT LITTLE CRACKS
IN WINDOWS.
WELL, I WOULDN'T
WORRY, HAROLD.
I'M SURE IF THE MOUNTAIN LION
IS UPSET IN ANY WAY,
HE'LL LET US KNOW.
SO NOW MOOSE IS
LOOKING TO RENT
A BEAR,
AND STINKY IS GOING
TO TRY TO BRING AN
ALLIGATOR IN.
I JUST THINK THE
COMPETITION IS SO CHILDISH.
THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU ALWAYS LOSE.
SO I'M THINKING OF GOING
HIGH TECH WITH MINE.
I'M GOING TO BUILD MYSELF
A RADIO CONTROLLED
ELECTRONIC DOG.
OH BOY,
A ROBO ROTTWEILER.
YEAH, I'VE ALREADY GOT
THE RADIO CONTROLLER
RIGHT HERE.
WHAT FREQUENCY
IS THAT ON?
107.3.
HEY, THAT'S THE SAME AS
MY VIDEO EFFECTS MACHINE.
THAT DIDN'T LOOK SO HARD.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
GET OUT OF MY HOUSE, BUDDY.
YOU WANT COMPETITION,
I'LL GIVE YOU COMPETITION!
ALL RIGHT, I FINALLY GOT THE
COMPONENTS OUT OF THE
THREE APPLIANCES.
IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN A LOT EASIER
IF SOMEONE HADN'T
STOLEN MY SCREWDRIVER.
ANYWAY, NOW I CAN SHOW YOU
HOW TO ASSEMBLE THESE
THREE THINGS
INTO YOUR VERY OWN
HOME SECURITY SYSTEM.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, I'M JUST
USING THIS CHEST AND
THE LID OF IT
AS KIND OF AN EXAMPLE OF
HOW YOU'D RIG UP A DOOR.
I GOT THE PRESSURE SENSITIVE
SWITCH FROM THE FRIDGE
DOWN HERE HOOKED INTO
WHERE THE DOOR CLOSES,
AND THAT WIRING GOES UP
THROUGH THE STOVE BUZZER,
WHICH IS NOW WIRED INTO
OUR TELEVISION SPEAKER.
SO WHEN A BURGLAR COMES
IN SAY A DOOR OR A WINDOW,
WHATEVER YOU GOT RIGGED LIKE
THIS,
ALL OF A SUDDEN...
[ HIGH-PITCHED BEEPING ]
WHOA, YOU'RE GOING
TO HEAR THAT.
THAT WILL WAKE YOU UP FROM
THE DEAD, THAT ONE.
AND THEN YOU CAN CALL 911
OR SIC YOUR DOG ON THERE
OR GO DOWN THERE AND START
THROWING BASEBALL BATS
AT THE GUY,
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO DO.
AND THAT WAY YOU GET TO
PROTECT YOUR JEWELS OR YOUR --
I GUESS THAT'S A FRIDGE
AND A STOVE,
A TELEVISION SET,
WHATEVER.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
MAN!
IT'S MAIL CALL.
NO QUESTION TOO BIG,
NO ANSWER TOO SMALL.
OUR FIRST LETTER IS FROM
BRINKMAN HOOFNER,
AND IT'S FROM,
OH, ACME, MISSOURI.
OH, LOOK, HE'S MADE US SOME
ARTWORK, ISN'T THAT NICE?
LOOK AT THAT.
MISSION INPOSSUMVILLE.
[ LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY ]
[ CHUCKLING ]
I DON'T GET THAT.
WELL, HAROLD,
YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE
"MISSION IMPOSSIBLE,"
MISSION IN POSSUM VILLE.
OHHHH! WHOO!
YOU STILL DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU, HAROLD?
NO, NOT REALLY.
HERE'S ANOTHER ONE.
THIS IS FROM KIM
FROM FLATROCK, MICHIGAN.
SHE WRITES: "DEAR RED,
HOW OLD ARE YOU?"
OH BOY, THAT'S A
TOUGH ONE, KIM,
BECAUSE WE TAPE THE SHOW
THREE DAYS BEFORE IT
GOES ON THE AIR
SO THAT WE HAVE TIME
TO GO HOME AND FIGURE OUT
HOW THE V.C.R.s
WORK AND SO ON.
SO IF I SAID I WAS 44 AND
THEN MY BIRTHDAY WAS TOMORROW
AND THEN I WOULD GO ON
THE AIR SAYING I WAS 44,
I WOULD BE 45 BY THEN.
AND THEN IF YOU DIDN'T
SEE THAT SHOW,
IT WOULD BE SIX MONTHS
LATER FOR THE RERUN,
AND THEN, YOU KNOW, I WOULD
BE SIX MONTHS OFF ON
THE AGE THING.
AND THEN, OF COURSE,
IF IT -- IF IT --
IF IT GOT INTO A LOT
OF RERUNS --
SOME OF THESE SHOWS
GO ON FOR YEARS,
THEY JUST STAY THERE
FOREVER LIKE A BAD SMELL.
WHAT DO YOU
CALL THAT, HAROLD?
SYNDICATION.
YEAH, SYNDICATION,
YEAH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW BUT OF COURSE
THAT'S WHERE THE BIG BUCKS ARE
REALLY, YOU KNOW.
I HOPE OUR SHOW GOES
INTO SYNDICATION.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
ALL WE NEED IS LIKE
A MUCH BETTER SHOW.
I THINK WE'RE CLOSE TO
HAVING A MUCH BETTER ONE.
YOU BETTER
BELIEVE IT.
SO I THINK THE SAFEST
ANSWER, KIM, THERE IS
THAT WHEN YOU SEE THIS SHOW,
I'M 10 YEARS, 6 MONTHS
AND 3 DAYS YOUNGER
THAN I LOOK RIGHT NOW.
SO YOU'RE IN YOUR
EARLY 60s THEN.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
OH, MISSION INPOSSUMVILLE!
YOU STILL DON'T
GET IT, DO YOU?
NOT A THING.
WE'RE OUT HERE BY THE MAIN
HIGHWAY AT HUMPHRIES
EVERYTHING STORE
TO LEARN A LITTLE BIT
MORE ABOUT ANTIQUES,
COLLECTIBLES AND CURIOS
FROM STORE OWNER,
DALTON HUMPHRIES.
NOW, DALTON, WHAT IS
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
AN ANTIQUE,
A COLLECTIBLE, A CURIO
OR JUST A PIECE OF
KITSCHY CRAPOLLA?
ABOUT $500
PROFIT FOR ME.
LET'S HAVE A LOOK.
NOW, THIS RADIO IS A CLASSIC
ADDISON, CIRCA 1930,
AND AT AUCTION THIS
WOULD FETCH $2,500.
OH MY GOSH!
YEAH.
HOW MUCH WOULD IT GET IF
IT WASN'T ALL BAFFED UP
LIKE THAT?
$200.
YOU SEE, WHAT YOU
CALL "BAFFED UP"
IS WHAT A CUSTOMER
CALLS CHARACTER.
OH I SEE.
YOU SEE BEFORE A GUY
PLOPS DOWN $2500,
HE WANTS TO KNOW A LITTLE
BIT ABOUT THE RADIO,
SO I WOULD POINT OUT TO
HIM THE BEAUTIFUL GRAIN
OF THIS TORTOISE SHELL CASE,
THE CLASSIC THREE-TUBE
ELECTRONICS INSIDE,
THE LOVELY DIAL HERE,
WHICH IS EXTREMELY RARE,
AND ENAMELED ON COPPER,
THE BAKELITE KNOBS
WHICH ARE INLAID WITH
MOTHER OF PEARL,
VERY RARE,
VERY GOOD QUALITY,
AND THESE PSEUDO-CERAMIC BARS
WHICH WERE HANDCRAFTED
BY A CERAMICIST BY THE
NAME OF JOHN REYNOLDS.
ALL AND ALL AN INCREDIBLE
PIECE OF HISTORY.
WOW!
YOU MADE THAT WHOLE
THING UP, DIDN'T YOU?
EVERY LAST WORD, RED.
QUITE A PERFORMANCE.
YEAH, WELL I WOULD SAY
IT'S WORTH $2,500.
THIS RADIO RIGHT HERE
I KIND OF GOT MY EYE ON.
DESCRIBE THAT ONE
THERE FOR US.
IT'S JUNK.
OH.
IT'S NOT OLD, IT WORKS,
AND IT'S NOT UGLY.
TWO BUCKS TOPS.
SOLD.
I'LL BREAK THIS OPEN
AND USE THE PARTS FOR MY
RADIO CONTROLLED GUARD DOG.
YEAH, WELL, CAN I HAVE THE
BROKEN CASE PIECES, PLEASE?
IT WILL BE
ALL SMASHED UP.
EXACTLY, IT COULD BE
WORTH QUITE A BIT.
"LOOKING FOR SHOES AT
A BARGAIN PRICE?
"WHY NOT COME BY STINKY
PETERSON'S ROADSIDE
SHOE ROUNDUP.
"WE HAVE ONE
OF A KIND SHOES,
"ALL SINGLES, ALL FOUND
ALONG THE SIDE OF THE ROAD,
"LEFTS AND RIGHTS, NO PAIRS,
"SINGLE OXFORDS,
SINGLE BOOTS,
"EVEN A SINGLE PAIR
OF LARGE FURRY SLIPPERS,
"WHICH MAY ACTUALLY BE A DEAD
RACCOON, I'M NOT SURE."
GOD BLESS THE
ENTREPRENEURIAL SPIRIT
OF THE SMALL BUSINESSMAN.
WELL, WE GOT THAT GUARD DOG
DOBERMAN PINSCHER BRUTUS
KIND OF SETTLED DOWN,
BUT BOY -- THANKS TO MY
REMOTE CONTROLLED ROBO DOG
AS A MATTER OF FACT.
STRANGEST THING,
THOUGH,
I TURNED THE THING ON
AND IT JUST GOES NUTS,
GOES RIGHT AFTER
MY LEG THERE,
RUNS AROUND SPRAYING
MACHINE OIL ON ALL
THE FIRE HYDRANTS.
AND THEN IT SCARED AWAY
THE DOG, IT RAN OFF,
WE WERE ALL OKAY.
BUT THE STRANGEST THING
WAS I HAVE NO IDEA WHY
THAT HAPPENED?
WHY WOULD IT
GO BALLISTIC?
I DIDN'T EVEN HAVE THE
RADIO CONTROLLER
TURNED ON.
THAT'S THE
STRANGEST THING.
I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU
SOLVED THE ROBBERY OF
THE LAWN ORNAMENTS.
WHY DON'T YOU
TELL ME ALL ABOUT THAT?
YEAH, I DID.
HAROLD, WERE YOU WORKING
ON THAT THING ABOUT
20 MINUTES AGO?
NO.
WELL, I WAS --
YOU SHOULD TELL ME ABOUT
HOW YOU SOLVED THAT BIG
ROBBERY BECAUSE --
AND TELL THEM BECAUSE
THEY WANT TO KNOW.
THEY'RE WATCHING,
YOU BETTER TELL THEM.
ALL RIGHT,
WELL, IT TURNS OUT --
TURNS OUT BUSTER HADFIELD'S
WIFE HAD DONATED ALL
OF THE ORNAMENTS
TO THE ST.VINCENT DE PAUL
BUNYON CENTRE FOR KINDLING.
I GUESS SHE DIDN'T LIKE
THE LAWN DECOR AS MUCH
AS BUSTER DID, HUH?
WELL, HE GOT THE LAST
LAUGH, HAROLD,
BECAUSE ALL THE TIME HE
WAS TRAPPED IN THE HOUSE,
HE BUILT A HUGE
GUARD DOG LAWN
ORNAMENT,
9 FEET LONG, GREEN AND
ORANGE WITH NEON EYES,
MOTORIZED TAIL,
AND HE PUT A CAR ALARM IN IT
SO NOBODY CAN STEAL IT.
WELL, I DON'T THINK
THAT WILL BE A PROBLEM.
[ ANIMAL ROARING ]
WHAT'S THAT?
OH, I FORGOT
TO TELL YOU,
I GOT A GUARD DOG
FOR THE LODGE.
REALLY? WHY?
YEAH, I'LL BRING HIM IN.
YOU STAND BACK.
OH. NO.
NO, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
KILLER.
KILLER, GOOD NAME.
COME ON, BOY.
DOWN BOY.
EASY BOY.
COME HERE.
THERE WE GO.
THERE WE ARE.
THAT'S A GUARD DOG?
DON'T MAKE A
FALSE MOVE, HAROLD,
HE CAN GO AT
THE DROP OF A HAT.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
OH, THAT'S THE CRY OF THE
POSSUM, I GUESS I'M GOING.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'M GOING TO TRY TO SETTLE
KILLER DOWN BEFORE I COME DOWN.
EASY BOY. EASY.
EASY. EASY.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I WAS KIND OF HOPING WE
COULD TURN KILLER HERE
INTO A HUNTING DOG,
THE THEORY BEING THAT WE GET
THE MOOSE LAUGHING THEN
IT'S ALL OVER.
OR MAYBE WE COULD
MAKE HIM A PET.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE AT
POSSUM LODGE, UNTIL NEXT TIME,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, ALL RISE.
OH, SORRY, YOU ARE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN, I GUESS.
WHAT IS THIS, HAROLD?