YOU KNOW, A LOT OF GUYS BRAG
ABOUT HOW THEY WEAR
THE PANTS IN THE FAMILY.
WHAT THEY DON'T MENTION
TO THEIR BUDDIES
IS THAT THEIR WIFE TELLS
THEM WHAT PANTS TO WEAR
AND WHEN TO WEAR 'EM
AND TO STOP TALKING
TO YOUR IDIOT FRIENDS
ABOUT THEIR MARRIAGE ANYWAY!
SEE, WOMEN HAVE ALL KINDS
OF RULES ABOUT CLOTHES.
JEANS ARE OKAY FOR HANGING
AROUND THE HOUSE
OR FOR THE HARDWARE STORE
OR WHENEVER YOU
GO SOMEWHERE ALONE.
BUT, WHEN
COMPANY'S COMIN',
YOU GOTTA GO
ALL THE WAY UPSTAIRS
AND PUT ON SOMETHING NICE.
SO I GOT TO THINKING,
WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
IF YOU COULD WEAR THE
SAME PANTS ALL THE TIME?
WELL, YOU CAN.
JUST GET YOURSELF
A PAIR OF JEANS
ONE SIZE BIGGER THAN
YOU NORMALLY WEAR.
ACTUALLY, BETTER MAKE IT
TWO SIZES BIGGER.
ONE SIZE BIGGER IS PROBABLY
WHAT YOU SHOULD BE WEARING NOW.
NEXT, YOU TURN YOUR
GOOD PANTS INSIDE OUT,
AND THEN YOU STUFF 'EM
INSIDE THE OVERSIZED JEANS.
THEN YOU JUST SEW
'EM TOGETHER.
OR SINCE YOU HAVE
NO IDEA HOW TO SEW,
USE THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON.
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
ONCE YOU GET EVERYTHING
DUCT TAPED INTO PLACE,
YOU'VE GOT SOMETHING BETTER
THAN A REVERSIBLE JACKET;
YOU'VE GOT REVERSIBLE PANTS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
HAD A BIT OF A SETBACK
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
I WAS TOWING THE
BACKHOE THROUGH TOWN,
AND I WENT BY THE TOWN HALL.
YOU KNOW, I NEVER NOTICED
THERE WAS A STATUE THERE,
AND AFTER I WENT BY IT,
THERE WASN'T.
BUT I DID THE RIGHT THING.
I TOLD THEM THAT
I HAD DONE IT...
BECAUSE A WHOLE BUNCH
OF PEOPLE SAW ME DO IT.
AND MY PUNISHMENT IS
I GOTTA REPLACE THE STATUE.
I WAS THINKING
OF USING HAROLD
JUST TO SEE IF HE COULD
STAND STILL FOR MORE
THAN FIVE SECONDS.
UNCLE RED! UNCLE RED!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SO -- SO WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE STATUE DOWNTOWN?
UH, I HEARD SOMEBODY
KNOCKED IT DOWN.
YOU KNOCKED IT DOWN!
COULD BE.
I DIDN'T ASK
FOR DETAILS.
DOESN'T MATTER, HAROLD.
I TOLD THEM I WOULD REPLACE
THAT STUPID STATUE.
STUPID STATUE!
STUP --
THAT IS
SIR DON A. McJOHNALDS.
HE'S THE FOUNDER OF THE
ENTIRE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
WELL, THE WAY
I HEAR IT,
HE JUST BROUGHT
A BUNCH OF PEOPLE HERE
TO FIND OUT WHERE THE
SMELL WAS COMING FROM.
AND AFTER A COUPLE OF
MONTHS THEY GOT USED
TO IT AND STAYED.
WE DON'T NEED
TO HONOUR HIM.
UNCLE RED, THAT STATUE
IS PART OF OUR HISTORY.
WELL, HAROLD, NOW THAT
STATUE IS HISTORY.
YOU'RE GOING TO FEEL A LOT
BETTER ONCE YOU SEE MY
REPLACEMENT STATUE.
TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS BABY.
THIS HAS TO GO ON
THE FRONT LAWN OF THE
TOWN HALL, YOU KNOW.
NOT THE PARKING LOT OF WACKY
WILLIE'S FIVE AND DIME.
WELL, HAROLD,
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THIS IS AN
ATTRACTION, SEE?
THIS'LL BRING
PEOPLE TO TOWN HALL,
EVEN WHEN IT'S
NOT THEIR COURT DATE.
IT'S A WAY SMALLER
TARGET FOR PIGEONS,
AND HERE'S THE
BEST PART...
IT'S A PROFIT CENTRE.
HUH? HUH?
COME ON! COME ON!
[ RED CHUCKLING/
HAROLD WHOOPING ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FOR ONE NIGHT'S STAY
AT THIS AREA'S ONLY PLACE
THAT URGES ITS
GUESTS TO SLEEP IN...
THE POSSUM LAKE
BED & LUNCH.
IT'S OKAY TO SLEEP
LATE AT POSSUM LAKE.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO SEE ANYWAY.
OKAY, COVER YOUR EARS,
WINSTON.
UH, MR. GREEN,
YOU GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET WINSTON
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH,
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND... GO!
UH, OKAY, WINSTON,
THINK OF A CELESTIAL BODY.
SUPER MODEL.
NO, NO, THESE
COME OUT AFTER DARK.
SOME OF THEM
AREN'T VERY BRIGHT.
SURE SOUNDS LIKE
A SUPER MODEL.
OKAY, THIS IS SOMETHING
PEOPLE LIKE TO WATCH AT NIGHT.
THE NEIGHBOURS' WINDOW.
NO, NO, THIS IS UP
IN THE SKY,
AND IT'S ON FIRE.
A GUY WITH
A GAS BARBEQUE.
NO, OKAY, NO.
IF YOU WAIT LONG ENOUGH,
YOU MAY SEE ONE
OF THESE SHOOTING.
A POSTAL WORKER.
OKAY, OKAY, LISTEN.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE WHEN
YOU SAY "RATS" BACKWARDS?
DYSLEXIA.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU'RE ALMOST
OUTTA TIME, MR. GREEN.
WINSTON, YOU REMEMBER
OUR SCIENCE TEACHER?
HE GOT UP IN FRONT
OF THE CLASS AND HE SAID,
OUR SUN IS ACTUALLY...
A DOCTOR.
NO, NOT THAT KIND OF SUN;
THE ONE THAT SHINES.
WELL, WE ALL SHINE, RED.
I MEAN,
EVERYBODY'S A STAR.
THERE WE GO!
[ LOON CALLS ]
MY PAROLE OFFICER SAYS
YOU'RE NEVER TOO OLD
TO START LEARNING.
Red: HE WAS JUST TRYING
TO SELL YOU HIS COMPUTER.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
WHERE ELSE CAN YOU GET A
COMMODORE 64 FOR 50 BUCKS?
WELL, THEY'RE FREE
AT THE DUMP.
I'M TALKING
ABOUT EDUCATION.
YOU KNOW, YOUR LACK OF
EDUCATION CAN REALLY LIMIT YOU.
HAVE YOU EVER
TALKED TO SOMEBODY
WHO KNOWS A WHOLE LOT
MORE THAN YOU DO?
EVERY TIME I STEP
THROUGH THE FRONT
DOOR.
WELL, THE WAY TO CORRECT
THAT IS BY LEARNING.
FOR EXAMPLE, I KNOW THAT
IN THE SCIENTIFIC TABLE
OF ELEMENTS
THE SYMBOL FOR
LEAD IS "PB,"
WHICH STANDS
FOR "PLUMBUM."
WHEN I TELL PEOPLE
I KNOW WHAT PLUMBUM MEANS,
THEY JUST STARE
AT ME IN AWE.
YEAH, LIKE THAT!
YEAH, WELL, OKAY,
EDUCATION'S IMPORTANT,
BUT EXPERIENCE IS
A PRETTY GOOD TEACHER TOO,
LIKE WHEN I'M HAVING HEART
SURGERY OR SOMETHING,
I DON'T WANT SOME GUY WHO'S
NEVER DONE IT BEFORE.
I WANT TO BE PART
OF HIS EXPERIENCE,
NOT PART OF
HIS EDUCATION.
YEAH, BUT YOU DON'T WANT
SOMEBODY WITH NO EDUCATION,
ESPECIALLY FOR
A HEART OPERATION.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT
SO BAD WITH KIDNEYS,
BECAUSE YOU'VE
GOT TWO OF 'EM.
Dalton: YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T
NEED EDUCATION TO
BE SUCCESSFUL.
EVEL KNIEVEL, HE WAS
RICH AND FAMOUS.
HE NEVER HAD
A COLLEGE DEGREE.
Red: YEAH, BUT HE ALSO BROKE
EVERY BONE IN HIS BODY.
AND SURVIVED, HUH!
HOW MANY OF YOUR FANCY
LAWYERS COULD BREAK EVERY
BONE AND LIVE?
Red: I KNOW A LOT OF PEOPLE
WHO'D LOVE TO FIND OUT.
JUST THINK, DALTON, THOUGH,
IF EVEL HAD GOTTEN
HIMSELF AN EDUCATION,
INSTEAD OF JUST JUMPIN'
OVER BUSSES IN HIS HARLEY,
HE COULD'VE BEEN
PRESIDENT!
PRESIDENT EVEL?
YOU KNOW, I THINK IT JUST
COMES DOWN TO THE PERSON.
A LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE
HAD SUCCESS WITH A
LOT OF EDUCATION.
BUT ME, I NEVER
HAD MUCH,
BUT HEY, I'VE HAD
A HAPPY LIFE,
A FAIR BIT OF SUCCESS,
A LITTLE BIT OF WEALTH ON ME
THERE, SOME SELF-ESTEEM,
AND THE RESPECT
OF MY FRIENDS.
YOU HAVE?
AND THEN YOU
LOST IT ALL?
BOY, YOU MUST
BE BITTER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, IN MY LIFE
I'VE EXPERIENCED
THERE ARE 10 THINGS
THAT ARE IMPOSSIBLE.
THE FIRST ONE IS
BACKING UP A BOAT TRAILER.
THE OTHER NINE
ALL INVOLVE MY WIFE.
SEE, THE PROBLEM
WITH THE BOAT TRAILER IS,
YOU'VE GOT TWO
SEPARATE VEHICLES
A FLEXIBLE
BALL HITCH IN BETWEEN.
PLUS, YOU'RE DRIVING
USING YOUR MIRRORS
OR ACTUALLY TURNING
YOUR HEAD AROUND,
IF YOU'RE UNDER 25.
AND THE CAR IS PUSHING,
RATHER THAN PULLING.
SO WHEN YOU TURN ONE WAY,
THE BOAT GOES THE OTHER.
IT'S ACTUALLY A LOT LIKE
THE PROBLEMS I HAD WHEN
I WAS DATING.
I ALWAYS GOT THE OPPOSITE
REACTION FROM THE ONE
I EXPECTED,
AND I WAS TRYING TO CONTROL
THE SITUATION FROM
THE WRONG END.
THE SOLUTION,
OF COURSE, IS MARRIAGE.
WE'VE GOTTA MARRY THE
TWO VEHICLES INTO ONE.
UNITED WE STAND;
DIVIDED WE JACK-KNIFE.
FIRST THING YOU WANNA DO
IS CUT OFF A PART OF THE CAR
THAT YOU DON'T
USE ANYMORE.
SADLY, AT MY AGE,
THAT'S THE BACK SEAT.
I MOUNTED A BUNCH OF CHISELS
TO THE EDGE OF THE
GARAGE DOOR,
AND A COUPLE OF HEAVY ANCHORS
ADD A LITTLE JAM TO IT.
THEY'RE ACTUALLY WOOD CHISELS,
BUT THERE'S LOTS OF 'EM.
ANCHORS AWAY.
OKAY, THAT'S THE
HARD PART DONE,
WHICH WAS CUTTING THE CAR IN
HALF WITH THE GARAGE DOOR
AND THEN GETTIN'
THE MESS ALL CLEANED UP
BEFORE THOSE
PEOPLE CAME HOME.
NOW WE'RE READY TO JOIN THE
FRONT HALF OF THE CAR
TO THIS BOAT TRAILER
IN HOLY MATRIMONY.
WHAT THIS MAN HAS
BROUGHT TOGETHER,
LET NO BOAT RAMP
REND ASUNDER, AMEN.
OKAY, I SHOULD'VE
MENTIONED THIS EARLIER,
GET A CAR THAT'S
FRONT-WHEEL DRIVE.
OTHERWISE WHEN YOU ATTACH THE
BOAT TRAILER TO THE DRIVE SHAFT,
SHE'LL GET SPINNING
AROUND LIKE A WHIRLIGIG...
NO.
AND IT'S JUST THAT EASY.
NO MORE JACK-KNIFES,
NO MORE HAVING THE BOAT
TRAILER UNHITCH AT 50 KLIKS
AND TAKING OUT
A BUS SHELTER.
AND MOST OF ALL,
NO EMBARRASSMENT FOR ME.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I WANNA TALK TO YOU
OLDER FELLAS ABOUT
YOUR EATING HABITS.
SO MANY OF YOU ARE JUMPING ON
THIS LOW-CARB BANDWAGON
I'M AFRAID SHE'S
GONNA BLOW A TIRE.
OKAY,
HERE'S THE THING...
IT'S NOT ABOUT
COUNTING CARBS;
IT'S NOT EVEN ABOUT
COUNTING CALORIES.
IT'S ABOUT COUNTING MEALS.
GOT A LITTLE SHOCK FOR YOU.
ACCORDING TO THE EXPERTS,
THERE ARE ONLY THREE OF 'EM...
BREAKFAST, LUNCH, DINNER.
NOW, YOU MAY
CALL "DINNER" "SUPPER,"
AND THAT'S FINE,
BUT IT'S AN EITHER/OR DEAL.
AND BRUNCH IS A REPLACEMENT
FOR BREAKFAST AND LUNCH.
NOT A TIDE ME OVER
BETWEEN THE TWO.
LIKEWISE, WE GOTTA STOP
INVENTING WHOLE NEW
MEALS OF OUR OWN.
MEALS LIKE "BREAKCARFAST."
THAT'S THAT SECOND
BREAKFAST YOU EAT IN THE CAR.
THEN THERE'S "LUNSNACKER,"
THE POST-LUNCH,
PRE-AFTERNOON SNACK
THAT GETS US
THROUGH TO DINSNACKER,
THEN THE SNACK FOR
WATCHING CABLE TV,
WHICH WE CALL "DIRECT FEED."
NOW, I KNOW CUTTING OUT ALL
THESE MEALS IS GOING TO
BE AN ADJUSTMENT.
BUT NO ONE WILL MIND IF
YOU DO A LITTLE COMPLAINING.
HECK, IT'LL PROBABLY
BE THE FIRST TIME
THEY'VE HEARD YOU TALK WITH
YOUR MOUTH EMPTY IN YEARS!
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ SAW BUZZING ]
UNCLE RED!
NO, NO, NO.
YEAH, IT'S IMPORTANT
TO WEAR --
[ SAW BUZZES LOUDER ]
WHAT ARE YOU CHOPPING
WOOD IN THE LODGE
FOR ANYWAY?
WELL, YOU SAID YOU DIDN'T
LIKE MY HORSIE RIDE,
SO I DECIDED
TO CARVE A STATUE.
YOU KNOW, A FACE THAT'S
HEROIC AND YET IT'S EVERYMAN,
IT'S INSPIRING,
BUT NOT INTIMIDATING.
HANDSOME,
YET INTELLIGENT.
LOOKS LIKE YOU.
Dalton: HEY, RED!
HOW'S THE STATUE COMING?
OH, PRETTY GOOD.
LOOKS LIKE YOU...
BUT KNOTTIER.
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT
HAROLD SAYS,
BUT I DON'T SEE IT.
WELL, THAT IS
NOT GOING TO DO.
I MEAN, WE ALSO NEED
A STATUE OF A MAN
THAT EXEMPLIFIES
THE POSSUM LAKE AREA.
UH-UH-UH-UH!
IT SHOULDN'T JUST
AUTOMATICALLY BE
A MAN, YOU KNOW.
IT SHOULD BE AN
ARTISTIC STATEMENT.
SOMETHING THAT MAKES PEOPLE,
STOP, PAUSE, WONDER,
MAKE THEM FEEL BETTER
ABOUT THEMSELVES.
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING THAT
HAS NO SPECIFIC SEXUAL
GENDER AT ALL.
OH, SO WE SHOULD MAKE A
STATUE THAT LOOKS LIKE YOU.
Red: YOU KNOW, THERE'S
NOTHING MORE RELAXING
FOR A GUY,
OR EVEN A HAROLD,
THAN TO GO OUT
INTO THE WOODS
AND GET BACK TO NATURE
INTO A MORE
SIMPLE EXISTENCE.
CAN'T THINK OF THREE
BETTER GUYS TO GET SIMPLE
THAN WALTER,
BILL AND HAROLD.
AND THEY GOT THE HAMMOCKS.
OKAY, YOU'RE MISSING SOME
BASIC CONCEPT HERE, BILL.
I'M SURE IT'LL
WORK OUT IN THE END.
THEY ENDED UP WITH FOUR TREES
FAIRLY CLOSE TOGETHER
THAT THEY COULD -- OH!
UH, CLOSER THAN HAROLD
THOUGHT, APPARENTLY.
WALTER'S GOT
A LITTLE MORE SENSE.
HE JUST TIED HIS
HAND TO THE TREE.
BUT BILL FINALLY
GETS HIMSELF IN BUSINESS.
ONE THING ABOUT BILL,
HE CAN FALL ASLEEP ANYWHERE.
LUCKILY,
HE HAS CRUISE CONTROL.
AND HAROLD'S TYING HIS
HAMMOCK TO THE SAME
TREE, OF COURSE.
AND HE TIED
A REAL GOOD KNOT.
HE SAW BILL'S KNOT,
HE THOUGHT THAT DIDN'T
LOOK QUITE RIGHT.
HE KIND OF GAVE IT A TUG.
IT'S A SLIP KNOT.
BUT, UH, BILL
HAD NO IDEA --
AND WALTER HAD --
IT WOULDN'T QUITE REACH,
SO HE HAD TO REALLY
HORSE HER OVER THERE.
'COURSE WHAT YOU'RE DOIN' IS
CREATING A LOT OF TENSION,
WHICH IS WHAT
HAROLD USUALLY DOES.
THESE HAMMOCKS ARE NOW
STRETCHED PRETTY TIGHT.
SO HE'S BACK IN BUSINESS.
SO BILL, WHY DON'T
YOU JUST --
SEE IF YOU CAN
GO BACK TO SLEEP.
THERE YOU GO.
AND HAROLD HAS HIS
REALLY TOO LOOSE HERE.
IT'S MORE OF A SLIP --
DOWN, YEAH.
SO HAROLD REALISES NOW --
TAKE HIS HATCHET
AND CUT LITTLE
NOTCHES IN THE TREE.
AND, UH,
WALTER'S DOIN' FINE.
IN MEXICO, I BELIEVE,
THESE ARE CALLED
BOWLESS NOTCHES.
AND HE PUTS THE HAMMOCK
ROPE RIGHT THROUGH THOSE.
NOW YOU'RE IN GOOD SHAPE.
NOW SAME THING
AT THE OTHER END.
AND, UH, HE'S MAKIN'
THE NOTCHES,
UNFORTUNATELY -- OH.
BUT HAROLD IS
OBLIVIOUS AS USUAL.
AND HE GETS INTO THE HAMMOCK,
JUST GETS COMFORTABLE,
AND THE NEXT
THING YOU KNOW...
A LITTLE TIT FOR TAT,
RIGHT, BILL?
ANYWAY, FINALLY ALL THREE
ARE SETTLED IN, RELAXING,
AND HAROLD STARTS TO GET
A LITTLE BIT HUNGRY.
AND HE GETS UP, WHICH
UPSETS THE WHOLE BALANCE
OF THE TENSION
BETWEEN THE HAMMOCKS.
AND HE HAD PUT A SMALL BAG OF
POPCORN INTO HIS BACKPACK,
IT'S DOWN AT
THE BOTTOM, HAROLD.
THERE YOU GO.
HAROLD EATS ENOUGH POPCORN
HE CAN ACTUALLY IMAGINE
THE MOVIE.
SO HE GOES BACK,
DOESN'T SEE THE HATCHET,
FALLS INTO THE HAMMOCK,
SPRINGS THE OTHER GUYS
UP THROUGH THE --
SO NOW HAROLD'S LYING
THERE KIND OF THINKING,
I WONDER WHERE THE
OTHER TWO GUYS ARE.
I'M SAYING TO HIM,
YOU KNOW,
I'M THINKIN' THEY'LL
BE BACK IN A MINUTE.
SO THEY DON'T REALLY
KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
HAROLD'S NOT THERE,
AND NO ONE SEEMS TO CARE.
ROCKABYE, BABY,
ON THE TREETOP,
WHEN THE WIND BLOWS,
YOU'RE STILL A DORK.
IN THE OLD DAYS WHEN MY
DAD AND I WOULD GO ON
A CANOE TRIP,
WE PACKED ALL OUR STUFF
INTO WICKER BASKETS.
LET THE BUGS IN
AND THE SMELLS OUT
AND THEY SUNK EVERY TIME
WE FLIPPED OVER,
WHICH HAPPENED
ON A REGULAR BASIS.
THEN DAD GOT A GREAT
BIG METAL COOLER.
IT HAD SHARP EDGES AND RUSTED
FASTER THAN A STUDEBAKER
AND WEIGHED MORE
THAN OUR FRIDGE.
I TELL YOU, THE GUY WHO THOUGHT
THAT A METAL BOX WOULD MAKE
A GREAT INSULATOR
SHOULD'VE SPENT A WINTER
IN A GARDEN SHED.
BUT EVENTUALLY SCIENCE
GOT INTO THE ATOMIC AGE
AND PRODUCED A MIRACLE
SUBSTANCE...
POLY-WANNA-CRACKERLINE.
FINALLY A COOLER
YOU COULD LIFT, HUH?
AND IT EVEN FLOATS --
UNLIKE DAD.
AND THESE THINGS
CLOSE OFF AIRTIGHT,
WHICH IS GREAT WHEN YOU'RE
TAKING FOOD TO THE CAMPSITE,
OR BRINGING
DIRTY LAUNDRY HOME.
NOW, THAT COOLER IN THE CANOE,
SURE, WAS A BIG STEP FORWARD,
BUT WHY JUST
TAKE ONE STEP?
IF YOU HAVE ENOUGH COOLERS AND
THE HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON
YOU CAN TAKE IT
TO A WHOLE NEW LEVEL.
I CALL IT A CANOOLER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I DUNNO, DALTON.
WHY DON'T WE JUST TAKE THAT
BIG RONALD McDONALD FIGURE
THAT'S AT YOUR STORE,
WE'LL PAINT IT GREY,
AND WE'LL CALL THAT
THE STATUE.
THAT'S NOT RONALD McDONALD,
THAT'S MY FATHER!
OH, LOOK, DALTON,
UNCLE RED HAS
FINISHED THE SCULPTURE.
HE SAID NO PEEKING
BEFORE THE UNVEILING.
HEY!
WELL, I'VE REALLY DONE IT
THIS TIME, BOYS.
IT'S IMPRESSIVE,
IT'S GENDER NEUTRAL,
IT REFLECTS THE VALUES OF THE
POSSUM LAKE COMMUNITY
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY...
IT'S DONE.
I PRESENT TO YOU
THE SPIRIT OF POSSUM LAKE.
Dalton: MY LORD!
HA, IT'S NOT
THAT GOOD.
IT'S NOT
ANY GOOD.
I MEAN, WHAT YOU GOT --
AND THE --
WHAT IS THAT?
WELL, IT'S CONCEPTUAL
ART, HAROLD.
YOU MAY NOT
UNDERSTAND THAT.
WHAT ABOUT THE PLAQUE?
WHAT'S THAT FOR,
AN APOLOGY?
NO, THAT'S THE
BEST PART.
"HERE STANDS THE
SPIRIT OF POSSUM LAKE.
"ALL WISDOM,
ALL KNOWLEDGE CAN BE YOURS...
""25 CENTS PER QUESTION."
WHAT?
YEAH, I INCORPORATED THE
HORSIE RIDE INTO MY STATUE.
I TELL YOU, THE ARTISTS WHO
CONNECT WITH THEIR COMMUNITY
ARE THE ONES WHO
MAKE SERIOUS COIN.
SO TELL ME, GREAT SPIRIT
OF POSSUM LAKE,
SHOULD I BUY THAT
BOAT I'VE HAD MY EYE ON?
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, THIS IS
EVERY MAN'S DREAM.
SOMEONE WHO
ALWAYS SAYS YES!
LET ME TRY!
OKAY, OH, GREAT SPIRIT
OF POSSUM LAKE,
DO WOMEN FIND ME --
HUH-HUH-HUH,
SEXY?
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
OH, I KNEW IT!
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
IT'S MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND NOW THAT I'M A SCULPTOR,
I THINK I'M READY TO TRY
A RECLINING NUDE.
YOU THINK SHE'LL
SHOOT ME DOWN?
TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN EVERYBODY.
SIT DOWN.
Mike: ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, WE'VE BEEN
LOOKIN' FOR A NEW NAME
FOR OUR STATUE.
NOW, AMERICA HAS
THE STATUE OF LIBERTY,
BUT THIS ONE LOOKS
SO MUCH LIKE HAROLD,
WE'RE CALLING IT
THE STATUE OF PUBERTY.