[quirky upbeat music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS IT.
WE'RE STARTING NOW.
THEY LAUGHED WHEN WE SAT DOWN
TO PLAY, BUT WE MADE COMEDY,
AND, BOY,
THEY'RE NOT LAUGHIN' NOW.
AND HERE'S THE MAIN REASON FOR
THAT, THE STAR OF OUR SHOW
AND THE BEST UNCLE
A PERSON EVER HAD; I DON'T
EVEN CARE WHO THEY ARE.
HE'S THE BEST.
THE STAR OF THE RED GREEN SHOW,
MR. RED GREEN.
OKAY.
IT'S OKAY, UNCLE RED.
COME ON IN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU, HAROLD.
ESPECIALLY THANK YOU TO ALL THE
VIEWERS FOR TUNING US IN WHEN
THERE--THERE'S SO MUCH MINDLESS
CRAP ON TELEVISION.
SPEAKING OF MINDLESS CRAP, COME
ON OVER HERE A MINUTE, HAROLD.
HAROLD IS NOT JUST THE ANNOUNCER
ON THE SHOW.
HE'S ALSO OUR PRODUCER AND
DIRECTOR, AND HE WENT TO SCHOOL
FOR THAT.
WHAT WAS THE NAME OF THAT
COLLEGE OF YOU WENT TO, HAROLD?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT JUST CAME--SORT OF CAME
IN THE MAIL.
WAS IT EVER EXCELLENT.
>> I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
THE SHOW IS IN REAL GOOD HANDS
HERE.
AND, WELL, HAROLD, MAYBE YOU
SHOULD EXPLAIN TO THE VIEWERS
ABOUT THIS LITTLE GIZMO HERE.
THEY MIGHT THINK IT'S SOMETHING
MEDICAL, YOU KNOW.
>> [laughs] NO.
NO, THIS IS A VIDEO EFFECTS
MACHINE.
IT'S LIKE THE EDGAR WINTER
MODEL.
[laughs]
IT CREATES VISUAL EFFECTS.
>> WELL, HAROLD TELLS ME THAT'S
THE KIND OF THING THAT THE
MODERN VIEWER GOES FOR, AND
HAROLD HERE KNOWS TELEVISION,
DON'T YOU, HAROLD?
>> YEAH, OKAY.
>> HOW WOULD YOU SAY THE SHOW'S
GOING SO FAR?
>> DRAGGIN' A BIT,
IN MY OPINION.
>> AH, THESE YOUNG PEOPLE TODAY.
THEY'RE NOT AFRAID TO SPEAK
THEIR MINDS.
I LIKE THAT.
NOT ALL THE TIME, MIND YOU.
LIKE, NOT NOW.
YOU KNOW, I WAS GONNA TELL YOU
THAT LAST NIGHT UP AT THE LODGE,
WE WERE MAKING CHILI, AND WE
FOUND A RUNNING SHOE
RIGHT IN THE CHILI,
WHICH ACTUALLY MAKES SENSE
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
WE FIGURED IT WAS PROBABLY
STINKY PETERSON'S SHOE,
BECAUSE HE LIKES TO GET
INTO THE CHILI POT
AND STOMP ON THE KIDNEY BEANS.
OTHERWISE, THEY GIVE HIM GAS,
SO WE DON'T SAY NO.
BUT IT WASN'T STINKY'S, SO--
>> UNCLE RED, I'M SORRY.
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR YOUR STORY.
YEAH, SORRY.
JUST GO TO THE NEXT CLIP.
JUST, YOU KNOW, GO.
NEXT CLIP.
>> WELL, I THINK THE PEOPLE WANT
TO FIND OUT WHAT HAPPENED
TO THE RUNNING SHOE.
>> YEAH, WE'LL TELL 'EM LATER,
'CAUSE RIGHT NOW, IT'S BORING.
I CAN HEAR PEOPLE
CHANGING THEIR TV CHANNELS.
CLICK, CLICK, CLICK, CLICK.
YOU BETTER GO TO THE NEXT
SEGMENT.
CLICK, CLICK, CLICK.
>> AH, WELL, I GUESS WE'LL GET
BACK TO THE STORY LATER AND
RIGHT NOW GO TO A FILM CLIP OF
SOME KIND.
WHAT IN THE SAM HILL IS THAT?
>> SPECIAL EFFECTS.
NEAT, EH?
>> THERE ONCE WAS A FELLA
THAT LIVED AROUND HERE
HE MADE HIS OWN CLOTHES
AND BREWED HIS OWN BEER
BUT THE ONE THING ABOUT HIM
THAT FILLED US WITH DREAD
WAS THE NUMBER OF CHEMICALS
HE KEPT IN HIS SHED
PESTICIDE BOB
HE USED WHATEVER WAS RIGHT
FOR THE JOB
WEED KILLER, RAT KILLER
ROSE DUST, AND MACE
HE NEVER WORE GLOVES
OR A MASK ON HIS FACE
HIS MANNER WAS DISTANT
HIS OUTLOOK WAS DRAB
WHEN HE DIED, HE SMELLED
LIKE A CHEMISTRY LAB
WE BURIED HIM DEEP
AND MADE SURE THEY PAID US
'CAUSE HIS CORPSE KILLED
ALL VEGETATION
WITHIN A 30-MILE RADIUS
PESTICIDE BOB
THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA TAKE YOU OUTSIDE
AND SHOW YOU HOW TO UPGRADE
YOUR VEHICLE.
YOU KNOW, THEY--THEY JUST DON'T
MAKE VANS LIKE THIS ANYMORE.
AND IF ANY OF YOU VIEWERS
HAVE ONE, WELL, YOU KNOW WHY.
NOW, I KNOW IN THE DAY,
YOU KNOW, YOU COULD FIX HER UP
BY DOING SOME BODY WORK OR MAYBE
FINALLY GETTIN' AROUND TO DOIN'
THAT RING AND VALVE JOB OR
ANYTHING, BUT I THINK
IT'S A LOT MORE FUN
AND SOMETHING YOU CAN TALK ABOUT
AT PARTIES TO INSTALL YOUR OWN
AIR CONDITIONER.
NOW, I GOT THE IDEA TO--
I GOT THE IDEA TO PUT IN
AIR CONDITIONING WHEN I--WHEN
I FOUND THIS AIR CONDITIONER.
IT WAS JUST SITTING
ON THE SIDEWALK
IN FRONT OF A HOUSE.
AND WHETHER IT WAS OUT THERE TO
GO IN THE GARBAGE, OR MAYBE THE
PEOPLE WERE MOVING AND JUST
HADN'T PUT IT IN THE TRUCK YET.
I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
BUT--OH!
THE DEAL IS THERE THAT
WITH AN AIR CONDITIONER NOW,
SHE RUNS 120 VOLTS.
AND THE VAN RUNS 12 VOLTS, SO
WHAT YOU NEED IS A STEP-UP
TRANSFORMER, WHICH ANY IDIOT
CAN MAKE, AND I'LL PROVE IT.
TO MAKE--TO MAKE THE
TRANSFORMER, YOU NEED ONE OF
THESE WHEEL RIMS.
WE HAVE A LOT OF THESE UP AT THE
LODGE, 'CAUSE THE MICE JUST EAT
THE RUBBER RIGHT OFF THE TIRES.
AND, YOU KNOW, THE--
THE DROPPINGS, THEY'LL BOUNCE
FROM HERE TO HOLLYWOOD,
YOU KNOW.
SO WHAT YOU NEED TO DO IS, YOU
GOTTA GO 12 VOLTS, 120 VOLTS.
SO THAT'S THE--THAT'S THE RATIO
ON THE TRANSFORMER.
SO YOU DIVIDE 12 BY 20, AND
THAT'S, UH...
120 DIVIDED BY 12.
UH, CARRY THE 4 IS...
[sniffs] 10.
10, OKAY.
SO NOW YOU--YOU GOTTA WRAP YOUR
WIRE AROUND ON THAT RATIO OF 10.
SO YOU'D PUT 30--SAY 30 COILS ON
ONE SIDE, AND THEN 10 TIMES--
30 TIME--UH...
[whispering]
418.
ALL RIGHT, THAT ONLY TOOK A FEW
HOURS, AND NOW WE--NOW WE CAN
HOOK HER UP TO OUR POWER SUPPLY.
WE GOT THE TRANSFORMER.
LET ME JUST GO AROUND
ON THE GROUND IN FRONT HERE
AND JUST HOIST THIS UP AND--
OH, HERE WE ARE.
RUN THESE BATTERY CABLES,
HOOK THEM ONTO THE BATTERY.
NOW JUST RUN THE CABLES--
AND WE'LL KEEP THEM APART
AND RUN THE CABLES AROUND HERE.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE JUST--THIS IS
JUST TEMPORARY UNLESS IT WORKS.
AND IF YOU WANTED TO MAKE
A REAL FANCY INSTALLATION,
I SUPPOSE YOU COULD, YOU KNOW,
GO IN THROUGH THE WINDOWS
AND THROUGH THE WALLS
AND SO ON, BUT THAT WOULD
INVOLVE A LOT OF HAMMERING.
OKAY, SO NOW WHAT WE DO IS,
WE HOOK HER UP
TO THE TRANSFORMER.
AND THIS IS GOING
ON THE SMALL SIDE HERE.
OH, FOR GOSH SAKE.
[laughs]
OKAY, WE'LL HOOK THAT UP THERE.
AND WE'LL--
OH, PERFECT, PERFECT.
OKAY.
NOW WE NEED TO HOOK THE OTHER
SIDE UP TO THE AIR CONDITIONER.
WHERE'S THE OTHER WIRE HERE NOW?
HERE WE GO.
YEAH, AND THIS IS A--THIS IS
THE STEP-UP TRANSFORMER
ASPECT OF IT.
NOW, A LOT OF YOU SAFETY NUTS
WOULD PROBABLY WANT
TO TAPE THESE.
THERE WE GO.
OKAY.
NOW WE GOT A--SHOULD BE
UP TO 120 VOLTS.
JUST A MATTER NOW OF JUST
HOISTING THE AIR CONDITIONER UP
INTO THE--JUST HOISTING HER UP--
JUST HOIST HER UP.
THERE WE GO.
[grunting]
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, THESE ARE--THESE ARE
A HEAVY UNIT, AREN'T THEY?
BY GOLLY.
[grunting]
ALL RIGHT, AND THAT'S JUST GOT
TO GET UP INTO THE WINDOW THERE
NOW, AND...
[sighs]
JUST WAIT FOR
ALL MY BODY PARTS TO GO BACK
INTO THEIR NORMAL SHAPE.
AND UP ONTO THIS--
UP ONTO THIS--
[grunting]
I SHOULD'VE PARKED ON A HILL.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE.
NOW, THIS IS NOT SOMETHING
YOU'RE GONNA BE TAKING IN
AND OUT, YOU KNOW,
ON A REGULAR BASIS.
[panting]
ALL RIGHT NOW, JUST--
[groaning]
I DIDN'T THINK IT HAVE TO WEAR
AND THE EQUIPMENT TODAY.
BUT GET THE AIR CONDITIONER
INTO THE WINDOW.
[groaning loudly]
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, LITTLE FARTHER.
HONESTLY, IT TAKES
A LITTLE TOUCH HERE,
A LITTLE--NOW JUST FIND THE
POINT JUST WHERE IT BALANCES.
OH.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, IGNORE
THAT PART, BUT OTHER THAN THAT,
A HECK OF AN IDEA.
OKAY, SO YOU GET THE IDEA.
UNTIL NEXT TIME, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME, THEY
SHOULD AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
YOU KNOW, I GOT ENOUGH THERE TO
MAKE A HEAT PUMP FOR THE VAN.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK
WITH THE REST OF THE STORY ABOUT
THE MYSTERIOUS RUNNING SHOE
RIGHT AFTER THESE MESSAGES.
>> AND LOTS OF OTHER THINGS TOO,
JUST IN CASE
YOU WEREN'T INTERESTED
IN THAT RUNNING SHOE THING.
JUST SAY.
>> "IT IS AUTUMN.
YOU SEE A PILE OF LEAVES
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF YOUR FRONT LAWN.
THEY WEREN'T THERE YESTERDAY.
THEY WON'T BE THERE TOMORROW.
AND SO YOU RUN AND JUMP
HEADFIRST INTO THE PILE.
AND THEN YOU REMEMBER
WHAT WAS HERE YESTERDAY
AND WILL BE HERE TOMORROW:
THE FIRE HYDRANT."
SO AS I WAS SAYING, IT WASN'T
STINKY'S RUNNING SHOE
IN THE CHILI AT ALL,
BECAUSE STINKY WEARS
RUBBER BOOTS TO SQUASH THE
KIDNEY BEANS, AND THAT WAY,
IT CLEANS THE BAIT OFF OF 'EM.
THEN WE THOUGHT, "WELL, MAYBE
IT'D BE MOOSE THOMPSON'S."
BUT NO, THOUGH,
'CAUSE THE SHOE HAD LACES,
AND MOOSE DOES NOT HAVE
THE KIND OF FIGURE WHERE HE CAN
REACH HIS FEET WITHOUT HELP.
AND BESIDES, MOOSE HAS REALLY
NOT BENT OVER
SINCE HIS DAYS IN THE ARMY,
WHICH WE HOPE IS JUST
A COINCIDENCE.
>> JUST TELL 'EM WHOSE SHOE
IT IS, UNCLE RED,
'CAUSE WE'RE LOSIN' 'EM.
HURRY UP, GO.
THAT'S--THAT'S, YOU KNOW,
MY OPINION.
>> FOUND OUT IT WAS
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S SHOE.
>> OKAY, GOOD.
ROLL THE NEXT INSERT!
>> BUT OLD MAN SEDGEWICK HADN'T
PUT IT IN THE CHILI, SO THIS IS
WHERE THE MYSTERY COMES IN.
I MEAN, IT COULDN'T HAVE JUST
CRAWLED IN THERE.
OR COULD IT?
>> READY TO ROLL THE PRE-TAPED
INSERT?
OKAY, GREAT.
GO. GO.
[laughs]
I LOVE THIS SENSE OF POWER.
I REALLY DO.
[laughs]
>> SEE, THE THING WAS THAT
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK HADN'T REALLY
SEEN THE RUNNING SHOE
SINCE ABOUT TWO YEARS EARLIER
WHEN HE WAS AT THE UNITED CHURCH
BADMINTON TOURNAMENT
AND HE GOT INTO THE PUNCH
IN A BIG WAY, FELL ON
HIS RACKET, AND COME HOME
WITH A CRUSHED BIRD.
>> UNCLE RED,
I'M NOT ON YOU ANYMORE.
WE'RE INTO THE NEXT SEGMENT,
WELL INTO IT.
>> WE'RE OUT HERE ON LOCATION ON
WHAT THEY CALL A LOCATION SHOOT,
AND I GOT MY GOOD FRIEND
DOUGIE FRANKLIN HERE.
AND, YOU KNOW, DOUGIE, THEY
ALWAYS SAY YOU CAN JUDGE A MAN
BY THE SHINE ON HIS TRUCK.
>> I APPRECIATE THAT, RED.
THANK YOU KINDLY.
>> YOU KNOW, DOUGIE HERE HAS GOT
QUITE A VEHICLE.
GOT A LOT OF SPECIAL EQUIPMENT
ON IT.
AND, DOUG, I KNOW A LOT OF OUR
VIEWERS WOULD LIKE TO HEAR ABOUT
THE SPECIAL EQUIPMENT.
SO MAYBE, DOUG,
YOU COULD TELL US ABOUT
SOME OF THE SPECIAL EQUIPMENT
THAT YOU HAVE.
>> I CAN DO THAT FOR YOU, RED.
>> ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
>> WELL, WE'LL START RIGHT BACK
AT THE TOP THERE.
ABOUT THE ONLY ORIGINAL THING ON
THIS FROM THE GUY WHO BUILT HER
WAS THE WINDSHIELD.
AND THEN HE DISCOVERED WOMEN,
AND THAT'S--
>> IT HAPPENS, DOUG.
>> IT DOES.
THAT'S HOW I GOT THE TRUCK.
>> YEAH.
>> ANYWAY, WITH THE--WITH THE
STOCK WINDSHIELD--
MIND, SHE'S GONE NOW--
WE HAVE THE--WE'VE GOT
BEAUTIFUL HEAVY-DUTY SUSPENSION
ALL AROUND WITH A QUAD.
WE GOT--[coughs]
SHE'S GOT YOUR LOAD LEVELERS,
LOAD LIFTERS, LOAD LIMITERS.
THIS BABY, SHE'S FULLY LOADED
WITH A QUAD.
NOW LET'S JUST--LET'S JUST HAVE
A QUICK BOO HERE
AT THE POWER PLANT.
>> YEAH.
>> GET TO THE POWER PLANT.
NOW, THIS IS WHAT THEY CALL
YOUR BLUEPRINT BIG-BLOCK.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> SHE'S A BIG-BLOCK
BLUEPRINT BLOCK WITH A QUAD.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> WE GOT TWO FUEL INJECTORS
IN HER, BUT ACTUALLY
I RIPPED THEM OUT,
AND I PUT IN THE PREDATOR
PERFORMANCE CARBURETORS.
>> OH.
>> AND I WANT TO TELL YOU
I'VE TUNED THOSE SUCKERS UP.
THEY COME WITH A QUAD AS WELL.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> AND SHE'S HAD A--A--SHE'S
AN ALUMINUM BLOCK.
SHE'S GOT YOUR HEMI BORED OUT
TO ABOUT 600 CUBE,
AND I'LL TELL YOU, RED,
YOU PUT YOUR PEDAL TO THE METAL
ON THIS BABY, YOUR FACE'LL
WHIP BACK ON YOU THERE SO TIGHT,
YOU'LL LOOK LIKE ONE OF THEM
WOMEN COMIN' OUT OF ONE OF THEM
HOLLYWOOD FACELIFT CLINICS,
I'LL TELL YOU.
SHE'S GOT TORQUE, THIS BABY.
>> WHAT ABOUT--WHAT ABOUT
THE ENGINE?
DID YOU MENTION THAT?
>> OH, YEAH.
THAT WAS THE BLOCK BUSINESS
WITH, UH--WITH THE CARBURETORS.
I THINK I DID, ANYWAY.
>> OH, NO.
WELL, YOU SAID THE POWER PLANT.
IS THAT THE ENGINE?
>> YEAH.
YEAH, YEAH.
THAT'S--WELL, LEGALLY SPEAKING,
YOUR POWER PLANT HAS TO BE
YOUR ENGINE.
LEGALLY SPEAKING.
BUT, OH, I'LL TELL YOU.
I MEAN, SHE IS STREET LEGAL
AS SHE SITS.
YEAH, SHE IS.
SHE'LL--EXCEPT FOR, LIKE,
ON A ONE-LANE BRIDGE
OR A PRIVATE SCHOOL,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
WOULDN'T WANT TO TAKE HER
IN THERE.
BUT, OH, SHE'LL MOVE.
SHE'LL DO ABOUT A TON IN--A TON
IN FIRST GEAR.
>> I NEED YOU TO EXPLAIN THAT,
DOUG.
A LOT OF OUR VIEWERS MAYBE
DON'T KNOW WHAT A TON--
>> FOR YOU FOLKS AT HOME
DON'T KNOW WHAT A TON OR NEVER
DONE A TON, I MEAN, IF THERE IS
SUCH A PERSON OUT THERE, A TON,
OF COURSE, IS 100 MILE AN HOUR.
NOW, SHE'LL DO 100 MILE AN HOUR
IN FIRST GEAR.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YOU BUMP UP TO ETHYLENE
OR, LIKE, AN AIRCRAFT FUEL...
>> OH, YEAH.
>> THIS BABY'LL MOVE.
SHE'LL PROBABLY DO A TON
AND A HALF IN FIRST GEAR.
ACTUALLY, WITH THE
PREDERATOR--THE PREDATOR
CARBURETOR, SHE'LL--YOU CAN
ACTUALLY RUN THIS BABY ON
TESTOSTERONE, BUT, YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN'T GET THE STATIONS
TO STOCK IT.
>> OH, NO.
>> THEY JUST WON'T STOCK IT,
NOT EVEN THE UNLEADED.
>> OH, FOR GOD'S SAKE.
YOU'VE GOT A LOT OF MONEY
TIED UP HERE.
>> YEAH, I DO.
>> WHAT WOULD SOMETHING LIKE
THIS--WHAT WOULD SOMETHING
LIKE THIS RUN?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY.
YOU LOOK AT IT AND GET MONEY--
DOLLAR SIGNS POP TO YOUR EYES.
THIS BABY'S WORTH PROBABLY
SOMEWHERE IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD OF
ABOUT $765.26 A MONTH
AS SHE SITS.
>> THAT'S THE MONTHLY PAYMENTS,
DOUGIE.
I WAS INTERESTED IN THE,
YOU KNOW, ACTUAL FULL PRICE
OF THE VEHICLE.
>> UH...
WELL, YOU'D HAVE TO SPEAK TO
THE BANK ABOUT THAT ONE.
WHAT I DONE WAS, I--[coughs]
I TOLD 'EM IT WAS A MOTOR HOME,
AND I TOOK OUT A 25-YEAR
MORTGAGE ON HER.
AND, YOU KNOW, BY THE YEAR 2010,
THOUGH, QUITE A REASONABLE
BUYOUT ON THIS BABY.
>> WOW, GOLLY.
SHE'S ALMOST BIG ENOUGH
TO BE A MOTOR HOME...
>> YEAH, SHE IS.
>> YOU KNOW, IF SHE HAD
A TOILET, YOU KNOW.
>> OH, SHE'S GOT A TOILET
BACK THERE IN THE QUADS, YEAH.
THE GUY BUILT HER
PUT ONE IN THERE.
>> OH, FOR GOSH SAKE.
WELL, I'LL STAY UP AT THIS END.
>> YEAH. [laughs]
>> AND, DOUG, HEY, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME.
>> RED, GOD LOVE YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, HAROLD, HIT YOUR BUTTONS.
>> MY BEARD IS A TREASURE
I WEAR ON MY FACE
IF I NEED TO HIDE THINGS
IT'S A PRETTY GOOD PLACE
IF YOU THINK HAVING A BEARD
IS A DISGRACE
THEN WHAT ABOUT LINCOLN
OR SANTA
OR STEVEN SPIELBERG?
NOT TO MENTION THE FACT
THAT I DON'T HAVE TO
GET UP EARLY TO SHAVE
WHICH MEANS
THAT IN MY LIFETIME
I'VE HAD ABOUT 4,000 HOURS
MORE SLEEP
THAN MOST MEN MY AGE
MM
>> OH, UNCLE RED, THIS IS GREAT.
ANSWERING THE LETTERS THIS WEEK
IS GONNA BE SO EASY
AND SO MUCH FUN.
THESE ARE MOST EXCITING AND BEST
LETTERS WE'VE EVER HAD.
THIS IS FANTASTIC.
THIS IS REALLY, REALLY GOOD
LETTERS.
IF I'M ANY JUDGE OF LETTERS--
AND WHICH I AM--
THIS IS A GOOD LETTER.
>> JUST READ THE GOOD LETTER,
WOULD YOU, HAROLD?
>> IT'S A GREAT LETTER
I'M GONNA READ, OKAY.
"DEAR RED, CONGRATULATIONS
ON YOUR GREAT SHOW.
THE PRODUCTION AND DIRECTION IS
WONDERFUL, VERY BERGMAN-ESQUE."
>> BERGMAN-ESQUE?
WE DON'T HAVE STRIPPERS.
>> NO, NO, NO, UNCLE RED.
BERGMAN-ESQUE.
THAT'S LIKE INGMAR BERGMAN.
HE WAS IN CASABLANCA.
>> OUR VIEWERS DON'T KNOW THAT.
LET ME SEE THAT LETTER
FOR A SECOND.
>> NO, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S OKAY.
>> THAT'S YOUR HANDWRITIN',
HAROLD.
WHY WOULD WE BE ANSWERING
LETTERS WRITTEN BY YOU, HAROLD?
HAVE WE SUNK TO THAT?
>> WELL, IT--WE DIDN'T GET
ANY MAIL THIS WEEK, UNCLE RED.
UNLESS YOU GOT A LETTER.
DID YOU GET A LETTER
OR A PHONE CALL OR ANYTHING?
>> NOT THAT I RECALL, NO.
>> OH.
DID YOU GET FAXED LATELY?
>> WELL, I DON'T THINK WE HAVE
TO TALK ABOUT THAT
ON TELEVISION, HAROLD.
BOY, THEY DIDN'T USE LANGUAGE
LIKE THAT IN MY DAY.
WHAT'S THE WORLD COMING TO?
THIS WHOLE
"ANSWERING THE MAIL" THING'S
GONE DOWN THE TOILET.
FOUL LANGUAGE AND FAKE LETTERS.
>> WELL, I THINK ANSWERING FAKE
LETTERS IS BETTER THAN ANSWERING
NO LETTERS AT ALL.
THERE'S NO SENSE HAVING
AN "ANSWERING THE MAIL" SEGMENT
OF A SHOW WHERE THERE'S NO MAIL
TO ANSWER.
[laughs]
>> WHY NOT?
WE TELL HUNTIN' AND FISHIN'
STORIES, AND WE NEVER SHOOT
OR CATCH ANYTHING.
>> SHH!
>> THIS WEEK ON "ADVENTURES
WITH BILL," HE WANTED TO GO
ORIENTEERING, WHICH IS,
YOU KNOW, KIND OF WALKIN' AROUND
WITH A MAP.
AND I WASN'T REAL INTERESTED
IN IT, YOU KNOW.
MY FIRST REACTION WAS, "NO."
FIRST OF ALL, HE HAD THE MAP
UPSIDE DOWN, WHICH TOOK AWAY A
CERTAIN AMOUNT OF MY CONFIDENCE.
AND ANYWAY, I JUST DON'T REALLY
ENJOY THAT TYPE OF THING.
BUT I WENT ALONG WITH IT,
YOU KNOW.
>> WHOA!
>> I DECIDED NOT TO DO THAT,
BUT, YOU KNOW, BILL SEEMED TO
KNOW WHAT HE WAS DOING.
HE'S GOT THAT CONFIDENT...
>> [grunts]
>> YOU KNOW, AIR ABOUT HIM
WHERE HE SEEMS TO BE IN CONTROL
OF EVERYTHING.
>> [shouts]
>> KIND OF MAKES YOU WANT TO GO.
NOW, WHAT HE WANTED TO DO WAS,
HE WANTED TO MARK THE TREE WITH
A HATCHET HERE JUST SO HE'D KNOW
WHERE HE WAS.
BUT THE, YOU KNOW, MAP BLEW UP,
AND THEN, YOU KNOW--
WELL, I GUESS IT'S OKAY.
AND HE'S GONNA TRY AND TAKE
THE HATCHET OUT OF THE TREE,
BUT--
WELL, THEN HE DECIDED
THAT'S A--THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD
MARKER ITSELF, THE HEAD OF THE--
HEAD OF THE AX THERE.
SO THEN WE JUST STARTED HEADIN'
OUT, AND BILL HAD THE CANTEEN.
WE HAD ALL THE EQUIPMENT
AND EVERYTHING.
HE OFFERED ME
A LITTLE DRINK OF THAT.
WASN'T BAD EITHER.
THE MAP WAS GETTING ALL WORSE
FOR WEAR, BUT HE HAD THAT
FEELING AND HE THE BINOCULARS
THERE, AND--AND HE HANDED THEM--
NO, BILL.
BILL. BILL.
GIVE ME THE--YEAH.
AND THEN HE'S BACK TO THE MAP,
AND I--I MUST ADMIT I WAS
STARTING TO LOSE MY CONFIDENCE.
AND THEN WHEN HE ASKED US
TO GET OUR COMPASSES OUT
AND COMPARE THEM,
THEY WERE COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
NOW I'M STARTING TO REALLY
WONDER WHAT I'M IN FOR HERE.
SO WHAT WE DECIDE TO DO IS JUST
TAKE A HALF THE MAP EACH,
AND I'D ALREADY DECIDED
WHAT I WAS GONNA DO WITH THE MAP
AND THE WHOLE IDEA, REALLY.
I FIGURED I COULD JUST FIND
MY WAY WITH THE COMPASS
AND THE CANTEEN
AND THE BINOCULARS AND SO ON.
BUT BILL WAS GOIN', I GUESS,
THE RIGHT WAY.
AND, YOU KNOW,
THE FUNNY THING IS,
I KNOW I DIDN'T WANT TO DO THIS,
BUT, YOU KNOW,
ONCE I GOT INTO IT...
>> YOW!
>> I GUESS BILL WAS ENJOYING
HIMSELF TOO, YOU KNOW.
AND THE COMPASS WAS WORKIN'
FINE, AND I WAS MAKIN'
GOOD TIME.
>> [grunting]
>> I FOUND THE WALKING
QUITE PLEASANT, ACTUALLY.
NICE DAY, SUNNY, YOU KNOW.
NO REAL UNDERBRUSH OR ANYTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
I WAS WONDERING HOW BILL WAS
DOIN' AT THIS TIME.
I WASN'T REAL CONCERNED.
I JUST WAS--I WAS JUST CURIOUS.
THAT'S ALL.
AND I COULD JUST TAKE MY TIME
AND, YOU KNOW,
THIS ACTUALLY WAS GOOD.
I WAS ENJOYING NATURE
A LITTLE BIT.
I FOUND OUT LATER THAT BILL
WAS HAVIN' SOME PROBLEMS,
BUT, YOU KNOW, HE'S A VERY
RESILIENT, YOU KNOW, INVENTIVE,
RESOURCEFUL KIND OF GUY.
SOME THINGS DON'T BOTHER BILL.
AND, BOY, IT WAS A NICE DAY
THERE.
THE BINOCULARS, I CAN JUST SEE
WHERE I WANT TO GO.
BILL WAS OKAY.
I BELIEVE HE HAD A TELESCOPE
WITH HIM, SO I DIDN'T LEAVE HIM
COMPLETELY HIGH AND DRY.
YEAH, THERE IT IS THERE.
LOOKS A BIT LIKE A THERMOS
ANYWAY.
BUT...
>> [grunts]
>> BOY.
OKAY, WELL,
LUCKY IT WASN'T HIS GOOD EYE.
I NEED TO STOP AND HAVE A DRINK,
AND, YOU KNOW, I WAS REALLY
KIND OF GLAD THAT I HAD GONE--
GONE ALONG WITH IT.
I WAS HOPING BILL HAD SOMETHIN'
TO DRINK.
YEAH, YEAH.
OH.
OH, WELL, BILL'S NOT HAVING
A GOOD DAY, I GUESS.
BUT, GOLLY, I WAS.
I REALLY WAS, AND THAT'S REALLY
ALL THAT MATTERED AT THAT POINT.
>> [panting]
>> BILL IS STARTIN' TO CIRCLE A
LITTLE BIT, WHICH APPARENTLY IS
INDICATIVE OF SOMEONE PRETENDING
TO BE LOST.
YOU KNOW, HE'S FUNNY THAT WAY.
YOU KNOW, IF I'D HAVE SEEN HIM
THERE, OF COURSE, I WOULD'VE--
I WOULD'VE STRAIGHTENED HIM OUT,
BUT, YOU KNOW, LIFE'S LIKE THAT
SOMETIMES.
AND STARTIN' TO MAKE PROGRESS
HERE, 'CAUSE BILL EVENTUALLY
COMES BACK TO THAT,
AND LUCKY THING THAT HE LEFT
THAT MARK IN THERE.
AND HE DIDN'T SEEM REAL PLEASED,
BUT TO ME, IT MEANT HE WAS
AT LEAST GETTIN' BACK
WHERE HE STARTED,
WHICH IS WHERE I WAS
AND JUST WAITIN' FOR BILL,
'CAUSE I WANTED TO THANK HIM.
I HAD A HECK OF A GOOD DAY.
IT WAS JUST UNFORTUNATE
THAT MAYBE HIS COMPASS WAS NOT
THE--NOT THE QUALITY OF MINE.
MAYBE HE DIDN'T--YOU KNOW,
DIDN'T PAY ENOUGH FOR IT
OR WHAT HAVE YOU.
BOUGHT IT USED, MAYBE.
BUT HE'S JUST GONNA--
NO, CHUCK IT AWAY.
CHUCK IT AWAY.
THROW IT AWAY.
TOSS IT.
GONE, OKAY.
AND SOMETHIN' WAS HURTIN' BILL
OR SOMETHIN' HE'D SAT ON,
SO I WAS HELPIN' HIM OUT.
WELL, FOR GOSH SAKE.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
THAT WAS THE PROBLEM.
SO YOU MIGHT AS WELL JUST--I SAY
JUST HAVE A LITTLE REST, BILL.
YOU DESERVE IT.
GREAT DAY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK, AND I'M NOT
EVEN GONNA MENTION
THE RUNNING SHOE IN THE CHILI.
>> [laughs]
EXCELLENT CHOICE.
>> SO ANYWAY, AFTER DINNER,
A WOMAN COME OVER TO THE LODGE
AND TOLD US SHE'S THE ONE
WHO'D ACCIDENTALLY DROPPED
THE RUNNING SHOE INTO THE CHILI.
APPARENTLY, SHE'D BEEN CARRYING
THE SHOE AROUND
FOR A COUPLE OF YEARS
AND TRYING IT ON EVERY MAN
SHE MET, HOPIN' TO FIND THE GUY
WHO'D HAD HIS HANDS ALL OVER HER
AT THE BADMINTON TOURNAMENT,
AND THEN THEY'D BE ABLE TO LIVE
HAPPILY EVER AFTER.
WELL, WE KNEW
IT WAS OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S SHOE,
SO, GOD, WE WERE SURPRISED
AS HECK WHEN HE TRIED IT ON
AND IT DIDN'T FIT.
HE TOLD US LATER THAT WAS
BECAUSE THERE WAS A PIECE
OF CELERY STUCK IN THE TOE
OF HIS SOCK.
SEE, OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
DOESN'T WANT TO GET MARRIED.
HE WANTS TO JUST PLAY THE FIELD
UNTIL THEY PLOW HIM UNDER IT,
WHICH IS FINE WITH US.
I MEAN, HE LOOKS LIKE
A SCARECROW ANYWAY.
ANYWAY, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
I'M GONNA COME STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE SHOW.
SO I'D LIKE YOU
TO LEAVE THE LIGHT ON
OVER THE GARBAGE BAGS.
I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT AGAIN.
SO ANYWAY, THANKS VERY MUCH FOR
WATCHIN', AND ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD AND THE WHOLE
GANG UP HERE AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.