You know, camping has come a long way since
Britney Spears threw me out of the house.
Nowadays, the fancy fold up hardtop units
that are kind of like a house except a little
smaller made out of canvas.
And they do about 70 miles an hour.
By golly, that's a lot of money to spend to
go away for the weekend and still find out
you've got a guy like me in the next
campsite.
And as usual, I got a better idea.
Pick one of the vehicles out of your
personal automotive parts department that you
keep behind your house.
Drop the engine out of her and convert it
into a hard top camper.
All you need is some camping gear, a couple
of old tents and a little imagination
That keeps the
Mosquitoes away. And the hood protects the
cook from the flying beer bottles that are so
much a part of any camping experience.
And look, how much extra space you get when
you rent out the doors using the handyman
secret hinge. There's your main living area.
That's your boudoir. The only real work you
have to do to set up a unit is to dig a hole
under the trunk, or, I should say, the
powder room.
Well, today is the big fishing trip for the
Lodge last when we went on was nine years
ago, just a bunch of lies members out in the
wilderness doing whatever the heck we want.
That's why I believe the nine year gap, so
the statute of limitations will kick in.
Yeah, I'll come to you here.
Yeah. All right.
And.
I'll just follow the bread crumbs, bread
crumbs.
Hey. Yeah, there you go.
Yeah, please help me off with this backpack.
Oh, sure. Yeah. Well, that's a big one.
Oh.
Thank you. Yeah.
Hey, Don. Cheers.
We had a French poodle that used to do that
to the wife's laundry.
We had to have him neutered.
Yeah, I think the same thing here would work.
Let's go fishing, boys.
I'm all packed up, got everything in the
waiters, I got my fishing gear, got the
hatchet clean shirt dip, net folding or even
stopped by a phone booth to pick up some
toilet paper. Right.
What's wrong, do I say something wrong?
Oh no, we're a little hard of hearing hearing
a hearing.
That's just a maybe you should go pack
Winston.
I just told you, I've already packed these,
I'll see you guys down at the dock.
Holy smokes.
Clark, what Westerners wearing an earring?
Yeah, I don't think I want to share a tent
with him.
It's just any rain.
Funny. He never married, huh?
And he's always wearing those rubber pants.
It's time for
The Possum Lodge word game.
Mike Hammer will be playing for a free meal
from Honkin Joe's Cafe, recently reopened by
the Possum Lake Health Department.
Come try Hank and Joe's all you can eat
buffet now with sneeze guard.
Cover your ears there, Mike.
Fred, you've got 30 seconds to get my camera
to say this word.
Party party.
All right. And go,
Ok, Mike. On your 18th birthday, what did
your parents
Throw you out of the house?
Ok. Ok. What do you call it when your friends
have a get together in your honor?
An intervention?
Ok. Ok, if you have a wedding in your family,
what do you call those people who are
standing next to the bride and groom their
children?
Ok. Ok.
This is a line that people sometimes get on
their phone.
What are you wearing?
Almost out of time
Here, right? I don't know, Mike, we may have
to cheat on this one.
Oh no, Mr.
Green. That's something I can never be a
party to.
Most Thompson, a possum possibly calls it a
colossal achievement.
Wendy McClintock says this was truly a
moving experience and that weird lady who
lives in the shed at the edge of town with
all the birds says, Do I know you get off my
property? The critics agree.
If you get your skeptics pumped only once
this year, you're pressing your luck.
Rothchild sewage and septic sucking services
the only show in town.
Now has a handy man, I get asked a lot of the
big questions in life.
What does it all mean?
Why are we here?
Why are you here?
No, really, sir. Why are you here?
You're not on the guest list.
And of course, the classic one.
Why is there only beef jerky?
Couldn't some creative free thinker come up
with a little variety?
Well, yes, I can go today on Handymen
Corner.
I'm going to show you how to make turkey
jerky.
The first thing you want to do is dry the
bird, not the way your grandmother does it by
roasting it in a four hundred degree oven
for the entire 12 days of Christmas.
No, no, that's not the way the creative
freethinker does it.
Ok, the next step in the process is to salt
the meat.
Oh, sure, I think that and salt to the drier
cycle, but where's the fun in that?
The last step we need to make our turkey
jerky is to compress the dry salt and meat.
I'm sure they sell machines made specially
for doing that, but I prefer to use this room
divider that Bernie's got to stop me from
watching TV while we're eating dinner.
The big question is, how much pressure is it
going to take to flatten this baby?
I'm guessing somewhere around 60 pounds.
Exactly 60 pounds.
And it's just that easy to remember the
women don't find you handsome.
They should at least find your handy.
Yesterday, it ran into an old friend of
mine.
I haven't seen in years.
I asked him how he was doing and he said
everything was great.
His family's great, his health was great, his
job is great.
Well, great. Great, great.
Oh, sure, I mean, I'm happy he's alive, and
I probably don't mean him any real harm, but
you know, the bottom line is most men don't
want to hear everything's great.
On the phrase everything's great is an
instant conversation ender.
Just like the phrase, I'm a police officer.
I mean, you know, when somebody says
everything's great, well, the only answer you
can give them is great, you know?
Then force a smile like Liza Minnelli on her
wedding night.
Well, I mean, what I want to hear, I want
the guy to say, Well, everything's OK.
You know, his boss is on his case and his
wife is on sabbatical and maybe his.
His car is on fire or something like that.
And his daughter just had her navel pierced,
you know, which is not so bad, except that
his daughter's name used to be frank.
You know? Well, well, now you're talking,
you know, because see that stuff that just
opens the door now I can tell them
everything that's wrong with my life.
And before you know it, we're exchanging a
few laughs and a little bit of advice, and we
both go away feeling better about ourselves
because we're thinking the other guy has got
it worse off than I. So it's like that old
saying, if you haven't got anything nice to
say, great.
Remember, I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
I'm not just the president of Rothchild
sewage and septic sucking services, I'm also
a client. Ok, I'll correct.
This is the last of my luggage.
Are you sure this fishing trip something in
the last five days?
Oh yeah, yeah, that's it, Harold.
It's five days maximum
Back from the hurricane.
Very funny. Is this supposed to accomplish?
Wait, it's just an earring.
We just want to show Winston how weird an
earring makes him look.
I mean, this is an act of love.
Yeah, yeah. Well, he just means man love.
I mean, for a friendly man like, you know,
not that friendly.
Just, Hey, I've got an idea.
Let's your Winston. How silly he looks.
Look, I got lipstick.
Oh, great. You know, Uncle Brad, if you're
uncomfortable around Winston, you know, as
someone who's afraid and insecure may well
be, why don't you just be up front and talk
to him?
Talk to Marilyn. Oh, jeez, I don't know.
I think it would be awful hard for us to
talk to them about it, yeah, I
Feel uncomfortable. You could be awkward for
sure.
Hey, Richard, can you do me a favor?
I don't want to pack these good lures in my
pants.
You can put them in here.
There you go. I sure hope you boys have been
drinking.
Well, I think Winston got the message and
that
Was
His face red.
So behind the lines with Sparky, they're just
throwing a stick, and he's kind of a.
He likes that, he likes just grabbing the
stick and he's very exuberant, he's very
focused, very focused dog and just loves
that stick and Walter come along.
And he had had some sticks of dynamite
there.
I didn't know quite what was going.
I thought, this is probably not a good time
to be playing with the dog.
So I just threw that. I figured Sparky, just
go in there and just stay in the body.
But he actually got the stick and brought it
over to me.
But the whole thing was Walter wanted to
remove a stump there, and
Dynamite seemed like the quickest, easiest
way.
Sparky. This is not a good time, not a good
time to just ask you where you go, where you
go. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wiggle weaver. Ok, so Walter grabs a stick
there and he's going to stick her in behind.
I think it's probably safer to get all the
rest of dynamite out of the way, and I guess
he'll wire it all up and then I'll go back
in and set it off.
I see the guy, OK, you got the plunger that
we're all all set up, and I'm sure he's just
about done there. Just take your wires up
and get this thing on.
We just stick her in there wires and then
OK.
And away we go. An odd sound from.
You know, I was kind of expecting more of a
bang than the than the slow hiss thing.
Ok, she's hooked up to my back tire there.
I don't know completely it, so I'm going to
go back to the stump and see what the problem
is and wonder just what had happened here.
I think it was. It's a change in technology.
I don't see any wires on the dynamite enough
here where they must be buried and they got
disconnected somehow. And I'm looking for
the meanwhile.
Apparently what they have is now is a
wireless detonator.
Which I know about now.
So we try to try again.
The one stick apparently wasn't enough.
Put a few sticks in, but I'd forgotten that
the dog.
Still don't, and that's I was in the
doghouse, and then I think this is probably
our second stick there and.
And Hassan seemed to have something against
that tree.
I don't know. And now we got three sticks of
dynamite.
Ok, now that makes sense.
And now we're all set, we while three sticks
of dynamite, we should
Get rid of that stump, no problem.
So Walter presses the button and what
happens is roughly nothing.
So he presses a few more times.
That stuff does. And that one went not real
good, and you'll never guess.
That's what we call it, mission
accomplished.
Ok, here comes a stick of dynamite and a dog
named Sparky, I'm out of here.
This is the experts portion of the show where
we addressed those three little words that
men find so hard to say, Oh OK.
And here's your letter, dear experts.
Men don't share.
Men don't allow feelings out.
Men don't talk about what matters.
And that's what makes us men so happy.
Why aren't women more like us sincerely?
Well, my theory is that they just love to
talk.
Yeah, as I've said on many occasions.
Well, that maybe that's the way it is.
Read.
I'm talking home. See, women don't understand
sports or cars or machinery, so what else do
they have to talk about, just their
feelings?
I'll see now. My theory is women talk more
about the feelings because they have more of
them, you know, I mean, you ask any of us
guys how we're feeling.
We're all feeling fine.
But a woman only Michael, there's so many
shades of.
And then they're like, say, Mike, they see
that that kind of gas or what color would you
say that is this way?
Ok? Color colors that chair dread.
Yeah. Ok, Mike Landon, it's red.
It's Ray. Exactly.
Like to us, it's red. Ok, but bernie's that
there is ruby crimson over here.
We got tropical coral and.
This unit would be wisp of tomato.
You know, women know all the shades.
Yeah, men are emotionally colorblind, so I
think that's it.
That's it. Exactly.
You know, it must be awful having all those
feelings.
She says it that they got so many feelings
there.
I'm afraid they're going to explode.
And that's why you're messing is just listen
to a woman while she talks about her feelings
and be darn thankful that you're a guy.
Now, what do you do if you won?
They want you to share your feelings with
them.
You have to make up stuff.
This kind of talk talks, talk slow and take
a lot of deep.
Wow, you almost teared up there.
How do you do that?
Well, it helps if you sit on some ice tongs.
You ever noticed that a lot of the heavy
construction equipment has these stabilizing
feet to go right down to the ground, stop
the unit from tipping over?
Some of them are strong enough to actually
lift a unit up into the air.
But I'm thinking, you know, something like
this could be really useful in a roadside
emergency. Had to adapt her a little to fit
my wheel studs, but we made it work.
He, of course, is to mount the foot upside
down on there.
I'll take her off once I'm out of the danger
zone.
Well, we put off our fishing trip until
tomorrow, and we asked Winston the so we can
have a little chat with him about his
alternate lifestyle.
You know, it's getting pretty serious when
men have to talk to each other.
Ok, I'm here. Please sit down.
Ok. Wow.
You know, something I really like what you
guys have done with this place.
Winston Reid and I have asked you here to
just to talk and a few things out in the
open. Good because it's kind of been
bothering me too.
How good is that? Yeah, you know, it sort of
threw me for a loop at first, but I think
I've got my head around it now.
Mm hmm. I'm just a little sad that you've
been so secretive about it, read.
It doesn't bother me that you're gay.
Pardon me. Oh, come
On. You know, lodge leader.
All male members.
You see, you got a wife, but no one's ever
seen her.
Yeah, yeah.
No, but but look, let's let's let's listen.
It doesn't matter, we're all on the same
team here.
Ok. It's just that you.
That from the other side of the plate.
I know you're in the Situation Room with us
tonight.
Come on. You're the one with the earring.
Hey. Yeah.
Oh, no. Ok, I remember this isn't an earring.
No, no. About a week ago, I was doing this
septic job right, and this little girl had
accidentally flushed her glitter pony doll
down the toilet, right?
Well, when when the back pressure from the
septic truck hit this thing, it was bits of
glitter pony doll everywhere.
Oh, I see said I'm a little disappointed,
though, that you'd assume that I would wear
an earring.
Oh, you know, you're right.
I mean, I should have known it was a glitter
pony that got caught in a toilet explosion.
Well, you see how talking to each other is
always the best way, yeah,
Yeah, you know what, Winston? Just a little
harmless misunderstanding.
Yeah, I don't. Don't worry.
No, I'm good. I mean,
I thought you were the gay one, right?
But listen, if if you ever muster up the
courage to talk about it, I'm here for you.
Free meeting time can take him with you and
Harold, please.
Ok. My wife is watching, I'll be coming
straight home after the meeting, and we had
some questions about my orientation today.
I'm hoping we can get some answers tonight.
And thanks for watching.
On behalf of myself and Harold and the whole
gang up here for watch people stick on.
We raised it all rise quite
smartly now.
Hey, now your heads for the man's prayer.
I'm a man, but I can change if I have to, I
guess,
But I don't ever plan on changing that much.
But.