If the show they said they couldn't be done,
here's the show they said shouldn't be done.
Here's the show they said wouldn't be done.
Here we are because they're only obviously
right about the shouldn't part.
We're broadcasting from the north, the real
far north, where most people don't go.
You know that really a hard place to get
out, like when you're in the middle of your
back or you. But anyway, that's where we're
coming from.
And here's the star of the show, the man who
signs the checks around here, and he's in no
danger of getting writer's cramp.
Believe me, you hear he is the star of the
show and my uncle by birth and marriage in
that order, ladies and gentlemen, Mr.
Red Green.
Thank you and welcome to Possum Lodge.
I'm going to be your guide for the mysteries
of nature like the lodgepole pine tree, the
white rump antelope and and my nephew Harold
here.
And when people get tired of that real nature
stuff, I can just throw in a little pizzazz.
Wow. Why do you do that, Harold?
Well, it's because it says right on my resume
that every show I promise to deliver a bunch
of pizzazz.
I thought it said pizza's.
I'm a television producer, what would I
possibly know about pizzas?
Try looking in the mirror sometime, Harold.
Anyway, we got a real, fun filled show for
you this week, I mean, it looks good on
paper. Then again, so did Harold's resume.
Actually, we almost didn't have didn't have
a show at all because a bunch of us last
night got playing. Sorry, I like him.
Oh, that's a good game. I like the game with
story.
That's a great board game. That one.
I hope they put it out with computer one
day, because then maybe I could play it too.
No, no. This is a different story.
This is Possum Lodge.
Sorry, the way this works is that you've got
to get up and do something that you're going
to be sorry for when you sober up.
Actually, Buster Hatfield won with his
eggnog nostril shower.
You know, I think what it is is he takes
down two full bags of milk and he actually
swallows the eggs in the shells.
That's what makes it such a consistent
winner.
Once he won that, we all, of course, had to
go down to the lake and watch the bits of nog
and egg and the eggnog even together off of
our southern.
Well, once we'd finished belly flop on our
coast, Clean Moose Thompson started the big
fire in the den and so we could all get
dried off
In the den. There's no fireplace in the den.
No, no. That's that's why we almost didn't
have a show.
Set the floor on fire.
That was that like smoky stench is in here
today.
No, no, no. That's that's from stinky
Peterson's long johns.
We use them to put out the fire.
Let's think pretty upset about it.
I guess we should have taken them off him
first rather than stinky, then burnt to a
crisp in the den being total, it's really no
harm done.
So without further ado, let's get the show
rolling, Harold.
Jen, at the end, I hate cards.
In Old Harold, Golf would be a perfect game
for you.
I could teach you.
Yeah, I carry the three this time.
No, thank you, though, Bob.
I can't throw the clubs as far as you can.
That's not on purpose.
That's all accidental.
Besides, if I was on the pro circuit, I
could afford better grips.
Well, actually, my time is very limited right
now at my all.
My career is also demanding.
I got to roll up cable, burned myself on
lights.
Things to do. Got five hundred.
You win again, Bill.
It all, Harold. That's why I work for the
Department of Natural Resources.
I'm able to combine my work with my hobbies.
You know, you play your cards, right?
I might be able to get you a job with the
department too and leave show
Business, huh?
Look what I caught today.
Basketball Hoop Possum Lake is devoid of
life.
Congratulations, Bob.
While you and your government buddies were
out dumping around the back nine, another
lake rolled over.
What do you care, right?
Just another water hazard as far as you're
concerned.
You know, doc, you seem to be carrying a lot
of tension.
Maybe if you got outside, got some fresh
air, maybe a little exercise might do you the
world of good.
You know, Harold, when I first started
fishing out here by the fish would jump right
up out of the lake and jump at your boot
laces.
Yeah, you ever see two people arguing over
who gets caught first?
You know, some days we'd catch so many fish
we couldn't haul them all in at the time, all
together and kind of a fish raft and float
the boat in on the fish.
Wow.
With that, ever, we need to believe,
You know, Doug, you may think that there's no
fish in that lake, but I find it's a lot like
life. You know, people blame their bad
scores on the golf course.
You know, either the the greens are too
rough or the trees are too hard, or what
idiot put the first tee so close to the
parking lot.
I've been catching fish since I was two years
old, and if I don't reel in a slew of trout,
it's because they're not there.
Possum Lake's dead red bob killed it.
Look, the lake is fine.
The problem is that in the past 15 years,
the fish have gotten smarter and dock here
hasn't been able to keep pace.
You see, what are you doing today?
Read Well, it's not going golf, and neither
are you, Mr..
Not A. Get out there and fix the Dead Sea.
Yeah.
And who are you to tell me how to spend my
workday?
Well, I'm a taxpayer, aren't I?
You are sales tax.
No.
Look, I got to be at work.
I've got a tee off time.
Yeah. Well, don't be surprised if your game
gets interrupted by a bunch of angry
fishermen. We can do a lot of damage with a
hundred pounds of live bait and an attitude
Of you stop me from golfing.
You will be interfering with government
business and
I'll interfere away.
Mr., won't you be touching me?
All right. Well, listen now what are you
doing today?
I got to go into town with the RV.
Oh, well, when you're in town, when you buy
dog, some fish, something slow and stupid
that bites at anything.
It's little stupid. Yeah, yeah.
You should talk, mister. You should talk.
Oh oh, he doesn't know what kind of a fight
I can put up when he gets his hooks in me.
You can quote me on that one, but go slow.
It's stupid. Who wants to go on a shopping
safari?
I got to get some tires all season radio.
Well, we're we're pretty booked up today.
Oh, are you sure?
I got to get six of them.
You know, I got the double wheels on the
back.
I am. Yeah, but I have to get a seventh.
Actually, I need a new maybe I need new
spare.
Well, somebody wants to come with me.
I might be able to be tucked in to getting
that new seventh tire.
Well, you don't go ahead. I think Harold
might be up for a tire trip.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, Harold.
Yes, sir. What are you doing, son?
Volunteer, sir?
My daddy was a poor sharecropper.
He crop things and share them.
We were so poor we couldn't afford windows,
but we had a door that opened a few inches.
I remember the day my daddy died, he called
me over to his side and he said, Who the hell
are you? That was a disappointment.
This week, the
Hey Man Corner, I'm going to show you how you
can turn an old piece of crap like this chair
into a beautiful recliner rocker, you know,
to me, anything that's called a La-Z-Boy.
Sounds like my kind of furniture.
All right. The first thing we have to do is
to disconnect the back from the seat right
down here, so we'll flop or down.
I guess you could put this in a vise.
If you're a purist, you know
How to talk inside.
A source very sharp, we use that one to cut
concrete blocks, we made our wet bar God,
just switch to the jigsaw.
There's nothing to it.
There's no no bleeding that oh, I remember
now we we broke that blade when we made that
architects drafting table out of an oil
tank.
You got lots of power tools here.
No problem.
All right, now, we got the back in here now,
why did I do that?
Oh, oh, oh yeah, yeah, we're making every
kind of rock for you.
So we now are going to reattach the back to
the seat with these hinges.
And so what we have now is more of a
collapse of rocker.
And what we need to do is to now install our
foot rest.
That's going to swing up.
Now what you want here is a real nice piece
of wood, something that matches the grain and
the same kind of general quality as the rest
of the chair.
I couldn't find one, so I'm going to use
this barbecue grill.
I got some cuff hooks mounted underneath the
chair there, and it'll just hang on there.
And you know, you might want to scrape some
of the mung and fat and gristle and feathers
off this thing if you're going to sit in
this chair in your good pants.
Ok, now what we need to put on here is the
supports for our armrests.
These are I got a couple of shelf brackets
here.
We have got a shelf over in the workshop.
There had four brackets on it.
No shelf needs four brackets, so I took
these two off and I figure they're not doing
anything anyway. Well, I guess I might as
well have taken all four.
I don't worry about it. Spilled paint dries
fast, OK, and I'm going to mount these
supports on here using the handyman secret
weapon.
Duct tape. All right.
And now the next step, we had this ABS
drainpipe on here.
Kind of a mixed media project we got going
on with the plastic toilet in the middle and
what have you. And not to mention the tape
and these go on here not only serve as
armrests, but also as guides for the
mechanism that's going to raise and lower the
foot pedal. And again, we'll use the
handyman secret weapon to attach these duct
tape. I'm not I'm not quite sure how much of
a secret it is anymore.
Oh, wow, wow.
How's it look? I run the sash cord up
through my armrest connected to my seat
lifting leg lifter and then up into the
eyeballs.
I've hooked into the back of the chair and I
was just, it's a fantastic thing.
When you lean back up, she comes, as we say,
just look at that now.
The easy part upholsterer.
I suppose you could. You could attach this
more permanent with staples.
Or maybe you want to duct tape that on there
or maybe put a screw into it or whatever.
But I suggest the paper clips and that way
you can, you know, take her by I take her off
every two or three years, give her a shake,
you know, get some of among other I know
she's comfortable and just just think of the
money that you've saved money that would have
gone to a furniture company.
This thing by clear cut money that can money
that can now go to a chiropractor.
So remember, women don't find you handsome.
They should at least find you lying down,
Got some cream soda and a lovely microwave
bundt cake?
You know, don't don't cry.
Sure, you come to know
Right up the door. Here we go.
It is summer, I remember when you could
cruise on the river for free.
Last week I went and it cost me $8000.
The river was dried up.
The eight grand was for boat repairs.
Oh, everybody's pretty concerned about the
lack of marine life in Possum Lake.
I mean, we drink that water, we bathe in
that water, so we would kind of like to know
what's killing the fish.
Well, you did say you bathed in it.
Well, you know, that's a thought.
That's how that is just a fart.
You know, one of those cause and effect kind
of thing, Carol.
You know, when we bathe in the lake, it adds
a whole bunch of life forms.
You know, without the stuff that washes off
us, the algae would probably starve to death.
Ok, I never I never considered that.
I mean, who actually knew that the lack of
personal hygiene amongst the lodge members
would, you know, would be actually
benefiting the Possum Lake ecosystem?
Yeah, exactly right, Harold.
Anyway, Doc Rinder wants Bob to join him in.
In a survey of the bottom of the lake and
old man Sedgwick has turned his pickup truck
into a two man submarine.
How do you turn a pickup into a submarine?
Oh, you park it too close to the lake?
It rolled and didn't it?
Yeah, I rolled in.
So who's going to drive bob or dock?
Well, they drew straws and the one who got
the longest straw used as an air hose.
Personally, I don't think they're going to
go.
Well, we have to go uncle that right over the
next segment.
Dive, Harold Dive.
Hey, Glenn. Oh, hi, IRA.
How's the Marina business going?
Oh, you know, going nuts?
It's a busy time of the year.
All right, Glenn, I want to talk to you about
the lake.
Take a look at these tire, Fred.
Like a good look? Don't get right in there.
The brand new tires.
Oh, travel, that's OK.
Not the
Tread. Read the nubs.
No. The tire. No. It's the little things
that stick out when you going to brand new on
the side there. They're like whiskers or
something.
Yeah, they're falling off.
Like, I can't believe.
Wow, what are you going to do, Glen?
They go down to the RV dealership and cut
the nubs off brand new tires and come back
here and glue them on under your tires every
time you want to go for a ride.
What kind of glue would you use for that,
right?
Right, I'm joking.
Then how do you mean?
Do you think there's any fish left in the
lake here?
What bottom
Lake? Yeah, oh, tons of fish out there,
still?
Yeah. You know, airplane glue, airplane glue
would do it.
You know, not now. Doc says that there's no
fish left in the lake at all.
What is it with duck and fish?
He's got a fish fixation that's not healthy.
They also don't go for a ride, right?
I got to get some airplanes with.
No, no, no, no. I got to see about getting
the lake restocked the fish.
Well, we'll go to the lake restocking fish
place.
Yeah, where they sell the fish.
Where's that?
I don't know. But what?
Chris Brown until we find one.
No, that's okay. I got to make a couple of
calls.
First off. I'll see you later, Lynn.
Ok, right? Sure. Yeah.
Whoa. Hey. Tires are made of rubber.
Rubber cement. Wait a go, Glenn.
And speaking of things made of rubber, it's
time for adventures with Bill.
Bill had smashed his car into Glen's holding
tank there, and so he was going to use this
to pretend that his car is on fire and stuck
on the side of the road and the various
safety, the various safety things that you
can do when your car are stuck on the side of
the road. So he's going to he wants me to
pretend that I've been in an accident and
injured when you stick your tongue out when
you're injured, apparently I didn't know
that. And then he's going to get some gear
area to bag or something and a fire
extinguisher. He's going to take the van and
pretend that, you know, he's just dragged
along and he sees me lying there injured.
First thing Bill has to realize is that
reverse starts.
When are OK?
So I'm lying there wondering, and I look
back and he's coming 30 40 miles an hour, and
then the fire extinguisher falls down.
Oh my god, oh my God.
Now he can't see. Oh oh, oh oh oh oh oh, oh
oh, I'm going to lie down.
Well, that gets rid of the door problem.
Things eventually clear up and.
I don't think this is part of the plan, but
you never know with Bill that's working well.
So Plan B, but we do now as he gets out his
little bag and I don't want to impress.
They're doing anyway. You could said he was
done there.
So flares, you've set these flares up all
around your car so that people can see them
go on. You know, that night I had noticed
something about the flares that he had.
They had a word on their belly.
I didn't. I didn't like to look at that in a
big way and suddenly occurred to bill that
maybe these weren't flares.
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy.
Oh boy, oh
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh.
And by golly.
Well, people have noticed you there and
looks like the car has gone to a safer place.
So anyway, Bob and Doc kind of chickened out
on the two man sub idea, but they still
wanted to inspect the bottom of Possum Lake,
so what they did was they popped a skylight
into the roof of the tool shed and then
flipped it over into the lake to uses a glass
bottom boat. Oh man, Sedgwick went with them
for luck.
Bad been out there about a half mile and
they had so many slugs and leeches on the
underside of the skylight they couldn't see
through it.
So Bob and Doc got down there, started
tapping on the plexiglass, trying to knock
those things off. Their old man says, we
thought somebody was knocking on the door, so
he opened it. The whole thing sank and they
managed to swim into sharks is really no harm
done other than the fact that old man
Sedgwick's pickup truck now has a tool shed
in the back.
You know, accurate. I heard that Bob and Doc,
they're still arguing about the condition in
the lake and that Bob, he's got conclusive
evidence that he's going to bring to the
lodge meeting tonight.
Well, I hope it's not his wife.
Which one? He had about five.
I hope it's not one through four.
There's the call the wild possum.
Come on, uncle. Let's go Lance.
This boil up.
Harold has a touch of a poet, doesn't he?
Anyway, I'll just nip down here.
If you don't take a minute and I'll either
relieve somebody's embarrassment or add to it
whatever seems in order.
Or more fun.
That's what being a leader is all about.
We have.
Right.
I know. The floor recognizes Bob Stevenson
Like a rebel. Well, I've been running a
Battery of tests on the lake water.
I was down at the ministry lab all afternoon
and I found that well, I was happy to find
that all the water in Possum Lake is fresh,
clean and pure.
What the heck could have caused that pop?
Well, nothing read just the test when I was
doing shows at the lake is brimming with
marine life. And if people can't catch fish,
it's because people can't catch fish.
Oh, I took the liberty of hiring a private
laboratory to run some checks on the lake
myself, somebody that knows what they're
doing.
I know I'm a golfer.
Possum Lake is totally sterile.
Nothing can go in that water.
Not fish, not worms, not algae.
And once more, there are highly toxic levels
of arsenic, palladium and mercury.
So, yeah, let me see this.
Hey, that's the same stuff I put in my tire.
Watch what a tire wash.
Yeah, I used to get all the germs and stuff
off my tires.
Yeah, yeah. Right away, it's sterilize the
rubber.
Yeah, stuff. I invented myself.
If you would, some of the stuff on the road
gets stuck on your tire.
You know you're saying wash washing tires
with this stuff, Glenn?
Yeah. And then you just rinse it right into
the lake.
Where else would you read this thing?
So Possum Lake died so you could have clean
white walls?
Is that it? Oh, wait me,
Bob, how long do you think it'd take possibly
to to regenerate all the fish life and
everything again?
Well, see arsenic, palladium, palladium, the
worst kind mercury.
Well, they're all fairly heavy.
And also, if the fish are soaked up all that
stuff and then die, they've probably gone to
the bottom of the league, so it should
recover fairly quickly.
I'd say that the lake will probably be
brimming again with marine life and about
three thousand years old.
Right wing
3000. That's a lot.
Three thousand years.
Well, that's not very long.
Well, it might not be long for Bob.
He works for the government.
Relax, the guy that I spoke to said that by
seeding the lake with the fingerlings and
plants and the various bacteria, well, we
can see the fish coming back in a couple of
months. Oh, really?
Yeah. Does that work?
Where do I fish in the meantime?
Well, I could take you to where the fish are.
Doc MRV Oh yeah, like maybe over to Lake
Morris.
Well, how about the Yukon for some salmon
the Yukon that you the tires?
Do we get back? Oh, OK.
Oh, just kidding, right? All right.
Well, if there's no other large business,
OK, then I'm going to call on Glenn here to
give us the evening's entertainment.
Am planning on it. Could you get those on the
way up there?
Thank you. Palladium.
These are slides. Are they glad, sir?
Well, I'm sure Possum Lake will restock
itself gradually will encourage people to
flush minnows down the toilet, so that
should get things started.
That's the least we can do, which is more or
less our specialty anyway.
My wife is watching. I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting, so you might want to
set the electric blanket on defrost.
Until next time on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole gang up here at Possum
Lodge. Keep your stick on the ice.
That's the name for himself right now.
I'm just going to grab a seat, put it in the
bucket.
Oh, this is the ninety five stuff right
here, right?
Yeah, we are going
In New England. Yeah. I cut off the other
side there.
One over here. Here, I cut her off.
Now what's way out?
I have just one hand. I got the guy out
there.
All right.
Sixty five, you want to do this?
A different speed of down.
I'll be. If we're breaking the law, you can
really figure one.