[breezy folk music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> SINCE THE BEGINNING OF TIME,
MEN HAVE TRIED TO DO THINGS THAT
DIDN'T ALWAYS MAKE SENSE OR
WERE SEEN AS POINTLESS AND
FOOLISH AND REALLY, REALLY DUMB.
WELL, KEEPING THIS TRADITION IN
MIND, WE WELCOME YOU TO A NEW
KIND OF TELEVISION SHOW.
WELL, YOU KNOW, IN A WAY, WELL,
IT MAY SEEM LIKE THAT, BUT WE'RE
NOT HERE TO CRITICIZE, AND MAYBE
YOU SHOULD CONSIDER THE SAME
APPROACH.
IT'S TIME FOR
THE RED GREEN SHOW,
STARRING MY OWN UNCLE
SINCE BIRTH, RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW AND
THANK YOU FOR TUNING US IN
AS YOU ZAPPED THROUGH
THE CHANNELS IN HOPES OF
FINDING SOMETHING BETTER ON.
WE CERTAINLY APPRECIATE THE
OPPORTUNITY.
YEAH, WE HAD A HECK OF A TIME UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
WE BUILT OURSELVES OUR VERY OWN
WATERSLIDE.
AND YOU KNOW, SPEAKING OF
WATERSLIDES, HAROLD,
COME ON OVER HERE.
HAROLD IS THE PRODUCER AND
DIRECTOR OF OUR SHOW.
THEY TELL ME HE HAS SOME SORT OF
A SENSE OF A PRODUCTION AND ALSO
HE HAS THIS MACHINE THAT DOES
THINGS.
>> OH, YOU MEAN THIS.
IT'S A VIDEO EFFECTS MACHINE.
IT ENABLES ME TO GO TO PRETAPED
SEGMENTS IF I DEEM IT DESIRABLE,
IF NOT ESSENTIAL.
>> IT'S A TEAM EFFORT TO DO A
SHOW LIKE THIS, AND, ACTUALLY,
BUILDING THE WATERSLIDE WAS A
TEAM EFFORT TOO.
WE ALL HAD TO DIG RIGHT IN AND
PITCH IN AND WORK TOGETHER.
>> SEE, UNCLE RED?
YOU KNOW, YOU GOT TO REMEMBER
SOMETIMES THAT A BREAK IS JUST
AS IMPORTANT AS THE WORK ITSELF.
RIGHT?
NOW, I REALIZE YOU'RE JUST ABOUT
TO TELL THIS WONDERFUL STORY
ABOUT THE WATERSLIDE, BUT AS
YOUR PRODUCER, I MIGHT SUGGEST
THAT YOU JUST SORT OF GO ON TO
THE NEXT SEGMENT, RIGHT?
AND THAT WAY, YOU HAVE A BREAK.
LET ME SHOW YOU.
[breezy folk music]
[acoustic guitar music]
>> I GOT A TERRIBLE HEADACHE
I'VE HAD ALL IT DAY
IT THROBS AND IT POUNDS
AND IT WON'T GO AWAY
I GOT IT FROM DRIVING
THAT VAN OF MINE
I'M EITHER GONNA HAVE
TO START WEARING A SEAT BELT
OR SLOWING DOWN
FOR THE SPEED BUMPS
MMM
>> [howling]
>> OH, NO.
[laughter]
THIS WEEK IN THE HANDYMAN
CORNER, WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
YOU CAN REPAIR THESE LITTLE
ANNOYING NICKS AND CRACKS AND
STONE CHIPS AND WHAT HAVE YOU
IN YOUR WINDSHIELD.
THEY HAVE A NEW PRODUCT OUT NOW.
IT'S KIND OF A LIQUID GLASS
SILICON KIND OF A DEAL.
BUT BEFORE WE GET TO THE SILICON
LIQUID GLASS, THERE'S A FEW
STEPS THAT YOU HAVE TO TAKE.
FOR EXAMPLE, YOU HAVE TO TAKE
THE CRACK THAT'S IN THE
WINDSHIELD AND YOU HAVE TO
ISOLATE IT BY PUNCHING A HOLE
AT EACH END OF THE CRACK SO THAT
THE CRACKS WON'T SPREAD.
[glass shatters]
UH, ALL RIGHT.
NOW, WHAT'S HAPPENED HERE IS
WE'VE ACTUALLY CREATED A FEW
MORE CRACKS, SO WE HAVE TO NOW
ISOLATE THEM BY PUTTING HOLES
AT THE END OF THOSE CRACKS...
[glass shatters]
UH, AND SO ON.
ALL RIGHT.
I SEEM TO HAVE ALL THE--
ALL THE CRACKS ISOLATED SO THAT
THE REMAINDER OF THE WINDSHIELD
WILL STILL BE SAFE.
NOW WHAT WE DO IS, WE TAKE THIS
BELT SANDER, AND WE HAVE TO
ROUGH UP THE EDGES OF THE CHIPS
OF GLASS SO THAT THE SILICON
WILL STICK TO IT.
[sander buzzing]
ALL RIGHT.
WE SEEM TO HAVE CREATED A BIT
MORE OF A PROBLEM HERE, SO WE
HAVE TO KIND OF ABANDON THE
SILICON LIQUID GLASS KIND OF A
SOLUTION, AND WE HAVE TO GO WITH
ANOTHER WAY TO SOLVE OUR PROBLEM
USING THE HANDYMAN'S SECRET
WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
[laughter]
ALL RIGHT, WELL, WE GOT
THE DUCT TAPE TO KIND OF HOLD
HER IN PLACE THERE.
WE JUST WANT TO TAP IT IN TO
MAKE IT KIND OF BE WATERTIGHT
OR RAIN WILL GET IN THERE,
SURE AS HECK.
[glass shatters]
WELL, SO THERE WE GO.
CLEAN AS A WHISTLE, NO CRACKS,
PERFECT VISIBILITY, AND YOU GET
THE ADDED BENEFIT OF THE FRESH
AIR AND THE VENTILATION COMING
AT YOU WHILE YOU'RE DRIVING.
AND ANY OF THE DOWNSIDE OF THIS
PARTICULAR REPAIR JOB IS MORE
THAN OFFSET BY MY AUXILIARY
WINDSHIELD.
SO THAT'S HOW EASY IT IS TO DO
YOUR OWN WINDSHIELD REPAIRS.
I WOULD HIGHLY RECOMMEND SOME
SORT OF SAFETY GLOVES WHEN
YOU'RE BREAKING THE GLASS,
THOUGH.
SO UNTIL NEXT TIME, REMEMBER,
IF WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I'VE GOT A CRACK IN 'EM.
DON'T GO AWAY.
I'VE GOT A STORY TO FINISH
AND A SHOW TO FINISH.
>> UNCLE RED'S STORIES ALWAYS
FINISH THE SHOW FOR ME.
[laughs]
>> "IT IS AUTUMN.
HALLOWEEN.
I FOLLOW THE PATH
OF THE PUMPKIN.
FIRST, IT'S A JACK-O'-LANTERN,
THEN IT'S A PUMPKIN PIE.
WOULD HAVE TASTED BETTER IF WE'D
TAKEN OUT THE CANDLE."
SO ANYWAY, AS I WAS SAYING,
WE WANTED TO BUILD THIS
WATERSLIDE, AND THE FIRST THING
WE NEEDED WAS THE SLIDE PART,
AND, BOY, THOSE THINGS
ARE EXPENSIVE,
SO WHAT WE DID WAS, WE WENT OUT
AT NIGHT AND WE JUST STOLE
ANIMAL FEED TROUGHS FROM FARMS
IN THE AREA.
WHAT THE HECK, YOU KNOW, I MEAN,
ANIMALS HAVING A PLACE TO EAT IS
NOT NEAR AS IMPORTANT AS US
HAVING FUN.
AND BESIDES, THEM FARMERS
ARE ALL ON GOVERNMENT SUBSIDIES
ANYWAY.
>> RED, I DON'T THINK YOU CAN
JUSTIFY TROUGH THEFT BY SAYING
IT'S JUST FOR FUN, NOR TAKING A
CHEAP SHOT AT THE POOR FARMERS
OF THIS GREAT COUNTRY.
DOESN'T DO MUCH FOR YOUR IMAGE,
AND I'LL ADMIT I'M DISAPPOINTED
IN YOU, UH-HUH,
SPEAKING AS YOUR NEPHEW.
>> IT'S JUST A STORY, HAROLD.
ALL RIGHT.
WE DIDN'T STEAL THE FEED
TROUGHS.
WE FOUND THEM ON OUR OWN
PROPERTY...
EVENTUALLY.
AND MAYBE I'M WRONG.
MAYBE FARMERS AREN'T GETTING
GOVERNMENT SUBSIDIES.
MAYBE THE ALFALFA CROP PAID FOR
THOSE CADILLACS.
I DON'T KNOW.
ANYWAY, WE ATTACHED THE TROUGHS
ALL TOGETHER USING THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE, AND THEN WE RAN
THE CHAIN OF TROUGHS
FROM THE ROOF OF THE LODGE
ALL THE WAY DOWN TO THE LAKE.
>> BOY, THAT SOUNDS GREAT,
UNCLE RED.
WAY TO GO.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF WORK.
BREAK TIME.
>> WELL, WHY WOULD I WANT TO
TAKE A BREAK NOW, HAROLD?
>> BECAUSE, BASICALLY,
YOU'RE A KIND PERSON.
>> WE'RE OUT HERE ON LOCATION
WITH MY GOOD BUDDY
DOUGIE FRANKLIN RIGHT HERE
AND HIS AMAZING MONSTER TRUCK.
DOUGIE, HOW ARE YOU TODAY?
>> I'M FINE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> WELL, I'M GLAD TO HEAR THAT,
'CAUSE YOU KNOW, DOUG, THE LAST
TIME WE WERE HERE, DOUG SAID
HE'D TAKE US FOR A LITTLE SPIN
IN THE TRUCK AND, WELL, WE'RE
KIND OF EXCITED ABOUT IT.
SO TODAY'S THE DAY.
HERE WE ARE, DOUG.
>> WELL, LAST TIME WHEN I MADE
YOU THAT OFFER, RED, I HAD MY
LICENSE, AND I'M AFRAID IT'S
BEEN SUSPENDED FOR A WHILE.
JUST A WHILE.
>> GOSH, DOUGIE, WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU GET A SPEEDING TICKET?
RUN A RED LIGHT?
HAVE AN ACCIDENT?
WHAT WAS IT?
>> YEAH.
>> OH, YOU HAD A BAD DAY.
>> WELL, I DID.
I WAS CAUGHT DOING ABOUT
60 MILE AN HOUR DOWN
THE SIDEWALK.
I TOOK OUT A RED LIGHT, AND,
ACTUALLY, I TOOK OUT THE POLE
THAT WAS HOLDING IT UP AS WELL.
[sighs]
AND I HAD A SLIGHT ALTERCATION
WITH A FEW AUTOMOTIVE VEHICLES.
>> A FEW?
>> NINE OF THEM.
NINE VEHICLES.
NINE CARS.
[mumbles]
>> OH, MY GOSH.
WAS ANYBODY HURT?
>> WELL, THAT'S THE--
IF THERE'S AN UPSIDE,
THAT'D BE THE UPSIDE.
FORTUNATELY NOBODY WAS HURT.
THEY WAS ALL PARKED, ALL NINE
OF THEM IN A ROW AT ONE OF THEM
B.M.W. DEALERSHIPS.
BIMMERS, I THINK THEY CALL THEM.
>> OH, MY GOSH, YOU RAN INTO
NINE B.M.W.s?
>> NO, IMELDA HERE,
SHE DOESN'T RUN INTO NOTHING.
I RAN OVER NINE B.M.W.s,
BUT FORTUNATELY, GOD BLESS HER,
I'VE JUST GOT A LITTLE SCRATCH
ON THE BOTTOM OF MY OIL PAN.
WHEN YOU'RE MOUNTING ONE OF
THOSE B.M.W.s, YOU KNOW, UP THE
SIDE, THE SUNROOF HAS A
TENDENCY TO FLIP UP ON YOU,
AND THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
THE SUNROOF COME UP--AND
ACTUALLY, IT'S RIGHT UNDER
THERE.
IT SCRAPED MY OIL PAN RIGHT OUT.
>> OH, FOR GOSH SAKES.
>> YEAH. IT'S OKAY.
>> I HOPE YOU WERE INSURED
FOR ALL THIS, DOUG.
>> WELL, I WAS INSURED,
BUT NOT ANYMORE.
I CALLED THE INSURANCE COMPANY,
YOU KNOW, MOMENTS AFTER.
I HAD A FRIEND'S MOBILE PHONE
IN THE--IN IMELDA THERE.
CALLED THEM AND THAT INSURANCE
SALESMAN, HE WAS DOWN THERE IN
JUST A MATTER OF MINUTES.
HE MUST'VE LIVED RIGHT NEARBY.
HE WAS A PERKY LITTLE FELLOW.
HE WAS RIGHT DOWN THERE, AND A
COUPLE OF MINUTES LATER, THIS
INSURANCE ADJUSTER, I THINK THEY
CALL 'EM, HE COME IN TOW, AND I
GUESS PROBABLY ABOUT, OH, JUST A
MATTER OF MINUTES AFTER HE WAS
THERE, THIS CROWD STARTED
GATHERING AROUND.
AND YOU KNOW, AS I'VE SAID,
THERE'S A GOOD SIDE.
YOU'VE GOT TO LOOK ON THE
BRIGHT SIDE.
>> YEAH.
>> AND THE BRIGHT SIDE OF THIS
WAS, I GOT SOME GREAT PUBLICITY
OUT OF IT,
AND I LEARNED SOMETHING.
>> UH-HUH.
>> YOU KNOW, EVERYTHING IS--
IT'S A BIG EXPERIENCE IN THIS
LIFE, AND I LEARNED SOMETHING.
I LEARNED THAT, FOR EXAMPLE,
THEM POLES THAT HOLD UP THE
STOPLIGHTS, THEY HOLD UP A LOT
MORE THAN THE STOPLIGHT.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT RIGHT NOW.
THEY HOLD UP--THEY ALSO HOLD
UP THE STREETLIGHT.
THEY HOLD UP POWER TRANSFORMERS,
AND THEY ALSO HOLD UP ENOUGH
CABLE THERE, ENOUGH TO POWER UP
THE ENTIRE DOWNTOWN CORE.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT.
AND THERE'S ONE FUNNY THING
I FOUND.
IT JUST--IT'S LIKE A DREAM,
BUT I CAN REMEMBER IT.
IT'S A FUNNY THING.
YOU KNOW THEM BUS SHELTERS?
YOU HIT ONE OF THEM AT 60 MILE
AN HOUR, AND WHEN THEY EXPLODE,
THEY MAKE KIND OF PA!
A POPPIN' SOUND.
IT'S LIKE, "BANG."
JUST ALL OVER.
THE FUNNIEST LITTLE SOUND.
IT'S A WEIRD, WEIRD THING.
>> WELL, YOU LEARNED A LOT.
>> I DID.
IT'S--YOU DO LEARN, AND
THERE'S A DOWNSIDE, BUT THERE'S
ALWAYS AN UPSIDE.
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING, I GUESS.
>> BEST OF LUCK TO YOU, DOUGIE.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE THAT, RED.
THANK YOU.
>> DOUGIE FRANKLIN, A MAN WHO
IS A LITTLE WISER.
>> I AM.
>> NOT TOO MUCH WISER,
BUT A LITTLE WISER.
>> YOU GOT TO TAKE YOUR BUMPS.
THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING HERE:
SITTING ON THIS BABY, AND I
CAN'T DRIVE HER NOWHERE.
>> NINE B.M.W.s, EH?
>> [sighs] YEAH.
I'LL TELL YOU, I LEARNED
SOMETHING ELSE TOO.
PEOPLE DON'T LIKE THEM YUPPIES
TOO MUCH.
THEY WERE APPLAUDING
WHEN THEY LOOKED AT
THEM THINGS WRECKED.
>> YEAH.
>> I GUESS IT JUST GOES TO SHOW
YOU, YOU DRIVE ONE OF THOSE,
ALL'S YOU'RE DOING IS TELLING
EVERYBODY HOW MUCH MONEY YOU GOT
AND HOW LITTLE EVERYBODY ELSE
HAS, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
WELL, YOU ROSE ABOVE THEM,
DIDN'T YOU?
>> I CERTAINLY DID.
I ROSE ABOVE ALL OF THEM
AND OVER THEM
AND DOWN THE OTHER SIDE.
>> THAT'S THE IMPORTANT PART.
>> THAT WAS.
I COME OUT AHEAD.
[acoustic guitar music]
>> THERE'S A TIME
IN THE EVENING
WHEN EVERYTHING IS STILL
WHEN THE MOON'S DOING THINGS
THAT THE SUN NEVER WILL
IT'S A MAGICAL TIME
THAT'S GOOD FOR YOUR SOUL
THEN SOMEONE MAKES
AN INCREDIBLY RUDE NOISE
AND BRINGS YOU BACK
TO REALITY
[laughter]
>> I SAID I WAS SORRY.
>> YOU KILLED THE FIRE.
>> UNCLE RED, I HOPE YOU'RE
READY FOR TODAY'S MAIL,
BECAUSE WE GOT SOME INTERESTING
QUESTIONS.
BETTER PUT ON YOUR THINKING CAP.
THEY'RE REALLY DEEP, AND WE WANT
SOME DEEP ANSWERS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
50 FATHOMS.
>> [laughs]
THAT'S FUNNY.
[laughs]
50 FATHOMS.
THAT'S REALLY FUNNY, 'CAUSE I
SAID SOME DEEP QUESTIONS, SO YOU
SAID, LIKE, A DEEP ANSWER,
BECAUSE THAT'S HOW, LIKE, THEY
MEASURE THE DEPTH OF WATER--
BODIES OF WATER WITH FATHOMS.
HA! 50 FATHOMS.
[laughs]
I'M GONNA WRITE THAT DOWN,
UNCLE RED.
THAT'S ONE OF YOUR BETTER ONES.
FATHOMS.
50 FATHOMS.
HOW DO YOU SPELL "FATHOMS"?
>> JUST READ THE LETTER, HAROLD.
>> I SHOULD JUST
PROBABLY WRITE--
>> DON'T MAKE ME KILL YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, LETTER NUMBER ONE.
"DEAR, RED, WHAT IS THE MEANING
OF LIFE?"
>> ALL RIGHT, HAROLD,
I'D LIKE TO ANSWER THAT QUESTION
IN TWO PARTS.
WHO KNOWS AND WHO CARES?
>> EXCELLENT.
THAT'S REALLY DEEP.
THAT'S FANTASTIC.
THAT'S GREAT.
IT'S VERY, WHAT DO THEY SAY,
IT'S LIKE, EXISTENTIAL.
WHO CARES?
THAT'S EXISTENTIALISM,
OR IS IT ALIENATION?
CONFUSION?
IS IT CONFUSION MORE SO--
>> NEXT LETTER, HAROLD.
>> THE NEXT LETTER.
MIGHT HAVE ANSWERED IT, BUT...
ALL RIGHTY, HERE WE GO.
LETTER NUMBER TWO.
"DEAR, RED, DO YOU THINK WE
SHOULD TEACH THE BIBLE IN
SCHOOL?"
>> WELL, HAROLD, AS YOU KNOW,
I READ THE BIBLE A GREAT DEAL,
WITH THE AMOUNT OF TIME I SPEND
IN MOTELS, AND I FIND THAT
THE BIBLE HAS A GREAT DEAL TO
SAY TO YOUNG PEOPLE TODAY, EVEN
20 CENTURIES AFTER IT'S WRITTEN.
I THINK YOUNG PEOPLE SHOULD
READ THE BIBLE, AND THEY SHOULD
ENJOY IT.
IT HAS A LOT TO TEACH THEM AND
HAS SOME TREMENDOUS INSIGHTS
INTO LIFE, SO, NO, I THINK THEY
SHOULD KEEP IT OUT OF THE SCHOOL
SYSTEM ALL TOGETHER.
>> THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
WONDERFUL, UNCLE RED.
OKAY, LETTER NUMBER THREE.
"DEAR, RED, SOMETIMES I STAND
ALONE ON THE TOP OF A HILL AT
NIGHT AND STARE UP AT THE STARS
FOR HOURS AND HOURS, MARVELING
AT THEIR BEAUTY AND COMPLEXITY,
AND THEN SUDDENLY I BURST INTO
TEARS AND THROW UP.
AND I WONDER, ARE WE ALONE
IN THIS UNIVERSE?"
>> WELL, I'M NOT, BUT IT
SOUNDS LIKE YOU ARE.
>> THAT WAS VERY NICE.
IT WAS--I MEAN, PERHAPS A BIT
INSENSITIVE, GRANTED, BUT IT WAS
DIRECT TO THE VIEWER.
THAT'S THE IMPORTANT THING,
I SUPPOSE.
OKAY, WELL THAT'S VERY GOOD.
WELL ANSWERED.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, UNCLE RED.
HA-HA! FATHOMS.
[laughs]
>> SOMETHING A LITTLE BIT
DIFFERENT FOR YOU ON THIS
ADVENTURE WITH BILL THIS WEEK.
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU ABOUT
SIGNALING.
WHAT THAT THING THERE IS, IT'S
SOME SORT OF A SMOKE, SMOG BOMB.
BILL, YOU KNOW, GOES JUST A
LITTLE BIT TOO FAR, AND IF YOU
INHALE THAT STUFF, APPARENTLY,
IT CAN KILL YOU.
HOWEVER, THESE ARE THE CHANCES
YOU TAKE.
AND THIS IS A BIG MIRROR.
HE'S GONNA--OH, THANK YOU,
BILL, THANK YOU.
THIS IS REAL GREAT, YOU KNOW,
IN EVERY WAY.
AND OF COURSE HE--
>> [screeches]
>> AND NOW BILL CAN'T SEE WHERE
HE'S GOING AND--
>> WHOA!
>> OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
WELL, YOU CAN EVEN SIGNAL WITH
PIECES OF A MIRROR, APPARENTLY.
LUCKILY WE BROUGHT THE
SUNGLASSES WITH US.
AND HERE'S SOME OTHER THINGS YOU
CAN SIGNAL WITH, LIKE A LADIES'
HAND MIRROR AND A BUTCHER KNIFE,
WHICH ISN'T A BAD IDEA TO HAVE
AROUND WHEN BILL'S THERE.
THE MIRROR OFF MY VAN AND JUST
A LITTLE LIGHTER, AND I GUESS
THAT'S A--THAT'D BE FRY PAN
THERE.
THIS IS A BUST OF ELVIS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TOO MANY OF
THOSE, BUT THEY GOT THE SILVER
SUNGLASSES ON THEM, AND YOU CAN
SIGNAL WITH THOSE.
AND A CAN OF--
OH, OH, I SHOULD HAVE SAID AN
EMPTY CAN IS PROBABLY BETTER.
LOOK AT THAT.
SPAGHETTI-O CAN REALLY STICK
TO YOU.
AND THEN THERE'S THE WHISTLE,
BUT BILL, BILL.
[whistle blows]
OH, OH, OH, IS THAT LOUD.
OH, OW, OW, OW.
OH.
[loud explosion]
>> [coughing]
>> ELVIS HAS LEFT THE BUILDING.
NOW, THESE ARE SOME
SIGNAL FLAGS.
I THINK YOU CAN GET MORE
SIGNALING OUT OF WHAT'S COMING
OFF HIS UNDERARMS THEN YOU DO
OUT OF THE FLAGS.
BILL'S A KIND OF UNUSUAL
HUMAN BEING, ISN'T HE?
HE CAN ALMOST FLY,
I WOULD THINK.
HIS HEAD IS LIGHT ENOUGH.
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
THERE THEY GO.
LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT, LOOK OUT,
LOOK OUT.
WELL, SERVES HIM RIGHT.
AND THEN HE HAD SOMETHING.
I KIND OF LIKE THIS.
THIS IS A SIGNAL KITE.
YOU PUT "S.O.S." ON IT, AND THEN
YOU SEND IT UP, AND I GUESS A
PLANE FLYING OVER OR MAYBE
SOMEBODY LOOKING UP INTO THE SKY
SEEN IT KNOWS THAT, YOU KNOW,
AT THE OTHER END OF THE STRING,
THERE'S SOMEBODY IN TROUBLE.
BOY, IS THAT EVER TRUE.
SO HE GOT HER UP THERE, FLYING
UP THERE PRETTY GOOD, AND
SHE WAS GOING UP AT LEAST
1,000, 2,000 FEET, AND ALL OF A
SUDDEN, WE GOT A SNAG, AND THE
DARN THING HAD WRAPPED ITSELF
AROUND THE HYDRO WIRE.
ANYWAY, YOU KNOW--
OH, THANK YOU, THANK YOU, BILL.
THE IDEA WAS--HERE'S ANOTHER
METHOD OF SIGNALING.
THIS IS A GUN.
YOU SHOOT FOUR SHOTS IN THE AIR.
IT'S A UNIVERSAL SIGNAL.
WHAT WE DIDN'T REALIZE WAS HE
WAS SHOOTING RIGHT AT THE HYDRO
WIRE THAT HAD THE KITE ON IT.
DOWN SHE COMES, AND THERE'S
ABOUT 10,000 VOLTS THERE.
OH, OH, OH, OH, OW, OH, OH, OH,
OW, OH, OH, BY GOLLY.
NOW, HERE'S ONE THAT WE KIND OF
STOLE FROM THE INDIANS, USING
THE BLANKET TO SIGNAL WITH AND
THE PROBLEM HERE IS BILL DIDN'T
REMEMBER WHERE THE BROKEN GLASS
WAS.
IT'S RIGHT THERE, BILL.
>> [yelling]
>> YEAH, YEAH, OH, BOY, OH, BOY.
BUT I HAD SOME VICE GRIPS WITH
ME, SO WE GO THAT OUT OF THERE.
OH, THIS WON'T HURT.
OH.
SO I WENT AND GOT ANOTHER
BLANKET AND PUT THAT OVER THE
FIRE, AND THE IDEA IS YOU LET
THE BLANKET KIND OF SIT ON
THERE, LET THE SMOKE BUILD UP,
SO THAT WHEN YOU RELEASE IT, YOU
KNOW IT'S GOING TO GIVE YOU REAL
GOOD PUFFS THAT'LL GO WAY UP
INTO THE AIR.
SO WE FLIP HER OFF, AND, WELL,
IT WASN'T REAL SUCCESSFUL.
OF COURSE, THIS IS BECAUSE THE
FIRE WAS PRETTY WELL DEAD OUT.
SO WE GOT ANOTHER FIRE GOING,
AND A REAL GOOD ONE GOING THIS
TIME AND GOT ANOTHER BLANKET
AND THREW THAT ON THERE.
AND AGAIN, YOU LET IT KIND OF
BUILD UP UNDERNEATH.
MAYBE WE GOT THE FIRE JUST A TAD
ON THE WARM SIDE.
MAYBE WHAT WE NEED IS MORE SMOKE
AND MAYBE--
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
BOY, IT'S A GOOD THING BILL
KNOWS WHAT TO DO IN AN
EMERGENCY, 'CAUSE HE CAUSES A
HELL OF A LOT OF 'EM.
"IT IS WINTER.
A TIME FOR QUIET WALKS AND
PEACEFUL THOUGHTS, TO STARE
BLANKLY AT THE GENTLE SNOWFLAKES
AS THEY FALL THROUGH THE NAKED
TREES AND THEN TO SLIP AND BANG
YOUR HEAD ON THE LAKE."
SAW A MOVIE FROM THE VIDEO STORE
THE OTHER DAY.
>> OH, GOOD ONE?
>> WELL, IT WAS GREAT.
IT WAS A TIME-TRAVELING THING.
THEY HAD A PHONE BOOTH, AND THE
GUYS WOULD GET IN, AND THE PHONE
BOOTH, THEY COULD TRAVEL TO A
DIFFERENT TIME.
>> OH, THAT SOUNDS EXCELLENT.
>> YEAH, YOU EVER THOUGHT OF
THAT?
>> OH, GETTING IN A PHONE BOOTH
AND JUST TRAVELING.
>> YEAH.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU HAD A TIME
MACHINE, WHAT IF YOU GOT IN IT,
AND YOU WENT, LIKE,
10 MILLION YEARS AND CAME RIGHT
BACK TO WHEN YOU WERE RIGHT NOW.
WOULD IT BE RIGHT NOW OR WOULD
IT BE A DIFFERENT NOW?
OR WOULD IT BE CLOSE
TO THE SAME NOW?
>> IT WOULD BE REALLY CLOSE TO
THE SAME NOW.
>> HOW CLOSE?
>> REALLY CLOSE, BUT ONLY
DIFFERENT.
WHAT TIME WOULD YOU GO TO
IF YOU COULD TIME TRAVEL?
>> I'D GO TO AROUND 7:30.
>> TODAY?
LIKE, THE FUTURE OR YESTERDAY
OR THIS MORNING?
THERE'S SO MANY.
>> I'D HAVE TO THINK ABOUT IT.
>> YOU'D HAVE TO.
YOU HAVE TO BE SPECIFIC.
>> YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW, TIME
FLIES WHEN YOU'RE HAVING FUN,
OR AS WE SAY, "TIME IS FUN WHEN
YOU'RE HAVING FLIES."
GET IT?
>> OH, IT'S A BAIT JOKE.
>> I'D LIKE TO APOLOGIZE TO ANY
OF THE FARMERS WHO I MAY HAVE
OFFENDED, AND IF YOU'LL FORGIVE
ME, I'LL TELL YOU THE REST OF
THE WATERSLIDE STORY.
>> DON'T GO FOR IT.
IT'S A TRICK.
>> ONE'S STILL KIND OF JAMMED
UNDER THERE.
>> WELL, THAT'S ONE OF THEM
SMALL ONES.
I THINK THEY CALL THEM
A "THREE SERIES."
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, THEY'RE JUST
A FOUR-CYLINDER.
>> KIND OF SPORTY-LOOKING,
THOUGH.
>> THEY ARE.
THEY COME WITH--APPARENTLY, YOU
CAN GET REAL LEATHER UPHOLSTERY
IN THAT MODEL, ALTHOUGH IF YOU
LOOK AT IT, THE GLOVE
COMPARTMENT IS STILL SHUT.
>> PERFECT.
>> YEAH, I THINK THE MANUAL AND
EVERYTHING IS RIGHT IN THERE
LIKE IT WAS BRAND-NEW.
>> I THINK THE KEYS ARE IN IT,
DOUGIE.
>> OH, I DOUBT SHE'LL TURN OVER
ON YOU THERE, RED.
>> I KNOW WE GOT A LOT OF YOUNG
PEOPLE WATCHING OUR SHOW AS SOME
SORT OF A PUNISHMENT, AND I KNOW
HAROLD GETS THE CHANCE TO TALK
TO YOU, BUT, YOU KNOW, THAT'S
MORE OF A CONTRACTUAL THING
THAT HE INSISTED ON RATHER
THAN A SEGMENT THAT HAS ANY
REAL VALUE TO IT.
AND NOW, TO MY MIND, YOU NEED
SOMEONE A LITTLE OLDER, SOMEONE
MAYBE WHO'S BEEN DOWN THE ROAD
A TIME OR TWO TO GIVE YOU
YOUNG PEOPLE SOME ADVICE
ON GROWING UP.
LIKE, MAYBE YOU JUST TURNED 16
AND YOU GOT YOUR DRIVER'S
LICENSE AND YOU'RE EXCITED AS
HECK ABOUT THAT, AND NEXT THING
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE STOLEN A CAR.
AND OF COURSE, YOU WANT TO GO
DOWN TO THE HIGH SCHOOL AND
START SHOWING OFF, DOING THE
DOUGHNUTS AND THE FIGURE EIGHTS
IN THE FLOWERBEDS THERE, AND
THEN GET UP ONTO THE TWO WHEELS
AND THROUGH THE FRONT DOOR
OF THE SCHOOL SO YOU CAN PEEL
RUBBER UP AND DOWN THE HALLS.
I KNOW THAT SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF
FUN, BUT PLEASE, PLAY IT SMART.
WEAR YOUR SEATBELT.
[laughter]
SO ANYWAY, YOU GOT TO PICTURE
THIS WATERSLIDE WITH ALL THE
TROUGHS DUCT-TAPED TOGETHER,
RUNNING FROM THE CHIMNEY
ALL THE WAY DOWN TO THE LAKE.
AND WE WERE ALL PRETTY EXCITED
ABOUT IT, YOU KNOW.
SO MOOSE THOMPSON,
HE WAS REAL RARED UP.
HE STRIPPED DOWN TO HIS
UNDERWEAR AND AWAY HE GOES
BEFORE WE'D ACTUALLY HAD A
CHANCE TO PUT ANY WATER ON IT,
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, ALL YOU COULD HEAR WAS
THE SQUEALING SOUND OF MOOSE'S
SKIN COMING OFF, YOU KNOW?
OF COURSE, THE REST OF US LAUGH,
AND WITH MOOSE GOING FIRST,
HE SOON REALIZED THAT
THE WATERSLIDE WENT ALMOST
TO THE WATER BUT, YOU KNOW,
NOT QUITE.
SO WE PUT ANOTHER TROUGH ON THE
END THERE, AND WE CALLED 911 FOR
MOOSE, AND THEN BUSTER AND
STINKY, YOU KNOW, HAD A COUPLE
OF GOOD RUNS ON IT, BECAUSE WE
HAD THE WATER GOING BY THEN, BUT
IT WASN'T FAST ENOUGH FOR OLD
MAN SEDGEWICK.
SO HE TOOK OFF ALL HIS CLOTHES,
SKIVVIES AND THE WHOLE DEAL, AND
COVERED HIMSELF WITH SALAD OIL,
RIGHT?
WELL, WE WERE OUT OF FRENCH
DRESSING, AND SO, I MEAN, HE WAS
REALLY WHIPPING DOWN THERE, AND
ABOUT 2/3 OF THE WAY DOWN, WE
HEARD WHAT WE HOPED WAS THE
SOUND OF HIM BREAKING THE SOUND
BARRIER.
AND HE COMES OUT THE END OF THE
WATERSLIDE, SKIPS FOUR TIMES
ACROSS THE LAKE, AND LANDS IN
THE BONFIRE AT THE AT THE
GIRL GUIDE'S CAMP.
BUT THEN HE ALWAYS MAKES A BAD
FIRST IMPRESSION ANYWAY.
WE ALL DECIDED, THOUGH, THAT THE
WATERSLIDE WAS TOO DANGEROUS,
AND, AS LUCK WOULD HAVE IT,
A MINUTE LATER, IT COLLAPSED
ANYWAY.
SO LIVE AND LEARN.
OR JUST LIVE, YOU KNOW?
ANYWAY, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
TONIGHT, AND I WOULDN'T MIND
A BACK SCRATCH IF YOU'RE NOT
TOO TIRED.
ANYWAY, FOR THE REST OF YOU,
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING AND ON
BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD AND
ALL THE REST OF THE GANG UP HERE
AT THE LODGE, KEEP YOUR STICK ON
THE ICE.
[laughter, applause]