And now it's time for a totally different
show.
A show based on the assumption that no
matter who you are or how busy you are.
You have at least one half hour to waste and
well, and here's a man who's wasted at least
half a century. My uncle, which is obviously
the downside of working with a severely
limited gene pool, but nobody's more than
the ones.
He's he's a Cushman and in most cases, a
huntsman.
Anyway, here you star of the red dream show
Mr.
Red Green.
Thank you, Eric. Thank you.
And welcome to Possum Lodge.
You've already met my nephew, Harold, who is
my brother's only child, which is certainly
understandable.
I got a neat one for you here off the rack.
Look at this one.
Well, Harold is responsible for the look of
the show, so don't come complaining to me
that they got a fun show for you this week,
although I must say I did start today with a
rude awakening, which sounds actually like
stinky Peterson.
But then when I got up and I washed my face
and I noticed there was no towel, and then I
noticed that my face wasn't wet, and then I
noticed there was no water.
And so I figure either the water pump is
broken again or Possum Lake evaporated.
I'll correct. Has anybody told Helmet?
Well, I don't think that's necessary,
Harold, because all you got to do is be
chewing on a cup of coffee and you realize
that we're out of water.
So the bunch of us were sitting around
chewing on cups of coffee, and old man Cedric
was, of course, sucking on a teabag, and he
was reminiscing about the good old days at
the lodge before they had any of the modern
amenities, you know, like a roof.
He said back then what they would do to make
coffee as they gloat and they gather up
condensation off the grass in the morning
or, as he put it, they may do so.
We nail them right on the scone with a
waffle iron for that one.
Don't you think you had a point, though?
Well, he certainly does. Now. Hurley's got
about thirty six little ones right up in
here. But OK, I guess we probably did
appreciate things more.
You know, back when the dinosaurs roamed the
Earth, did they
Even have like outhouses back then?
Yeah, they did. But there was no home anyway.
You know, once you get used to modern things
like a water pump or sweeping compound, you
know, it is very difficult to go back.
Well, I'm here to say that we're not going
back.
We're going forward because progress may be
destructive, inhumane, but technology sure is
neat.
Well, unless it's a water pump.
At this washer and
Urine bill and the blockage.
Ok, what do you
Say you're blowing that and I'll see if the
back pressure valve closes.
Ok. Keep blowing helmet.
I just turned on the sink and all I got was
this gurgling noise like stinky minx, but no
water came out. Is there anywhere in this
large?
I can wash my hands.
What am I asking you for your phone,
possibly at the other end of that dock?
Or you can wait until I'm done fixing this
pump.
I use the lake and please make me a list of
everything that you touch, especially food.
All that. Come on, have you ever noticed
that we seem to be having an inordinate
amount of breakdowns? You know, I'm just I'm
just, you know, like pipes and pumps and
stoves and doors.
You know, well, my TV equipment, it's a lot
more complicated and it hardly ever needs
servicing, you know?
Why do you think it is? The infrastructure
of this lodge is in constant need of repair.
Why do you think that is, Harold?
This place is a dump filled with crap.
Ok. All right.
So what's the problem with the pump, their
helmet?
You know, other than it's craftiness,
It's either a CS bearing on the impeller
shaft or the back pressure valve.
Spring is fatigued.
Well, Mr. Pumps not feeling too well.
And neither is Bill.
Well, so are you working on your water pump
there, huh?
No. Harold, you want to go scare me up some
tin snips about seven feet of shoe leather
already.
Ok, we're getting seven feet of shoe leather
from seven different pairs of shoes.
Well, glad to hear your water pumps working
fine.
Delighted, really, because you know, we just
dropped by to get ourselves a pail of fresh
cold water. Now, where would we find your
nearest?
Ok, Mary, all right.
All right. The pump is broken.
The question was Where's the tap?
Don't you listen, Helmut?
Dwayne, the pump is broken.
That means there is no water coming out of
the taps, which means you don't
Need to know where the taps are.
Exactly. Told you.
Well, you're in luck today, helmet.
We're having a sale on water pumps down at
the store.
We bought this one out for you on sale.
Wow. It's such a good memory.
It's only been six weeks.
Our memory is as short as our warranty.
That's our slogan. Or is it our cream read?
I can sell you a brand new reconditioned
water pump out of a Mack truck, complete with
conversion kit for only one hundred
And fifty dollars. Maybe it's a model.
I can fix this one. Good as new for a
hundred bucks,
But what about you and Dwayne? What's your
offer?
I can sell you a hot air corn popper for
fourteen point ninety five.
Well, I'm going to
I'm going have to think it over, guy, so I'll
let you know later.
Oh, by the time he thinks it over Bill and
I'll have this pump fixed.
Oh, well, I don't think so there.
While you weren't looking, I got Dwayne to
eat one of the parts.
Well, I guess when I scare up my tin snips,
I'm going to have to scare that part up too.
Got it.
My friend had a sliver in the back of his
arm.
It was big and huge and
Looked like it could cause them a great deal
of discomfort in some future time.
So I took my needle and vice grips and a
bottle opener.
I proceeded to remove the sliver with the
occasional break for refreshments.
Well, I dug
Away at it for an hour or two.
Can you imagine my embarrassment when my
friend pointed out that it was actually a
tattoo
put down?
This week on the
Handyman corner, I'm going to show you how to
change your oil or more specifically, how to
change the oil on your car.
That's something that you have to do every
couple of years and darned inconvenient.
Plastic can cost upwards of 15 bucks.
Besides, when you get it done at a gas
station or whatever it, you're just not sure
whether or not they've done a bad job, you
know, whereas if you do it yourself, you
know, OK, the first thing you're going to
need is something to catch the oil with when
you're taking your old oil out. I like to
use one of these foil roasting pans.
This is when I used to cook a turkey and
last night in the microwave oven, which is
actually created another handyman corner for
us later in the season.
How to fix your microwave.
Next thing you need is an adjustable wrench.
This is to loosen the nut drain plug on the
bottom of the oil pan.
And this is another handy little item here
that I like.
It's a creeper. It's got the wheels on the
bottom and use that to lie down on and roll
yourself under the vehicle. So what the
great friend plays guitar fan got a wrench.
And honey, we go, Oh, OK.
All right. Here you go.
Oh, OK, how many of you handy man noticed my
little trick there?
I on purpose now I.
I forgot to raise the jack.
I pretended. I forgot.
That's it. I pretend. Yeah, that's it.
Yeah, OK, so you go around to the jack
because you've got to raise the car up to get
under it. You know, any idiot knows that.
It's obvious that Jack to raise.
It's like going to your boss and saying, Hey
Jack, how about a raise up children?
Oh boy, oh OK, I may need a longer jack.
Oh by golly.
So if the mountain won't come to Mohammed,
get yourself one of these engine arm lift and
change engine one of these things.
So she goes out of power here, a lot of
power.
Hmm. All right.
What's happening here is that the is coming
up with the engine because because the engine
motor mounts are still done up because you
have to undo them from underneath, which we
can't get underneath because we can't jack
the car up.
So we're back to square one.
So we have to revert to the laws of physics,
which is if we can't get the engine to come
up, we can get the car to go down.
She went a little bit. Ok, now the reason
the engine was so heavy was that we didn't
bother with the time consuming job of
removing the transmission.
So now what we can do is just take out the
drain plug.
Let me get the get our little pan here to
catch the and we're going to get the old oil
out over here.
Hey, you know.
Yeah, yeah. Mm hmm.
Mm hmm. Mm hmm. To come.
Yeah. Yeah.
Ok. That's got her well.
She was definitely ready for a change, huh?
Take that up again. And now we can put the
new oil back in.
I say new oil, but it's actually just the
oil I took out of the out of the thing last
time I did the oil change, OK, 2010 and put
it right in here, I could spill any there.
And that's basically it for doing your oil
change, so that Temple
Feel a little bit there. Ok.
All right. And that's it.
So until next time, remember the women don't
find you handsome.
You should at least find your handy.
Now here, you
Can take a bit more. His
autumn hunting season opens today.
Some say hunting isn't a sport.
We have guns.
The animals have nothing, but we know how to
even up the odds.
We give ourselves a handicap.
It's called beer. Wow, this water pump thing
is causing a
real stir around here.
Douglas says we can't afford a new pump, but
the old ones held together with string and
chewing gum, which actually fluoridated the
water somehow.
But Buster Hatfield, an old man, Sedgwick,
they want to go back to the way things were
with no water system, no telephone, no
electricity.
Well, what am I supposed to do?
Playing Nintendo by candlelight?
No thank you.
You don't hear the simpler things are, the
less there is to go wrong.
At least that's the rule.
You're the exception.
Personally, I think we should let a helmet
go ahead and try and fix the pump because
he's got his mind set on it.
And I don't really want to argue with
anybody who's larger than my van.
You know, Uncle Red, I was down at Murray's
store and he says he'll sell us like a water
pump. That's the service plan and a
warranty.
Well, does it include life insurance for you?
Why would I need that? Because you're the
one who would have to tell helmet.
No, no.
You send somebody that nobody likes to do
that.
Murray. That's the one you're looking pretty
good there.
Oh, hello, Red Hill.
Just trying to keep the resale value up.
I'm not that I'd ever sell her.
No, no, no, no, no.
When's the last time you whacked your van?
Well, I run into a beehive one time.
Well, it's a pride thing read, I take great
pride
In my car. Well, that's tough to do with an
ass.
It's not a nash, it's a gremlin.
Is that your idea of a joke?
No, I think this is Detroit's idea of a joke.
I'm not about to argue taste in cars with a
man whose truck is painted like a 20 foot
drunk.
Well, actually, I guess I'm just here to talk
to you about the new water pump, how much
money we got in the launch kitty.
I'm not telling you. And the reason I have a
Treasury is because I don't let anybody know
how much is in there.
That's what makes me the best treasure this
lodge has ever had.
So it's under a hundred dollars way under.
Well, it doesn't matter whether we repair
the pump or replace it, we can't afford to do
either one,
Not from the kitty.
Well, we're not going to worry about money
right now because it's time for adventures
with Bill. You don't worry about money.
Was Bill Weir or worry about
Personal injury now?
Well, you get you get the idea, but I've got
a sense of possum arena there, and he writes
Franson garbage cans with them, and I wasn't
quite sure what he had in mind.
I wanted to line these up and I thought I
was going to play.
Where's the pea under the under the carpet?
Oh, OK, Bill.
Bill, get your head out of there, bill.
Yeah. Then I'll play recipe under the can or
the head of the cannon.
Well, anyway, he knows.
Sure. I'm not sure Bill is familiar with how
slippery ice can get when it's golden.
Anyway, you got them all lined up there.
And then he tried to explain to me what he
was going to do.
He he reached into one of the barrels, pulls
out his skates.
So this was a clue.
And he is going to come along and then I'll
leap into the air.
He's going to leap into the air. And so this
is basically your barrel, jump in your
Olympic barrel jumping.
And I was going to wave to something, make
him go, and he's pretty excited about it.
But then he's a natural athlete.
So he went up, got a skates on, and I just
sort of stood by the barrel with the flag at
the ready waiting for my cue.
And now you look a little a little a little
better with the skates on.
So I figured, Well,
All right, let's let them go.
He's he's back up again.
He's all right. It's either this or, I
guess, are his warm up exercises.
Kind of unusual, but then builds up kind of
guy, isn't he?
And this was really not working out so well.
So Bill had another plan.
Now he tried shoes and tried.
This is different. Cross Country, I believe
those are cross country barrel jumping up and
comes on.
Get the heck out of there.
He's in the air flying.
Oh my god.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh.
Oh, there he is, there he is.
He seems all right. All I got to do now is
get him up at the end of the driveway by
Tuesday.
Well, now everybody's getting involved in
this water pump crisis, busters designed kind
of a manual system actually for bringing
water up from the lake.
He got the idea from the movie Swiss family
Robinson, which just opened at the theater in
town. It's on a double bill with pillow
talk.
All that means is seven bathtubs and a three
inch thick clothesline.
The clothesline we have now, Douglas, that
the treasurer is, you know, he wants us all
to just dig ourselves a new well.
Well, we tried that before we ended up with
just a big open pit mine and that eventually
flooded and that's how we got the big bay up
at the North End.
In fact, for sure, like the Big Bang.
Really? Are you sure?
Sure. As I'm standing here.
Oh, no helmet thought he had the the water
pump fixed, you know?
But unfortunately he plugged it in and now
we need a new pump and a new fuse box.
Anything hurt except his pride and of
course, all of our aluminum wiring.
But the unfortunate thing here is the helmet
is now taking that pump thing as a personal
issue, and that's bad. The last time helmet
took something personally, we ended up having
to reforest over 100 hundred acres.
You know, I don't think we can rule out
Murray's plan, either.
You know, he has a very impressive proposal
for tonight's meeting.
Oh, I helped him with the graphics.
All right. Well, that's it.
That's it. Well, it's time for the meeting.
D-day. Oh, to pump or not to pump.
That is the pulsating question.
Oh, it's a meeting.
Let's go. Let's go.
Well, I'll be right back this.
This won't take too long.
We're definitely not dealing with an
unlimited attention span down there.
All right. All right.
Everybody going to see here, you get so
cranky and irritable and hi, everybody else
stand up. Well,
now. The floor recognizes helmet Whitaker.
Thank you, red. I'm happy to announce to
everybody
I have fixed the pump.
Well, now don't bother billing us because
there's no money to pay for it.
Oh, Douglas,
The last thing we need when the world is in
trouble is an accountant, a billionaire.
Nine Scrounged up every part for free.
Mind you, you're going to have a little
trouble starting your nashe.
Filthy mix.
Touch my gremlin.
Oh, hang on. Hang on.
Let's remember Bill and helmet.
Fix this. It's not going to work.
That's an excellent point.
I second that.
Yeah, shut up, Dwayne.
I was a cruel and heartless thing to say.
Well, isn't it, Marie? Shut up, Harold.
Ok, let's shut up, Murray.
Bill, fire up the pump.
You know it up.
Well, I'm sure it'll turn on eventually, but
while we're waiting, I think I have something
that might interest all of you, Dwayne.
Oh, thanks.
No one's ever called me interesting before.
Maybe it's my haircut or the fact that I
have that drawing Dwayne.
Oh. Now, while we were arguing over whether
we should fix the pump or replace it, I
couldn't help get the feeling that, well, we
just weren't thinking big enough.
Well, so I decided we should invest in a big
water turbine and put it in this Dwayne.
What the drawing.
Oh yeah. Murray's water theme park, a water
theme park as Dwayne has so wonderfully
pre-empted Murray's wild and woolly water
wonderland.
I wanted to call it Dwayne's wet spot.
Now, wait a minute. We can't afford that.
We can't even afford this drawing.
The place is a gold mine.
Oh, it'll be a magnet for tourists will
recruit new members and oh well, we will get
a lot of media attention.
Let me tell you.
Hold on a minute here, Murray.
That's going to bring a lot of families up
to the lodge.
They don't need that sort of thing.
No. Forget the last family here.
Think what we have to do is a whole bunch of
us have just got to do a little bit of
thinking here for a minute or two.
Some other brilliant
Ideas. Oh no, you realize what you're asking
here.
Look. Think about it.
I don't like this anymore than you do, but
I'm sure if we all put our minds together,
something good will happen.
Someone's going to get along.
Well, okay, so let's get to that.
Oh, oh no.
Well, I think this is a perfect example of
water water everywhere and not a thought to
think. I don't know how religious you are,
but if there is a greater power at work here,
neither has a very unusual sense of humor or
way too much time on his hands.
Anyway, if my wife is watching, I'll be
coming straight home after the meeting and
I'm feeling lucky tonight.
So why don't you leave the television on?
So next time I'll be asking myself, Harold
and the whole gang up here at Possum Lodge.
Keep your stick on the ice.
No, oh, no, oh no.
And. Oh, I know, I know this.
Oh my God.
I got it.