As you get older, you know, you start to
realize that your true wealth is time, partly
because you don't have much of it left,
partly because of true wealth was money, you
blew it. So anything that can save you time
becomes more and more valuable.
Now, for me, driving into the garage is a
real waste of time because you got to do it
so slowly. Otherwise, you go right out the
back end again.
Oh, sure, I guess you could get the brakes
fixed on your car, but who has that kind of
money? So instead, I've been collecting
boxes and boxes of these Styrofoam chips that
they used for packing, like when you buy a
Chia pet on the internet.
And I'm going to put them into this plastic
resealable bag that our new mattress came in.
Furnace went with the king size, so she get
a little further away from the action.
Or she calls it snoring.
And I figure if I filled this bag full of
these Styrofoam chips and then seal her up
tight, I'll be able to go into the garage at
any speed that I want.
I want to take off the hood ornament first.
It. Our big,
Big week up at the launch this week, the town
of Possum Lake is decided to get rid of the
old wishing well down town.
I know the odd time might go by there and
throw in a handful of coins and then make a
wish that I wish I hadn't done that.
Couple read, Yeah, well, Fred, what can you
tell the guys to hold it down?
I have a terrible headache.
Oh, I'm sorry. Sorry to hear that, Harold.
Well, maybe if we could just turn off his
truck?
No, I can't do that. The battery's dead, and
I don't think we want to be pushed.
Start a sewage truck here on.
You're trying these. Well, thank you.
Ok. Those aspirin are huge.
Oh, they weren't aspirin, they were
earplugs.
What's that? Oh, there's some coins we took
out of the wishing, well, we're doing kind of
a late night withdrawal last night.
Oh, sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
A lot that's just a spillover.
We suck most of it up with Winston Strut.
All right, Winston, let her go.
Money is going to need to be laundered.
It's time for the Possum Lodge word game.
Today's winner will
Receive this coupon for one free session from
Mario's male
Hair removal center,
Where we specialize in speedo waxes.
For the little European in all of us.
Ok, Gordon, cover your ears, read you got 30
seconds to get Dalton to say this word.
Scale scare.
All right and go, OK, Dalton, this is
something you have in the house that tells
you when you're gaining weight.
Oh, my wife.
Ok. What's this called Do-Re-Mi for solar,
tido French.
No. Ok.
Ok. This is what you find on a fish eye
tartar sauce.
Ok. Ok. If you have a model that's a lot
smaller than the real thing, it's called a
something model anorexic model.
Ok, OK, OK, OK, Don.
Now, if you're going to climb Mount Everest,
people would say you were going to do what?
On the mountain die.
Read almost out of time here.
Ok, well, I know Dalton, there's there's a
statue, it's supposed to represent justice
and it's a woman holding something.
You probably have one of these in your
store.
No, that sounds way too upscale for my
customer.
Rothschild, sewage and septic sucking
services, we love to see you smile.
When I go camping with the guys, I don't take
my Swiss Army knife anymore.
Oh sure, it's a good looking unit and it's
nice to have handy in case the Swiss invade.
But for me, the joy of having 12 tools and
one is dampened by having to eat my dinner
with the same utensil Buster Hatfield just
used to clip his toenails.
Now, personally, I think it's time for the
Swiss Army knife to evolve into something a
little more practical like, say, a Swiss
Army surfboard.
Oh, sure, it sounds like the title of an old
Elvis movie.
I think it finds a lot more entertaining now
for this to work.
What you need are a couple of good sized
wind surfboards.
Shouldn't be too hard to come by.
Just look for a couple of guys coming out of
a midlife crisis, and I think you'll be able
to pick them up for a song.
Maybe something by the Beach Boys.
Why don't you get them lined up one on top
of the other?
You want to seal the one side?
Top to bottom with the handy man secret
weapon duct tape.
And there you go. Now all you have to do is
secure the open side for easy transportation.
You might want to do that with some type of
a rust proof graphite metal clasp.
I would do it with another piece of duct
tape.
Now I don't want you thinking, Oh, sure,
it's a good looking unit red, but how do I
get all my camping gear in the car?
Well, that's the beauty of it.
This is your camping gear.
This is all you need. Got a couple of
changes of underwear here?
I'll see about that kind of thing.
There's your knife and your forks and your
spoon and a big enough slab of beef jerky
that you'll never need any of them.
There's more so much more a bedroll, you're
a fishing rod.
And the comfort here, but still.
An old van, I commend you one of these, if
you need it.
I got my share of old fans for your nightly
entertainment.
Oh, here we go. A 22 inch television.
Oh, I know what you're thinking. That's
impossible.
And it is without this portable generator.
Remember, if the women don't find you
handsome, they say, Oh, I almost forgot.
They also want to throw a paddle in there.
Let me show you why. It's not just a Swiss
Army surfboard, it's also a
Swiss Navy surfboard.
Sometimes when couples get older and the
kids leave home, they'll move into a smaller
house. Usually it's the wife's decision, you
know, one day she'll turn to her husband and
she'll say, We really don't need all this
space anymore.
And the next thing you know, there's a sign
on the front lawn and a guy in a mint green
jacket is walking strangers through their
kitchen.
Most men fight the downsizing.
That's because the phrase we have too much
space is outside of their vocabulary.
Men don't have too much space.
Men don't have enough space ever.
We've spent a lifetime hunting and gathering
a basement full of bounty.
We're darn proud of it. That's why your
husband needs to keep the fun for futon from
college and the Boxcar Willie eight tracks
and that world's greatest lover T-shirt he
got 20 years ago, which was a rough guess
then and is right off the radar at this.
See, the smart wife knows that moving into a
smaller house is the only way to get her
husband to ditch all that crap because given
the choice between move it or lose it, a guy
my age will always choose to lose it.
We're just too lazy to pack it up and take
it somewhere so that somebody come over and
haul her all the way to the dump.
That's where most of it came from in the
first place.
Remember, I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
That town's sewage and septic sucking
Services where everywhere you don't want to
be.
Hello, sat back and I wish you well,
project, the bank won't accept the coins
unless we sort them first by, the banks
always have to be so difficult.
I wish I had a nickel for every time I've
said that.
You do. Headaches gone.
Headaches gone. Headaches gone.
Headaches gone wrong.
I think mine just got here.
That's too bad. Mine's gone.
One. Well, I'm all better, what can I do?
What can I do? We're sorting, Harold, what
denomination do you like?
Lutheran?
Do the pennies herald, OK?
You know, I'm doing pennies.
No, I know why.
Because I got the most sense.
Well, still early,
Where's the coin tubes?
You've got to roll the coins, the banks
won't take them in these banks.
Why not? That's the way they give it out.
Yeah, the Mike, don't forget you have that
Smith and Wesson ATM card.
Carol, are you saying we have to roll the
coins as well as stardom?
Oh yeah. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Who has more
money than a bank?
Celine Dion? The point is casino.
That's right. They'll sort it for us.
Let's go.
Great idea, Mr.
Great.
I can help you get there.
But I can't technically go into the casino
for another 30 days.
All right. Bring all the coins.
Ok. There's one that fell on the floor here,
too.
I'll get that one. Yeah, I'm got to get them
all.
All right.
Is that behind the line there, because I
Heard the Bill and Walter were fooling around
and boy, something knocks off mirror right
off the truck. It's a little kind of an odd
projectile on them.
There goes another one. So I thought they
were having a fight.
They seem to be punching each other in the
stomach.
But oh okay.
Yeah, it's a little all in the water, right?
Ok, no. I know water rockets.
I know you help them up and then you fire
them off like that.
And then, yeah, that's that's exciting.
Way to go. And then Bill being a little
older.
So now I'm enjoying that, and I can see the
final debate.
Yeah, I mean, that's I can see that now.
Yeah, yeah. So now they're going to take her
up a notch.
Bill's got the idea instead of using it.
Why don't we use the cola bottles?
You know, because a little bit bigger with
the carbonation, you're going to get a
little, but you've got to get some of the
liquid out of there.
And of course, these guys don't want to
waste anything.
So instead of just pouring it out, they they
they fart in.
You know what I'm saying? I don't know if
you've ever tried this, but there's there can
be some pain involved with that.
When I was afraid of getting caught in the
overspray, so Bill luckily had something in
his pants for a change and.
All that's got to hurt that that's that's
painful.
I would if I was you, I'd quit, but I'm not
you.
Soldiers talking it down, and we we get a
sense that there's something coming our way.
All right. And that's fine. That was from
this very tastefully done bill, maybe not
quite as tasteful as Walter.
No sense of decorum.
And he figures he's outdoors.
Easy now. Easy, easy, easy.
Easy.
Harry, I think I'm just going to step back a
little bit.
So they hook the they hook the coal, I put
the umbrella for my head at first and then
they got him up the bicycle tire pumps and
they're pumping up and getting the pressure
going. And I get a feeling these are
probably going to blow sideways rather than
up. So I'm probably better to go the
horizontal.
Umbrella thing, and you know, right about
now, I'm looking pretty smart because that's
exactly what.
Patches in your head.
Oh, so now we take up another notch.
Got the water cooler with the dual throat
carb fuel injection air intake on her there
and is starting to distort a little under
the pressure so.
Second, you know, we wait.
Maybe that's enough pressure built and one
more elbow, maybe one more.
And no, I think we're good bill.
Bill, we're good Bill. We're good.
We're good, we're good. One more.
And and oh boy, hang on.
While hang on, hang on.
And of course, one more.
And that may have been too much for you.
And I look at Bill, get soaked,
I'm loving this, and I think Walter's
Coming your way, bill. Here he comes down.
Oh.
Today, I'm talking animals, local animal
control officer Ed Frit is here to tell us
all about spiders.
Yes, that's spiders.
No, no, no, no, the spiders read, who told
Jaws, Go talk about spiders.
I thought you did.
Well, yeah, you thought you thought.
You thought you thought you thought that
weasel wouldn't bite.
Yeah, yeah.
You thought that skunk had been descended.
Yeah, yeah. You paid the price there, huh?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. I think we're through
making decisions based on what you think.
All right. That's why tonight we're going to
meet Mr.
Possum. Oh, yeah.
You know anything about possums red?
While this is possible, I'm the leader of
Possum Lodge, we have the possum on our
crest, and when I was in high school, my
nickname was possum.
Well, I didn't know that you made it to high
school.
Anyway, possums are very civilized animals.
They don't bite you or sting you or hide in
your underwear drawer.
We get them when they're scared.
What do you think they do?
Lay down? They play.
Yeah. Anyway, let's take a look at this
possum.
But first, I'm going to scare it so it'll
act dead.
All right. Oh.
Kate, take a look.
I know something else about possums.
They need air.
No, no, no, he's fine.
He's just toying with us.
I think you're going to have to resuscitate a
man.
Suggested CPR.
Oh, I'm a mouth to mouth resuscitation.
Hey, folks. Once he had performed a miracle
here.
Yeah. And just small puffs now, don't
inflate them.
Should a nun spiders?
They're seen one of these things.
It's called a photovoltaic cell.
Whenever light shines on it, it makes
electricity, so you can actually use this as
a switch that's turned on by light.
Some of the finest restaurants use these so
that when your headlights shine on them, it
rings a bell inside and then the waitress
comes out on roller skates, bringing you your
jumbo triple cheeseburger and large order of
fries so that you can have the heart attack
in the privacy of your own vehicle.
Speaking of which, I've come up with a way
to use these little switches to make it a lot
easier to drive a car.
These days, we got way too many distractions
while you're behind the wheel and the old
days. All it was is a fuzzy dice and the
eight track player to worry about.
Now you've got triple odometer weather
detectors, CD players, air conditioning,
power windows, airbag locks, GPS tracking
system and cup holders.
That's a lot to ask from a mind that's got
more miles out than the car does.
So what I did was I attached a photovoltaic
cell on each and every one of the new dads
and gadgets on the automobile, which means
that the turn each went on.
Also have to do is shine a light on it.
That's what this spotlight is for.
I just turn it on and then aiming at my own
head.
Next, they put on these mirrored sunglasses,
which will reflect the light to whatever I'm
looking at, which we'll turn it on like
this.
And it's just that easy.
Oh, sure, you get the odd headache from
staring into a blinding light all the time
you drive,
But I'm sure you'll get used to that.
Aren't.
Well, this has been a very educational day
for me.
For example, I never realized how heavy
coins are when you get enough of them.
And in conjunction with that revelation, I
had never seen four tires blow
simultaneously. Not to mention what the
possam van crashing to the ground can do to
an exhaust system.
Oh, uncle, correct your back.
I didn't hear the possum van pull up, boy,
it must be running quiet, huh?
Not really, Harold.
I walk back from town here.
We just got to the edge there and we ran
into a huge pocket of gravity.
And then we had to get the van towed to
Fenty's place, and there's six hundred
dollars damage to her.
The plot, I didn't think that was possible.
Six hundred dollars, can you afford that?
Well, when you open up the back of the van,
he says, we got enough coin to cover it.
And I had known a couple of hours.
So she's shaken pretty good.
And with all the different sized holes in
the floor, you can actually start the coins
right in the Service Bay.
Right. That's incredible, you know, well,
when you figure, you know, you got all that
change, you know, from the wishing well and
tried to cash it in, which was wrong.
But in the end, you got your man fixed, so I
guess you got your wish.
No, I didn't. But meeting time.
You go ahead, Harold. I'll be right.
My headaches back. Well done, my work here
is done.
My wife is watching, I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting and OK, maybe I never
got my wish to come true, but hey, thanks to
me, neither did your dad.
Thanks for watching on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole gang up here in Possum
Lodge. Keep your stick on the ice.
Three, three, three.
Let's go. Everybody, take your seats, yeah,
sit down, sit down.
All right.
Seems like there's more time now.
By your hands for the man's fair, I'm a man,
but I can change if I have to, I guess.
Ok, guys, Winston tells me he's still got a
bunch of coins in the tank of his septic
truck, if any of you want to go sniff them
out.
But.