(Engine revving)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
NOW HERE'S THE MAN
WHO'S MADE POSSUM LODGE
WHAT IT IS TODAY,
AND STILL NO APOLOGIES,
YOUR HOST, MY UNCLE...
RED GREEN.
(Audience cheering)
(Howling)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THIS IS A BIG DAY FOR
POSSUM LAKE ROAD CONSTRUCTION.
THEY'RE FIXING THAT BUMP AT
THE TOP OF THE HILL INTO TOWN.
BOY, THE THINGS THAT
HAVE SMASHED AGAINST
THE INSIDE OF MY VAN THERE.
WHAT ARE THE EGGS FOR?
YOU GOING TO POSSUM LAKE
LITTLE THEATRE?
NO, I'M USING THESE
TO TEST THE BUMP.
IF I CAN DRIVE OVER
WITHOUT CRACKING THESE BABIES,
I'LL CALL IT FIXED.
HA,
GOOD IDEA.
WEAR
OLD CLOTHES.
(Horns honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): IN THIS SHOW, HAP
DISCUSSES HIS DAYS AS A WHALER,
AND HAROLD AND I CHANGE PLACES.
DON'T WORRY,
IT'S NOT PERMANENT.
I GET DOUGIE FRANKLIN
TO SAY A WORD
HE HARDLY EVER THINKS OF.
WELL, I'LL HAND IT TO
THOSE CONSTRUCTION GUYS.
THEY TOOK 4 HOURS
TO DO A 15-MINUTE JOB,
BUT BETWEEN
LEANING ON SHOVELS
AND ROLLING SMOKES,
THEY MANAGED TO FIX THAT BUMP.
I CAN'T COMPLIMENT THE COPS
RUNNING THE RADAR TRAP.
EXACTLY HOW FAST
WERE YOU GOING?
'CAUSE TICKETS
CAN BE EXPENSIVE.
DID THEY SAY ANYTHING ABOUT
YOU LOSING POINTS?
TWELVE OF THEM.
WOW, I DIDN'T KNOW
THE VAN COULD GO THAT FAST.
NO --
I LOST THREE FOR SPEEDING,
THREE FOR THE CONDITION
OF THE VEHICLE,
AND I LOST THREE FOR DRIVING
WITH AN OBSTRUCTED VIEW.
WAIT --
THAT'S ONLY NINE POINTS.
I LOST ANOTHER THREE
FOR SPEEDING ON THE WAY BACK.
THEY LEFT HER
ON THE SIDE OF THE ROAD.
THEY WERE GOING TO TOW IT,
BUT THE CHIEF
THOUGHT IT WOULD MAKE
THE POLICE COMPOUND LOOK BAD.
(Singing) UNCLE RED HAS TO GO
TO DRIVER'S SCHOOL
NO, I DON'T --
I JUST HAVE TO BE RETESTED.
BUT UNTIL THEN, I GOT
NO LICENCE AND NO WHEELS.
AND YET, YOU STILL HAVE
A SPARE TIRE.
(Red): WHEN YOU HAVE A PROBLEM,
IT'S NICE TO HAVE FRIENDS.
AT LEAST YOU'D THINK THAT.
I DON'T HAVE MY VAN.
SO BILL'S SUGGESTING
OTHER WAYS I CAN GET AROUND.
I'M SURE HE MEANS WELL.
HE DOESN'T DO WELL.
(Audience laughing)
DO YOU HAVE ANY OTHER IDEAS?
ANYTHING ELSE AT ALL?
OH GOOD.
YOU'RE INTO IT
UP TO YOUR BIG MOUTH.
NO SOONER DO YOU START PUTTING
YOUR NEW GAS BARBECUE
TOGETHER...
YOU GET STUCK --
TAB "A" WON'T FIT IN SLOT "B".
SHE SAYS,
"WHAT DO THE INSTRUCTIONS SAY?"
(Audience laughing)
NOW YOU'RE REALLY STUCK.
BECAUSE YOU HAVEN'T READ
THE INSTRUCTIONS, HAVE YA?
THEY'RE SEALED IN
A LITTLE PLASTIC BAG
THAT YOU'RE KNEELING ON.
(Audience laughing)
TIME TO THINK FAST.
SOMETHING YOU'RE NOT GOOD AT
OR YOU WOULDN'T BE CURSING
TAB "A".
TRY SAYING YOU WERE
TRYING TO PUT IT TOGETHER
WITH YOUR EYES CLOSED
TO TRY AND UNDERSTAND
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE
TO BE STEVIE WONDER.
THIS IS AS FAR AS YOU GOT.
PRETTY GOOD, HUH?
OR TELL HER YOU READ
ABOUT A GUY
WHO GOT A BARBECUE FROM TAIWAN.
THEY MADE A MISTAKE WHEN THEY
TRANSLATED THE INSTRUCTIONS.
THE WHOLE THING EXPLODED.
BUT SAY SOMEONE GOT KILLED.
THAT WAY IT SOUNDS REAL.
NEXT TIME YOU GET
SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
FIRST THING YOU DO,
FIND THE INSTRUCTIONS,
THROW 'EM AWAY.
YOU CAN CLAIM THAT
IT DIDN'T COME WITH ANY.
IF THERE'S ANOTHER SET
IN ANOTHER LANGUAGE,
HANG ON TO THEM.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED TO
LOOK AT THOSE PICTURES LATER.
(Strums guitar)
IT'S SO EASY
TO FOOL YOUR SENSES
YOU CAN'T BELIEVE
WHAT YOU SEE
BUT YOUR NOSE KNOWS
THE INSIDE STORY
IT CAN'T BE TRICKED BY
THE POWERS THAT BE
SO WHENEVER YOU
MAKE A DECISION
TAKE A WHIFF OF
THE AIR LIKE THIS
'CAUSE IT MAY
WALK LIKE A DUCK
AND TALK LIKE A DUCK
BUT IF IT SMELLS
KIND OF CHEESY, IT IS
JUST BUILT A TABLE FOR THE WIFE
TO MAKE UP FOR THE FACT THAT
I'VE LOST MY DRIVER'S LICENCE.
WE CALL THAT "MERCY FURNITURE".
THIS WEEK I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW YOU CAN BEAT RADAR TRAPS.
THAT WAY YOU CAN AVOID
THE EMBARRASSMENT
THAT I HAVE TO PUT UP WITH,
OR AT LEAST SOME OF IT.
THE WAY RADAR WORKS IS
A BEAM COMES FLYING
TOWARDS YOUR CAR,
BOUNCES OFF SOMETHING METAL,
HEADS BACK TO THE COP CAR,
TELLS THEM HOW MUCH YOU'RE
EXCEEDING THE SPEED LIMIT.
HE PULLS YOU OVER
AND GIVES YOU THAT $200 SMILE.
SO, YOU HAVE TO CONTROL
WHAT PART OF YOUR CAR
THE RADAR HITS.
WHAT WE DO IS
WE TAKE A PIECE OF FOAM,
OR A BOX OF CHOCOLATES
OR A BOX OF CEREAL,
OR ANY BOOK BY DICKENS,
AND WRAP THAT WITH WIRE,
THEN WE'LL HOOK THE WIRE
UP TO THIS NINE-VOLT BATTERY.
THIS IS WHAT WILL ATTRACT
THE RADAR.
SIMILAR TO THE TECHNOLOGY
USED IN THAT STEALTH BOMBER,
EXCEPT IN REVERSE.
AND A COUPLE OF DOLLARS CHEAPER
I BELIEVE.
THERE WE GO.
THIS WILL ATTRACT EVERY PIECE
OF RADAR IN YOUR NEIGHBOURHOOD.
YOU'LL BE PICKED UP BY
SHIPS AT SEA.
YOU DON'T MOUNT THIS
ON YOUR CAR ANY OLD WHICH WAY.
THIS HAS TO BE SECURED
ON A MOVING BELT,
SORT OF LIKE
MOOSE THOMPSON'S BUCKLE.
YOU COULD GO TO
YOUR GROCERY STORE
AND PORK THE CONVEYER BELT
WHILE THE MANAGER'S
GETTING YOU A FRESHER CABBAGE.
BUT, I PREFER TO USE
A LADDER AND SOME--
BED SHEETING.
I HAVE THE SHEET
RUNNING OVER THE LADDER.
SHE'S ALSO RUNNING OVER
THIS COPPER PIPE.
YOU CAN GET COPPER PIPE
OUT OF YOUR BASEMENT.
REMEMBER TO TURN THE WATER OFF.
THAT'S EASY TO SAY NOW.
AT THE END OF THE PIPE
I'VE GOT A HUNK OF CLOTHESLINE
WRAPPED AROUND
A CLOTHESLINE PULLEY.
THE BEAUTY OF STEALNG
A CLOTHESLINE SET
IS YOU GET TWO PULLEYS.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO
WITH THE OTHER PULLEY?
I HOPED YOU'D NEVER ASK.
BOLT IT TO THE REAR WHEEL
OF YOUR FAVOURITE VEHICLE.
TAKE THE CLOTHESLINE,
HOOK THAT ON TO THE PULLEY.
THEN THAT GOES UP
AND ATTACHES TO...
OUR BELT.
WHEN THE CAR MOVES,
THAT DRIVES THE PULLEY,
THAT DRIVES THE BELT,
AND THAT MOVES OUR
RADAR-ATTRACTER-THINGY
IN THE OPPOSITE DIRECTION.
SO, IF YOU'RE GOING,
SAY, 60 MILES AN HOUR,
WELL, THE RADAR TRACKER
IS GOING 20 MILES AN HOUR
BACKWARDS.
SO, THE RADAR READS IT AS
60 MINUS 20 IS...
LEGAL.
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
WHEN THIS COMES AROUND
AND GOES UNDERNEATH,
IT'S GOING TO JAM UP
AGAINST THE ROOF.
I NEED SOMETHING
TO RAISE THE LADDER UP.
HMM?
OH, OH, OH, OH.
TELL YOU WHAT,
THIS CRAFT TABLE
WOULD BE PERFECT
IF IT DIDN'T HAVE A TOP ON IT.
THAT'S THE BEAUTY OF
USING ONE NAIL.
(Audience laughing)
PERFECT.
WE GOT HER ON A JACK
SO WE CAN DEMONSTRATE...
YOU GOTTA HAVE A TWIST IN THIS.
OTHERWISE THEY'LL BE
GOING IN THE SAME DIRECTION,
WHICH WILL DOUBLE YOUR SPEED.
YOU'LL GET A TICKET
FOR DOING 120.
LET'S GIVE HER A TRY.
(Engine starting)
AND THAT'S WORKING PERFECT.
OH, OH, OH,
JUST THOUGHT OF SOMETHING.
DON'T MESS AROUND
WITH THE RATIOS OF THE PULLEY.
OTHERWISE YOU'RE GOING
60 MILES AN HOUR FORWARD.
THE RADAR THING IS GOING
60 MILES AN HOUR BACKWARD.
THE COP WILL PULL YOU OVER
AND GIVE YOU A TICKET
FOR PARKING ON THE FREEWAY.
REMEMBER, IF WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I'M GOING TO PUT
THE PEDAL TO THE METAL.
(Red): STAY TUNED FOR GARTH
AND HIS SNAKE.
LOSE YOUR CAR AND
DISCOVER WHO YOUR FRIENDS ARE.
LODGE MEMBERS TEASING YOU?
I CAN'T TAKE IT
FROM OLD MAN SEDGWICK.
HE'S BLIND, HE'S DEAF.
HE'S GOT THE REFLEXES
OF A HOUSEPLANT.
HE'S DRIVING
A 60-FOOT MOTOR HOME.
HE'S A MENACE AT THE WHEEL.
HE'S ASLEEP AT THE WHEEL,
HAROLD.
ASK ME QUESTIONS
FROM THE DRIVER HANDBOOK.
"WHAT'S THE PROCEDURE
FOR STOPPING AT A STOP SIGN:
"STOPPING AT THE SIGN
OR AT THE CORNER?"
WELL, IF NOBODY'S COMING,
I USUALLY SLOW DOWN TO 40,
UNLESS MY HORN'S BROKEN.
I'LL MARK THAT AS
"I HAVE NO IDEA,
AND I JUST FAILED THE TEST."
DID YOU READ THE HANDBOOK?
HAVE YOU SEEN THE SIZE
OF THE PRINT?
MAYBE YOU NEED GLASSES.
MY EYES ARE FINE.
HOW MANY FINGERS
AM I HOLDING UP?
BETTER BE MORE THAN ONE.
YOU NEED GLASSES.
I GOT NO WAY OF GETTING TO
THE EYE DOCTOR.
THE GUYS ARE ON THE LAKE.
WELL, I HAVE MY LICENCE.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS ASK...
NICELY.
OH MAN.
HAROLD, WILL YOU DRIVE ME
TO THE EYE DOCTOR, PLEASE?
OK, SURE.
WHAT VEHICLE ARE WE TAKING?
I SAID I HAVE MY LICENCE.
I DIDN'T SAY I HAVE A VEHICLE.
YOU WANT TO RIDE ON
THE HANDLEBARS OR THE RAT TRAP?
YOU HEAR A LOT OF TALK
ABOUT POWER SAWS.
BUT A SHARP HAND SAW
IS JUST AS EFFECTIVE.
ALL YOU'VE GOT TO DO
IS CUT A NOTCH IN YOUR WOOD,
THEN CUT A NOTCH
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
AND THEN JUST VERY QUICKLY
FINISH OFF YOUR CUT.
REMEMBER, ANY TOOL
CAN BE THE RIGHT TOOL.
THIS IS
THE BIG ONE.
THE GRAND PRIZE IS FOR
OVER A HUNDRED DOLLARS,
LESS EXPENSES
AND ALL THAT SORT OF STUFF.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO MAKE MR. FRANKLIN SAY
THIS WORD.
THIRTY SECONDS, AND GO.
ALL RIGHT, UH... MASCULINE.
CHUCK NORRIS.
OPPOSITE.
WILLARD SCOTT.
(Audience laughing)
WOMAN.
MAINTENANCE.
PERFECT WOMAN.
EXPENSIVE?
DOUGIE, YOU SEE A WOMAN.
SHE'S PETITE, SHE'S PRETTY.
YOU SAY SHE'S VERY...
VERY...
NOT FROM
AROUND HERE.
(Audience laughing)
YOU'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME,
UNCLE RED.
I CAN'T THINK OF
ANYTHING ELSE TO SAY.
YOU'RE SITTING THERE.
SAY SOMETHING, ANYTHING.
UH... ALL RIGHT...
HAROLD.
FEMININE.
(Bell ringing)
(Applause)
GARTH HARBLE HERE...
ANIMAL CONTROL,
WITH ANOTHER LESSON
IN WILDLIFE MANAGEMENT.
COME ON IN HERE, RED.
WHAT DID YOU DO
TO YOUR LEG THERE, GARTH?
I HAD A BIT OF A RUN-IN
WITH A CARIBOU
DOWN AT
THE ANIMAL CONTROL CENTRE.
I HAD TO TAKE ONE
FOR THE TEAM, RED.
OH, OH,
I FORGOT SOMETHING.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OH, AH.
IT LOOKS LIKE IT WAS
A SHORT CARIBOU.
NO, NO --
I WAS STANDING ON MY DESK.
TODAY WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT SNAKES.
LOTS OF CIVILIANS
ARE AFRAID OF SNAKES.
WE IN THE A.C. UNIFORM
KNOW THAT SNAKES
ARE BASICALLY HARMLESS...
UNLESS YOU STEP IN THEIR NEST.
I'LL NEVER FORGET
THAT TRIP TO THE HOSPITAL.
I HAD SO MUCH POISON IN ME
I DIDN'T THINK I COULD
KEEP THE TRUCK ON THE ROAD.
I JUST STAY AWAY FROM SNAKES.
YOU DON'T LIKE ANIMALS,
DO YOU, RED?
WELL, NOT AS MUCH AS LIFE, NO.
(Rustling)
WHAT THE--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT ARE YOU--
THIS MEANS SNAKE.
SORT OF A STANDARD HAND SIGNAL.
ALL RIGHT.
(Rustling)
I THINK WE HAVE AN AUTHENTIC
"MISSISSAUGA" RATTLER.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
GRAB HIM AROUND THE HEAD
WITH THIS SNAKE POLE.
GOT HIM!
WHOA, WHOA, BOY.
HE'S A BIG ONE.
OH, SETTLE DOWN THERE.
HE'S GOT AN ATTITUDE.
I'VE GOT A BURLAP BAG
ON THE PORCH.
I'M GOING TO PUT HIM IN THAT.
GARTH, I THINK YOU GOT HIM
BY THE TAIL THERE.
HUH?
(Chomping sound)
OH!
OH, OH.
ANOTHER SUPER DAY.
OH.
(Sighing)
WELL, SURPRISE, SURPRISE.
THE BUMP IN THE ROAD IS BACK
AND IT'S BIGGER
AND BETTER THAN EVER.
WHAT?
NOTHING.
(Laughing)
APPARENTLY,
WHEN THEY FIXED THE BUMP,
EVERYBODY STARTED SPEEDING
SO MUCH INTO TOWN
THAT THEY DECIDED TO PUT
A SPEED BUMP IN THERE,
A REALLY BIG ONE.
(Laughing)
OK, OK, I OWE YOU ONE.
YOU OWE ME ANOTHER ONE, HAROLD.
I WANT YOU TO GO DOWN THERE
AND PRETEND YOU'RE ME.
AT THE
EYE DOCTOR?
THE LICENCE OFFICE --
YOU TAKE THE TEST FOR ME.
WE'VE GOT THE SAME LAST NAME,
THE SAME ADDRESS.
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T TELL THEM
YOUR I.Q.,
THEY'LL THINK YOU'RE ME.
I GUESS THE BELL FELL OFF.
I HOPE THE BELL FELL OFF.
(Red): SO BILL'S STILL LOOKING
FOR OTHER-- OW.
BILL'S STILL LOOKING FOR WAYS
THAT I CAN GET AROUND.
OK, BILL, I'LL HELP YOU.
THAT'S WHAT FRIENDS ARE FOR.
SO, THIS IS
THE SKATEBOARD THING.
THEY'RE VERY POPULAR
WITH YOUNG PEOPLE.
NOT THAT MUCH TO IT,
I WOULDN'T THINK.
WHAT?
OH BOY, OH BOY,
WHERE'S THAT GOING?
OK, UH, THAT'S NOT GOING TO
WORK OUT THAT WELL.
OK, NOW HE'S GOT
THE INLINE SKATES.
WANTED ME TO HELP HIM
GET THAT-- OH.
OH.
LOST A LITTLE BIT
OF PATIENCE HERE.
ALL RIGHT, THERE, THAT-- OK.
THE THING WITH INLINE SKATES,
I BELIEVE
IT'S LIKE ICE SKATING.
IT'S A QUESTION OF BALANCE.
IT'S MORE OF SORT OF
A NATURAL ATHLETIC ABILITY,
AND I GUESS IT TAKES
A LITTLE WHILE TO GET THE...
WHEN YOU START THINKING ABOUT
HOW SHORT LIFE IS --
THERE HE GOES.
THERE'S THAT TECHNIQUE --
OH, WHAT'S THIS?
SKATEBOARD AND INLINE SKATES,
AND WHAT'S -- OK.
I DON'T WANT TO GET--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, BILL?
OH, I SEE.
HITCHHIKING.
WELL, THAT MAKES SENSE.
YOU GO AHEAD, BILL.
I'LL WAIT HERE.
(Red): COMING UP,
HAROLD WILL IMPERSONATE ME.
SOMETIMES YOU DO GET A GLIMPSE
OF JUSTICE IN THIS LIFE.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK
WAS SO BUSY RAZZING ME,
HE DROVE HIS MOTOR HOME
THROUGH A STAND OF TREES,
RIPPED THE SIDE MIRROR OFF.
HE WON'T EVEN NOTICE
TILL HE LOOKS IN IT,
WHICH IS NEVER.
HAROLD HAS AGREED TO TAKE
THE DRIVING TEST FOR ME
AS A WAY OF SECURING HIS PAY.
HAROLD, COME ON IN.
(Applause)
AFTER
THE TEST,
I'LL HAVE TO SIGN
THE ORGAN DONATION CARD.
WHAT, WHAT,
HOLD IT, HOLD IT!
I'M NOT DONATING ORGANS.
WHAT IF I GET TO HEAVEN
WITHOUT KIDNEYS
AND THERE'S AN OPEN BAR?
(Mimicking Red):
I'D CALL IT A SET-BACK.
(Audience laughing)
DON'T DO THAT, HAROLD.
(Applause)
(Mimicking Red): AHHHH,
DON'T DO WHAT?
AHHHH, STOP CALLING ME HAROLD.
JUST GET DOWN
AND GET MY LICENCE, PLEASE.
(Mimicking Red): ALL RIGHT.
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Mimicking Harold): HAAA HAAA,
HA HA HA, HA HA HA.
THAT'S FUNNY, UNCLE RED.
RANGER GORD AGAIN.
HERE'S AN INTERESTING PIECE
OF WILDLIFE LORE.
DURING THE MATING SEASON,
ANIMALS WILL CLAW THE TREES
TO MARK THEIR TERRITORY.
BEARS DO IT.
BADGERS DO IT.
SO DO WOLVES.
BUT THESE MARKINGS
AREN'T FROM ANY OF THOSE.
THESE ARE...
OH YEAH.
WELL, I'M ONLY HUMAN.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW.
THIS WEEK, WE HAVE MY UNCLE RED
AND WATER TAXI CAPTAIN,
MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
(Applause)
THIS WEEK'S LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS.
OH, COOL,
IT'S GOT A NAUTICAL THEME.
HE'S A... THING.
"DEAR EXPERTS, HOW CAN
I HELP PROTECT THE WHALES?"
OH MAN,
I GOT TO TELL YOU,
I DON'T GET THIS.
I HEAR A LOT ABOUT THIS.
YOU GOT AN ANIMAL,
THIS THING'S 100 FEET LONG,
WEIGHS ABOUT 1,000 TONS.
IF THIS THING
CAN'T TAKE CARE OF ITSELF,
REALLY, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I CAN DO FOR THEM.
NO, RED --
HAROLD IS TALKING ABOUT WHALING.
OH.
WE GOT TO AGREE TO STOP
KILLING THE WHALES.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
NEXT TIME I SEE A WHALE
IN POSSUM LAKE,
I'M GOING TO BACK OFF.
I'LL SPEAK TO BERNICE
AND GET HER AND HER FRIENDS
TO EASE OFF
THE WHALING ACTIVITIES.
JUST BECAUSE NOBODY
YOU KNOW KILLS WHALES
DOESN'T MEAN
IT'S NOT HAPPENING.
DON'T ASSUME
THINGS AREN'T HAPPENING
'CAUSE LODGE MEMBERS
DON'T DO IT.
I'M THE FELLA
YOU'RE LOOKING FOR, HAROLD.
I WAS A WHALER AT ONE TIME.
(Audience laughing)
NEVER A PROFESSIONAL,
NOT LIKE
THEM BIG JAPANESE SHIPS.
NO, I WAS MORE OF
A SPORT WHALER.
(Audience laughing)
I WENT OUT IN THE CANOE,
YOU KNOW.
(Audience laughing)
A 20-FOOTER, A BIG ONE.
YEAH, SOUNDS
LIKE A BIG ONE.
MR. SHAUGHNESSY,
HOW DID YOU GET
A BIG HARPOON GUN
INTO A CANOE?
A HARPOON? --
WHERE'S THE SPORT IN THAT?
NO, I'D WRAP A ROPE
AROUND MYSELF AND DIVE IN.
I'D GRAB HIS TAIL, HANG ON,
AND WEAR HIM DOWN.
IT WASN'T EASY.
DID YOU EVER SEE THEIR TAILS?
THEY'RE INCREDIBLE.
WELL, INCREDIBLE TAILS
WOULD BE RIGHT UP YOUR ALLEY,
I WOULD THINK.
(Audience laughing)
HOW LONG DID IT TAKE YOU
TO WEAR THIS WHALE DOWN?
UH, 10, 20 MONTHS.
(Audience laughing)
AND ME OUT THERE
THRASHING AROUND
HANGING ON FOR A YEAR OR MORE.
I TELL YOU, I BEGAN TO HATE
THE TASTE OF SEAFOOD.
ALL EXCEPT THE STINGRAY.
THEIR LITTLE TOES
ARE A DELICACY.
THAT WHALE WOULD COLLAPSE.
I'D TOW IT INTO SHORE.
THAT VILLAGE HAD
ENOUGH BLUBBER FOR THE YEAR.
MR. SHAUGHNESSY, THAT...
IS A LOT OF BLUBBER.
(Audience laughing)
I STOPPED
AFTER I TRIED TO BATTLE
THE GREAT WHITE WHALE
MOBY RICHARD.
(Audience laughing)
I THINK YOU MEAN MOBY DICK.
NO,
I DIDN'T KNOW HIM THAT WELL.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
I COULD HAVE PASSED
THAT TEST EASY.
WELL, YOU DIDN'T.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT --
YOUR BELLY GOT STUCK
IN THE STEERING WHEEL
AND I DROVE THE CAR
THROUGH MURRAY'S FRUIT STAND.
OH MY GOSH.
AH HA HA.
THOSE STEMS REALLY HURT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
IF THEY THINK YOU'RE ME,
DO I GET BLAMED FOR THIS?
NO, NO.
MY BEARD WENT FLYING.
I GOT HIT BY A KIWI.
SO I HAD TO TELL THEM
WHO I REALLY WAS...
OLD MAN SEDGWICK.
HIS LICENCE HAS BEEN
PERMANENTLY REVOKED.
THAT IS EXCELLENT WORK.
THANKS TO ME, THE ROAD
IS A SAFER PLACE TO BE.
DON'T COUNT ON IT --
I GOT MY LICENCE BACK.
WHILE YOU WERE
MAKING FRUIT SALAD,
I WENT TO COURT AND BLAMED
THE MESS ON THE BUMP.
THE JUDGE HATED THE BUMP, TOO.
HE POINTED TO
A LUMP ON HIS HEAD
WHERE HIS HAIR USED TO BE.
SO I GOT MY LICENCE BACK.
AS SOON AS I GET MY VAN BACK
I'LL BE COMPLETE.
HOW SAD.
(Possum squeal)
OH, MEETING TIME.
I'M GOING TO GO.
I'VE GOT TO GET
SOME WATERMELON PITS
OUT OF MY UNDIES.
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE GO FOR A MOONLIT DRIVE
DOWN BY THE LAKE?
A ROMANTIC SPOT
WHERE WE CAN PARK.
DON'T WORRY,
I'LL TAKE EVERYTHING SLOW.
I CAN'T AFFORD ANY MORE
DEMERIT POINTS.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND ALL
THE GUYS AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
(Harold): ALL RISE.
ALL RISE.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.