If you go out in the woods today, you're in
for a big surprise because you're going to
smack your face right into the red green
show, broadcasting live from the beautiful
possum lodge high up in the hinterlands
where we're coming from, you know, a small
promotional fee has been paid by several
companies in order that we do not mention
their name. And here he is, the man who's
mad about plaid, the king of canvas.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'd like to present a
man who really needs no introduction
whatsoever. Go ahead, I'll go ahead.
You don't need an introduction whatsoever.
Oh oh, all right.
Thank you. Hell for not mentioning my name.
Thank you and welcome to Possum Lodge.
Harold, here is my producer and director,
which is a showbiz term meaning nephew.
And as my producer director, Harold's job is
what is it you do again, Harold?
Oh, I do this.
This is my job.
It's a living hell, Harold.
You are a talented man.
Well, actually, you're not a man yet.
And the talent, it seems a little strong.
Harold, you're a multi big deal up at the
Lodge this week.
We've had a theft.
Our Lodge Treasurer, Douglas, he had his
pants stolen.
Not a pretty sight.
It sounds like a crime of passion.
Well, I don't think so, Harold.
These were lime green polyester jobs,
probably the work of one of them bad taste
posses. Now I can make jokes, but Douglas is
pretty upset about it.
These were his favorite pants his mum gave
him to him for his 20th birthday back in
nineteen seventy five.
So anyway, he contacted our head of
security, Noel, and he put Noel on the case.
Our head of security
Is quite a case. He's so short that he's a
briefcase.
Thank you, Harold. Anyway, Noel is just using
this as an excuse to get himself a whole
bunch of surveillance equipment.
Right now, he's about $5000 over his level
of comprehension.
But idiots with equipment is something you
see a lot of up here at the Lodge.
As a cute Harold.
Oh, right. In
all, Lockerbie, you got camera stuffed up
inside the stuffed animal.
What's that like Robo Smurf or something?
Oh no, that's for surveillance at daycare
centers.
Yeah. What is all this paranoid duress having
to sell?
I'll have, you know, the Douglas asked me to
improve the security of the lodge no matter
of the cost. Ok, Bill Money's all wired in.
Plug that in. If you wouldn't much power up
this system and see if we get any output.
Carol, watch a TV monitor.
See if you can see me. Ok.
Nothin yet. I don't think it's good to do
that.
What did you spend $5000 on it?
Where is he? No, behind door number two.
That hurt. That's nothing.
What did you spend $5000 on
Security system for the lodge?
Got the deluxe model?
What? Why?
Well, you told me to, you know, last week
when your polyester pants went missing, you
said, tighten up the security in the lodge.
So. Huh?
I meant a few latches on the windows.
A lock on the door.
I didn't mean for you to turn this large
into dark Vader's get star.
To return this stuff right now, Mr, or I'll
have your badge.
Don't you threaten me? I know one hundred and
fifty ways to kill a man with a tuning fork,
does it?
The only threat to security around this logic
is you and bill.
No offense bill. No, I'm invoking 333 g.
I'm a large
Charter. You can't have that chart you read.
What's he talking about?
Oh, no, I just run the law.
I have no idea how it works.
I'm replacing you as head of security and
appointing an interim head of security
pending an internal investigation.
Meet a coup d'etat.
I taught. I taught coup d'etat.
I'm not giving up this job without a fight.
You don't do anything without a fight.
You brawl with your close every morning.
Look at you. You're a disaster.
This is a head of security.
You look like a street performer.
The head of security looks like like this,
huh?
This is our new head of security.
No chance.
No way. I'm I'm too busy being head of
maintenance.
How much have you had the security?
That job requires brains.
Would you like to have your requirements
squeezed out your head?
No offense helmet, I'm just suggesting
possibly, you know, have you don't have the
cutting or maybe you're not quite as quick
as you could be?
No, I'm beginning to understand why you need
to learn how to defend yourself and if I
going to tell you that much, but
I'll tell you, I'm not giving up this job.
You can't have my badge badges.
We don't need no stinking badges.
Raise your right hand. Ok, you're left.
One will do fine. Do you swear to uphold and
enforce the Possum Lodge rules?
Just fix my axe.
I take that as a yes.
All right. I know officially proclaim you as
the temporary head of security.
If I had the wings of an angel, John, none of
my clothes would fit.
So instead, I'll have the wings of a chicken
Walk, walk
With medium socks and a large draught.
This week in Handyman Corner, we're going to
talk about making your very own fine, highly
crafted furniture, which is something
everybody wants to do.
But then you build something and it turns
out to be a piece of crap you couldn't give
away at a garage sale.
Whereas building, you know, a fine heirloom
piece is something to take a little extra
time, and it's something that can be done
within your grasp.
I'm guessing we got to do something like
that right here today.
We're going to take this canoe we have here,
and we're going to make it into a grandfather
clock. Ok, now the first thing we have to do
is cut the end off here because you want to
stand it up and it's got to be flat,
something flat to sit on.
Now, you could cut it off a lot of different
ways you could use, I guess, the hacks on
that or you could use tin snips or you could
use a circular saw you could chew that off
you want. You could just smash it off with a
sledgehammer.
Just keep pounding it. You could back your
van over it.
Personally, for me, I prefer using acetylene
torch because it just works so much faster.
Acetylene torch really does the job, doesn't
it?
Now what we have to do is you need to bring
this around and flatten these out of it, of
all that. So flat, our base looks pretty
good
now, we stand her up on our wooden base,
just
we're her into place here.
Sticky, Peterson said. I could have just
thrown some paint cans, piled them up in here
and the weight of them would held it in
place.
But I don't know.
That's that's not the way I like to do
things.
I'm more of a detail guy.
Ok, OK,
now you can fancy that up with a trim or
even do a bit of sanding, you know, depending
on how valuable an heirloom you're trying to
create.
Ok, now now we need the precision timepiece.
What I do is I just sniff the whole workings
out of the clock, in the kitchen, at the
lodge here. It's got its own little power
pack on the back.
And to mount that on, we use the universal
clock mounting device, which you can find in
most closets. Like so and then we just grab
a little galvanized me, although we want this
thing to last a long time.
I got home to pop that in there and then
hang the clock right on there.
Twelve o'clock high.
Ok, starting to take shape.
Now what we need to do is to put in the
chains and the weights and the pendulum and
all that type of thing. But the mechanism is
already on the clock.
So these things are strictly cosmetic, which
is a decorator term for fake.
So we use these chains and we need some
pieces of Dowling.
But I don't have pieces of Dowling and I'm
not interested in buying pieces of Dowling,
but I do have an old, an old paddle here.
Now, Harold always tells me that gold is
worth a lot more than silver, so I'm painting
her gold. That should be about 18 carats
worth, huh?
I'll just wait till it dries.
Good enough, so
Now we take this over and I put a hook in
behind the clock, so we hang hang the chain
from the hook. One man's meat is another
man's hanging clock.
There we go. Now what we need to do is to
add some sort of a pendulum.
What I've done is I took the anchor out of
the fishing boat.
I don't want to drift too far.
The wind's not. Not too bad today.
Can't catch up later on. Oh, well, now we
hang this.
Hang this rig up in here as well.
And there we've got our whole phony looking
mechanism now that really top it off here.
You can put some plastic wrap across the
canoe and it gives it kind of a leaded glass
look, or you could just leave it open.
But at this point, I'm not about to cheapen
off first class all the way.
And there you have it.
Very own beautiful grandfather clock.
A little bit wrinkled, but then again, so
his grandfather.
And if you don't like the aluminum look, you
could cover that with a wood grain or
simulated leather or whatever Mac that comes
in.
You can also get some doorknobs, you know,
to put on the points and the stuff sticking
out. And it's up to you.
But I'll tell you one thing you've got a one
of a kind here.
So remember, if the women don't find you
handsome, they should at least find your
handy. Does that every hour on the hour?
So that's the way they want to play it?
Well, I'll go in the car.
That's right. That's fine.
I'm not going quietly.
It is spring.
The river is raging.
Our gill nets are strung across it.
We wind them in to examine our catch.
Three canoes for lawn chairs, eight tool
sheds in the dock.
You can make money in this business and you
know where to fish.
I'll tell you things around here have gone
from bad to weird.
No skulking around plotting revenge and
saying that everybody's out to get them, you
know, and they took his strawberries and
helmets turned out to be a worse security
guard than Noel. Helmet ever was easy going,
but now he's turned into Jason's evil
brother. You see a sign of diagram, Harold.
I can only hope he's out at a job interview
anyway.
Helmet put a sign up in the dining room says
No shirt, no shoes, no consciousness.
And he gave us a whole list of rules.
Incredible stuff like no picking your teeth
with cutlery.
Since when did we get cutlery?
There's a whole bunch of rules like that.
And if you look past the spelling, you can
see Douglas's simple mind at work there.
So I think what I have to do is go down and
have a word with helmets.
So, Harold, why don't you just get on with
the show here, Aaron?
All right. All right. Oh boy.
Oh boy, oh boy, did I do that?
It's kind of neat. Now, let me read I wanted
to talk to you about this live
security business.
Oh, Douglas told me not to discuss large
security with anybody.
Did you know that anyone could just drive up
here and walk into the lodge even if they
weren't members?
Yeah. Well, nobody ever does that helmet.
Not not even members of our own families.
You're right.
My mom's never been here.
Never even seen the place.
You know, she went through twenty eight
hours of labor to give birth to me.
No, I didn't know that.
Yeah. Twenty eight hours of screaming.
Well, I'm not surprised you're so big.
The doctors probably had to make two trips.
Let me think pretty handsome woman.
All right. Nice tattoo.
There you should see her in color.
And someday you will as soon as this place
is clean and suitable for mom and Douglas.
Yeah, helmet vote all these new rules.
A lot of the guys think that you're really
cramping our style here.
Well, we have to make this place clean and
suitable for our moms to come up and visit
that. Wouldn't that be nice? Wouldn't you
love to have your mom up here and maybe even
your mother in law?
Well, I spend a lot more time at home, that's
for sure.
Something to be honest here.
Are you really enjoying this large security
job?
No, not, not really.
I miss servicing my pump.
I haven't filled her grease caps all day.
You know, nobody wants to be the heavy.
I don't want to be the heavy.
I don't think anybody likes being there.
Well, how come you're going around making
everybody's life so miserable in?
Well, Douglas told me that if I fail as head
of security at the Lodge, that I'd bring
shame to my family and my mom, and I want my
mom to be proud of me.
Well, I don't want to come between you and
your mother helmet.
Not without my pads on.
Now, here's a clue to this week's adventures
with Bill.
A great big pile of rocks.
You guessed it yet. Think about it.
You've got a dog house and a ladder, and we
got a kid's playpen in a garbage can.
But we're going to do is, of course, build a
catapult.
Now Bill gets down there with the garbage
can.
He's duct tape and that on to one end of a
ladder.
And that's going to be where he goes.
And on the other end, I'm tying the kid's
playpen as one of those old wooden ones that
I must've had a kid with a big head.
He's probably going to kill himself in that
thing.
I'm tying that on to the other end.
So Bill's got that pretty damn, pretty well
done there.
The handyman secret weapon.
Now he takes a little piece of rope and he
takes this off, and this is basically going
to be the trigger of the catapult because as
long as it's tight around that heavy log
that's rooted right into the forest there,
then it's not going to call.
So he he climbs into the garbage can, which
seemed extremely appropriate to me, and I put
the rocks in here because what's happening
is the ladders bending, bending way down.
So eventually the whole playpen sitting
right on the ground with all the weight and
the ladder is bent right around almost
double.
There's a lot of spring in that thing and a
lot of tension that's really pulling up on
the rope. Now I got to do is I got to cut
the rope and we had brought an axe along to
cut the rope on it.
I don't know where the axe is.
Oh, I'm not
Going to ask, so I cut the rope and their
goal.
Oh, my God. Oh, that's great back into the
cannon that launched
The rocks from the other end.
I noticed Iraq Soledad before a building.
Finally. Oh, oh, oh, Bill.
But these are these are industry.
Some of the rocks out there and.
It seems OK, although he looks a little
pale.
Now that I have things around here have gone
from worst bratwurst and it rules about where
you can sit, where you can walk, you can't
talk too loud, you can't whisper to anybody.
As far as I'm concerned, everybody has been
stripped totally of all of their rights,
every last single and
Back until I'm ready to do my job.
Oh hi, Harold. Where's my axe?
My axe is gone. Someone stole my axe.
You're wearing and you're wearing it.
Would you do it? Don't break it.
Ok, it's fine.
Apple Watch this thing.
No problem.
Oh, you can do that now to Kenya.
Well, and back, you know, your producer
slash director is here to do my job.
Oh no. Oh, Harold. Harold, we've been get
along.
Fine without you. Anyway, as I was saying,
as far as I'm concerned, Possum Lodge has
turned into Orwell's nineteen eighty four
marked down to nine ninety five.
You weather is real nice.
We have to say that even if there's a
hurricane,
Can I give you a hand with this?
No, I'm fine. I'm fine, really.
I figure that it's going to be a huge revolt
at tonight's Lodge meeting and probably going
to end up with, you know, people getting
their jobs back.
Everybody, you know, bigger.
No, no. I figured just no helmet
Off as the phone. So how you been getting
along with me?
How are you coping? It's good.
It's good. Can I give a hand with that?
Oh no, I'm fine. I don't mind helping with
that because hail,
Hail, hail to go to the meeting.
Ok, I'm going to get brainwashed brainwash.
Do you really good? Great.
Great. Great.
Great. Yeah.
Oh. My my.
I'm sorry, red.
I'm invoking the emergency clause of the
large charter, which means I'll be running
this meeting, you might not correct.
Fine. What I know about me is.
Did I say you may sit?
Yeah, you did right after, did I say,
Oh, OK,
Well, let's not beat around the bush today.
Phil is our first order of business.
No Christmas.
Our former head of security, spent five
thousand of large money on a surveillance
system which randomly explodes, showering us
all with singe teddy bear stuffing.
Now, now I feel very strongly that Noel
should pay for it and or be expelled from the
lodge. All those in favor on the.
I think we've got a bigger issue than that to
vote on.
Now I've collected an extensive list of
complaints against helmet lights carry.
Some weren't even mine, so I say we vote to
return things back to the way they were.
Yes. Yeah, I think that's a great idea.
It is. It is. So but that's including my job
too.
Yeah, I second that motion.
You know, I had a vote.
I would do that because
I don't have a vote. I think it's okay.
Just a minute or something like that.
Not many people
Haven't thought of it. Shut up.
Now there'll be no vote and there'll be no
discussion and no one will leave this place
until I get my pants back their lime green
polyester, and they're very difficult to
replace.
Try the rag in the car wash.
Lime green, I took those bands home, what I
thought they were ladies slack, so I gave it
to my mom, but they didn't really fit her
until she let the crotch out on them.
And now they look quite good.
I gave my
Birthday pants to your mother.
Oh, calm down, I can bring them back.
I don't want them now that your mother's
worn them.
What's wrong with my mother?
You're saying there's something wrong with my
mother?
No, no.
Me in your dreams.
Get up. For
all those in favor of reinstating me as head
of security, say, I thank you very much.
Oh, and all those in favor of reinstating
red as leader of Possum Lodge J.R..
Well, hey, welcome back Bret Michael and all
those in favor of reinstating me.
As you know, the special effects technician
on the Red Green Show say I just.
You say out loud you want
All those in favor of reinstating me as head
of large maintenance say, I thank God I was
really getting tired of playing the
Heavy.
Well, since there's nobody left to reinstate,
I call on Douglas to supply the evening's
entertainment. That's.
Thank you all.
Well, fellas, my topic for today is knowing
your own limitations.
Well, there you see a democracy in action.
Well, I should say Noel in action.
Actions speak louder than words.
And take a heck of a lot less horsepower.
Anyway, Douglas is not too happy, but the
people have spoken, albeit rather
incoherently. But we're all gone back now to
being free, man, although you really are
never truly free, are you?
And speaking of which, if my wife is
watching, I'll be coming straight home after
the meeting tonight, and I really I'm really
glad that our marriage is a democracy, even
if you do have nine votes.
So until next time, on behalf of myself and
possibly Harold and the rest of the gang up
here at Possum Lodge?
Keep your stick on the ice.
Well, the me man hurt you, my precious baby,
huh?
Oh. That's.