THE ONE THING ABOUT GUNS
THAT I FIND CONFUSING
IS THAT MOST PEOPLE -
WELL, OKAY, MAINLY MEN
- HAVE A FASCINATION
WITH SHOOTING.
GUYS WHO WOULD NEVER KILLED
ANYTHING, NEVER EVEN
HURT ANYTHING,
LOVE THE THRILL OF
SHOOTING AT A TARGET.
MAYBE WHEN YOU SPEND YOUR DAYS
WORKING AT A JOB
WHERE YOU DON'T SEEM TO
SEE ANY RESULTS FROM
WHAT YOU'RE DOING,
YOU START THINKING THAT
THE WORLD WOULD BE
EXACTLY THE SAME IF
YOU WEREN'T HERE.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT
FEELING GOES AWAY
WHEN YOU CAN STAND 50 FEET
BACK WITH A GUN IN YOUR HAND
AND BLOW THE HINGES
OFF YOUR GARAGE DOOR
OR EVEN BETTER YOUR
NEIGHBOUR'S GARAGE DOOR.
THERE'S INSTANT
GRATIFICATION.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT MAKES US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
HERE ARE A FEW SCENES
FROM THIS WEEK'S EPISODE.
IT'S WAY BETTER THAN ONE
OF THE ONES WE DID
A LONG TIME AGO.
WE GOT ALL KINDS OF
THINGS WE'RE GOING
TO BUILD FOR YOU
AND SAY TO YOU AND
FOOL AROUND WITH YOU.
WE GOT ALL KINDS
OF THINGS THAT HAPPEN
LIKE THINGS LIKE
THAT AND OTHER THINGS
SORT OF
LIKE THIS.
AND NOW HERE IS A MAN WHO
CAN'T SEE THE FOREST
FOR THE FLEAS,
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HERE'S A GUY WHO SEES
THE FOREST AND THEN FLEES,
MY NEPHEW, HAROLD.
[ APPLAUSE ]
BIG STUFF GOING ON
UP HERE THIS WEEK,
THE FIRST ANNUAL POSSUM
LAKE TAXIDERMY SHOOTOUT.
YOU'RE GOING TO SHOOT
A TAXIDERMIST?
OH, OH, OH, UNCLE RED,
ARE YOU GOING TO
HAVE HIM MOUNTED?
NO, NO, HAROLD, THIS
IS A BRILLIANT IDEA.
YOU KNOW WHAT WITH HUNTING
BEING KIND OF A CONTROVERSIAL
SPORT THESE DAYS
ARTIE KAY'S TAXIDERMY
SHOP, BOY THE BUSINESS
IS JUST FALLING OFF
THE TABLE DOWN THERE.
IT ALWAYS SEEMS BUSY
WHEN I GO BY.
YEAH, PEOPLE JUST ACT
THAT WAY WHEN THEY SEE
YOU COMING, HAROLD.
SO ARTIE'S GOT THIS IDEA
WHERE HE'S GOING TO
CHARGE PEOPLE
TO GO HUNTING FOR DEAD,
WILD, STUFFED ANIMALS.
WHAT?
I MEAN, WELL, OKAY --
WELL WHERE --
-- WELL WHERE
THEY -- WHO -- IF YOU HAD
AND THEY WERE,
YOU KNOW -- AND THEN.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
A THING.
CAN YOU EXPLAIN?
I'LL TRY, HAROLD.
ARTIE'S GOING TO
CLEAN OUT THE STUFF
OUT OF HIS STORE,
YOU KNOW, UNCLAIMED
ITEMS AND DISPLAY MODELS
AND OLD BURNED OUT ARTICLES
AND THAT KIND OF THING.
HE'S GOING TO PROP
THE ANIMALS UP ALL
OVER THE FOREST
AND THEN YOU PAY
HIM A $10 FEE
AND YOU GET TO GO
OUT AND HUNT ALL
THE DEAD STUFF.
I MEAN SAWDUST-FILLED
ANIMALS ARE ALWAYS
IN SEASON, HAROLD.
HUNTING FOR WHAT?
WELL, WHATEVER HE
GETS IN THE STORE,
RACCOONS, OTTERS,
ELEPHANTS, SWORDFISH,
AN OLD COUCH,
WHATEVER YOU FIND,
YOU TRACK THEM DOWN,
STARE THEM IN THE GLASSY
EYES AND FIRE AWAY.
THE FIRST PRIZE GOES
TO THE GUY WHO SHOOTS
THOR THE MIGHTY POLAR BEAR.
THOR?
THAT MANGY, YELLOW LUMP
THAT'S BEEN HANGING
IN ARTIE'S FRONT WINDOW
FOR THE PAST 20 YEARS?
YEAH, IT'S JUST A
BIG RACCOON THAT
HE BLEACHED.
IT'S RANCID.
JUST ONE BULLET AND
POOF IT WILL DISINTEGRATE.
YEAH, BUT WE CAN
PRETEND THAT IT'S A
MIGHTY POLAR BEAR, HAROLD.
THE MOST DANGEROUS
ANIMAL ON THIS PLANET.
I MEAN, IT'S GOT THE
SCARIEST SMELL I KNOW.
AND IT WILL JUST BE NEAT
JUST TO KIND OF TRACK
IT DOWN LIKE THAT.
I REALLY LIKE THE
IDEA OF SHOOTING
DEAD STUFF, HAROLD.
THERE'S NO TRACKING,
NO STOPPING,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE QUIET,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO CLEAN THEM.
I DON'T SEE
A DOWNSIDE HERE.
I DON'T KNOW, THE LODGE
MEMBERS GOING AFTER
MOLDY, OVER-STUFFED,
LIFELESS ANIMALS,
IT'S GOING TO BE HARDER
THAN EVER TO TELL THE HUNTERS
FROM THE HUNTED AROUND HERE.
[ AIRPLANE SOUND EFFECTS ]
THAT'S HOW I LOST
MY PILOT'S LICENSE.
OH........
I WISH I'D BEEN
BORN A RACE HORSE
BECAUSE I TELL YOU THAT
SOUNDS LIKE A PRETTY
GOOD GOAL,
WITH A TRAINER AND
A 90-POUND JOCKEY
WHO WOULD RIDE ME
FOR A MINUTE OR SO.
WELL, I'D WIN
THE DAILY DOUBLE,
THE TRIFECTA AND
THE EXACTOR,
CAUSE I KNOW WHAT
A STUD FARM IS
AND MOTIVATION WOULD BE
A SIGNIFICANT FACTOR.
AND NOW WE'VE COME TO
A SEGMENT OF THE SHOW
THAT I REALLY ENJOY,
WHAT I LIKE TO CALL
MEET YOUR MEMBER.
WELL, TO BE FAIR AND HONEST,
MR. GREEN, I'M NOT REALLY
A MEMBER YET.
I ONLY APPLIED
A FEW DAYS AGO.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT MIKE,
YOU'RE STILL IN YOUR
TRIAL PERIOD.
YEAH, AND I USUALLY DON'T
DO TOO GOOD AT TRIALS.
OH, NO, THAT'S ALL
BEHIND YOU NOW.
MIKE HAS UNFORTUNATELY
SPENT MOST OF HIS ADULT
LIFE BEHIND BARS.
YEAH, PLUS I'VE
LEANED ON A FEW.
I THINK IT'S BEEN GOOD
FOR YOU, DON'T YOU,
BEING AROUND THE LODGE,
AROUND THE GUYS AND SO ON?
OH, YEAH, YEAH,
YEAH, SURE.
I MEAN BEING AROUND
YOU GUYS HAS BEEN
GREAT, YOU KNOW.
I'VE BEEN SEEING THE WAY
YOU DRESS AND HEARING
THE WAY YOU TALK
AND SEEING WHAT YOU'VE
MADE OF YOURSELF.
I MEAN THAT'S CONVINCED
ME I GOT TO GET
MORE EDUCATION.
OH, SO YOU'RE GOING BACK
TO SCHOOL, ARE YOU?
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, I GOT MY EYE
ON A BUSINESS DEGREE.
I'M GOING TO TAKE
MY THESIS IN ECONOMICS
AND PROBABLY DO A MASTERS
IN INTERNATIONAL
MONEY LENDING.
WOW.
AS SOON AS I
GET MY GRADE 8.
MIKE, WE HAVE BEEN
WATCHING YOU
AND WE THINK YOU DESERVE
A LITTLE PAT ON THE
BACK HERE.
SO, MIKE, WELCOME
TO POSSUM LODGE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
OH, REALLY?
REALLY?
YEAH.
I'M A MEMBER?
QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORITATI.
THIS IS AMAZING.
I'VE NEVER BELONGED
TO NOTHING LEGAL BEFORE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GOING
TO DO, MR. GREEN,
I'M GOING TO SAVE UP MY PAY
AND I'M GOING TO CHANGE
MY SATAN TATTOO
INTO A POSSUM.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT
ELSE I GOT FOR
YOU IN MY WALLET?
I HAVE YOUR MEMBERSHIP
CARD FOR THE POSSUM LODGE?
REALLY?
YEAH.
YOU DID THIS FOR ME?
THANKS MR. GREEN.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR --
WELL, YOU ALREADY
RETURNED MY WALLET
THAT I GUESS I MUST HAVE
DROPPED ACCIDENTALLY
SOMEWHERE, RIGHT?
SURE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THIS WEEK ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I THOUGHT I WOULD ADDRESS
ONE OF THE GREAT ECOLOGICAL
ISSUES OF OUR TIME,
MAINLY THE LOW TRADE-IN
VALUE OF USED VEHICLES.
HOW MANY TIMES HAS IT
HAPPENED TO YOU
THAT YOU FINALLY DECIDE
TO BITE THE BULLET AND
GET YOURSELF A NEW CAR?
YOU DRIVE DOWN THERE
IN THE OLD CLUNKER,
RUNNING ON ONE CYLINDER,
COUGHING UP SMOKE LIKE
A JAMAICAN BARBECUE,
YOU SAY TO THE SALESMAN
HOW MUCH ARE YOU GOING
TO ALLOW ME FOR IT
AND HE SAYS
ROUGHLY ZERO.
SO YOU PUSH THE WHOLE
UNIT BACK HOME
AND THAT'S WHY WE GOT SO
MANY OF THESE SITTING OUT
IN THE BACKYARDS
OF EVERYBODY'S HOUSES ALL
THE WAY ACROSS NORTH AMERICA.
SO I'M THINKING WITH
THIS TAXIDERMY SHOOTOUT-
THING THAT WE GOT GOING ON,
MAYBE WE CAN TURN THIS
THING INTO A DUCK BLIND.
NOW, THE FIRST THING
YOU HAVE TO DO
IS YOU HAVE TO BREAK
THE UNIT DOWN INTO
ITS COMPONENTS,
WHICH IS ACTUALLY NOT
THAT HARD TO DO
BECAUSE THESE CARS USUALLY
HAVE A SWEET SPOT.
YEAH, THERE WE ARE,
RIGHT THERE.
THEN YOU JUST HIT HER
RIGHT AT THAT AREA.
THERE WE GO.
NOW, YOU THROW AWAY
ANYTHING THAT DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE A DUCK BLIND
AND THEN YOU REASSEMBLE
ALL THE DUCK BLIND-LIKE
COMPONENTS
USING AN ACETYLENE TORCH
OR BOLTS OR RIVETS
OR THE HANDYMAN'S SECRET
WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
OKAY, THAT'S THE BASIC
SHAPE OF IT BUT IT'S
NOT EXACTLY PORTABLE,
SO YOU SHOULD EITHER HAVE
THOUGHT OF THAT BEFORE YOU
RIPPED THE WHEELS OFF
OR YOU CAN DO
WHAT I'LL DO,
CAMOUFLAGE IT.
OKAY, NOW TO ME THIS
JUST SCREAMS DUCK, HUH?
THAT PAINT JOB MAKES IT
LOOK LIKE THEY'VE BEEN
FLYING OVER IT FOR YEARS.
I ADDED THE DECOYS ON TOP
THERE FOR A LITTLE EXTRA
TOUCH OF CREDIBILITY.
IF YOU DON'T
HAVE ACTUAL DECOYS,
YOU COULD TAKE SOME HOOD
ORNAMENTS AND PUT FUR
MITTS ON THEM.
AND, YOU KNOW, IF YOU
LEAVE THE CAR BATTERY
HOOKED UP,
YOU CAN HAVE
YOUR RADIO ON
OR YOUR DEFROSTERS
RUNNING
OR YOUR LIGHTS ON FOR
NIGHT HUNTING OR WHATEVER.
NOW, I KNOW MOST OF YOU
WILL DO YOUR SHOOTING
OUT THE WINDOW
BUT SOMETIMES IF
THE BUGS GET BAD,
YOU CAN ROLL UP ALL THE
WINDOWS AND STILL
KEEP HUNTING.
WATCH THIS.
NECESSITY IS A MOTHER OF AN
INVENTOR, ISN'T IT?
THINK OF THE THINGS
YOU CAN MAKE LIKE THIS:
A BUS SHELTER
FOR THE KIDS,
A DOG HOUSE,
AN IMPRESSIVE TOBOGGAN,
A WHITE WATER
SUICIDE MACHINE.
YOU'RE ONLY LIMITED
BY YOUR OWN IMAGINATION
AND THE LAWS
IN YOUR AREA.
TO ME IT MAKES
A GREAT DUCK BLIND.
SO REMEMBER UNTIL
NEXT TIME,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[ DUCK QUACKING ]
COMING UP, I'M GOING TO
COMMENT ON THE TEENAGERS,
I SHOT MY FIRST TROUT AND
BILL IS GOING TO DO
HIS IMPRESSION OF
KAREEM ABDUL DORK.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, YOU KNOW, TEENAGERS
HAVE ALWAYS BEEN DOING
STUPID STUFF, ANYWAY.
ACTUALLY IT SEEMS EVERY
GENERATION TRIES TO PUSH
THE ENVELOPE OF IDIOCY.
BUT THIS NEW GANG, I MEAN
THEY'RE NOT ONLY PUSHING
THE ENVELOPE,
THEY'RE LICKING IT AND
CUTTING THEMSELVES ON IT.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THESE
KIDS NOW GETTING THEIR
BODIES PIERCED.
I WAS JUST STARTING TO
GET MY HEAD AROUND
EARRINGS ON GUYS
AND NOW THEY'RE PUNCHING
HOLES IN THEIR EYEBROWS
AND THEIR NOSE AND THEIR
BELLYBUTTONS AND WHO
KNOWS WHAT ALL.
I'M WAITING TO SEE A GUY
COME DOWN THE STREET
WITH A THREE-RING BINDER
ATTACHED TO HIS CHEST.
WHAT IS THE POINT
OF ALL THIS ANYWAY?
ARE THESE MOORING
RINGS SO THEY CAN
TIE THEMSELVES
TO A SCHOOL DESK
AND LEARN MORE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
I SAW A GIRL SHE HAD SEVEN
BUTTONS ON HER TONGUE.
LOOKED LIKE A
LITTLE NEAT VEST.
NOW, HER FOOD HAS TO
GO OVER SPEED BUMPS.
I TELL YOU, FOLKS,
I DON'T GET IT.
WE WERE TAUGHT THAT YOU
GROW UP CLEAN AND HONEST,
YOU BE KIND TO
YOUR NEIGHBOUR
AND YOU TRY TO
END LIFE'S JOURNEY
WITH THE SAME NUMBER OF
HOLES YOU STARTED WITH.
WELL, THE FIRST ANNUAL
TAXIDERMY SHOOTOUT
IS WELL UNDERWAY
AND WE'VE ALREADY
BAGGED A FEW TROPHIES.
JUNIOR SINGLETON SHOT
A STUFFED WEASEL THAT
WAS DUCT TAPED TO A TREE.
BUSTER HATFIELD, BEAUTY,
HE NAILED ONE OF THEM
BIG BALD EAGLES.
IT WAS STAPLED TO THE
TOP OF A TELEPHONE POLE.
WE HAD A LITTLE
SETBACK THERE,
JUNIOR SINGLETON
EMPTIED A FEW ROUNDS
INTO A COUPLE OF BEARSKIN
RUGS THAT WERE HANGING
ON A CLOTHESLINE
BUT THAT'S JUST
PURE ENTHUSIASM.
AND I GOT THIS BABY HERE.
IT WAS SITTING ON TOP
OF A BIG OIL DRUM
DOWN BY THE DOCK.
LIKE SHOOTING FISH
ON A BARREL, HUH?
YEAH, TROUT ARE GOOD
HUNTING, AREN'T THEY HAROLD?
SO UNCLE RED, HAS
ANYBODY SHOT THOR YET?
OH, THE POLAR BEAR, NO.
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
THOUGHT HE SAW HIM,
BUT IT WAS JUST
MOOSE HUNTING NAKED.
I TELL YOU, THIS HUNTING
STUFFED ANIMALS,
I THINK IS GOING TO BE
THE NUMBER ONE SPORT
AROUND HERE.
OH, NOT NECESSARILY,
UNCLE RED.
SOMEONE HAS REPORTED
SEEING A UNICORN OWL.
YEAH, I THINK ARTIE STUCK
ONE UP IN THE BARN RAFTERS
WITH DRY WALL SCREWS.
NO, NO, NO, THIS IS
LIKE A REAL ONE, BUT
IT FLEW AWAY.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN ONE OF
THOSE AROUND HERE
IN 15 YEARS.
THEY'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE EXTINCT.
YEAH, I THINK OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK BAGGED THE
LAST ONE WITH HIS BREATH.
I DON'T KNOW, UNCLE RED, BUT
I THINK YOU GUYS SHOULD
STOP YOUR HUNTING
JUST IN CASE THIS RARE
BIRD GETS HIT ACCIDENTALLY.
NO.
WE'LL JUST CANCEL
OUT THE BIRD PART
OF THE COMPETITION.
GUYS CAN STILL HUNT THE
ZEBRAS AND THE OSTRICHES
AND THAT,
THE BIG STUFFED RECLINER
THAT ARTIE MADE FOR HIS
FATHER-IN-LAW.
I DON'T KNOW UNCLE RED.
I FIND IT VERY EXCITING,
A UNICORN OWL RIGHT
AROUND HERE.
ISN'T THAT EXCITING?
YEAH.
HE'S JUST PASSING
THROUGH, RIGHT HAROLD?
FOR SALE, SET OF BAGPIPES.
NO LONGER PLAYS MUSIC
BUT MAKES A GREAT WINE
SKIN FOR SIX PEOPLE
AT ONCE.
HERE WE ARE WITH OUR
FRIEND, RANGER GORD.
HI RED.
HI EVERYONE.
I'M FINE.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE UP
IN THE TOWER THERE
SO YOU CAN KEEP AN EYE
OUT FOR THE FOREST
FIRES AND SO ON?
NO.
NO, NOT TODAY RED.
ARTIE KAY HOT GLUE GUNNED
A STUFFED DUCK TO MY ROOF
AND WITH ALL
THE SHOOTING
GOING ON TODAY,
IT'S JUST NOT SAFE.
[ BULLET RICHOCHET ]
OF COURSE WITH THE
RETURN OF THE UNICORN
OWL, ALL THAT WILL CHANGE.
GORD THERE IS NO
UNICORN OWL AROUND HERE
AND SO WHAT IF
THERE WAS?
WELL, THAT WOULD MEAN
THAT THE ENTIRE
POSSUM LAKE AREA
WOULD BE TURNED
INTO A SANCTUARY.
[ BULLET RICOCHET ]
SO I'M LOOKING OUT
FOR THAT OWL, FOLKS.
AND I THOUGHT EVERYBODY
MIGHT LIKE TO SEE
HOW WE TRACK ANIMALS
IN THE WILD.
ALL RIGHT.
TAKE A LOOK AT THOSE.
OH, YEAH, WE USE THESE.
YEAH, CANDIES
ATTRACT ANIMALS.
THESE ARE DARN
GOOD, GORD.
THOSE ARE RABBIT DROPPINGS.
DON'T EAT THOSE, THEY'RE
FULL OF CHOLESTEROL.
SO THAT'S HOW WE
IDENTIFY ANIMALS.
THAT'S FROM
A RACCOON.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO TRACK A MOOSE.
YOU WANT TO -- OH,
I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
YOU KNOW, FOLKS, AROUND
THIS TIME OF YEAR
A MOOSE WILL EAT A
LOT OF BERRIES AND --
SO THERE IT IS, IF YOU
EVER WANT TO IDENTIFY
SOME OF THE ANIMALS
THAT ARE IN THE
WOODS AROUND YOU,
JUST LOOK FOR THE
KINDS OF DROPPINGS
THAT ARE AROUND
AND IT WILL TELL
YOU EXACTLY WHAT'S
AROUND YOU.
AND IF YOU SEE SOMETHING
THAT LOOKS LIKE IT COME
OUT OF A UNICORN OWL,
KICK IT UNDER THE BUSHES
SO NOBODY SEES IT.
IT'S MAIL CALL.
[ BELL RINGING ]
OKAY.
HERE IS A LETTER
FROM PHIL MORTON OF
BRADBURY, ALBERTA,
OR BILL MARILYN OF
BRANTBRICE, ALABAMA.
IT COULD BE DILL MARTIN
OF GREAT PROUD AMERICAN.
BAD HAND WRITING HAROLD?
IT LOOKS LIKE
BARBED WIRE.
I DON'T KNOW.
MUST BE A DOCTOR.
"DEAR RED" -- OR IS
THAT DEATH BED?
"DEAD BEAR" --
YEAH, CALL ME DEAD BEAR.
DEAD BEAR?
OKAY.
"I AM YOUR NUMBER ONE
FAN OR FUR OR FUDGE...
"NUMBER ONE FUDGE.
"I NEVER MUST
A SIMPLE EPILOGUE.
"I HAVE EVERY EPILOGUE
OF THE DEAD BEAR
SHOW ON TYPE.
"MY FLAVOURITE
PART OF THE SNOW IS
HANDYMAN'S CORONARY.
"MY WAIF SAYS HER FLAVOURIT
PART OF THE PROYAM
"IS ADWRENCHERS
WITH BOIL.
"SHE RALLY LICKED THE ONE
WHERE BOIL FILLED THE
HAND GLITTER
"AND TRIED TO FRY IT.
"KELP UP THE GORD WALK.
"AND KELP YOUR
STEAK ON THE ICE.
"YOUR FRIED BLEB.
"OH, BS BLEACH CINCH ME UP
FOR THE POSSUM LOUNGE
FARCLUM."
OKAY.
WELL, THANKS
FOR ROTTING BLEB.
VERY GLAD YOU
EMPLOY THE SHAW.
AND I'LL CERTAINLY TELL
BOIL THAT YOUR WAIF
REALLY LICKED
ADWRENCHERS WITH BOIL.
DROP US A LINE
AGAIN SOMETIME SOUP
AND I'LL GET MY
NEPHEW HERMAN HERE
TO SINGE YOU AND YOU
WAY UP TO THE BOSSUM
LOUNGE FARCLUM.
[ APPLAUSE ]
RED GREEN:
THIS WEEK ADVENTURES WITH
BILL BILL GOES TO COURT
AND WITH GOOD REASON.
YOU KNOW YOU GET THAT
ONE GUY, JUST A GOOF GUY.
LOOK AT THIS.
OH, THANK GOODNESS.
BILL THAT'S NOT --
YOU GOT TO DRILL.
BILL --
OH, FOR GOSH SAKE.
OH, NICE SHOT.
YOU'VE HEARD
OF THE NATURAL?
BILL IS THE
ARTIFICIAL.
BILL THIS IS NOT
WORKING FOR YOU.
BILL.
YOU STINK, BILL.
SO HE GETS AN IDEA.
HE FIGURES THAT THE
PROBLEM IS THAT
THE NET'S TOO HIGH,
IT'S NOT THAT THE
BALL IS TOO LOW.
SO HE'LL LOWER
THAT NET.
THAT'S KIND OF
A PERMANENT SOLUTION.
LOOK OUT THERE, HAROLD.
HAROLD, THE NET!
OH, I'M SURROUNDED HERE.
ALL RIGHT SO BILL UNDOES
ONE OF HIS MANY TENSOR
BANDAGES
AND HE USES THAT TO
ATTACH THE CUT POLE
SO NOW LOOK AT THE
HEIGHT OF THAT.
THERE'S A CHANCE HE MIGHT
BE ABLE TO ACTUALLY
DUNK THIS ONE
ISN'T THERE, BILL?
MAYBE NOT.
SHOOT WITH THE LEGS.
GO HOME BILL.
GO HOME.
HE'S GETTING PRETTY
FRUSTRATED NOW.
OH -- OH, YOU BETTER WATCH
THE BALL THERE HAROLD.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, I FORGOT, HIS THEORY NOW
IS THAT IT'S THE SHOES.
IT'S THE SHOES AND THEY
ARE NOT TOTALLY BLAMELESS.
SO OUT HE GOES TO GET
HIMSELF SOME OF THE FANCY
WHAT ARE THEY $12,000.
SO HAROLD AND
I KIND OF --
HAROLD IS GOOD WITH
A HAMMER, ISN'T HE?
I HOPE HE GETS
AN EDUCATION.
AND HERE HE COMES.
HE'S LOOKING A LITTLE THINNER
BECAUSE HIS WALLET'S GONE.
HE GOT HIMSELF SOME
OF THOSE FANCY
SIGNATURE SHOES THEY
USE ON THE BIG BASKETBALL.
LET'S HAVE A LOOK.
WHAT DO THEY LOOK LIKE?
WHAT ARE THEY LIKE?
OH MY GOSH,
LOOK AT THAT.
WOW.
YOU PUMP THOSE BABIES
UP, DO YOU BILL?
WHAT'S THIS, 10-W-30?
YOU CAN PLAY IN THE
WINTER AND EVERYTHING.
OH MY GOSH, DON'T HURT
YOURSELF THERE, BILL.
OH MY GOSH LOOK AT
THE DIFFERENCE.
IT IS THE SHOES.
OH BOY, OH BOY, OH BOY.
THAT'S GOOD SHOOTING.
BILL DON'T GET OVER CON ---
I'LL GET HIM DOWN.
OH, SORRY BILL, I
DIDN'T MEAN THAT.
OH, A BUTT DUNK.
COMING UP WE GOT A FASHION
STATEMENT FROM ME
AND BUZZ SHERWOOD
ACTING LIKE A TAILOR
AND TAKES HAROLD
INSEAM MEASUREMENT.
WELL THE ANNUAL POSSUM
LAKE TAXIDERMY SHOOTOUT
IS REALLY PICKING UP SPEED.
THE GUYS ARE REALLY
GETTING INTO IT.
JUNIOR TOOK THE FUN FUR
SEAT COVERS OUT OF
HIS PLYMOUTH
SO WE CAN
PRACTICE ON THOSE.
WE JUST GOT TO GET GET THE
UNICORN OWL OUT OF HERE
BEFORE THE
CONSERVATIONISTS SPOT IT.
THAT'S RIGHT, BECAUSE ONCE
THEY SEE IT,
THERE WON'T BE ANYMORE
HUNTING OR FISHING
OR CHOPPING
OR DIGGING OR BURNING
OR TRAMPLING.
I KNOW, HOW ARE WE GOING
TO COMMUNE WITH NATURE?
UNCLE RED, ARE YOU
AWARE THAT YOU'RE
STANDING UNDER A BEAR?
A LOT OF US ARE DRESSING
UP LIKE ANIMALS TO
CHASE THE OWL AWAY.
CAN OWLS FLY WHEN
THEY'RE LAUGHING?
IT'S NOT FAIR, HAROLD.
WE FINALLY FIND SOMETHING
TO DO THAT DOESN'T
HURT ANYBODY
AND THEY'RE GOING
TO MAKE US STOP.
HOW COME WHEN YOU GET
OLDER THEY TAKE AWAY
EVERYTHING THAT'S FUN?
HOW COME FUN ALWAYS
HAS TO MEAN SOMETHING
THAT'S USELESS,
DANGEROUS AND DESTRUCTIVE?
IT JUST DOES,
THAT'S ALL.
COME ON, UNCLE RED,
THINK ABOUT IT.
WOULDN'T IT BE EXCITING
TO HAVE LIKE A UNICORN
OWL AROUND POSSUM LODGE?
WE'VE ALREADY GOT ONE
GUY WHO'S BIG BEAKED,
BIRD BRAINED
AND BEADY EYED AND
SOUNDS JUST LIKE AN OWL.
WHO?
I DON'T KNOW HOW MANY
ENDANGERED SPECIES ONE
LODGE CAN STAND?
FOR SALE: 78 AMC PACER,
ENGINE SEIZED UP, MAKES
A PERFECT GREENHOUSE.
WE'RE UP HERE WITH OUR
RESIDENT BUSH PILOT,
BUZZ SHERWOOD
TO GET AN UPDATE ON
THE UNICORN OWL SITUATION.
YO, THE BIG RED GUY!
HOW'S IT GOING?
AND HAROLD, WOAH.
COME ON, HAROLD, STAND
UP STRAIGHT OR START
WEARING A SUPPORTER.
BUZZ WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
RED, I'M DISGUISING
MY PLANE TO LOOK LIKE
A GIANT UNICORN
OWL, RIGHT?
THEN I'M GOING TO GO
FLYING AROUND LOOKING
FOR THE LITTLE GUY.
OH, YOU'RE GOING TO
SCARE HIM AWAY, RIGHT?
NO, I'M NOT GOING TO
GO SCARING HIM AWAY,
NOT WITH THE
CONSERVATIONISTS
TRACKING HIM DOWN.
YOU KNOW THEY GOT A
TRANSMITTER ON HIM
TRYING TO STEER HIM
TOWARDS A FEMALE
FOR A BIG LOVE-IN.
WELL, I STILL DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHY
YOU'RE TURNING YOUR PLANE
INTO THE UGLY DUCKLING.
WELL, YOU SEE, I FIGURE
I'M GOING TO FLY AROUND
AND THEN I'M GOING TO
SHOW HIM SOME MAJOR
UNICORN OWL MOVES
SO THAT HE CAN REALLY
IMPRESS THE BABES, RIGHT,
CAUSE HE'S BEEN ALONE A
LONG TIME, GONE WITHOUT
AND I REALLY KNOW
HOW THAT FEELS.
YEAH, YEAH.
BUT BUZZ WHAT KIND OF
BIRD MOVES CAN YOU
SHOW AN OWL?
OH, WELL, I WAS READING
UP ON THAT RED, RIGHT,
AND THERE'S LIKE TWO HE'S
GOT TO REMEMBER, OKAY?
SO LIKE HE FLIES IN
BESIDE HER, RIGHT
AND HE GOES HI, HOW ARE
YOU, COME TO THIS
SWAMP OFTEN
AND LIKE CAN
I GET YOU A MOUSE?
AND THEN SHE GOES,
BACK OFF CREEP, I'M
HERE WITH MY SISTER,
AND THEN SHE TRIES TO
SCRATCH HIS EYES OUT.
THAT COULD BE DANGEROUS.
COULD BE.
BUT I FIGURE WE'LL BE
OKAY AS LONG AS I DON'T
TRY TO FLAP MY WINGS AND,
YOU KNOW, WHEN
IT COMES TO THE
INTIMATE MATING STUFF,
YOU KNOW, WE'LL TRY TO
KEEP HIM AWAY FROM
THE PROPELLER.
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW,
THEY'LL BE EVISCERATED.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M THINKING?
WHY DON'T YOU GET HIM A
LONG WAYS AWAY FROM HERE
TO TEACH HIM THIS STUFF?
GOOD IDEA.
YEAH.
YEAH, BECAUSE,
YOU KNOW, HE'LL BE
A LITTLE EMBARRASSED,
RIGHT, HITTING ON
THE BABES FOR THE
FIRST TIME.
HE COULD BE A
LITTLE RUSTY.
HE COULD STRIKE OUT A
COUPLE OF TIMES, RIGHT?
OH, FOR SURE.
FIGURE SKATING BY ME.
WE'RE SKATING
ON THE POND
AND MOOSE THOMPSON
DOES A TRIPLE AXLE
FOLLOWED BY A QUADRUPLE LUTZ
AND A TRIPLE-TOE LOOP.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
YOU'RE ON A BREAKAWAY
AND YOU CATCH YOUR TOE
ON A FROZEN WEASEL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, THE POSSUM LAKE
TAXIDERMY SHOOTOUT
WAS A HUGE SUCCESS.
WE ENDED UP WITH THE SAME
NUMBER OF DEAD THINGS
WE STARTED WITH,
SO THAT'S ALWAYS GOOD.
THE ONLY DRAWBACK WAS
NOBODY WANTED TO GIVE
ANYTHING BACK TO ARTIE.
THEY SAID I SHOT
IT, I KEEP IT.
I GUESS NEXT YEAR WE'LL
BE SHOOTING PICTURES
OF ANIMALS.
THE CONSERVATIONIST CAME
AND THEY TOOK, YOU KNOW,
THE UNICORN OWL BACK TO
HIS MATE SO THEY COULD MATE.
SO THAT WAY,
THEY'LL BE MATING
IF ANYONE WENT LOOKING FOR
THEM, THEY'LL BE BUSY
BECAUSE THEY'RE MATING.
THE KNOW THE WAY A BIRD
HAS A BIRD, YOU KNOW.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE
HAVING ONE YOURSELF
THERE, HAROLD.
AND OF COURSE
THE GOVERNMENT CAN'T
STICK ITS NOSE IN
WITHOUT COMING UP
WITH SOME CASH,
SO THEY GAVE
ME THIS INFRACTION.
WHAT DO YOU GOT THERE?
WELL, I SHOT
THEIR TRUCK.
AMAZING HOW MUCH
A LANDROVER LOOKS
LIKE A BLUE RHINO.
ESPECIALLY WITH
YOUR EYESIGHT.
WELL, THAT'S WHY I HAD
THE SEMI-AUTOMATIC.
THE AIM IS NOT
SO CRUCIAL ON IT.
SO THEN, I GUESS THE
BIGGEST PRIZE OF THE DAY
IS THIS HUNDRED DOLLAR
TICKET OF YOURS.
ARE YOU GOING TO
HAVE IT MOUNTED?
NO, BUT I MAY
HAVE YOU STUFF IT.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
WELL, THERE'S THE
CRY OF THE POSSUM.
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO
AHEAD HAROLD.
I WILL BE DOWN
IN A LITTLE WHILE.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, AS YOU GET
OLDER YOU REALIZE
YOU CAN'T ALWAYS
GET WHAT YOU WANT
BUT IF YOU TRY SOMETIMES
YOU CAN GET YET ANOTHER
FINANCIAL SETBACK.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
THE GREAT WHITE HUNTER
WILL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING
AND I'LL BE BRINGING
A SECOND TIME AROUND
WILD TURKEY,
KIND OF LIGHT
ON THE MEAT
AND HEAVY ON THE STUFFING
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH
FOR WATCHING.
UNTIL NEXT TIME, ON
BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK
ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL YOU GUYS STAND UP.
STAND UP!
ALL:
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI