I KNOW IT'S IMPORTANT TO HAVE
YOUR HOME NICELY DECORATED,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU WANT
YOUR WIFE TO CONTINUE
TO LIVE THERE.
I MEAN, A FEW DAINTY AND
FRILLY DECOR ITEMS ARE FINE,
HERE AND THERE.
BUT YOU GET TOO MANY
FEMININE TOUCHES IN THERE
AND THE MAN STARTS TO FEEL
DISCONNECTED FROM
HIS ENVIRONMENT.
WHENEVER YOU SEE A GUY MOVE
A COUCH AND BEER FRIDGE
INTO THE GARAGE
IT'S A PRETTY GOOD BET THAT
HIS WIFE DID ALL THE
DECORATING.
YOU NEED SOME
MASCULINE TOUCHES IN
THERE SOMEWHERE, DON'T YOU?
FOR EXAMPLE:
A CHANDELIER.
FLAME-SHAPED LIGHT BULBS
AND CRYSTAL BAUBLES
IS NOT GONNA DO IT.
INSTEAD, I SUGGEST SOMETHING
THAT'S ATTRACTIVE
AND PRACTICAL
BUT STILL HAS Y CHROMOSOME
STAMPED ALL OVER IT.
TAKE A FEW RIMS OFF
OF DIFFERENT SIZED BICYCLES,
PUT THEM TOGETHER
WITH 40-POUND FISHING LINE
AND THEN YOU WANNA
HANG SOME SHINY LURES,
BOTTLE OPENERS AND MINI
FLASHLIGHTS TO THE
OUTSIDE EDGES.
THIS BABY'S
ONE OF A KIND.
THE BEAUTY OF USIN'
FLASHLIGHTS IS
YOU'LL HAVE LIGHT
EVEN IF THE POWER'S OFF.
AND YOU CAN SET THE MOOD
BY THE NUMBER OF FLASHLIGHTS
THAT YOU HAVE ON.
SEE, THIS IS NOT
JUST A CHANDELIER,
IT'S A MAN-DELIER.
[ MUSIC PLAYS ]
BUT YOU KNOW THE REAL BEAUTY
IS WHEN DINNER'S OVER
YOU TURN YOUR DINING ROOM
INTO A DISCO.
DINNER AND DANCING WITHOUT
EVER LEAVING YOUR HOUSE.
[ DISCO ]
CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIG, BIG WEEK UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
IT'S THE START
OF PLUM HARVEST.
BUT WAIT,
THERE'S MORE.
OH, YEAH.
WE ALWAYS KICK OFF
PLUM HARVEST
WITH A CELEBRATION
RIGHT HERE AT THE LODGE.
EVERYBODY MEETS
OUT IN THE PARKING LOT,
AND WE TELL OUR
FAVOURITE PLUM STORY.
SOME OF THEM ARE
MORE PLUM THAN OTHERS.
BUT THE BIG FINALE
IS THE POSSUM DROP.
WE DROP A POSSUM
DOWN THE FLAGPOLE.
OH, MY GOSH,
UNBELIEVABLE.
AND WE'VE GOT A
GREAT BIG ONE THIS YEAR,
SO IT'S GOING
TO BE FANTASTIC.
THAT GUY GALILEO SAID
EVERYTHING DROPS
AT THE SAME RATE,
WELL, I'M GUESSIN'
HE NEVER CHUCKED A POSSUM
OUT OF HIS HOTEL WINDOW.
UNCLE RED!
YEAH?
I DO NOT THINK I CAN
STAND HERE ANY LONGER
AND ALLOW YOU TO
GET AWAY WITH THIS.
GREAT,
WHERE YOU GOIN'?
NOWHERE!
AND NEITHER IS THAT
DEFENCELESS LITTLE POSSUM.
YOU CANNOT THROW
AN ANIMAL OUT OF THE SKY
JUST FOR YOUR
OWN ENTERTAINMENT.
[ sigh ]
HE'S NOT GONNA
HIT THE GROUND.
IT'S A 40-FOOT DROP,
THE ROPE IS ONLY 39.
WHAT'S THE POINT?
WHAT DOES A FALLING POSSUM
HAVE TO DO WITH PLUM HARVEST?
WELL...
IT PLUMMETS.
YOU KNOW, THE ORIGINS
OF THE POSSUM DROP
ARE SHROUDED IN
THE MISTS OF TIME.
AND THE HAZE
OF ALCOHOL.
HEY, RED!
YEAH?
THIS FAX JUST
CAME IN FOR YOU.
AND THEY AGREE
WITH YOU.
FANTASTIC.
DON'T YOU WANNA
KNOW WHO IT'S FROM?
NOT RIGHT AWAY.
LET ME ENJOY
THE MOMENT.
IT'S A NATIONAL
ANIMAL RIGHTS GROUP.
YEAH, YOU ASKED THEM
FOR A COURT INTERVENTION
TO STOP THE POSSUM DROP,
AND THEY'RE DOIN' IT!
WHAT?
YEAH, WHY WOULD
YOU DO THAT?
WATCHIN' THAT
POSSUM FALL
IS ABOUT THE ONLY FUN
I HAVE LEFT IN LIFE.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
WERE THE MEMBER OF
AN ANIMAL RIGHTS GROUP.
WELL, I'M NOT,
DALTON.
WELL, LOOK, THIS A FAX
IS ADDRESSED TO
MR. GREEN,
C/O POSSUM LODGE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR
THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FOR A FREE
PHYSICAL EVALUATION
FROM PORT ASBESTOS
PIANO MOVERS.
FIND OUT IF YOU
CAN STILL CARRY A TUNE.
ALL RIGHT, COVER YOU
EAR HOLE THINGS, DALTON.
MR. GREEN, YOU'VE
GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET DALTON
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, YEAH,
ALL RIGHT.
AND... GO!
UH, OKAY, DALTON,
SUGGESTION...
STUPID.
UM, CLUE...
LESS.
UH, OKAY, TIP...
DON'T GET MARRIED.
OKAY, S'POSIN' YOUR
WIFE IS UPSET WITH YOU,
BUT SHE DOESN'T WANNA SAY
ANYTHING OUT LOUD.
OH, HO, HO,
THAT'LL BE THE DAY.
THESE THINGS THAT
I'VE BEEN SAYIN'
TO HELP YOU GUESS
THE WORD HAVE ALL BEEN...
CRAP.
OH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
THIS IS AN
EXPRESSION YOU HEAR
WHEN THERE'S A WHIFF OF
SOMETHING IN THE AIR.
IT WASN'T ME.
UH, WE'RE ALMOST
OUTTA TIME, MR. GREEN.
YEAH, I KNOW.
OKAY, SUPPOSING YOU COME
HOME AND ANNE MARIE'S
WAITIN' THERE
IN A SKIMPY OUTFIT.
THAT WOULD BE A...
MIRACLE.
TROUBLE IN PARADISE?
AH, RED, YOU KNOW,
HEH-HEH,
I SPEND ALL MY
FREE TIME AT THE LODGE.
DOES THAT GIVE
YOU A HINT?
THERE WE GO!
[ DALTON YAWNING ]
DALTON, YOU CAN'T
BE BORED.
YOU'VE ONLY BEEN
OUT HERE NINE HOURS.
I DIDN'T SLEEP
WELL LAST NIGHT.
ANN MARIE KEEP YOU
UP ALL NIGHT, DID SHE?
NO, HER JALEPEÑO
LASAGNA DID.
AH, I ONLY SLEEP WELL
IN PRISON.
NOT AT HOME,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
I MEAN, MY MOM
SLAMS THE FRIDGE DOOR
AND YELLS,
LIGHTS OUT!
BUT IT'S NOT THE SAME.
I SLEEP LIKE A LOG.
THAT'S A WEIRD EXPRESSION,
ISN'T IT?
SLEEP LIKE A LOG?
HOW DO WE KNOW LOGS
ARE WELL RESTED?
I'VE NEVER SEEN ONE YAWN.
I CAN SLEEP
ANYWHERE, ANY TIME.
WELL, I HOPE YOU DON'T
HAVE CRUISE CONTROL.
I HAVEN'T SLEPT ONE GOOD
NIGHT IN MY WHOLE LIFE.
WELL, DALTON, YOU JUST
GOTTA LET YOUR MIND GO BLANK
AND THEN YOU CAN
SLEEP ANYWHERE.
OH, SURE,
THAT'S EASY TO SAY,
BUT I GOT STUFF
I GOTTA WORRY ABOUT.
IF I DIDN'T WORRY
ABOUT EVERYTHING,
THE WHOLE WORLD WOULD
GO TO HELL IN A HANDCART.
HOW CAN I LET
MY MIND GO BLANK?
WELL, CONVERSATIONS LIKE
THIS ARE A PRETTY
GOOD START.
SO YOU'RE SAYING THAT
WE HAVE TROUBLE SLEEPING
BECAUSE WE THINK
TOO MUCH?
THAT CAN'T
BE RIGHT.
IT'S NOT
THE THINKING,
IT'S THE WORRYING.
MY WHOLE FACE IS
COVERED IN WORRY LINES.
YEAH, BUT THEY MAKE
A NICE PATTERN WITH
THE LIVER SPOTS.
YOU JUST GOTTA CHANGE
YOUR ATTITUDE, DALTON.
IF YOU CAN FIX SOMETHING,
FIX IT.
IF YOU CAN'T FIX IT,
FORGET IT.
EITHER WAY, THERE'S NO
POINT IN WORRYING ABOUT IT.
WELL, THAT DOESN'T
ALWAYS WORK.
LIKE, I HAD THIS
SPEEDING TICKET ONCE
THAT I COULDN'T FIX,
AND SO I FORGOT ABOUT IT,
AND, UM, I LOST MY
LICENSE FOR TWO YEARS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IN THE HUMAN
DIGESTIVE SYSTEM,
THE NUTRITION IS
REPRESENTED BY TWO SEPARATE
YET EQUALLY
IMPORTANT GROUPS...
THE MOUTH AND STOMACH
WHO INGESTICATE FOOD,
AND THE LARGE INTESTINES
WHO REDISTRIBUTE THE OFFENDERS.
THESE ARE THEIR STORIES.
Red:
BEAUTIFUL, AREN'T THEY?
YOU KNOW, NOTHING
GETS A MAN MORE EXCITED
THAN A CUSTOMIZED CAR.
WELL, OKAY, THERE
IS ONE OTHER THING,
BUT A CAR'S A LOT
EASIER TO GET AHOLD OF.
PLUS A CAR WON'T
GET MAD AT YOU
WHEN YOU CHECK OUT
OTHER MODELS.
AND TRADING UP
IS A LOT CHEAPER.
OKAY, I BETTER STOP
IN CASE BERNICE IS
ACTUALLY WATCHIN' THIS.
BUT MAYBE FOR A
GUY ON A BUDGET,
YOU HAVE TO SKIP
THE FOUR ON THE FLOOR
AND GO DIRECTLY TO
TWO ON THE SIDEWALK.
BUT MAYBE THERE'S
ANOTHER OPTION.
AND THIS IS GONNA SOUND
BLASPHEMOUS COMIN' FROM ME,
BUT WHAT ABOUT A...
BICYCLE?
JUST BECAUSE
YOU RIDE A BIKE
DOESN'T MEAN YOU HAVE
TO LOOK LIKE A DUFUS.
DON'T GO BY HAROLD.
NOT IF YOU TAKE A PAGE OUT
OF THOSE CAR MAGAZINES
AND CUSTOMIZE YOUR RIDE.
SO TODAY ON
HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
TO MAKE A COOL LOOKIN' BIKE.
A DE-NERDICYCLE.
OKAY, RIGHT AWAY,
HOW CAN YOU LOOK COOL
ON A SEAT LIKE THAT?
IT'S LIKE STICKIN' YOUR
BUTT ON A BUNDT CAKE.
YOU NEED SOMETHING
THAT SAYS MACK-DADDY.
WHATEVER THE HECK
MACK-DADDY IS.
I'M THINKIN'
OLD CAR WASH MITT.
OR AS I LIKE
TO CALL IT,
FUN FUR UPHOLSTERY.
OKAY, NOW, A LOT
OF THE GREAT CARS TODAY
ARE CUSTOMIZED
TO RIDE LOWER.
TEENAGERS LIKE
EVERYTHING RIDIN' LOWER...
THEIR CARS,
THEIR PANTS,
THEIR MARKS.
NOT TO MENTION THE
LYRICS TO THEIR RAP SONGS.
OKAY, WE CAN'T GO THAT LOW,
BUT WE CAN DROP
THE BIKE A FEW INCHES
BY EXTENDING THE
FORKS ON THE FRONT.
GET YOURSELF SOME
OLD METAL TUBING --
ANOTHER REASON TO
FINALLY GET THAT DISH.
PRETTY SLICK, HUH?
NOW, YOU'RE GONNA NEED A
COUPLE EXTRA PIECES
OF BRAKE CABLE
FOR THE ADDED DISTANCE
YOU STUCK ON THE FRONT WHEEL.
FORTUNATELY FOR ME,
DALTON HAS A 12-SPEED BIKE
THAT HE DOESN'T CARE ABOUT.
WELL, I'M ASSUMING
HE DOESN'T CARE ABOUT IT.
HE DIDN'T LOCK IT UP.
YOU KNOW, ONE OF THE
HOT LOOKS ON ANY HOT ROD?
FENDER SKIRTS,
WHICH YOU CAN MAKE YOURSELF
OUT OF ONE OF THESE
FLYING SAUCER SLEDS.
OR IF YOU'RE ON A BUDGET,
YOU CAN USE
A GARBAGE CAN LID.
NOW, THAT'S SEXY, HUH?
BUT THOSE HANDLE BARS
STILL LOOK A LITTLE DORKY,
SO I'M GONNA GO
WITH A LEATHER COVER
LIKE THEY HAVE ON THE STEERING
WHEEL OF A 'MASEROOTI'
I HAVE A PAIR OF MOOSE
THOMPSON'S PANTS HERE
THAT I WILL NEVER RETURN,
BECAUSE THEY COULD
BE HIS ONLY PAIR,
AND I NEVER WANNA
SEE HIM LIKE THAT.
GONNA TAKE OUT THE BELT
AND WIND THAT AROUND
THE HANDLE BARS.
I MAY BE ABLE TO
DO THE WHOLE FRAME.
AS THE MASSEUSE
SAID TO THE CLIENT,
IT'S ALL ABOUT
THE LITTLE TOUCHES.
YOU KNOW HOW THOSE SHARP CARS
HAVE THE GROUND EFFECTS?
YOU KNOW, THOSE
CRAZY NEON LIGHTS
DOWN UNDER THE VEHICLE?
WELL, I'VE DONE
THE SAME THING
BY JUST MOVING
THE BIKE HEADLIGHT
DOWN UNDER THE UNIT.
I MEAN, A BIKE HEADLIGHT
IS USELESS ANYWAY.
AND NOW WHEN SHE
SAYS YOU GOTTA GO HOME,
YOU CAN SAY,
I CAN'T,
I'VE GOT NO HEADLIGHT.
AND THEN, WELL,
YOU KNOW.
SHE'LL DRIVE YOU HOME.
NOW, FOR MOST
LODGE MEMBERS,
THE VOLUME OF THEIR EXHAUST
IS A POINT OF PRIDE.
EVERY KID KNOWS YOU CAN MAKE A
BIKE SOUND LIKE A MOTORCYCLE
BY JUST HAVING A
COUPLE OF PLAYING CARDS
FLICKING AGAINST
THE SPOKES.
BUT I'VE ADDED A COUPLE
OF JOKERS TO THE DECK
WITH THESE MEGAPHONES.
SPEAKING OF WHICH,
I REPLACED THE BELL WITH A
COUPLE OF TRUCK AIR HORNS.
[ LOUD HONK ]
BECAUSE WHEN YOU'RE INVOLVED
IN A ROAD RAGE CONFRONTATION,
YOU DON'T WANNA BE
THE ONE DOING THE TINKLING.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW, WE'LL JUST GET RID
OF THESE DINKY STREAMERS,
AND I'M GONNA GO
CRUISE THE MAIN DRAG.
[ HONKING ]
I WANNA TALK TO ALL YOU GUYS
WHO HAVE BEEN MARRIED
FOR A WHILE
AND ARE SPENDING ALMOST
EVERY MINUTE OF EVERY DAY
WITH YOUR WIFE.
NOW, IF I WAS THE
HEAD OF THE NATIONAL
RELATIONSHIP SECURITY,
I'D BE PUTTIN' YOU
ON ELEVATED ALERT.
YOU ARE IN A CRISIS
SITUATION, MY FRIEND.
BUT I HAVE THE SOLUTION.
YOU NEED TO FIND
A GIRLFRIEND.
NOT FOR YOURSELF.
YOU NEED TO FIND A
GIRLFRIEND FOR YOUR WIFE.
SEE, YOUR WIFE HAS A LOT OF
INTERESTS THAT YOU DON'T,
AND SHE NEEDS TO TALK
ABOUT THEM TO SOMEBODY,
SOMEBODY WHO CARES ABOUT WHAT
PURSE GOES WITH WHAT SHOES.
OR WHETHER SOME ACTOR'S
GOT BOTOX INJECTIONS.
OR ANYTHING, REALLY.
IF SHE DOESN'T
HAVE A GIRLFRIEND,
THAT LEAVES YOU.
AND SHE'S EVEN MORE UPSET
ABOUT THAT THAN YOU ARE.
NOW, THE FIRST PLACE TO LOOK
IS THE WIVES OF YOUR FRIENDS.
BECAUSE IF YOUR FRIENDS
ARE ANYTHING LIKE YOU,
THEY'RE PROBABLY
IN THE SAME BOAT.
BUT EVEN IF IT'S A GUY
YOU THINK IS A REAL DINK,
IF YOUR WIFE
LIKES HIS WIFE,
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
TAKE ONE FOR THE TEAM.
BECAUSE IF YOU'RE THE ONLY
FRIEND YOUR WIFE HAS,
YOUR LIFE WILL
BECOME A LIVING HELL.
SO GO OUT THERE AND
FIND HER A GIRLFRIEND.
IF YOU DON'T, SHE MAY GO OUT
AND FIND HERSELF A BOYFRIEND.
AND THAT'S BAD NEWS
FOR EVERYBODY,
INCLUDING HIM.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL
IN THIS TOGETHER.
AT ROTHSCHILD'S,
YOU DON'T PAY A CENT
UNTIL YOU SMELL ONE.
BOY, IT'S FUNNY HOW THINGS
HAVE A WAY OF WORKING OUT.
OKAY, WE'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO DROP THE POSSUM,
BUT WE'VE COME UP
WITH A SUBSTITUTE
THAT EVERYBODY
IS PRETTY HAPPY WITH --
WELL, ALMOST EVERYBODY.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
IS THIS REALLY
NECESSARY?
YOU VOLUNTEERED TO
REPLACE THE POSSUM.
WELL, SOMETIMES
WHEN YOU GET EXCITED,
YOU SAY THINGS
YOU REGRET LATER.
I KNOW, THOSE ARE CALLED
MARRIAGE PROPOSALS.
SO YOU REALLY THINK
I SHOULD DO THIS?
YEAH, YOU'LL BE SAFE
WITH IT, HAROLD.
IN FACT, I PHONED
THE ANIMAL RIGHTS PEOPLE,
AND ONCE THEY FOUND OUT
YOU WERE REPLACING THE POSSUM,
THEY WERE FINE WITH IT.
I MIGHT FEEL A LITTLE
BETTER ABOUT THIS
IF I THOUGHT I WAS
GOING TO SURVIVE.
YOU'RE GOING
TO BE OKAY.
WE BEEFED UP THE FLAGPOLE,
WE GOT A HEAVIER ROPE,
HEY, I KNOW.
WHY DON'T YOU PUT A COUPLE
OF TIRES AROUND YOU,
YOU KNOW,
LIKE THAT GUY DID
THAT WENT OVER
NIAGARA FALLS.
I BET HIS HONEYMOON
WAS DOING GOOD, HUH?
THAT WAY, EVEN IF
YOU HIT SOMETHING,
YOU'LL PROBABLY JUST
BOUNCE, LIKE THIS.
SEE? SEE?
OKAY, YEAH, OKAY.
THIS MIGHT BE FUN.
YEAH!
Red: OKAY, SO FOUR LOSERS
HAD WASHED UP ON THE BEACH.
AND HAROLD, WHEN HE
GETS INTO A COMIC,
HE GETS INTO A COMIC.
THEY'RE JUST
SITTIN' THERE,
AND THEY DIDN'T NOTICE
THE TWO YOUNG GIRLS --
WELL, I THINK BILL
MAYBE DIDN'T NOTICE,
AND WALTER FOR
SURE DIDN'T NOTICE.
VERY, VERY IMPRESSIVE.
NOW HE NOTICES.
SO ALL OF A SUDDEN
THEY'RE TRYING TO MAKE A --
OH, THEY HAVE ONE OF
THOSE BEACH VOLLEYBALLS.
I GUESS THEY WANNA
PLAY BEACH VOLLEYBALL.
SO THE GUYS ARE
SUDDENLY INTERESTED AND --
GET THE MAGAZINE
OFF YOUR FACE.
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, YOU'RE
LOOKIN' GOOD.
WELL, THIS IS THE ADVANTAGE
OF BEING IN A SMALL TOWN.
THERE'S NOT
A LOT OF CHOICE.
THEY GO OVER THERE.
HAROLD'S A LITTLE
STAND-OFFISH,
WHICH IS USUALLY
IN HIS BEST INTEREST.
YES, HAROLD,
UNCLE SAM WANTS YOU.
SO YEAH, I GUESS THOSE ARE
TECHNICALLY CALLED SHORTS,
BUT I'M NOT SURE.
SO THEY DECIDE THEY'RE GOING
TO HAVE HAROLD ON THEIR TEAM.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME HAROLD'S
BEEN PICKED FIRST
FOR ANYTHING IN
HIS ENTIRE LIFE.
SO HE'S ALL EXCITED
AND OVER HE COMES.
I DON'T THINK
HE WAS EXPECTING
THE GIRLS TO TOSS HIM
THE BALL IN ALL FAIRNESS,
BECAUSE HE'S USUALLY A LITTLE
MORE COORDINATED THAN THAT.
OF COURSE, THE OTHER
THREE ARE THINKING,
WE'RE LOOKING GOOD,
GONNA WIN --
YOU KNOW, HAROLD'S NOT LOOKING
SO DUMB RIGHT NOW, IS HE?
OKAY, LET'S GET GOING.
LET'S GET
THE GAME STARTED.
SO THE FIRST THING
THAT'S GONNA HAPPEN
IS HAROLD'S GONNA SERVE.
YEAH, YOU GUYS
ARE READY.
AND HAROLD'S NOT AS
ATHLETIC AS HE LOOKS.
OH!
OKAY, THAT'S UNFORTUNATE.
IT'S VERY TOUGH TO GET
INJURED PLAYING VOLLEYBALL.
BUT I'M SURE HAROLD
CAN FIND A WAY.
AND WALTER FIRES IT
OVER THE NET TO HIM.
OH... OH...
OH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, LATER THAT DAY
THE GIRLS ARE
WINNING MAJORLY.
OH.
GUESS YOU CAN SEE
WHERE THIS GOING.
AND IT GETS TO POINT WHERE
IT'S GETTING PRETTY
RIDICULOUS.
HAROLD'S MAKING
A SAND CASTLE,
AND THE GIRLS ARE
SPIKING EVERYTHING.
I THINK THAT WAS AN ATTEMPT
TO JUMP OVER THE NET
TO CONGRATULATE THEM.
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT HAROLD COMES
OVER AND SCORNS THEM
LIKE HE WAS THE ONE WHO
WON THE WHOLE DARNED GAME.
COULDN'T FIGURE OUT WHY THE
GIRLS WERE SO GOOD,
AND THEN WHEN YOU LOOKED AT
THEIR SPORTS BAG,
THERE WAS A BIT
OF A CLUE ON THERE.
APPARENTLY THERE WAS
SOME KIND OF NATIONAL TEAM.
[ APPLAUSE ]
SOMETIMES WHEN
YOU HAVE A BEARD,
YOU GET ACCUSED OF LOOKING
SCRUFFY ALL THE TIME.
HERE'S SOME ADVICE...
DON'T TAKE THAT
AS A COMPLIMENT.
THE WOMAN WHO'S
MAKING THOSE ACCUSATIONS
IS SOMEONE WHO CAN SHAVE
YOU WHILE YOU'RE ASLEEP.
JUST LIKE DELILAH
DID TO SAMSONITE.
YOUR WIFE MIGHT
EVEN SUGGEST
YOU SHAVE YOUR
BEARD RIGHT OFF.
JUST SHOW HER A PICTURE
OF YOUR CLEAN SHAVEN
GRANDFATHER.
THAT'LL PROBABLY MAKE
HER COME TO HER SENSES.
SO INSTEAD OF THROWING OUT THE
BEARD WITH THE BATH WATER,
JUST TRIM YOUR BEARD
SO THE WHISKERS ALL
EXACTLY THE SAME LENGTH.
FOR EXAMPLE, I LIKE MY BEARD
TO BE 3/8 OF AN INCH LONG.
WHICH HAPPENS TO BE THE SAME
DIAMETER AS RED LICORICE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, THE PLUM HARVEST
KICK-OFF IS GOING GREAT.
HAROLD'S ALL SET FOR
HIS BIG POSSUM DROP THERE.
HE'S GOT A COUPLE
OF TIRES AROUND HIM,
HE'LL BE FINE.
I THINK IT'S GOTTA
BE THE FIRST TIME
HE'S WORN RUBBER
FOR PROTECTION.
BUT I WANNA MAKE IT
EXTRA SAFE,
SO I'M GETTING HIM AN EXTRA
LAYER OF UNDERWEAR,
BECAUSE THAT COSTUME
IS A RENTAL.
IT'S TIME!
C'MON RED, HE'S GOIN!
NO, NO, IT'S SAFER
TO WATCH HIM IN
HERE, DALTON.
THOSE TIRES CAN SMASH
INTO A MILLION PIECES.
Harold: GERONIMO!
BOY, HAROLD FALLS
FASTER THAN THAT POSSUM.
I THINK IT'S THE EXTRA
WEIGHT OF ALL THAT RUBBER.
I THINK HE'S GONNA
HIT THE GROUND!
HOLY COW!
HE BOUNCED!
HE BOUNCED AGAIN!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
HE'S HEADED
FOR THE LAKE!
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH.
UH... OKAY,
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
UM, PROBABLY WON'T BE COMING
STRAIGHT HOME AFTER
THE MEETING.
HAROLD MAY HAVE
A COUPLE OF INJURIES,
BUT I'M SURE
HE'LL BOUNCE BACK.
NOW, NOW, NOW.
COME ON.
YOU'RE GOOD.
YOU'RE FINE.
I'M FINE?!
HEY, HEY, HEY.
DON'T YOU
START WHINING.
YOU GOT OFF LUCKY.
COMPARED TO WHAT?!
WELL, ALL THE
OTHER POSSUMS WITH
A TREAD MARK ON THEM.
HERE YOU'LL NEED THIS.
OH, YEAH.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND WHOEVER THAT WAS
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
COME ON, SIT DOWN.
GUYS, COME ON IN
AND TAKE YOUR SEATS.
HURRY UP, MEETING'S
COMING TO ORDER.
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD,
I WONDER IF YOU
MIGHT MIND
STANDING UP JUST
FOR A MINUTE?
HAROLD, ON BEHALF
OF THE LODGE,
I JUST WANTED
TO THANK YOU
FOR DOING A TERRIFIC
POSSUM DROP,
AND WE'RE WONDERING
IF YOU'D MIND DOING
IT ONE MORE TIME?
NOT A CHANCE!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
TOO TIRED?