THERE'S NO BETTER PLACE TO ENJOY
YOUR FAVOURITE MALT BEVERAGE
THAN IN THE GREAT OUTDOORS.
UNFORTUNATELY NOW,
THE GREAT OUTDOORS DOESN'T COME
WITH BUILT-IN END TABLES
AND YOU END UP FORGETTING
WHERE YOU LEFT YOUR BEER.
I'VE GOT THE PERFECT SOLUTION.
GET YOURSELF ONE OF
THESE PLUMBER'S HELPERS.
THAT'LL DO THE TRICK FOR YOU.
NOW, GO HIGH-END ON THIS.
GET THE DELUXE MODEL
WITH THE BUILT-IN...
IT'S GOT THE EXTENDABLE CUFF.
YOU STICK THAT INTO THE GROUND,
RAM HER IN THERE GOOD
AND THERE'S YOUR PERFECT
BUILT-IN DRINK HOLDER.
ALWAYS CLOSE AT HAND
AND YOU'LL NEVER FORGET
WHERE YOU PUT YOUR BEER.
IT'S THE RED GREEN SHOW!!!
AND HERE'S A MAN WHO NEVER
SAYS DIE BECAUSE IT JUST
MIGHT BE TRUE.
YOUR HOST AND HERO, MY UNCLE:
RED GREEEEEN!
[applause]
THANK-YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
A BIT OF A DISAPPOINTMENT
UP AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
WE HAD A FISHING DERBY
AGAINST CARIBOU LODGE
UP THERE ON MERCURY CREEK.
WE CAUGHT MORE FISH,
BUT THEY ENDED UP WINNING.
SOMEBODY GOT PAID OFF SOMEWHERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
MOST OF YOUR FISH ENDED UP
GETTING DISQUALIFIED.
THEY WERE FROZEN AND STILL HAD
THE PRICE TAGS ON THEM, SO...
I DON'T THINK SO, HAROLD.
WE CAUGHT MORE FISH.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD BE
PENALIZED FOR INGENUITY.
TO ME, CHEATING JUST MEANS
YOU CARE ABOUT WINNING.
I KNOW A WAY YOU CAN GET
REVENGE ON THOSE GUYS.
BECAUSE IT'S NATIONAL
HEALTH CARE WEEK,
YOU CHALLENGE THEM TO
A BLOOD DONOR COMPETITION.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YEAH, A BLOOD DONOR
COMPETITION!!!
ALL YOU'VE GOT TO DO
IS DONATE MORE BLOOD
THAN THEY DO.
I DO IT ALL THE TIME.
IT DOESN'T HURT
OR NOTHING.
AND THE BEST PART IS...
A NURSE COMES UP TO YOU
WEARING A WHITE DRESS
AND WHITE STOCKINGS
AND GIVES YOU JUICE
AND COOKIES
AND RUBS YOUR ARM AND
ASKS HOW YOU FEEL.
NO, HAROLD.
OUT OF THE QUESTION.
I CAN'T GIVE BLOOD.
I NEED IT ALL
FOR MY LIFESTYLE
AND TO HOLD
MY VEINS OPEN.
OH, OKAY.
IF YOU'RE AFRAID,
I UNDERSTAND.
I'M NOT AFRAID.
THAT'S NOT FEAR
IN YOUR EYES?
I THOUGHT THAT WAS
FEAR IN YOUR EYES.
OKAY.
I TELL YOU WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO.
I'M GOING TO CHALLENGE
THE CARIBOU LODGE GUYS
AND IF THEY'RE UP FOR IT,
I'M IN.
YOU THINK THEY
MIGHT REFUSE?
I'M BANKING ON IT.
IT'S TIME TO PLAY
"THE POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME."
OUR GUEST IS EXPLOSIVES EXPERT,
MR. EDGAR MONTROSE.
[applause]
TODAY, MR. MONTROSE IS PLAYING
FOR A FANTASTIC GRAND PRIZE
OF A BRAND NEW STEREO RECEIVER
SUPPLIED BY SOUPY'S
ELECTRONIC EMPORIUM.
[metal rattling]
SOME REASSEMBLY REQUIRED.
UNCLE RED, YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. MONTROSE TO SAY
THE FOLLOWING WORD:
YOU HAVE TO COVER YOUR EARS,
MR. MONTROSE.
NOT NECESSARY.
TODAY'S WORD IS:
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD.
GO!!!
EDGAR, EDGAR!
THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT'S EASY TO BREAK.
MARITAL COMMITMENTS.
NO, NO.
WHAT WORD COMES TO MIND
WHEN YOU THINK OF
BONE CHINA OR CRYSTAL?
OOPS!
SAY YOU'RE ON ONE OF
YOUR DEMOLITION SITES
AND THERE'S A LITTLE
FLOWER THERE.
A TINY FLOWER WITH
DAINTY LITTLE PETALS.
YOU WOULD SAY
THAT FLOWER IS...
TOAST.
REMEMBER THE OLD
WATER TOWER?
YOU BLEW THAT UP
AND YOU DIDN'T EVEN SCRATCH
THE FACTORY NEXT DOOR.
YOU MUST'VE BEEN VERY...
EMBARRASSED.
EMBARRASSED?
ACTUALLY, I WAS HIRED TO
DYNAMITE THE FACTORY.
OH, OH, OH!
ALMOST RUNNING OUT
OF TIME, UNCLE RED.
MOVE IT ON!
I'VE GOT IT!
LUNCH HOUR,
YOU TAKE A BREAK AND GO OVER
TO SCHAEFER'S DELICATESSEN.
WHAT DO YOU ORDER?
CORNED BEEF ON RYE.
OKAY, BUT NOT JUST
ANY CORNED BEEF.
YOU ORDER SCHAEFER'S SPECIAL...
DELI CUT.
[ring! ring! ring!]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THE CARIBOU LODGE GUYS ACCEPTED
OUR BLOOD DONOR CHALLENGE.
[applause]
THIS IS SO EXCELLENT.
WE'RE GOING TO
BEAT THEM SO BAD.
HOW DO YOU FIGURE
ON THAT, HAROLD?
YOU GUYS HAVE NEVER
GIVEN BLOOD BEFORE.
YOU'RE RIPE.
IT WILL BE GREAT.
THE BLOOD IS JUST GOING TO
COME GUSHING OUT OF YOU GUYS.
CAN YOU TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING ELSE?
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
SOMEONE STEP ON A GRAPE?
THHHPPLT!!!
WE SHOULD RACE DOWN TO
THE BLOOD DONOR PLACE
AND GIVE OURSELVES
A HEAD-START ON THEM.
NO, I CAN'T!
I CAN'T GIVE BLOOD TODAY.
BECAUSE IT'S STILL FULL
OF TOXINS FROM THE WEEKEND.
THAT'LL BE OKAY.
IF ANYTHING IS WRONG
WITH YOUR BLOOD,
THEY'LL TELL YOU.
SO, COME ON.
NO HAROLD, HAROLD!!!
I'LL GO WHEN I'M
GOOD AND READY.
ALL RIGHT?
OKAY.
I DIDN'T WANT
TO SAY ANYTHING,
BUT I'M NOT FEELING
ALL THAT GOOD.
REALLY?
ARE YOU COMING DOWN
WITH SOMETHING?
I GOT A THROAT THING.
THIS COULD BE THE MUMPS.
FEELS LIKE THE MUMPS.
THE MUMPS?
MUMPS ARE BAD.
MUMPS ARE REALLY BAD.
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
MUMPS, WOW!
I THOUGHT IT WAS SOMETHING
LIKE THE CHICKEN POX.
[clucking like a chicken]
CHICKEN!!!
CHICKEN POX!!!
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
I KNEW THAT WOULD
GET HIS BLOOD UP.
OH, THERE ONCE WAS A GUY
NAMED "HARDHEAD MCCALL"
WHO LIKED TO DO THINGS FAST
HE RAN LIKE THE WIND
AND ATE THE SAME WAY
ALWAYS READY
AND FULLY GASSED
HE HAD A FAST BOAT
WITH 400 HORSE
I TELL YOU THAT
BABY COULD FLY
BUT WHEN HE HIT THE BRIDGE
DOING A HUNDRED AND TEN
HE DECIDED TO GIVE
STOPPING A TRY
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN MEANING TO
GET THE POSSUM VAN CLEANED UP
FOR THE LAST COUPLE OF YEARS.
I JUST CAN'T JUSTIFY PAYING
FIVE BUCKS AT A CARWASH
WHEN I CAN DO AS GOOD A JOB
AT HOME FOR NOTHING.
AND THEN, WHEN I GET HOME,
I CAN'T JUSTIFY WASHING THE VAN
KNOWING A CARWASH IS EASIER.
IT'S A VICIOUS CIRCLE, ISN'T IT?
SO THIS WEEK ON
"HANDYMAN CORNER"
I'VE COME UP WITH
A SIMPLE SOLUTION.
WE'RE GOING TO BUILD
OUR VERY OWN CARWASH.
WE CAN'T GET THE POSSUM VAN
INTO THIS DISHWASHER.
MAYBE IF I TAKE THIS OUT...
NO, NO, NO.
SO, WHAT I NEED IS
AN EMPTY WATERPROOF BOX
THAT'S BIG ENOUGH
TO HOLD THE VAN.
WHICH I BELIEVE
WE HAVE RIGHT HERE.
TO SUPPLY THE WATER
FOR A CARWASH,
YOU COULD USE ONE OF THOSE
SPECIAL IRRIGATION HOSES
OR YOU CAN CONVERT
A NORMAL HOSE
USING YOUR LAWNMOWER.
RUMMAGE AROUND IN YOUR BASEMENT
FOR OLD CLOTHES THAT
YOU'LL NEVER WEAR AGAIN.
I KNOW YOU CAN GIVE YOUR
OLD CLOTHES TO POOR PEOPLE,
BUT POOR PEOPLE DON'T HAVE
CARS TO WASH, DO THEY?
LOOK AT THIS STUFF, HUH?
SILK TIES.
THESE WERE GREAT.
THE GHOST OF CHRISTMAS PAST.
BY GOLLY, LOOK AT THESE.
SIZE 30.
REMEMBER THE 60s?
NEITHER DO I.
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS ATTACH
ALL THIS STUFF TO THE INSIDE
OF YOUR GARAGE DOOR.
JUST LIKE PUTTING UP
CHRISTMAS LIGHTS.
EXCEPT WITH THESE,
YOU PUT THEM UP ONCE AND
YOU CAN LEAVE THEM UP FOREVER.
SO, IT'S EXACTLY LIKE
PUTTING UP CHRISTMAS LIGHTS.
YOU CAN ATTACH THESE ON HERE
WITH SOME METAL RIVETS OR
FASTENERS OF SOME KIND.
OF COURSE, I RECOMMEND THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON:
OH, OH!
I GUESS WE'RE DONE FOR TODAY.
SO, YOU WANT TO MAKE THIS
A REGULAR PATTERN ON HERE,
THAT WAY YOU GET EVEN
COVERAGE ON YOUR VEHICLE.
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS PARK
THE VAN IN THE GARAGE,
TURN ON THE HOSES
AND OPEN THE DOOR
AND THESE HOSES
RUNNING ACROSS THE DOOR
WILL WASH THE TOP OF THE VAN.
AND THESE LOOPS HANGING DOWN
WILL RINSE OFF THE SIDES.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, I NEED SCRUBBING BRUSHES.
SOFT SCRUBBING BRUSHES
MADE OF SILK AND CLOTH.
SEE WHERE I'M GOING?
LET'S START WITH THE WORKPANTS.
LET THE WORKPANTS DO THE WORK.
NOW, THESE ARE GOING TO GIVE
THE FRONT AND THE TOP OF MY VAN
A BEAUTIFUL SHAMMY WASH
AND I'VE MOUNTED THESE
BROOMS ON HERE,
SO AS YOU'RE COMING IN,
THAT'LL SCRAPE THE FOOD OFF
FROM THE DRIVE-THRU.
LET'S GIVE HER A TRY.
LOOK AT THAT.
ISN'T THAT...
SEE HOW IT WORKS?
I'M NOT GETTING SCRATCHED HERE.
NO SCRAPES, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
JUST A COUPLE OF MORE FEATURES.
I'VE MOUNTED A HOSE
RIGHT ONTO THE FLOOR
AND IT'S GOING TO SHOOT UP AND
WASH UNDERNEATH THE VEHICLE.
AND HERE'S A FEATURE:
I'VE GOT SOME HOCKEY STICKS
MAKING RAILINGS FOR US
TO KEEP THE VEHICLE STRAIGHT
WHILE IT'S IN YOUR GARAGE.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO PUT THESE IN,
EVEN IF YOU DON'T
BUILD A CARWASH.
I JUST NEED THE DETERGENT, NOW.
I FIGURE THAT ANY DETERGENT
THAT'LL TAKE BAKED CHEESE
OFF A FRYING PAN
WILL TAKE BAKED MOSQUITOES OFF
THE FRONT OF YOUR WINDSHIELD.
LET'S LOAD UP THE WORKPANTS.
ONCE YOU'VE GOT YOUR HOSES
ATTACHED TO THE DISHWASHER,
YOU'RE ALL SET TO GO.
SO REMEMBER...
"IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY."
EXCUSE ME, IF I LOOK
A LITTLE SMUG,
BUT I JUST SAVED FIVE BUCKS.
[water spraying]
AND IT ALSO CLEANS THE INSIDE.
[running water]
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU OLDER GUYS
ABOUT SOMETHING THAT'S
VERY, VERY DIFFICULT.
APOLOGIZING TO YOUR WIFE.
THIS IS THE TOUGHEST THING
THAT YOU WILL EVER DO.
NOW, WHATEVER THE ISSUE IS,
I REALIZE THAT YOU ARE 99.99%
SURE IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT.
BUT, YOU KNOW SOMETHING,
THAT SHOULD REMAIN
OUR LITTLE SECRET.
YOU'VE BEEN MARRIED
LONG ENOUGH TO KNOW
IT'S NOT YOUR JOB TO BE RIGHT.
IT'S YOUR JOB TO APOLOGIZE.
AND YOU GOT TO DO IT PROPERLY.
YOU CAN'T JUST SAY:
"I'M SORRY FOR EVERYTHING WRONG
THAT I'VE SAID OR DONE
IN THE PAST
AND POSSIBLY SAYING OR DOING NOW
OR MAY SAY OR DO AT
SOME POINT IN THE FUTURE."
THAT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
YOU CAN'T DO THE BLANKET.
WHAT YOU NEED TO DO IS
BE ABLE TO FAKE SINCERITY.
NOW, YOU'VE DONE THAT
AT LEAST ONCE BEFORE
OR YOU WOULDN'T BE MARRIED.
OH, YEAH.
[applause]
WELL, YOU NEED TO LEARN
HOW TO DO IT AGAIN.
WHAT I SAY YOU DO IS APOLOGIZE
TO SOMEBODY YOU DON'T KNOW,
LIKE A STRANGER YOU'VE
NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
GET YOUR SKILLS UP
AND GET READY
AND WHEN YOU THINK YOU'RE READY,
LOOK YOUR WIFE STRAIGHT
IN THE EYE AND SAY:
"HONEY..."
"IT'S ALL IN..."
"I JUST..."
[laughter]
SORRY.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YA,
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[laughter]
I FEEL A LITTLE
LIGHTHEADED.
YEAH.
I'VE NEVER GIVEN THAT
MUCH BLOOD BEFORE.
ARE YOU OKAY NOW?
I'M ALRIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED THERE, HAROLD.
I STARTED TO GIVE BLOOD
AND THEN I JUST BLACKED OUT.
I THINK THEY TOOK TOO MUCH.
TOO MUCH?
THEY TOOK ONE DROP
TO TEST IT.
YOU SAW THAT
AND YOU FAINTED.
YES, YOU DID!
BUT THAT'S OKAY,
I THINK IT'S BECAUSE
YOU HAVE TYPE O BLOOD.
OOOH!!!
OOOOH!
HEY, HEY!
THAT'S WHY.
I WASN'T THE ONLY
ONE TO KEEL OVER.
OKAY, THAT'S TRUE.
A LOT OF THE GUYS FAINTED.
EXCEPT MOOSE THOMPSON.
HE GAVE 12 LITRES OF BLOOD AND
ONLY HIS LEFT LEG WAS TINGLING.
THAT'S GREAT.
I BET WE'RE BEATING
CARIBOU LODGE ALREADY.
NO, THEY'RE STILL AHEAD
BY 10 LITRES OF BLOOD.
I'VE GOT A GREAT IDEA.
I'M GOING TO UP THE ANTE.
I'M GOING TO INCLUDE
ORGAN DONATIONS.
THAT'S GOOD, I LIKE THAT.
SO, HERE'S WHAT
WE'RE GOING TO DO:
YOU'LL KEEP ON
GIVING THE BLOOD.
I'M GOING TO GET OUT OF
THAT BUSINESS COMPLETELY.
I'M GOING TO SIGN OVER
MY ORGANS, HAROLD.
THAT'S WHAT I'M
GOING TO DO.
I KNOW MY LIVER HAS
A FEW MILES ON HER,
BUT I TELL YOU,
MY SPLEEN IS LIKE THE DAY
SHE CAME OUT OF THE SHOWROOM.
THAT'S A GREAT START.
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOUR HEART,
YOUR LUNGS AND YOUR EYES?
I BET YOU GOT A GALLBLADDER
LIKE A BUTTERNUT SQUASH.
WHATEVER IT TAKES, HAROLD.
WHATEVER I CAN DO
FOR MY FELLOW MAN.
LET'S GO DOWN THERE.
YOU GIVE A LITTLE BLOOD
AND I'LL SIGN
MY ORGANS OVER.
I DON'T KNOW IF I CAN
GIVE MORE BLOOD TODAY.
HAROLD, IF I CAN SIGN
A PIECE OF PAPER,
THE LEAST YOU CAN DO IS
GIVE A FEW LITRES OF BLOOD.
[narrated by Red]
BILL IS GOING TO DO
A LITTLE GARDENING.
JUMPING UP AND DOWN ON
THE SHOVEL AS HE DOES.
CAREFUL, CAREFUL, CAREFUL.
AH, AH!
OH!!!
SO, HE'S CUT OUT THE SOD.
HE'S GOING TO ROLL THAT UP.
JUST SET THAT ASIDE.
SET IT ASIDE, BILL.
I SAID SET...
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE OFF TO OUR USUAL START.
NOW, HE'S GOING TO...
DON'T STEP ON THE FLOWERS.
HE'S GOING TO TILL UP THE GROUND
WITH ONE OF THOSE
SPECIAL THINGS.
I HAPPENED TO NOTICE A SIGN.
PERHAPS THIS IS WHY
WE GOT THE LAND SO CHEAP.
THE TRANS-CANADA PIPELINE IS...
...GOING RIGHT THROUGH.
BILL, I THINK WE SHOULD
PICK ANOTHER SPOT.
BILL! BILL!
ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS WHAT I'M SAYING.
YEAH, YEAH.
IT'S REALLY...
BILL...
IT'S REALLY HARD TO DEAL
WITH 2,000 MILES OF GAS.
WE LEARNED THAT
ON "MEXICAN NIGHT."
THERE WE ARE.
BEAUTIFUL JOB.
YOU DIDN'T SEAL THE LEAK,
YOU JUST PUT OUT THE FLAME.
THAT'S GAS.
BILL, THAT'S GAS.
WHY DON'T WE JUST LEAVE?
LET'S GO.
BILL, I DON'T...
NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S A SHORT-TERM SOLUTION
TO A LONG-TERM...
DON'T JUMP, DON'T JUMP.
[BOOM!]
WATCH OUT FOR THE RAKE!
THE RAKE! THE RAKE!
OH!!!
HERE COMES THE ROLLER!
OH, BILL!
OH, OH, OH.
OH BOY, OH BOY.
OH, MY GOSH!
THIS IS THE PART
OF THE PROGRAM
WHERE WE LIKE TO EXAMINE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO HARD TO SAY:
[studio audience]
I DON'T KNOW!!!
IT'S TRUE, ISN'T IT?
JOINING UNCLE RED
IS MR. MIKE HAMAR.
[applause]
OUR LETTER TO THE EXPERTS
GOES AS FOLLOWS:
"DEAR EXPERTS:
I HAVE A PROBLEM.
I HAVE A BIRTHDAY COMING UP AND
MY HUSBAND IS FAR TOO GENEROUS.
LAST YEAR HE GOT ME
A NEW FOREIGN SPORTSCAR.
THE YEAR BEFORE IT WAS AN
EMERALD AND PLATINUM RING.
WE'RE NOT WEALTHY,
WE CANNOT AFFORD HIS LARGESSE.
HOW DO I MENTION IT WITHOUT
HURTING HIS FEELINGS?"
OH, IT'S SO LOVELY.
WELL, IT MIGHT BE
LOVELY FOR HER,
BUT THANK GOODNESS
NOBODY ELSE'S WIFE IS
WATCHING THIS SHOW.
WAS THAT SPORTSCAR, EMERALD
RING LADY A LOCAL ADDRESS?
ST. PAUL, MINNESOTA.
THAT'S TOO FAR TO GO.
TOO FAR TO GO TO...
WELL, THEY JUST SEEMED
LIKE SUCH NICE PEOPLE.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
I'LL TELL YOU.
IT'S NOT JUST
THE GIFT, EH?
THE GIFT IS NOT THE BEST WAY
TO SAY YOU LOVE SOMEBODY.
YOU CAN DO THAT WITH
A REALLY NICE CARD.
HA! HA! HA!
NICE TRY, UNCLE RED.
MR. GREEN, THERE'S A BETTER
WAY TO BUY GIFTS, YOU KNOW.
YOU BUY EXPENSIVE STUFF,
THEN YOU FENCE IT AND
YOU COLLECT THE MONEY.
THEN YOU CLAIM YOU LOST IT
OR IT GOT STOLEN, RIGHT?
AND YOU COLLECT FROM
THE INSURANCE AGENT.
THEN YOU BUY ANOTHER
REPLACEMENT PRESENT
AND THEN YOU END UP
WITH A BIG PROFIT.
OKAY, I THINK
THAT'S A GOOD PLAN,
EXCEPT FOR THE GOING
TO THE SLAMMER PART.
WELL, YOU TRADE JAIL TIME
FOR THE PROFITS OF YOUR CRIME.
IT'S PRETTY STRAIGHTFORWARD.
I MEAN, YOUR TIME FOR
SOMEONE ELSE'S MONEY.
IF YOU TRADED THE JAIL
FOR AN OFFICE,
THAT'S WHAT STRAIGHT
PEOPLE CALL WORK.
[laughter]
IS IT JUST ME, HAROLD,
OR IS MIKE MAKING SENSE HERE?
I'M JUST PULLING YOUR LEG.
A LOT OF PEOPLE
DO THAT IN PRISON.
I WOULDN'T WANT ANYBODY
TO BE BREAKING THE LAW
AND GETTING THROWN
IN THE SLAMMER.
I WOULD FEEL JUST
TERRIBLE ABOUT THAT.
WELL, I'M REALLY GLAD
TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT.
SO LISTEN, EVERYBODY:
DON'T GET CAUGHT.
[laughter and applause]
COME ON, HAROLD.
I'M OKAY.
YOU CAN DO IT.
YOU'RE ALRIGHT,
YOU'RE ALRIGHT.
EASY, EASY, EASY.
ARE YOU ALRIGHT?
ALL RIGHT?
DRACULA!!!
NO, NO, NO.
I'M YOUR UNCLE RED.
UNCLE RED?
THAT'S OKAY, I GUESS.
HAROLD, YOU DID A GREAT JOB
BY GIVING ALL THAT BLOOD.
YOU BEAT CARIBOU LODGE
ALL ON YOUR OWN THERE.
CAN I GET YOU ANYTHING?
YEAH, I'M THIRSTY.
WE'VE GOT A BUNCH
OF DRINKS DOWNSTAIRS.
GET YOURSELF SOMETHING.
I WOULDN'T MIND A POP
WHILE YOU'RE DOWN THERE.
OKAY.
BY THE WAY, I FORGOT TO
MENTION THIS EARLIER.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU WANTED ANY
OF MY ORGANS AFTER I'M GONE,
YOU KNOW, HEART, LUNGS,
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
JUST SAY THE WORD.
I WOULDN'T MIND YOUR BRAIN.
YOU GOT IT BUDDY.
OH, THANKS.
I FIGURE IT'S BRAND NEW.
[applause]
[squeal of the Possum]
IS THAT MY VEINS OR
IS IT MEETING TIME?
NO, IT'S MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
I'M OKAY, I'M OKAY.
JUST GIVE A PUSH.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I KNOW I PROMISED YOU MY HEART,
BUT YOU MAY HAVE TO
SETTLE FOR MY GIBLETS.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU:
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND...
HAROLD, HAROLD!
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE:
"KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE."
[applause]
Red:
OKAY, SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
[lodge members]
QUANDO, OMNI, FLUNKUS, MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
THE BLOOD DONOR CLINIC
ANNOUNCED THAT THEY'VE
GOT SO MUCH BLOOD
THAT WE'VE GOT THE GREEN LIGHT
TO USE OUR POWER TOOLS AGAIN.
HAROLD, ARE YOU...
THAT'S REALLY NOT HOW
YOU GIVE BLOOD, HAROLD.