THEY SAY THERE’S GOING TO BE
A BIG SNOW STORM TONIGHT.
WHICH MEANS THAT IF I WANT
TO GO ANYWHERE TOMORROW,
I'LL HAVE TO SHOVEL
OUT THE DRIVEWAY,
AND OF COURSE I'LL
HAVE A HEART ATTACK,
AND THAT'LL LEAD TO A BIG
ARGUMENT WITH MY WIFE ABOUT
ADEQUATE INSURANCE COVERAGE.
SO TO AVOID ALL THAT
I'VE HOOKED UP
A RIG HERE, WHICH I
THINK IS ABSOLUTELY BRILLIANT.
LAID DOWN A COUPLE OF
SHEETS OF MARINE PLYWOOD,
AND I GOT THIS ROPE RUNNING
FROM THE CENTRES
UP THROUGH THESE PULLEYS
ON THE SIDES OF THE GARAGE,
DOWN TO THIS
LITTLE RAMP HERE.
NOW, JUST IMAGINE IF THIS
WAS ALL COVERED WITH SNOW.
LET ME SHOW YOU
WHAT HAPPENS.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
EASY.
YEAH, BOY, I APPRECIATE THAT.
WELL, I HAD A BIT OF A
DISCOVERY THIS WEEK,
UP AT THE LODGE.
APPARENTLY IF YOU'RE
A CLUB LIKE WE ARE,
AND YOU ASSOCIATE YOURSELF
WITH A CHARITYF SOME KIND,
YOU GET ALL SORTS OF
TREATS FROM THE GOVERNMENT.
I MEAN, THEY WILL GIVE US
TAX REFUNDS AND GRANTS,
AND THEY'LL STOP
TRYING TO CLOSE THE LODGE
AND STOP TRYING TO SEND US
ALL UP TO BAFFIN ISLAND.
SO, UH, WE'VE BEEN IN TOUCH
WITH A BUNCH OF CHARITIES.
SO FAR NO LUCK.
THEY'RE ALL SAYING THEY
DON'T NEED THE MONEY,
QUITE THAT BAD.
HEY, RED, LOOKS LIKE WE GOT
OURSELVES A CHARITY.
YEAH.
GREAT.
WHICH ONE?
RED CROSS,
SALVATION ARMY,
DAUGHTERS OF
THE EMPIRE, MAYBE?
YEAH, RIGHT.
NO, RED, THIS IS ONE OF THE
LESSER KNOWN CHARITIES.
IT'S THE
DANDRUFF FOUNDATION.
THE DANDRUFF
FOUNDATION?
WELL, THAT'S KIND
OF A LET DOWN;
ALTHOUGH, YOU'D MAKE
A GREAT POSTER BOY,
I'M THINKING.
NO, IT'S A REAL
DEDICATED GROUP, RED.
HAVE YOU HEARD
THEIR CAMPAIGN SLOGAN?
IT'S ALL
ON OUR SHOULDERS.
AND ALL THEY NEED FROM
THE LODGE IS A CHEQUE
FOR $500.00.
PARDON ME?
$500.00 IS THE
MINIMUM DONATION
THAT WILL QUALIFY US AS
AN AFFILIATED PARTNER.
WE DON'T HAVE THAT
KIND OF MONEY.
DO YOU THINK THEY'D ACCEPT
A '73 K-CAR AS PAYMENT?
MAYBE,
IF YOU PUT 500 BUCKS IN
THE GLOVE COMPARTMENT.
WHERE ARE WE GOING TO COME UP
WITH THAT KIND OF CASH, GUYS?
WELL, WHY DON'T WE SELL
PEANUTS OF CHOCOLATES,
DOOR-TO-DOOR
LIKE SOME OF THEM
OTHER CHARITIES?
YOU KNOW A LOT OF PEOPLE
WILL PAY TWO BUCKS FOR A
50-CENT CANDY BAR
JUST TO GET YOU OFF
THEIR PROPERTY.
NOW, YOU TELL ME WHAT
KIND OF CANDY YOU WANT,
'CAUSE I KNOW A GUY WHO
CAN GET ALL THE STUFF
REAL CHEAP.
IT ISN'T MIKE,
IS IT?
NO, NO, MIKE GETS ALL
HIS STUFF FREE.
I KNOW, HE STEALS IT
FROM MY STORE.
NO, THE GUY I'M TALKING ABOUT
IMPORTS EVERYTHING FROM CHINA.
OH, CHINESE
CHOCOLATE BAR.
SWEET-AND-SOUR
SNICKERS?
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
AND TODAY'S PRIZE IS
THIS ALUMINUM BUCKET
FROM BIG BOB'S
BUCKET BOUTIQUE.
ALL OTHERS "PAIL"
BY COMPARISON.
HEY, GORD, YOU GOTTA
COVER YOUR EARS NOW.
GORD!
OH, RIGHT. SORRY.
OKAY, Mr GREEN,
YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET RANGER GORD
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH,
ALRIGHT, MIKE.
AND GO!
OKAY, GORD,
WORKING BY YOURSELF UP
HERE AT THE FIRE TOWER,
MAKES YOU FEEL...
OMNIPOTENT.
I WOULD DOUBT THAT.
SOMETIMES I FEEL I'M
ADRIFT ON A SEA OF EVIL,
WITH ONLY MY ANIMAL CUNNING
AND MIGHTY PHYSIQUE
FOR PROTECTION.
I JUST SAID A LOT
OF WORDS THERE, RED.
ARE YOU SURE IT WASN'T
IN THERE, SOMEWHERE?
NO, IT WASN'T
IN THERE.
OKAY, NO, THIS IS
SOMETHING THAT YOU FEEL
WHEN NO ONE
ELSE IS AROUND.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THAT'S A LITTLE
PRIVATE, RED.
NO, NO.
I KNOW --
OKAY. WHEN YOU HAVEN'T SEEN
OTHER PEOPLE FOR A LONG TIME,
YOU GET...
AN INFLATABLE FRIEND.
OH, NO, NO.
ALMOST OUT OF
TIME, Mr GREEN.
OKAY, MIKE. OKAY.
THERE WAS A BIG HIT SONG FOR
PAUL ANKA, "I'M JUST A
SOMETHING BOY."
CABIN?
NO. NO.
OKAY, GORD, WHAT IS
THE WORST PART
ABOUT BEING UP HERE IN A
FIRE TOWER ALL BY YOURSELF?
OH, WELL, SOMETIMES
I WAKE UP IN THE MORNING
WITH MY NOSE FILLED
WITH MOSQUITOES.
SO I'D HAVE TO SAY MOSQUITOES.
THEY'RE PRETTY BAD.
STILL, THEY KEEP MY
FROM GETTING TOO LONELY.
HEY!
[ RINGING BELL ]
[ APPLAUSE ]
HI, WINSTON ROTHSCHILD HERE,
OF ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
IF ROSES ARE ORANGE
AND VIOLETS ARE BLACK,
IT SOUNDS LIKE YOUR SEPTICS
ARE WAY OUT OF WHACK.
TODAY ON
TALKING ANIMALS,
LOCAL ANIMAL CONTROL
OFFICER, ED FRID,
IS GOING TO TEACH US
ALL ABOUT LEECHES.
C'MON.
COME ON
UP HERE, ED.
IT'S SAFE.
THEY'RE IN A BUCKET.
ALTHOUGH I CAN
UNDERSTAND YOUR HESITANCY.
I MEAN, THESE
THINGS ARE UGLY,
BLACK, DISGUSTING WORMS,
AND THEY STICK ON YOU
AND SUCK YOUR BLOOD, RIGHT?
YEAH.
THAT'S PART OF IT.
PLUS THEY HAVE
32 BRAINS.
NO, I'M NOT KIDDING.
EVERY LEECH HAS
32 LITTLE BRAINS.
SOUNDS LIKE A
LODGE MEETING.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY, FOLKS?
YOU WANNA SEE A
LEECH OR NOT?
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
IF YOU GO ON THE INTERNET YOU
CAN SEE LOTS OF PICTURES
OF LEECHES THERE.
OR VISIT YOUR
LOCAL BAIT SHOP.
COME ON, ED.
YOU BROUGHT IN
A WHOLE BUCKET.
JUST GET OUT ONE LEECH.
THAT'S ALL I'M ASKING, EH?
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
I'M GOING TO TRY AND
GET ONE OUT HERE.
OH! DIDN'T GET ONE
SORRY.
THEY'RE QUICK.
THEY'RE VERY
QUICK, YEAH.
I THINK THERE'S
ONE ON YOUR ARM THERE.
YEAH.
OH BOY!
OH, THAT'S A BIG ONE
OH MY.
AND IT'S GETTING BIGGER!
I THINK IT'S TAPPED
INTO AN ARTERY THERE.
AT THIS POINT, YOU HAVE
A COUPLE OF CHOICES.
YOU COULD PUT
SALT ON THE LEECH.
RED, WOULD YOU HAPPEN TO
HAVE ANY SALT HANDY?
PLEASE.
HERE'S SOME SALT.
YEAH, I'VE GOT SOME.
OH, BOY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK YOU'RE JUST
MAKING HIS THIRSTY.
OH, YEAH.
OKAY.
NO, PROBLEM.
OH, GEEZ, I'M LOSING
A LOT OF BLOOD.
CAN I HAVE
A CIGARETTE?
UH, NO, BUT I CAN GET
YOU A BLINDFOLD.
NO, BURNING THEM
WITH A LIT CIGARETTE
IS AN EFFECTIVE WAY OF
GETTING RID OF LEECHES.
OH, I DON'T SMOKE.
MAYBE WE SHOULD RUSH
YOU TO A BINGO HALL.
YOU KNOW, EVERYBODY ENJOYS
FIREWORKS ON A SUMMER'S NIGHT.
THEY CAN BE EXPENSIVE,
AND SOME STORES WON'T SELL
THEM TO YOU ON A BUY NOW
PAY LATER DEAL.
OR MAYBE THEY'VE BEEN WARNED
ABOUT YOU BY THE LOCAL
AUTHORITIES.
SO THIS TIME,
ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW
YOU CAN MAKE YOUR OWN
FIREWORKS DISPLAY
USING AN OLD RADIO
AND A BUNCH OF SCREEN DOORS.
THIS IS A TUBE RADIO.
I'M SURE YOU YOUNG PEOPLE
DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT IS.
BUT IN MY DAY, WE HAD TO TURN
THESE BABIES ON,
LET THEM WARM UP
BEFORE THEY'D WORK.
THAT'S HOW PEOPLE IN MY
GENERATION LEARNED
TO BE PATIENT.
KIDS TODAY, THEY JUST
EXPECT EVERYTHING TO
TURN ON IMMEDIATELY,
THAT CAN BE A REAL PROBLEM
DURING A HONEYMOON,
I'LL TELL YOU.
NOW, WE'RE GOING TO
TAKE THE RADIO APART,
BECAUSE ALL WE NEED
IS THE TRANSFORMER,
WHICH IS THIS HEAVY THING USED
TO STEP UP THE VOLTAGE.
IT DOES THAT BY INDUCTION.
I'M NOT QUITE SURE
WHAT THAT IS,
BUT I'VE HEARD OF
PEOPLE BEING INDUCTED.
I'M SURE IT'S VERY SIMILAR.
ANOTHER THING YOU GOT TO WATCH
FOR IS THE CAPACITORS.
A CAPACITOR CAN HOLD A CHARGE
OF SEVERAL THOUSAND VOLTS
LONG AFTER A
UNIT IS UNPLUGGED.
NOW, IS THAT A CAPACITOR,
OR IS THAT JUST A RESISTOR?
I THINK I'VE
JUST BEEN INDUCTED.
OKAY, I'VE GOT MY
TRANSFORMER OUT OF THERE,
AND I'VE ATTACHED THE OUTPUT
TO MY WALL OF SCREEN DOORS.
I'VE GOT A WIRE
ON EACH SIDE.
I FIGURE I'VE GOT ABOUT
100,000 VOLTS RUNNING
THROUGH THESE BABIES.
I THREW AWAY THE WELCOME
MATS THAT CAME WITH THEM.
I DIDN'T WANT TO SEND
OUT A FALSE MESSAGE.
NOW, ALL I GOT TO DO IS
GET MYSELF COMFORTABLE.
SOMEWHERE WHERE I'LL
HAVE A GOOD VIEW.
THIS OUGHT TO BE
PERFECT RIGHT OVER HERE.
THERE WE GO.
NOW ALL I HAVE TO DO IS
PLUG IN MY TRANSFORMER
AND WAIT FOR THE
FIREWORKS TO START.
OH, I KNOW.
FORGOT TO TURN ON
MY LANTERN.
YOU NEED THAT
TO ATTRACT THE BUGS.
( coughing )
THAT ONE SMELLED
LIKE A BAT.
YOU KNOW, I KNOW THERE
ARE A LOT OF FACTORS
THAT GO INTO MAKING
UP A HUMAN BEING.
BUT THE MAIN ONE
HAS TO BE CHEMISTRY.
AND FOR A MAN THE MAIN CHEMICAL
INGREDIENT HAS GOT TO BE
TESTOSTERONE.
I MEAN, YOU TAKE
AN AVERAGE MAN
AND YOU GREATLY REDUCE THE
TESTOSTERONE IN THERE,
AND YOU'LL EITHER
GET AN UGLY WOMAN
OR A GUY WHO WALKS FUNNY
AND WORKS IN A HAREM.
NOW, I KNOW THERE ARE OTHER
CHEMICALS INVOLVED.
YOU GOT A TABLESPOON OF BILE;
YOU GOT A SIX-PACK OF BARLEY;
YOU GOT A CUBIC FOOT OF
B.S.; AND A TANK FULL OF GAS.
BUT THE MAIN ONE IS
TESTOSTERONE.
SO WE'VE GOT TO
BE REAL CONCERNED
WHEN WE SEE NEGATIVE
MESSAGES ABOUT TESTOSTERONE;
FOR EXAMPLE,
ANIMALS BEING NEUTERED.
OKAY, I UNDERSTAND THE
RATIONALE ABOUT TAKING A PIG
AND LOPPING OFF HIS PRIVATE
PARTS TO FATTEN HIM UP.
YOU KNOW, THE CONCEPT
BEING HE'LL EAT MORE
WHEN HE HAS NOTHING
BETTER TO THINK ABOUT.
BUT, NOW, GETTING YOUR DOG
FIXED TO MAKE HIM MORE
MANAGEABLE,
THAT'S A
DANGEROUS PRECEDENT.
I'M THINKING THE ODD TIME
YOU'VE PROBABLY CHASED A CAR.
MAYBE BARKED AT A NEIGHBOUR.
MIGHT'VE EVEN HAVE LEFT
A LITTLE MESS ON THE
FLOOR SOMETIMES.
THE LAST THING YOU WANT IS FOR
YOUR WIFE TO LOOK AT YOU
AND THEN GLANCE
OVER AT THE FRIENDLY,
MANAGEABLE FAMILY DOG
AND START GETTING
CRAZY IDEAS, HUH!
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THE TOGETHER.
HI, I'M WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
FROM ROTHSCHILD'S SEWAGE AND
SEPTIC SUCKING SERVICES.
IF YOU'RE BLUSHIN'
FROM ALL THE FLUSHIN',
I'LL COME RUSHIN'
TO STOP THE GUSHIN'.
THIS DANDRUFF FOUNDATION
IS KIND OF INTERESTING.
STARTED BY TWO GUYS WHO
HAD SIMILAR PROBLEMS
AND PUT THEIR
HEADS TOGETHER.
PROBABLY A COUPLE OF FLAKES.
RED, GOT THE CHINESE
CANDIES FOR US TO SELL!
WE GOT A DEAL
ON THEM TOO!
WHAT KIND OF
CANDY IS IT?
YOU KNOW, I THINK IT'S
A TYPE OF LICORICE.
THEY HAVE REAL UNUSUAL
INGREDIENTS OVER THERE,
SO THIS IS LITTLE DIFFERENT
LICORICE THEN WE'RE USED
TO AROUND HERE.
THE COLOUR LOOKS OKAY.
HOW DOES IT TASTE?
OH, OH.
GOOD, FINE.
YEAH, THEY DON'T LOOK BAD.
I'VE SEEN A LOT WORSE STUFF.
ALTHOUGH, I DON'T WORK AT THE
THE INPUT SIDE OF THINGS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELL, UH, GUYS, YOU KNOW IF
WE'RE GOING TO SELL THESE
TO THE PUBLIC,
WE BETTER
TASTE THEM FIRST.
YEAH, THAT MAKES SENSE.
YEAH,
WE COULD DO THAT.
NOBODY.
TO START FIRST?
SO, WHO WANTS
WELL, WE HAVE TO
DO IT TOGETHER.
THAT'S ALL THERE IS TO IT.
FAIR IS FAIR.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, SURE. FINE.
THOSE ARE CHEWY.
I LIKE THEM.
IT'S SORT OF AN
UNUSUAL FLAVOUR.
WHAT IS THAT?
IT'S A
CHINESE TASTE.
IT'S EITHER SOY SAUCE
OR FIRECRACKERS.
HOW MUCH DO YOU
THINK WE SHOULD
CHARGE PEOPLE
FOR A BOX OF
THESE THINGS?
OH, WE GOT TO
GET TWO BUCKS A BOX.
AS LONG AS WE DON'T LET
THEM TASTE THEM FIRST.
I THINK WE'D BETTER
GO FIVE BUCKS,
'CAUSE WE DON'T HAVE MANY
POTENTIAL CUSTOMERS,
AND THERE'S GOING TO BE
NO REPEAT BUSINESS.
YOU FIGURED YOU ASKED ALL
THE RIGHT QUESTIONS.
CAN I HELP YOU
WITH ANYTHING?
ARE YOU SURE?
YOU NEED?
IS THERE ANYTHING
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE SURE?
THEN, YOU MADE THE BIGGEST
MISTAKE OF YOUR LIFE.
YOU TOOK HER AT
HER WORD.
SEE, SHE FIGURES IT'S
OBVIOUS SHE NEEDS
SOME HELP.
YOU FIGURE, YOU ASKED,
SHE SAID NO,
YOU'RE OFF
THE HOOK, RIGHT?
NOW THE THERMOSTAT
JUST WENT DOWN
25 DEGREES.
"NO, I'M FINE," DIDN'T
MEAN, "NO, I'M FINE."
THAT'S 'CAUSE SHE SAID
IT LIKE, "NO, I'M NOT FINE."
SEE, SHE EXPECTS YOU TO
LISTEN TO THE WAY SHE
SAYS THE WORDS,
NOT JUST THE WORDS.
YOU FIGURED JUST LISTENING
WAS A BIG STEP FORWARD,
NEVER MIND INTERPRETING.
AND LET'S FACE IT, YOU'RE
NOT GETTING ANY MORE
SENSITIVE.
SO HERE'S A
RULE OF THUMB...
IF SHE LOCKS HERSELF ALONE
IN THE BATHROOM WEEPING,
THAT MEANS SHE SAID THE EXACT
OPPOSITE OF WHAT SHE MEANT.
SO YOUR EXCUSE HAS TO BE YOU
MEANT THE EXACT OPPOSITE
OF WHAT YOU SAID.
SEE, MEN AND WOMEN HAVE
BEEN SENDING EACH OTHER
THAT KIND OF MISINFORMATION
SINCE THE DAWN OF TIME.
IT'S CALLED
COMMUNICATING.
DON'T THANK US.
THAT'S WHAT
FRIENDS ARE FOR.
HAD A BIT OF A TENNIS MATCH
OUT BY THE LODGE THERE.
TWO AGAINST TWO.
A THREE-POINT GAME THERE.
A LOT OF
SPORTSMANSHIP INVOLVED,
AND DALTON'S GOING TO
BE THE UMPIRE FOR US.
MIKE'S READY AND WALTER
CAN REALLY FIRE THAT BABY,
AND THEN RIGHT THROUGH
AND OFF THE BACK
AND IT'S IN, IT'S IN.
THAT'S A POINT.
WE GOT THAT ONE.
LITTLE ARGUMENT THERE.
WON'T DO YOU ANY GOOD.
HE SAW IT WAS IN.
WELL, HANG ON, MIKE.
DON'T DO THAT.
WELL, THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT, SERVE AGAIN.
NOW, WATCH THIS.
WALTER CAN REALLY
PUT A SPIN ON A BALL.
WATCH THE SPIN ON THIS BABY.
NOW -- LOOK, THEY THINK
THE BIG ONE'S COMING.
THAT'S RIGHT, GET BACK.
GET BACK.
BACK UP.
OH, TOO FAR.
TOO FAR.
COME BACK.
THERE YOU GO.
PUT SOME SPIN ON HER, WALTER.
PUT SOME SPIN ON HER.
GIVE HER A GOOD SLICE.
LOOK AT THIS.
JUST DIED.
THAT'S ANOTHER POINT.
THAT'S TWO.
ONE MORE POINT TO GO.
WE GOT OURSELVES --
YEAH, THAT WAS GOOD.
IT WAS GOOD.
OH, OH. IT WON'T DO
YOU ANY GOOD.
NOPE, LEAVE
THE UMP ALONE.
OH, THAT'S GOTTA HURT.
THAT'S GOTTA HURT.
NO, I DON'T THINK WINSTON
DID IT, SOMEHOW.
ALL RIGHT, POINT THREE.
THIS IS GAME SET MATCH.
A HIGH ONE.
OH, IT'S A HIGH ONE.
NO, NO, NOT YET.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THERE WE GO.
GOT HER.
AND THAT'S OUT.
THAT'S A GAME.
WE GOT HER.
WAY TO GO.
WAY TO GO, WALTER.
WE NAILED HER.
AND GREAT UMPING
THERE, DALTON.
MIKE AND WINSTON
ARE SO LOSERS,
WHICH IS UNFORTUNATE.
TODAY ON
UP CLOSE AND PERSONAL,
WE'RE GOING TO MEET EXPLOSIVES
ENTHUSIAST, EDGAR MONTROSE.
GET A CHANCE TO LOOK AT THE
MAN BEHIND THE POWDER BURNS.
EDGAR, MAYBE YOU COULD TAKE
US BACK TO THE BEGINNING,
WHEN YOU WERE
GROWING UP AS A KID.
OH, YEAH. WELL, RED,
MY FATHER WAS AN ACCOUNTANT,
AND MY MOM WAS A LIBRARIAN.
IT WAS A VERY
QUIET HOUSE,
UP UNTIL MY
SEVENTH BIRTHDAY.
THAT'S WHEN I GOT
THE CHEMISTRY SET.
WAS IT A
LARGE HOUSE, EDGAR?
WELL IT GOT A LITTLE
SMALLER THAT DAY.
SO YOU STARTED EXPERIMENTING
WITH EXPLOSIVES AT A
VERY EARLY AGE.
I WOULD SAY SO.
I KIND OF LOST TRACK
OF TIME THERE.
I'D BLOW SOMETHING UP,
AND THEN IT MIGHT TAKE A
WHILE BEFORE I REGAINED
CONSCIOUSNESS.
BUT I GOT RIGHT
BACK AT IT.
I WAS CURIOUS TO KNOW WHERE
THINGS GO WHEN THEY EXPLODE.
AND WHERE
DO THEY GO?
A LONG WAY.
ONCE I FILLED MY BICYCLE
HANDLEBARS WITH DYNAMITE.
WHEN I SET THAT OFF IT BLEW MY
HORN HALFWAY TO PORT ASBESTOS.
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN GET
HURT HAVING THAT KIND
OF FUN, EDGAR.
OH, I DIDN'T DO IT
FOR FUN, RED.
IT WAS EDUCATIONAL.
I LEARNED A LOT.
FOR EXAMPLE, I LEARNED THAT AN
EXPLOSIVE IS VERY STRONG,
STRONGER THAN,
SAY, A FINGER.
OH, BOY. THAT MUST
HAVE BEEN PAINFUL.
OH, YEAH.
THEY SAID THEY MIGHT HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO REATTACH THE FINGER
AFTER THE EXPLOSION,
BUT IT TOOK TOO
LONG TO COME DOWN.
YOU KNOW, PERSONALLY I WOULD
NEVER MESS AROUND WITH
DYNAMITE.
THAT'S 'CAUSE YOU HAVE
NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE
DOING, RED.
I'M AN ARTIST.
WHEN SOMEBODY WANTS
THEIR HOUSE MOVED,
I CAN MOVE THAT UNIT
RIGHT OFF THE FOUNDATION
AND STAND IT UP ON ONE
CORNER WHILE THE
PLUMBING DRAINS
AND THEN LAY IT SIDEWAYS
ON A FLATBED TRUCK.
AND I'LL TELL YOU,
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN BEAUTY
UNTIL YOU'VE SEEN A 60-FOOT
MAPLE TREE BOUNCING
END-OVER-END THROUGH
A CANADIAN SUNSET.
ALL RIGHT, EDGAR.
JUST A SECOND.
WE DON'T WANT TO
BE SENDING OUT THE
WRONG MESSAGE HERE,
SO TO WRAP IT UP WHY DON'T
YOU JUST LOOK RIGHT INTO
THE CAMERA
GIVE A LITTLE BIT OF ADVICE
TO ANY OF THE YOUNGSTERS
THAT ARE WATCHING US?
ALL RIGHT.
I'M JUST KIDDING.
THAT WAS A LITTLE
INSINCERE, I THINK,
DON'T YOU?
OKAY.
DON'T FOOL AROUND WITH
ANY TYPE OF EXPLOSIVES.
YOU NEED LOTS OF TRAINING TO
WORK WITH EXPLOSIVES,
AND YOU NEED
A SPECIAL PERMIT,
WHICH YOU CAN ONLY GET BY
PASSING A RIGOROUS
GOVERNMENT TEST.
AND WHY DON'T YOU SHOW
THEM WHAT THE PERMIT
LOOKS LIKE?
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, LICORICE SALES
HAVE NOT BEEN BRISK.
I HAVEN'T SOLD ANY.
I DON'T THINK
WINSTON'S SOLD ANY.
DALTON SOLD 10 BOXES
TO MOOSE THOMPSON.
BUT, HEY, WITH MOOSE,
IF YOU PUT ENOUGH HOT SAUCE ON
IT, HE'D EAT A GARDEN SHED.
YOU KNOW I KINDA
LIKE THIS LICORICE.
I MUST BE GETTING
USED TO IT.
WELL, YOU'RE MARRIED
TO ANNE-MARIE.
I THINK YOU COULD GET
USED TO ANYTHING, DALTON.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
I THINK I'VE FIGURED OUT
WHY WE'RE HAVING SO MUCH
TROUBLE SELLING THIS LICORICE.
BECAUSE IT'S EXPENSIVE
AND TASTES LIKE ASPHALT?
NO, NO. I WAS TRYING TO SELL
THIS STUFF DOOR-TO-DOOR,
AND THERE WAS THIS CHINESE
EXCHANGE STUDENT STAYING AT
BUSTER HADFIELD'S PLACE.
HE TOOK ONE LOOK
AT THIS BOX AND SAID,
"THOSE LETTERS DON'T
SAY LICORICE."
WELL, WHAT DO THEY SAY?
EARRINGS.
RED, WE'RE IN A
LOT OF TROUBLE HERE.
WE COULD BE CHARGED.
WELL, HOW COULD
WE BE CHARGED?
AS ACCESSORIES.
OH, COME ON.
I DON'T
FEEL SO GOOD.
YOU KNOW
YOUR TROUBLE?
YOU DON'T LOOK GOOD
WITH EARRINGS.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
WE DO NOTHING.
WE KEEP OUR MOUTHS SHUT.
WE CAN'T GO BACK TO
THE SAME CUSTOMERS
AND SELL THEM THESE
CANDIES AS JEWELLERY NOW.
WELL HOW ARE WE GOING
TO GET THAT $500 TO THE
DANDRUFF FOUNDATION?
WE'RE NOT GOING
TO GET IT TO THEM.
THEY'VE GOT DANDRUFF.
THEY CAN FIND THEIR
OWN SCRATCH.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
AWAY YOU GO.
WELL, MEETING TIME.
THIS IS SO GREAT,
ISN'T IT?
BOY, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING
AND I'M BRINGING
YOU A GREAT GIFT,
50 BOXES OF EARRINGS
ALL LEFTS.
AND I KNOW THE GUYS
WHO LEFT THEM.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE.
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN, EVERYBODY.
SIT. SIT. SIT.
COME ON IN AND SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
OKAY, MEN,
THE DANDRUFF FOUNDATION
HAS A LITTLE RESEARCH
PROJECT GOING.
SO IF ANY OF YOU HAVE DANDRUFF
THEY WOULD LIKE YOU TO GIVE
THEM YOUR HEAD AFTER
YOU PASS ON,
OR YOU CAN SEND IT OVER NOW,
IF YOU'RE NOT USING IT.