(Car crashing)
(Siren)
IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
HERE HE IS, THE ANSWER
TO CANADA'S QUESTION,
"HOW TOUGH CAN IT BE
TO GET A SHOW ON TELEVISION?",
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
(Whistling)
THERE'S HAROLD.
HOW ARE YOU, HAROLD?
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WELL, THE BIG DAY
HAS FINALLY ARRIVED.
POSSUM LAKE'S ONLY BONA FIDE
MEDICAL MAN RETIRED TODAY.
WE STILL GOT DR. HARRIS.
HAROLD, DR. HARRIS IS A WOMAN.
DON'T TELL ME YOU GUYS
ARE THAT OLD-FASHIONED
AND INSECURE.
YES, WE ARE, HAROLD.
WHY DON'T YOU SEE DR. HARRIS?
I'VE GOT
NOTHING TO HIDE.
SO I HEARD.
(Horns honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): TODAY, GARTH HARBLE
HAS A DEER INSIDE HIS HOUSE.
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO MAKE
A BRAND-NEW GOLF CART
WITHOUT SPENDING 10 BUCKS,
AND BUZZ SHERWOOD HAS SOMETHING
TO PROTECT YOUR MELON.
I'M INVITING ANY DOCTOR
WATCHING THE SHOW
TO COME ON UP TO POSSUM LAKE.
THE ONLY DOCTORS WATCHING
THIS SHOW ARE PSYCHIATRISTS.
SAYS MR. CASE STUDY.
WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT YOU'LL BE REPLACING
OUR RESIDENT MEDICAL MAN,
DR. FINGER.
DR. FINGER'S THE ONE THAT LEFT?
HE'S A VETERINARIAN.
CURED OUR CAT OF WORMS.
WELL, SO WHAT, HAROLD?
PEOPLE TREAT PETS
LIKE MEMBERS OF THE FAMILY.
DR. FINGER TREATED THE FAMILY
LIKE PETS.
HE'S ONLY QUALIFIED TO TREAT
HAIRBALLS, FLEAS, AND MANGE.
CALL THEM BY THEIR RIGHT NAMES:
STINKY PETERSON, MOOSE
THOMPSON, AND OLD MAN SEDGWICK.
BILL'S RESPONSE
TO LOSING OUR DOCTOR
WAS TO TAKE THIS WEEK
AND SHOW YOU HOW TO BARBECUE
TO EAT MORE HEALTHY FOODS.
SEE WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE?
I COULD TELL BILL
THAT HE'S DOING THINGS WRONG
AND THAT HE HASN'T NOTICED
THE BARBECUE HAS LEFT,
BUT THERE'S NO POINT.
I'LL LET BILL SEE IT THROUGH.
I'M SURE HE'LL COME
TO THE CONCLUSION
THAT HE IS DOING SOMETHING
THAT IS NOT TOTALLY CORRECT.
MAYBE AN EYE DOCTOR
WOULD BE IN ORDER.
UH-OH!
OH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
AND THEN MAYBE
SOME BEHAVIOUR THERAPY.
DON'T WORRY -- WE'LL BE BACK
TO FINISH 'ER OFF.
RANGER GORD,
HAROLD HAS ARRANGED IT
SO THAT WE CAN PLAY
THE POSSUM LODGE
WORD-GUESSING GAME RIGHT HERE.
YES!
I'VE PLAYED THIS GAME BEFORE.
I NEVER RECEIVED
THE GIFTS I WON LAST TIME.
THEN YOU WON'T NEED TODAY'S
PRIZE -- A SHELVING UNIT.
OK, YEAH.
I'LL GET THE WORD.
DON'T PEEK, NOW.
I GOTTA SHOW THE PEOPLE.
OK.
I'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET YOU TO SAY THAT WORD.
READY?
PREPARED.
I HAVEN'T STARTED YET.
UM... ISOLATED.
HERO.
NO... DEPRESSED.
MARTYR.
ALONE.
UM... 16 YEARS.
FOREST RANGER.
OH, GROOVY.
NO, NO, NO, THE SAD PART.
LIGHTNING... OH, YEAH.
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
UM... YOU.
OH!
UH, HANDSOME.
NO.
UH, TRUSTWORTHY.
UH, LOYAL.
UH... UH... VIRGIN!
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
NOTHING.
I GIVE UP, I FORGET.
HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
WHAT'S THIS HERE?
(Strums acoustic guitar)
OHHH, FINGERS ARE HANDY,
YOU MUST UNDERSTAND
YOU CAN DO MORE THINGS
WITH YOUR FINGERS
THAN YOU CAN COUNT
ON ONE HAND
WORK WITH THEM,
POINT WITH THEM
PICK WITH THEM, SCRATCH
BUT IF YOU GIVE A BIG GUY
THE FINGER
YOU MAY NOT GET IT BACK
WITH DR. FINGER
FINALLY WASHING HIS HANDS --
OF HIS MEDICAL CAREER --
I'M GETTING HIM
A RETIREMENT GIFT.
I'M THINKING GOLF CART.
I COULD BUY ONE OF THEM
FANCY RIDING ONES,
BUT I'D HAVE TO FORGET
WHAT I THOUGHT OF DR. FINGER
OR I'D HAVE TO BE RICH
OR AN IDIOT OR BOTH.
INSTEAD, I'LL BUILD
ONE OF THOSE GOLF CARTS
THAT YOU PULL ALONG.
I NEED SOME PLASTIC PIPING
AND VARIOUS ODDS AND ENDS,
AND A KID'S BIKE,
LIKE THIS ONE.
FIRST, I GOTTA
GET THE WHEELS OFF.
TO DO THAT, I'LL RUN 'ER
AS FAST AS I CAN
INTO THAT BRICK WALL.
DONE.
MAYBE I SHOULD CUT BACK
ON DESSERTS.
YOU'RE GONNA PUT THESE
ON YOUR GOLF CART.
NORMAL GOLF CARTS HAVE
LITTLE WEE WHEELS,
BUT THEY'RE ONLY GOOD
FOR THE FAIRWAY.
HOW MANY OF US ARE EVER THERE?
NEXT, GET YOURSELF
A CAN OF SOUP.
OH!
MAKE THAT AN EMPTY CAN OF SOUP.
ATTACH THAT
TO ONE OF THE WHEELS
AND JUST USE ONE BOLT.
USE ONE BOLT
SO THE CAN STAYS LEVEL
AS THE WHEEL GOES AROUND.
YOU PUT WATER IN THERE
AND DROP YOUR BALL IN...
YOU HAVE A CONTINUOUS
BALL WASHER.
SOUNDS LIKE HEAVEN TO ME.
TAKE YOUR PIECES
OF PLASTIC PIPE, HERE,
AND YOU WANT TO CUT THESE
INTO ABOUT 30-INCH LENGTHS.
YOU CAN MEASURE, IF YOU LIKE.
I PREFER TO JUST EYEBALL.
WE GOT PLENTY THERE.
YOU COULD CUT THAT
WITH A FINE-TOOTH HACKSAW
OR A CARPET KNIFE.
LIKE I SAY, I NEVER
REALLY LIKED DR. FINGER.
YOU ATTACH ALL THOSE TOGETHER,
USING THE HANDYMAN'S
SECRET WEAPON, DUCT TAPE.
ALL RIGHT, REACH WAY DOWN
INTO YOUR BED
AND YOU COME UP WITH...
A HOT WATER BOTTLE.
IF YOU COME UP WITH SOMETHING
ELSE, CHANGE THE SHEETS.
YOU CUT THIS ALL THE WAY AROUND
AND STRETCH 'ER
OVER THE END OF THE TUBES.
BE CAREFUL -- WORKING WITH
RUBBER CAN BE TRICKY.
I HAVEN'T BEEN SLAPPED
THAT MANY TIMES SINCE THE PROM.
HERE'S HOW SHE WORKS.
GET A CLUB AND STICK THEM DOWN
INTO THESE TUBES
SO THE HANDLE RESTS
AGAINST THE RUBBER
OF THE HOT WATER BOTTLE.
WHEN YOU WANT A CLUB,
PUSH DOWN FIRMLY...
AND SHE POPS UP
INTO YOUR HANDS.
GET YOURSELF THE REST
OF THE PIPES
AND YOUR FISHING REEL
AND YOU'RE READY TO PUT
THE UNIT TOGETHER.
WE GOT OUR CLUBS IN THERE.
WE GOT OUR BALL WASHER.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU
ANOTHER FEATURE.
GET YOURSELF
A HEAVY-DUTY FISHING REEL,
MOUNT THAT ON THERE,
AND ON THE END OF THE LINE,
ATTACH A RUBBER HOSE WASHER
OUT OF YOUR HOSE.
WHEN YOU PULL THE CLUB OUT,
FIRST OF ALL,
FLIP THIS HOSE WASHER
OVER THE GRIP.
THAT WAY, IF THE SHOT
DOESN'T GO EXACTLY
THE WAY YOU WANTED IT TO
AND YOU'RE SLIPPING
INTO A BLINDING RAGE
AND TRYING TO THROW THE CLUB
TO THE MOON,
AFTER YOU COOL OFF,
ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS REEL
THE CLUB BACK IN...
UNLESS YOU NAILED SOMEBODY,
IN WHICH CASE, I WOULD SAY,
CUT THE LINE AND KEEP WALKING.
ANOTHER FEATURE I'VE GOT IS
I'VE ATTACHED A BOW SAW
TO THE HANDLE,
FOR WHEN YOUR BALL
GOES BEHIND A TREE.
YOU STAND BEHIND THE TREE
AND ROCK YOUR CART
BACK AND FORTH
WHILE YOU'RE MAKING YOUR CLUB
SELECTION, AND YOU'LL FIND
THE PROBLEM WILL PROBABLY
TAKE CARE OF ITSELF.
ANOTHER THING I GOT --
REALLY GREAT --
THE HANDLE IS ANOTHER PIECE
OF PLASTIC PIPING.
GOES DOWN INTO AN ELBOW
AND OUT A PIPE.
WHEN YOU'VE LOST YOUR BALL
OR PUT IT INTO THE WOODS
OR IT'S ON ANOTHER FAIRWAY
AND YOU WANT
TO KEEP THAT SECRET,
YOU KINDA GET CLOSE
AND DROP A BALL DOWN HERE
AND... OH!
THERE'S MY BALL THERE.
THERE'S YOUR SET OF GOLF CLUBS.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I THINK I'LL USE A FOUR IRON.
WONDER WHY THEY CALL IT
A FOUR IRON.
FORE!
(Glass
breaking)
NEXT, BUZZ SHERWOOD,
WHO'S ALWAYS IN THE CLOUDS,
BUT USUALLY WITH HIS PLANE.
GETTING A DOCTOR HERE
IS HARDER THAN WE THOUGHT.
THEY SAY THERE'S NO DEMAND.
WE'RE TOO HEALTHY.
PEOPLE PRETEND THEY'RE HEALTHY
TO AVOID SEEING DR. FINGER.
HE KEEPS YOU OVERNIGHT
IN A CAGE ON SOME NEWSPAPER.
WE'RE NOT HEALTHY HERE.
THERE'S ENOUGH SICKOS HERE TO
KEEP A M.A.S.H. UNIT HUMMING.
FLINTY McCLINTOCK HAS
THAT EYE THING.
STINKY PETERSON -- YOU GOTTA
HAVE SOMETHING WRONG WITH YOU
TO HAVE A NICKNAME
LIKE "STINKY".
WHAT ABOUT GIMPY O'HARA?
TYPHOID LARRY.
BLOTCHY WILLIAMS
AND HIS BLOTCHES.
LUMPY MITCHELL AND HIS LUMPS.
SCABBY JOHNSON AND HIS JOHNSON.
HI, THIS IS RANGER GORD,
STANDING ON GUARD FOR YOU
23 HOURS A DAY.
(Gunfire)
THE OTHER HOUR'S MY TIME!
MY TIME!
NO ONE IN YOUR FAMILY
HAS THE NERVE TO TELL YOU,
SO I WILL.
I'VE SEEN YOU DRIVING
THROUGH TOWN,
TURNING WITHOUT SIGNALLING,
DRIVING TOO SLOW,
TURNING RIGHT
FROM THE LEFT-HAND LANE,
PARKING WITH YOUR CAR
HALF UP ON THE SIDEWALK.
OK, HERE'S WHAT'S HAPPENING.
YOU'RE STARTING TO DRIVE
LIKE YOUR DAD.
(Audience laughing)
THERE'S NOTHING SCARIER
THAN A LITTLE MAN IN A BIG CAR
PEEKING UP OVER THE DASHBOARD
WITH A SOUR LOOK ON HIS FACE.
SOME PEOPLE SAY
THAT LOSING YOUR DRIVING SKILLS
IS JUST PART OF NATURE'S WAY
OF THINNING THE HERD.
(Laughing)
BUT I SAY, "GIVE IT UP,"
AND I SAY THAT,
KNOWING THAT YOU WON'T,
'CAUSE THE GUYS
I'M REFERRING TO
THINK I'M REFERRING
TO SOMEBODY ELSE.
HERE'S A SOLUTION
YOU CAN LIVE WITH.
AT OUR AGE, WE ONLY GO
TO FIVE DIFFERENT PLACES.
YOUR WORK, YOUR LODGE,
YOUR GROCERY STORE,
YOUR GAS STATION,
MAYBE YOUR CHURCH.
JUST MEMORIZE
THOSE FIVE ROUTES.
YOU'LL GO DOWN SO FAR,
YOU'LL PUT THE TURN SIGNAL ON,
YOU'LL TURN HERE,
YOU'LL STOP HERE.
DO EVERYTHING JUST BY MEMORY.
TRY TO KEEP UP
TO THE SPEED LIMIT.
THEY HAVE IT ON BIG SIGNS.
YOU GET THOSE FIVE ROUTES DOWN
AND DON'T GO ANYWHERE ELSE
EVER THE REST OF YOUR LIFE,
YOU'LL STOP BEING A MENACE.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
PEOPLE ALWAYS SAY SAFETY IS
NUMBER ONE AND HERE'S A FELLA
WHO'S PROBABLY COUNTING
BACKWARDS -- BUZZ SHERWOOD.
IT'S GOTTA BE SAFETY FIRST,
NO MATTER WHAT YOU'RE RUNNING
'CAUSE YOU NEVER KNOW
WHEN YOU'LL TOTAL IT.
I ALWAYS RECOMMEND
GET A GOOD HELMET.
THAT IS A VERY UNIQUE UNIT.
I MADE IT MYSELF.
KIND OF A PAPER.
IT'S LIKE PAPIER MACHE
THAT KIDS DO,
AND IT FITS AND IT WORKS.
HERE, LOOK -- SAY THIS MELON
IS MY HEAD.
OH, YEAH, SURE.
EXCEPT THIS IS GREEN
WITH NO HAIR ON IT.
YEAH, YEAH.
IT'S FULL OF JUICE AND SEEDS
AND I DON'T HAVE THE SEEDS.
YOU KNOW WHEN THESE GO RIPE
AND YOU GET THOSE FLIES
BUZZING AROUND
AND THEY DIE ON THE SOAP
IN THE BATHROOM?
YEAH.
I GET THOSE.
SO SAY THIS IS MY HEAD AND
SAY I'M OUT ON MY DUNE BUGGY.
I SEE, YEAH.
I'M GOING ACROSS THE COUNTRY
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
I WIPE OUT!
AHHHH! LOOK OUT!
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH, OH!
MY GOSH.
QUITE A BEATING, HUH?
WATCH THIS -- LOOK AT THAT.
FOR GOSH SAKES!
THIS MELON IS OK.
OH!
ISN'T THAT GREAT?
YOU WANT TO TRY IT?
UH, NO, BUT
I THINK HAROLD WOULD.
OH, COOL -- HAROLD, COME HERE.
PARTICIPATE, HAROLD --
THAT'S THE THING.
IF YOU'RE LOOSE,
YOU DON'T GET HURT.
SOMETIMES I'M SO LOOSE
I COULD DIE.
(Laughing)
OK, HERE WE GO.
HERE COMES THE SHERWOOD
PAPIER MACHE HELMET.
BRACE YOURSELF.
OH! OH!
(Moaning)
HAROLD, YOU OK?
I THINK HE'S PEOPLE MACHE.
I GOTTA PUT MORE GLUE
AND NEWSPAPER ON THAT SIDE,
RIGHT, HAROLD?
HERE'S A HANDYMAN HINT.
YOU HAVE DIFFERENT SCREW HEADS.
YOU'VE GOT THE SLOT HEAD.
THE STAR-SHAPED
OR PHILLIPS SCREW HEAD.
YOU HAVE THE SQUARE HOLE,
OR AS WE CALL IT IN CANADA,
THE ROBERTSON SCREW HEAD.
EVEN HAVE MACHINE SCREWS
THAT TAKE AN ALLEN KEY.
FOR ALL THESE SCREW HEADS,
I RECOMMEND THE FLAT HEAD.
REMEMBER, ANY TOOL
CAN BE THE RIGHT TOOL.
THE MEDICAL CRISIS IS OVER.
WE GOT OURSELVES A DOCTOR.
AW, GREAT -- WHO DID YOU GET?
THE GUY WHO ANSWERED THE AD.
CHECK OUT THE RESUME.
GOT HIM FROM PORT ASBESTOS.
ARE WE STEALING
THEIR DOCTOR?
NO, HE WASN'T PRACTISING
MEDICINE IN PORT ASBESTOS.
HE WAS A BARTENDER.
HE'S GOT A MEDICAL DEGREE.
SIGNED BY
SALLY STRUTHERS.
YEAH, SO?
HE WAS EIGHT YEARS
AT A TROPICAL RESORT.
HA! CLUB TANABANANA.
I'M SURE THOSE RESORT DOCTORS
TREAT A VARIETY OF ILLNESSES.
WELL, HE WAS THE LIFEGUARD.
LOOK, HE'S GOT OTHER DEGREES.
V.C.R. REPAIR,
FURNACE RENOVATIONS...
WHAT'S THAT GOT TO DO
WITH ANYTHING?
HE PROBABLY MAKES HOUSE CALLS.
(Buzz): HAROLD!
HAROLD, YOU OK?
HAROLD, WHOA!
I HAD NO IDEA IT WOULD DO THAT
AFTER I LIT IT.
MAN, YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN IT.
IT ROCKETED
RIGHT OVER YOUR HEAD.
YOU DIDN'T SEE IT,
BUT MAN, IT WENT... IT WENT...
IT WENT TO THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE LAKE.
BUT YOU'RE OK, RIGHT?
COME ON, MAN, TALK TO ME.
HOW DO YOU MAKE YOUR EYES
GO LIKE THAT?
HAROLD?
(Red): ALL RIGHT, HERE IT IS.
GOOD OLD BILL
AND HIS BARBECUE SPECIAL.
GOT THE WIENIES OUT.
THAT'S THEM FOR SURE.
HE'S GONNA DO SOME BARBECUING.
BILL HASN'T DONE BARBECUING
FOR A WHILE.
HE PUTS THE BRIQUETTES IN
AND HE PUTS THE STARTER ON
AND YOU CAN TELL
WHEN A FELLA HASN'T BARBECUED
FOR A WHILE, AND HE HAS
HIS OWN SPECIAL-- WHAT IS THAT?
10W30, IN CASE WE HAVE
A COLD SNAP.
THROWS THAT ON THERE.
HE'S EVEN GOT
THE PARAFFIN SOAP... NITRO...
THE REASON I KNEW
HE HADN'T BARBECUED FOR A WHILE
IS THAT THIS IS ACTUALLY
A PROPANE BARBECUE.
TURN THE GAS ON
AND THEN THERE'S...
THERE'S SOME CONTROLS.
YOU GOT TWO BURNERS --
YOU CAN CONTROL
EITHER BURNER, ANYWAY,
SO BILL, HE'S MORE OF
A DOER THAN A THINKER --
BOY, THAT PROPANE'S
GOT A-- WHAT?
UH-OH... UH...
NO, TURN IT OFF AT THE TANK.
JUST TURN THAT, TURN THAT...
OH!
UM...
ALL RIGHT, UH...
NO, NO, BILL -- SPARKS!
AHHHHH!
(Red): OH.
OHHH...
(Red): LATER THAT DAY,
BILL AND I ARE WONDERING
WHERE THE BARBECUE IS.
OH, THERE'S THE TABLE.
AND, UH...
THERE'S WIENIES
AS FAR AS THE EYE CAN SEE.
OOH! AHHH...
STUFF'S DROPPING
OUT OF THE SKY.
WHAT IS THAT STRANGE
BIRD-LIKE THING DROPPING?
OH, IT'S THE BARBECUE LID.
WOW.
ALL RIGHT,
WE GOT EVERYTHING BACK.
OH, BOY.
WELL, THAT'S RARE.
IT'S CERTAINLY
NOT WELL-DONE, ANYWAY.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
GARTH'S GONNA TAKE A DEER
OUT OF HIS HOUSE.
OUR NEW DOCTOR
SET UP HIS PRACTICE.
HE RENTED THE OLD
MR. TASTY-FREEZE STAND.
YOU KNOW THE BIG
MR. TASTY-FREEZE?
THAT FAT MAN HOLDING
THE BUTTERSCOTCH SUNDAE.
THAT SUNDAE IS NOW A BEDPAN.
HE COULDN'T AFFORD A NEW SIGN
SO FROM NOW ON,
WE'LL CALL HIM
DR. TASTY-FREEZE.
DR. TASTY-FREEZE COULDN'T
AFFORD MEDICAL EQUIPMENT.
HE SOLD IT TO PAY
FOR BARTENDING COLLEGE.
HE HAS TO USE THE EQUIPMENT
AT THE TASTY-FREEZE.
ONE GUY HAD A BROKEN ARM
AND CAME OUT
WITH A BANANA SPLINT.
I DON'T KNOW,
HAROLD.
MOOSE THOMPSON SAYS
DR. TASTY-FREEZE IS GREAT.
HE'S JUST FAKING IT
FOR THE ICE CREAM.
I'M NO DOCTOR,
BUT I DON'T THINK
A PEANUT BUSTER BROWNIE PARFAIT
IS ANY CURE FOR GOUT.
DO YOU WANT ANYBODY OPERATING
ON YOU WITH PLASTIC CUTLERY?
I LIKE THE IDEA
OF GOING TO SOMEBODY
NAMED DR. TASTY-FREEZE.
YOU WON'T WHEN YOU FEEL
HOW COLD HIS FINGER IS.
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL,
SHOWING YOU HOW TO MAINTAIN
MAN'S DOMINANCE
OVER THE WILD BEASTS.
SPEAKING OF WILD BEASTS...
COME ON IN HERE, RED!
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT FOR US?
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
SOMETHING SPECIAL, RED.
I'M GOING TO TAKE
THIS OPPORTUNITY
TO SHOW YOU HOW TO GET A DEER
OUT OF YOUR HOUSE.
(Crashing and banging)
HOLY MACKEREL! WOW!
WELL, DON'T WORRY, RED.
IT'S NOT THAT HARD TO GET
A DEER OUT OF YOUR HOUSE.
IT'S A LOT EASIER THAN, SAY,
GETTING A MUSKRAT OUT.
OH, OH.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
ALL I NEED IS A FLASHLIGHT,
A BRIGHT FLASHLIGHT.
SORT OF LIKE A HEADLIGHT.
SURE, THE WAY A DEER--
WHOA, WHOA!
THE WAY A DEER WILL FREEZE
IN THE HEADLIGHTS.
EXACTLY!
(Crashing and banging)
ALL RIGHT, DEER, WHERE ARE YOU?
OH, GREAT!
DRINKING OUT OF MY AQUARIUM!
FREEZE!
GOTCHA!
HELLO, DEER!
I'M HOME!
ALL RIGHT.
(Deer panting)
EASY, NOW, EASY.
GET OUT THERE.
AH... WHOA!
CAREFUL, CAREFUL, CAREFUL.
DON'T DO THAT.
HOLY MACKEREL.
ALL RIGHT.
WOW, THAT'S GOOD WORK.
ALL I DO IS TAKE HIM BACK OUT
INTO THE WOODS AND, UH...
KEEP A STEP BACK SO I DON'T GET
KICKED BY HIS HOOVES,
AND THEN I TURN OFF
THE FLASHLIGHT.
FOR GOSH SAKES --
BOY, THAT WORKS GREAT.
IT SURE DOES.
MIGHT EVEN WORK
ON YOU, RED.
REALLY?
(Kicking)
OH! OW!
OHHH...
THAT WAS A SCAR!
OH!
EEE! OH!
OW! OW! OW!
GET UP -- RUN!
OH, ANOTHER
SUPER DAY!
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION.
THIS WEEK, WE HAVE TWO EXPERTS:
MY UNCLE RED
AND HIS BEST FRIEND,
MR. DALTON HUMPHREY.
(Applause and cheering)
(Whistling)
HERE'S THE LETTER HERE.
IT GOES AS FOLLOWS:
"DEAR EXPERTS..."
"WHAT IS AN APPROPRIATE
"WEDDING GIFT WHEN IT'S
THE THIRD TIME FOR THE GROOM
"AND THE FOURTH FOR THE BRIDE?"
WELL, HOW ABOUT ONE OF THEM
DO-IT-YOURSELF DIVORCE KITS?
GOT THE LITTLE SIGN
ON THERE --
"SOME DISASSEMBLY REQUIRED".
(Laughing)
NO, RED, WHEN
A WEDDING
IS THE Nth TIME AROUND,
LIKE THIS ONE IS,
YOU WANT TO GET SOMETHING
THAT WILL CAPTURE THE FEELINGS
OF THE BRIDE AND GROOM.
ALL RIGHT.
I WOULD SUGGEST SOMETHING USED.
(Audience laughing)
OR AS WE SAY
IN THE ANTIQUE BUSINESS,
"PREVIOUSLY ENJOYED".
(Audience laughing)
WHEN A COUPLE'S
BEEN MARRIED A LOT,
THEY'VE GOT
ALL THE WEDDING GIFTS.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WITH A DOZEN TOASTERS?
I GUESS YOU COULD HEAT
YOUR HOUSE.
WHAT SETTINGS
ARE YOU GONNA PUT THEM ON?
WELL, IF IT'S NIGHT,
YOU SET IT FOR "DARK".
(Laughing and applause)
YOU KNOW...
Y-Y-YOU KNOW,
A COUPLE THAT'S
BEEN MARRIED BEFORE
MAY NOT BE SO HARD TO SHOP FOR,
ESPECIALLY IF
THEY'VE BEEN WIPED OUT
IN A PREVIOUSLY MESSY DIVORCE.
GREAT TO BUY FOR SOMEBODY
WHO'S HAD A TERRIBLE
PERSONAL TRAGEDY LIKE THAT.
YEAH!
ANYTHING --
THEY'LL TAKE ANYTHING!
YEAH!
(Red): YEAH, I LOVE THAT.
YEAH.
SAD, THOUGH -- IT'S SAD.
(Laughing)
GOD, IT'S A SHAME.
I'VE GOT--
YOU GUYS ARE AWFUL.
YOU'RE SO CYNICAL.
YOU MAKE MARRIAGE SOUND SO
CHEAP AND COLD AND USED AND--
NO, NO, NO,
NOT "USED", HAROLD.
"PREVIOUSLY ENJOYED."
(Laughing and applause)
GARTH HARBLE HERE,
ANIMAL CONTROL.
YOU KNOW, CONTRARY
TO POPULAR FOLKLORE,
BATS WILL NOT SUCK THE BLOOD
OUT OF YOUR BODY.
THAT'S YOUR BOSS'S JOB.
(Laughing)
OUR MEDICAL CRISIS IS OVER.
DR. TASTY-FREEZE
WAS A HUGE SUCCESS.
WHEN HE STARTED USING
A THERMOMETER
WITH A MARASCHINO CHERRY
ON TOP,
EVERYBODY SAID,
"NO, I'M FEELING FINE."
I THINK
DR. TASTY-FREEZE
IS GOING BACK TO BARTENDING.
FOR MY HERNIA CHECK-UP,
HE ASKED IF I WANTED IT
WITH A TWIST.
WELL, DOESN'T MATTER, ANYWAY.
JUNIOR SINGLETON FOUND A DOCTOR
OVER IN PORT SANDBAR.
DR. TUNA OR DR. TWOFUN
OR SOMETHING...
DR. TUNE-UP?
DR. TUNE-UP, YEAH.
THAT'S NOT A DOCTOR'S OFFICE.
THAT'S A GARAGE FOR CARS.
ALL'S I KNOW IS HE GOT HIS
PLUGS, POINTS, AND FLUIDS DONE
FOR $19.95, AND
THEY FIXED HIS CAR.
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME,
UNCLE RED.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M FEELING GREAT
FOR A MAN OF MY AGE.
I'M CURIOUS ABOUT HOW YOU FEEL
FOR A WOMAN YOUR AGE.
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause)
(Possum squeal)
ALL RISE, ALL RISE.
THE PRESIDENT'S
IN THE ROOM NOW.
QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORITATI.