GUYS AREN'T REALLY GOOD AT
DOING TWO THINGS AT ONCE.
THAT'S WHY YOU'LL NEVER SEE US
SIMULTANEOUSLY HAVE DINNER
AND MAKE CONVERSATION,
OR DRIVE AND
LOOK AT A MAP,
OR GO SHOPPING AND SMILE.
WHEN WE SIT DOWN
IN OUR FAVOURITE CHAIR,
WE'RE THERE FOR
ONE OF TWO REASONS...
EITHER TO READ THE PAPER
OR TO WATCH TELEVISION.
THE PROBLEM IS THESE
DAYS THE GENIUSES WHO
BROADCAST THE SHOWS
ARE ALWAYS FILLING UP
THE BOTTOM OF THE SCREEN
WITH WORDS TO DISTRACT US.
LIKE WEATHER WARNINGS
AND URGENT NEWS UPDATES
AND OTHER STUFF THAT HAS
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING TO DO
WITH GILLIGAN'S CHANCES OF
GETTING OFF THE ISLAND.
SO HERE'S WHAT YOU DO...
GET YOURSELF ONE OF
THESE OLD, TOP LOADING VCRs
AND THEN DUCT TAPE A METAL
RULER ONTO THE TAPE
LOADING MECHANISM.
NOW THE NEXT TIME MY FAVOURITE
SHOW IS RUDELY INTERRUPTED
BY REALITY,
I JUST HIT THE
EJECT BUTTON,
AND I'M BACK
IN FANTASY LAND.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
TAKE A LOOK AT
THIS BABY, HUH?
YOU EVER SEE A BIT THAT LONG?
I CAN DRILL HOLES IN THE WALL
WITHOUT EVEN GETTING
OUT OF MY RECLINER.
MAN, I LOVE TOOLS.
HI, UNCLE RED!
WELL,
NOT ALL TOOLS.
WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM.
YEAH, WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM.
'CAUSE I WAS
OUT MEASURING,
YOU KNOW,
WITH MY SPIRIT LEVEL,
AND I REALISE NOW THAT
THE LODGE IS OUT OF PLUM.
INDOOR PLUMB
OR OUTDOOR PLUM?
BOTH!
YEAH, THE WHOLE LODGE
LEANS A LITTLE TO
THE LEFT.
HAROLD,
THIS IS CANADA.
EVERYTHING LEANS A
LITTLE TO THE LEFT.
YEAH, OKAY, BUT I
THINK YOU REALLY --
YOU GOTTA DO
SOMETHING, THOUGH,
BEFORE IT TURNS
INTO A SERIOUS PROBLEM.
OH, HAROLD,
GEE, YOU KNOW,
STOP LOOKIN' FOR
THINGS TO WORRY ABOUT.
WELL, YOU THINK IF
YOU IGNORE PROBLEMS,
THEY'LL GO AWAY.
WELL, IT HASN'T
WORKED SO FAR.
UNCLE RED,
WE ARE NOT LEVEL.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
OF THE WAY YOU'RE
HOLDING THE THING.
IF YOU LIE IT DOWN ON
THE FLOOR, IT'LL BE
PERFECT.
OH, REALLY?
SURE, IT'LL BE FINE.
LOOK. YOU LOOK.
LOOK. LOOK. LOOK.
SEE?
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FROM SUPER SUCK
INSTALLED VACUUM SYSTEMS
FOR THEIR HOME
LIPOSUCTION KIT,
FOR YOUR MAT, YOUR CAT
AND YOUR EXCESS FAT.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
THINGIES, DALTON.
UH, MR. GREEN, YOU HAVE
30 SECONDS OR ONE-HALF MINUTE,
WHICHEVER COMES FIRST,
TO GET DALTON HUMPHREY
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
MIKE.
AND... GO!
OKAY, DALTON, YOU TELL SOMEBODY
YOU'RE GONNA DO SOMETHING
AND YOU CAN COUNT ON IT,
THAT IS A...
LIE.
OKAY, REMEMBER WE SAW THAT
GIRL SINGER AT THE
AMATEUR SHOW?
WE ALL SAID SHE
SHOWED A LOT OF...
CLEAVAGE.
OKAY, THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
YOUR PARENTS ALWAYS TOLD YOU
TO KEEP YOUR...
PANTS ON.
NO, OKAY. OKAY.
WHEN YOU AND ANN MARIE
EXCHANGED MARRIAGE VOWS
THAT WAS A...
HORRIBLE MISTAKE.
NO, OKAY, NO, I'M SAYING
YOU MARRIED ANN MARIE
BECAUSE SHE
GAVE YOU HER...
ULTIMATUM.
ALMOST OUTTA
TIME, MR. GREEN.
NO, DALTON, ANN MARIE VOWED
TO LOVE, HONOUR AND OBEY,
AND THAT WAS A...
FANTASY.
I PROMISE YOU THAT.
THERE WE GO!
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT
PORTION OF THE SHOW.
IT'S THE PART OF THE PROGRAMME
WHERE WE EXAMINE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
IT'S FUNNY COZ IT'S TRUE.
OKAY, TODAY'S LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS..."
LA LA LA.
"MY ADULT SON RECENTLY
MOVED BACK HOME
"AFTER QUITTING A SERIES OF
UNREWARDING JOBS.
"MY WIFE AND I
ARE HAPPY TO SEE HIM
"AND PLEASED TO HELP HIM OUT.
"ONE QUESTION: HOW LONG DO WE
HAVE TO KEEP THIS ACT UP?"
WELL, I FIGURE THAT LETTER
TOOK THREE OR FOUR DAYS
TO GET HERE,
SO I WOULD SAY
YOUR WORK IS DONE.
WELL, THIS FELLA'S BOY
SOUNDS A BIT LIKE
MY SON ORVILLE.
OH, YEAH?
ORVILLE HAS TROUBLE
HOLDING DOWN A JOB?
HOLDING DOWN A SANDWICH.
HE DON'T HAVE WHAT THEY
CALL YOUR WORK "ETHNIC."
WORK IS "OBSOLETELY"
FOREIGN TO HIM.
A BIT LAZY,
IS HE, CHARLIE?
HE DON'T DO ENOUGH
TO BE LAZY.
HE'S MORE IN THE
COMATOSE CATEGORY.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
I THINK PARENTS GOTTA
LEARN TO BE MORE PATIENT,
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE SOMETIMES
IT TAKES A WHILE
FOR A CHILD
TO FIND HIMSELF.
ORVILLE'S NOT EVEN
LOOKIN' FOR IT.
WELL, TO ME, IT STARTS
WITH GETTING A JOB,
BECAUSE ONCE YOU
MAKE AN INCOME,
THE GUY CAN START
TO FIND HIS OWN WAY.
THAT'S KINDA WHAT I DID.
REALLY?
WHAT JOB WAS THAT?
I DON'T REMEMBER
YOU EVER HAVING A JOB.
WELL, I MARRIED
BERNICE, HAROLD.
THAT'S A VOCATION
WITH NO VACATION.
WELL, I WOULDN'T MIND
SO MUCH IF THE
YOUNG PEOPLE
WOULD AT LEAST HELP
OUT A LITTLE BIT
AFTER THEY MOVE
BACK HOME.
I MEAN REAL HELP,
NOT WHAT ORVILLE DOES,
SITTIN' AROUND ALL DAY
IN HIS UNDERWEAR,
SAYING THAT'S HIS WAY OF
CUTTING DOWN ON THE LAUNDRY.
VALEDA'S CHURCH GROUP
FINDS IT TERRIBLY DISTRACTING.
AND IT CAN'T BE GOOD
FOR THE HOUSE PLANTS.
OH! OH!
I HAVE AN IDEA!
WHY NOT SEND HIM
HERE TO THE LODGE?
YEAH. BECAUSE THERE'S
ALWAYS THINGS AROUND HERE
THAT NEED FIXING
AND APOLOGIZING FOR.
OKAY, CHARLIE, I THINK
WHAT HAROLD MEANS IS
THAT IF ORVILLE COMES
HERE TO THE LODGE,
THEN HAROLD WOULD
GO AND STAY WITH YOU.
ARE YOU FAMILIAR WITH THE
EXPRESSION FAIR EXCHANGE?
ARE YOU FAMILIAR
WITH THE EXPRESSION,
NOT A SNOWBALL'S
CHANCE IN HELL?
WELL, SEE,
THERE'S YOUR ANSWER.
MAKE THE BEST OF
THE ORVILLE YOU HAVE,
BECAUSE THERE COULD BE A
HAROLD RIGHT AROUND
THE CORNER.
YOU KNOW, MARRIAGE
IS A COMPROMISE.
IF YOU'RE MARRIED,
YOU'RE COMPROMISED.
SO YOU END UP MAKING DEALS.
YOU KNOW, TRADE-OFFS.
LIKE IN MY CASE, FOR EVERY
TEN VEHICLES I BRING HOME,
MY WIFE IS ALLOWED
TO RENOVATE THE KITCHEN.
ON THE PLUS SIDE, BERNICE SAYS
I CAN USE ALL THIS OLD STUFF
TO BUILD ANYTHING I WANT,
AS LONG AS YOU CAN'T
SEE IT FROM THE STREET.
SO I'M THINKIN' IF I COULD USE
THE DISCARDED APPLIANCES
AND WHAT HAVE YOU
TO CUSTOMIZE ONE OF THE
VEHICLES THAT CAUSED THE
PROBLEM IN THE FIRST PLACE,
HEY, THAT'S THE CLOSEST A GUY
LIKE ME EVER GETS TO WINNING.
AND THE BEST PART ABOUT
RENOVATING YOUR VEHICLE
WITH KITCHEN FIXTURES
IS YOU'RE ONLY LIMITED
BY YOUR OWN IMAGINATION.
[ SNORING ]
OKAY, LET'S SAY YOU NEED TO
REPLACE THE OLD HOOD ORNAMENT
BECAUSE THE ORIGINAL ONE WAS
STOLEN, OR MAYBE IT BROKE OFF.
MAYBE WHEN YOU WENT FOR
SUPPER AT BOZO'S FAST
FOOD DRIVE-THRU
AND YOU CAUGHT THE HOOD
ORNAMENT IN ONE OF THE
CLOWN'S NOSTRILS.
WHO HASN'T DONE THAT?
OKAY, SO IF YOU'RE
A BUICK MAN,
YOU MIGHT WANNA GO WITH
SOMETHING TALL AND THIN,
LIKE THIS MEAT THERMOMETER.
PERSONALLY, I'VE ALWAYS
WANTED TO DRIVE A JAG.
SO I STUCK THE OLD KITCHEN
FAUCET ON THERE,
BECAUSE IF I EVER
DO BUY A JAG,
I'LL BE TAPPED OUT.
OF COURSE, NOW,
THE FAUCET DOESN'T RUN.
BUT HEY, IT'S A JAGUAR.
NEXT I WANNA JAZZ UP
MY OLD RIMS
WITH SOMETHING STYLISH,
SOMETHING UNIQUE.
I'M THINKIN'
STOVE TOP ELEMENTS.
THE ONLY WAY THIS
BABY'LL EVER BURN RUBBER.
NOW, AT THE BACK OF THE CAR
YOU'VE GOT A COUPLE
OF OPTIONS.
IF YOU'RE A YOUNG, RICH KID,
YOU'RE PROBABLY SPOILED.
YOU'RE GONNA
WANNA HAVE A SPOILER.
HOW ABOUT THE
OVEN HOOD, HUH?
THE BEAUTY THERE IS,
IF YOUR CAR BURNS OIL,
YOU CAN ALWAYS TURN ON
THE EXHAUST FAN.
OR MAYBE YOU'RE INTO THE
WHOLE RETRO NOSTALGIA CRAZE.
WELL, THEN MAYBE YOU
NEED A RUMBLE SEAT.
OKAY, YOU MIGHT WANNA
TEST THESE FIRST
WITH SOME KIND OF BALUST
TO MAKE SURE THEY DON'T
FALL OFF AT HIGH SPEED.
HAROLD!
I'VE GONE AHEAD
AND REPLACED
THE DOOR THAT STICKS
ON MY GLOVE COMPARTMENT.
IN FACT I REPLACED
THE WHOLE COMPARTMENT
WITH THIS EASY
TO OPEN BREAD BOX.
I'VE ALSO EXPANDED MY CAR'S
BEVERAGE HOLDING CAPACITY
WITH THIS TRAY
FROM MY DISHWASHER.
HOW MANY DOUGHNUTS CAN YOU
GET IN YOUR CUP HOLDER?
AND THAT'S NOT A EUPHEMISM.
OH, AND ONE MORE THING...
THE NEXT TIME
YOU GET PULLED OVER,
AND YOU WILL
GET PULLED OVER,
NO MORE FUMBLING
AROUND IN YOUR WALLET
FOR YOU LICENSE
AND REGISTRATION.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD --
OH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
YOU EVER WANTED
A TINTED WINDOW?
WELL, GUESS WHAT?
IF YOU'VE GOT AN OVEN DOOR,
YOU GOT ONE.
LOOKS PRETTY HOT,
DOESN'T IT?
NOT THE FIRST TIME
I'VE DRIVEN A HOT CAR.
WANNA TALK TO YOU OLDER GUYS
ABOUT NOT BEING THE CENTER
OF ATTENTION ANYMORE,
NOT AT WORK,
NOT AT HOME,
NOT EVEN AT
THE POLICE STATION.
AND WE WERE RIGHT THERE,
WEREN'T WE, HUH?
I MEAN, MUSIC, TV,
MOVIES, LITERATURE,
IT ALL REVOLVED
AROUND US,
BECAUSE WE WERE THE BABY
BOOMERS, HUH?
WELL, BABY,
WE BOOMED.
AND IT'S A TOUGH ADJUSTMENT
WHEN THE ADVERTISERS
DON'T CARE
ABOUT YOU ANYMORE.
ESPECIALLY AFTER
WE DID OUR PART,
BUYING THE PET ROCKS
AND THE PATTY STACKERS
AND ALL THOSE ABBA ALBUMS.
WELL, I'M BETTIN' YOU CAN
HEAR THE DRUMS, FERNANDO,
'CAUSE THERE ARE
50 MILLION NEW KIDS IN TOWN
AND WE'RE HANGING ON BY
THE SKIN OF OUR DENTURES.
OKAY, SO POP CULTURE
HAS PASSED US BY.
SO WHAT?
WE'RE NOT OLD;
WE'RE CLASSIC.
WE'RE RETRO.
WE'RE SO OUT WE'RE IN.
LET MADISON AVENUE
JUST BARREL ON OUTTA SIGHT.
THEY'VE MOVED ON TO
THE NEXT GENERATION,
WELL, SO HAVE WE.
NOW THAT OUR KIDS HAVE KIDS,
WE HAVE SOMETHING
BETTER THAN POP CULTURE,
WE GOT GRANDPOP CULTURE.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, THERE ARE A
LOT OF WAYS TO GET RICH,
BUT MOST OF THEM INVOLVE
HARD WORK AND PERSEVERANCE.
WHERE'S THE FUN IN THAT?
BUT IF YOU'RE
LAZY ENOUGH,
YOU CAN FIND
ANOTHER PATH TO WEALTH.
WHAT IF YOU COULD GET ONE
APPLIANCE TO DO THE JOB OF TWO?
HUH? WOULDN'T
THAT SAVE YOU MONEY?
WHICH IS THE SAME
AS BEING RICH...
SORT OF.
OKAY, HERE WE HAVE
A FRESH LOAD OF LAUNDRY,
WHICH IS NOW SUPPOSED TO
GO INTO AN EXPENSIVE DRYER.
BUT I'M NOT GONNA DO THAT.
I'M GONNA PUT IT
INTO THIS OLD FISH NET.
OH, SURE,
IT'S NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO HOLD PERCH
OR PICKEREL ANYMORE,
BUT I THINK IT CAN
HANDLE A LOAD OF FRILLIES.
NOW WATCH AND LEARN HOW THE
EXPERIENCED FISHERMAN
CAN TURN A WASHER
INTO A DRYER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ RED HUFFING AND
PUFFING ]
WELL, THE LODGE
IS SINKING FAST.
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
SAYING THAT FOR YEARS.
I TELL YOU, IT'S REALLY
CUTTING INTO THE BEER
CONSUMPTION
BECAUSE YOU GET
THE GLASS HALF FULL,
SHE STARTS SPILLING
RIGHT OVER THE SIDE.
UNCLE RED. UNCLE RED.
YOU OKAY?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, OKAY.
OKAY.
THERE WE GO.
I GOT THE QUOTE FROM
FLINTY McCLINTOCK.
HE SAYS HE CAN JACK
THE LODGE BACK UP
FOR $37,000.
$37,000!
HE'S JACKIN' UP
MORE THAN THE LODGE!
WELL, WHAT DO
YOU WANNA DO?
OH, MAN, HAROLD.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT
THAT BAD.
YOU TAKE OFF ONE SHOE,
YOU LEAN A LITTLE.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S NOT BAD.
ALL THESE YEARS,
I THOUGHT THAT
BEAR WAS DEAD.
HOW DID THIS
HAPPEN, HAROLD?
WELL, OBVIOUSLY THE
LAND UNDER THE LODGE
IS TOO SOFT TO SUPPORT
THE LODGE ITSELF.
WELL, IS THAT
THE LODGE'S FAULT,
OR IS THAT THE
GROUND'S FAULT?
IT'S YOUR FAULT.
POSSUM LODGE
HAS LIKE 100 YEARS
OF ENVIRONMENTAL
INFRACTIONS AGAINST IT.
YOU KNOW, FINALLY IT'S
CAUSED A BIG POCKET
OF AIR OR GAS
OR SOMETHING
UNDERNEATH THE LODGE,
AND NOW, YOU KNOW,
IT'S SINKING.
HAROLD, YOU KNOW,
WHEN I ASK YOU
A QUESTION,
I WANNA HEAR GOOD NEWS,
NOT THE TRUTH.
NO, NO!
I'M NOT GIVING UP.
I'M GONNA FIND SOME WAY
TO STRAIGHTEN THE LODGE.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
DO WITH THAT?
I DUNNO.
I JUST THINK BETTER
WHEN I'M DRILLIN' HOLES.
[ APPLAUSE ]
Red: WE WERE CLEANIN' UP SOME
LEAVES OUT BEHIND THE LODGE.
YOU KNOW, JUST KINDA FILLIN'
IN ON A SATURDAY THERE.
AND THE THING
WITH LEAVES IS
YOU GOTTA PICK YOUR SPOT.
AND DALTON WAS
OVER IN MY AREA,
SO I PUSHED HIM
AWAY A BIT,
AND THEN HE DECIDED
TO MOVE INTO WINSTON'S AREA,
AND WINSTON THOUGHT INSTEAD OF
RAKING THEM OFF THE LAWN
HE'D SKIP THE MIDDLE MAN
AND GO RIGHT INTO THE
TREE FOR THE LEAVES.
AND HE HOOKED ONTO AN OLD
BEEHIVE THERE.
DOWN SHE COMES,
AND WE'RE --
WE HEAR A BUZZ,
BUT YOU KNOW, I'M THINKIN',
THAT BUZZ IS NOT COMIN'
FROM THE BEE --
THAT BEEHIVE IS DEAD.
THERE'S A BUZZ COMIN'
FROM SOMEWHERE ELSE.
AND THEN WE
REALISE WHAT IT IS.
IT'S WALTER WITH ONE
OF THOSE GAS POWERED
LEAF BLOWER THINGS.
AND HE GOES OVER
TO THE HIVE.
IT FLIES THROUGH
THE AIR, RIGHT IN --
WELL, NOW WE GET
AN IDEA, SEE.
SOMETHING LIKE BROOM BALL,
EXCEPT CALLED
"VROOM" BALL.
GET THE GAS POWERED
LEAF BLOWERS.
GOT A GOAL AT EACH END.
AND WALTER AND DALTON
ARE ON THE ONE TEAM,
WINSTON AND I
ARE ON THE OTHER TEAM.
SO IT'S VROOM BALL
NIGHT IN CANADA
AND DROP THE HIVE
AND AWAY WE GO.
AND WALTER, A LITTLE
QUESTIONABLE PLAY THERE.
HE TAKES OFF AND
HE'S HEADIN' FOR --
WINSTON'S THERE AND --
DEFENCE, DEFENCE, DEFENCE.
ILLEGAL!
THAT'S HIGH STICKING.
AND DOWN HE GOES.
AND THEN DALTON
AND I ARE TAKIN' --
WHAT I NOTICED,
I HAD THE DELUXE UNIT,
WHICH HAD NOT ONLY THE
BLOW SETTING ON IT,
BUT ALSO HAD
THE SUCK SETTING,
SO IT'S GREAT FOR DEFENCE.
AND.. IT JUST...
NOW I SWITCH
HER OVER TO BLOW
AND FIRE AWAY OFF
WINSTON'S HAT.
WE GOT A GOAL!
[ CHUCKLING ]
HEY, HEY, HEY.
THAT'S
UNSPORTSMANLIKE CONDUCT.
TWO MINUTES.
OH, BOY.
AH, YOU OL' BLOWHARD.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, PAINTING
THE OUTSIDE OF YOUR HOUSE
IS A JOB THAT CAN
RUIN YOUR SUMMER
OR YOUR MARRIAGE
OR BOTH.
EATS UP YOUR FREE TIME
AND IT REQUIRES
A LOT OF WORK.
AND IF YOU'RE LIKE ME,
YOU LIKE TO HAVE A
LOT OF THE FIRST
AND PRETTY MUCH
NONE OF THE SECOND.
OH, SURE, I SUPPOSE YOU
COULD PAY SOMEBODY TO
PAINT YOUR HOUSE.
BUT IF YOU'RE
WATCHIN' THIS SHOW,
YOU'RE PROBABLY MORE OF A
SELF-SERVE GAS KIND OF GUY.
SO HERE ARE A FEW WAYS TO
ACTUALLY MAKE THIS JOB
ENJOYABLE.
JUST DON'T LET YOUR WIFE KNOW
YOU'RE HAVING A GOOD TIME.
IF SHE WANTED
YOU TO HAVE FUN,
SHE WOULD NEVER
HAVE MARRIED YOU.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WELL, I WAS OUT DRILLING
HOLES IN THE BIG PINE TREE
OUT BEHIND
THE LODGE THERE,
AND THAT'S WHEN IT HIT ME.
I MEAN, WE'RE TRYING TO
JACK UP THE LODGE FROM
UNDERNEATH,
BUT WE COULD ALSO PULL
IT UP FROM ON TOP.
SO I LOOK UP AND
I SEE A GREAT BIG BRANCH
COMING OFF
THAT VERY SAME TREE,
I MEAN, THAT GOES RIGHT
OVER THE PEAK OF THE ROOF.
I REMEMBER MY SUNDAY SCHOOL
TEACHER SAYING,
YOU ALWAYS LOOK FOR
SIGNS FROM UP ABOVE,
AND SO FAR IT HAD ONLY
BEEN PIGEON DROPPINGS.
OKAY, UNCLE RED,
I GOT IT --
YOU ALL RIGHT?
NOT A PROBLEM.
EASY. EASY. EASY.
I GOT THE ROPE ALL TIED
AROUND THE TREE BRANCH.
NOW, IF I KNEW WHAT
YOU WERE DOING,
WOULD I LIKE IT
ANY BETTER?
PROBABLY NOT,
HAROLD.
OKAY, I DON'T WANNA KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING THEN.
WELL, SEE, I'VE GOT
A HEAVY DUTY BOAT
WINCH HERE
ATTACHED TO THE MAIN
POST THAT HOLDS UP
THE LODGE HERE.
I DON'T WANNA KNOW!
LA-LA-LA-LA
THEN I RAN THE ROPE UP
AROUND THE TREE BRANCH
AND SO I CAN ACTUALLY
PULL THE LODGE UP
JUST BY TURNING
THE CRANK.
AND YOU THINK THAT POST IS
GONNA TAKE ALL THAT STRESS?
[ CHUCKLING ]
COULDN'T RESIST PUTTI''
YOUR TWO CENTS IN,
EH, HAROLD?
YOU MAY BE A MAN YET,
YOU KNOW THAT?
HAROLD, THIS POST HAS BEEN
HOLDING THE LODGE UP
FOR A LOT OF YEARS.
IT'S NOT GOIN'
ANYWHERE.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S STRONG ENOUGH.
NO, I THINK
IT'S GOOD.
I THINK IT'S FINE,
HAROLD.
WELL, I SAY NO.
THANK YOU, HAROLD.
NO, I'M STILL
SAYING NO, UNCLE RED.
NO, I THINK
IT'S GOOD.
THAT POST IS
GONNA BREAK!
I DON'T THINK SO,
HAROLD.
SEE?
YOU'RE DEAD WRONG.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD,
HAROLD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
UM, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
UM, I'LL BE COMIN'
HOME A BIT LATER TONIGHT.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU ALWAYS WANTED
SOMEONE TO LEVEL THE LODGE?
WELL, AS ALWAYS,
I THINK I'M YOUR MAN.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHIN'.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN NOW.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
NOW, MEN, I'VE BEEN THINKIN'.
men: UH-OH!
NO, NO, SEE THE PROBLEM HERE IS
THE REASON THE LODGE IS SLANTED
IS BECAUSE WE GOT SOME
TRAPPED AIR OR GAS
UNDER THE ONE SIDE.
AND THAT OF COURSE
IS THE HIGH SIDE.
WE'RE TRYING TO JACK UP THE LOW
SIDE TO MATCH THE HIGH SIDE.
WELL, THAT'S DUMB.
I FIGURE IF WE CAN
DRILL A HOLE IN THE FLOOR,
WE CAN RELIEVE
THE PRESSURE, SEE,
AND THAT'LL DROP THE HIGH SIDE
RIGHT DOWN TO THE LOW SIDE
AND WE'LL BE GOLDEN.
[ MEN COUGHING ]