Ever since man is first walked upright
billions of years ago, he has been a hunter,
a fisherman, and he's lived off the land.
Ok, all right. Well, now billions of years
ago, because, you know, dinosaurs only went
extinct about, you know, like, maybe about
sixty five million years ago.
And oh yeah, OK.
Sometimes, though, science fiction movies,
you see, like a Tyrannosaurus rex being some
cave guy that couldn't happen.
There's no way because like humanoids,
they've only been around like for like, I
don't know, maybe a few million years.
Whereas in real people, I've only been
around like maybe a couple of hundred
thousand, OK. But by real people, what I
mean is, like Homo erectus thought, OK, you
know you're laughing, but don't. Even
because this is this is a real term.
These are the people who existed between
like Neanderthals and like The Flintstones,
right in there. That's special time.
And they're the ones they develop off by the
fill ops and the Flint Knife.
And these are real bones in the air.
Like that movie two thousand and one and see
that did not understand that movie
whatsoever. I'll tell you that it had like a
black cartridge or something.
It's like a Nintendo game cartridge.
I had no idea. Harold, I'm sorry.
Here he is, the star of the red green show
Red Green.
Awesome possum watch overstaying his welcome
is Harold.
Harold is my producer and director and due
to an unfortunate family situation, he's also
my nephew. Harold has eaten most of our time
with a stream of unconsciousness there.
I'm sorry, uncle rat.
Sometimes you just get ideas and I can't stop
it.
Here comes an idea right now. Here comes.
Oh, with that cool and or hip or what?
Oh, that's eaten up even a little more time.
So I'm going to I'm going to have to keep
things moving him very quickly, and I'm
running out of time, very little time left.
I've got Ernie, you know, I sound exactly
like Christine.
Like, it was good.
Wasn't he one of the better ones?
I thought he was really something else.
He was so true. David Copperfield, he was
good, too.
He made a Statue of Liberty disappear.
Oh, where are you going to put that your
closet?
I don't even think so. I'm sorry, uncle red.
You go right ahead. What you're doing?
Thank you, Harold. Three seconds I have left.
I thought I would mention that the lodge has
gone for a new life insurance policy.
That you should tell that story.
That's a really good story to tell because
You know, a better. So we all had to have
examinations.
But the problem was that Glen Braxton
flunked his exam.
I mean, his physical was so bad.
I think his cholesterol was five thousand
over something, and they ended up taking away
his driver's license, which means he can't
drive his beloved RV.
I'll tell you, Glenn is not a happy camper.
In fact, he's not a camper at all.
Sixteen thousand one.
What was that?
Whose house do the next segment once you?
Ok.
I think that's the whole deal.
My stakes. Yeah.
Just ask your feet.
Oh, I say you should be up on your feet, you
know, moving around, get your circulation
going.
Well, doctor just gave me a death sentence,
Harold.
What it is, you know, a death sentence.
You might as well pull out a shotgun, put up
beside my head and blown it off.
I don't think general practitioners can do
that.
She only said that you're out of shape.
Shouldn't say you're going to die, Glenn.
She said, I couldn't drive my RV anymore.
I mean, it's it's worse than dying.
I mean, what else do I have in my life?
I own and operate the only marina for 20
miles.
Yeah, but some of my like.
Bill, have you seen Glen Braxton?
Oh, hey. Gleno, huh?
Up and at. Let's go at it.
Drop dead and all, I'm about to shape up,
man.
We're going to get you back in the driver's
seat.
Look at I brought. Oh, I've heard about
these diets.
I'd rather stick your fingers down my
throat.
This happens to be a simple, portable muscle
machine.
Let me demonstrate. Whoa.
Whoa, whoa.
So what? I got to smack myself with a hose
to get in shape.
No, no, no, no.
That was an accident. But but I can
guarantee that in two weeks you can have a
body like mine. Oh, great, he's going to
soft my legs.
Ok, fine. Thank you very much.
I'll have, you know, Mr. I'm in terrific
shape, Harold.
Sir, come on over. You try to hurt me.
Oh no,
No, no, no, no.
And all I know this one. This is where you
tear up my heart and show it to me just
before I die.
I think enough girls have done that to me in
my lifetime already.
Thanks very much.
It's my last sprint, but that hurt me.
All right. You're short and you can't get a
date.
I meant physically. No thanks.
I'm going to drink.
Bill, Gary, come on.
Try to hurt me. Huh? Come on.
I met with your heads. Wow.
Yes. I wasn't ready if you were going to get
mugged.
They'd have the phone ahead and make a
reservation.
Who'd like a better time?
Starboard. Oh, yeah, sure.
Whoa. Are you crazy?
Half my politics are stuck to the ceiling.
This man does not need a buttercup.
You might as well have taken one of those
things and jab it right into his heart.
I'd like to take one of those things and jam
it down your throat.
Those took me two hours and nine pounds of
flour.
I thought you said they were Stortford.
Well, you wouldn't notice the difference.
You know, Glenn has given up junk food.
Whoa. Whoa, no.
Since when since you decided to lose 20
pounds in shape up your pathetic blubber
butt? Oh, good.
Well, let me look, you got a buddy like a
sack of tapioca.
You've you talking to me?
Yes, you. The government asks you to list
your first three ingredients.
You'd have to list
Fat, fat, fat.
And what are you laughing at me?
Yeah, I mean, you put out another five
pounds.
You'd have your own gravitational field.
Have you laughing at I don't say who me that
those dreams out one more time, you can have
nine separate pieces of denim.
Ok. Ok.
All right. I think we've established that
you're all a little overweight.
So can we get started now?
Assume this position?
Well, let's just assume I assumed it.
And don't get the floor, you guys.
Oh, fine. How are we not going to turn our
bodies into lethal weapons?
At night, you'll see the men sitting on the
porch, chewing and spitting in the light of
the propane cart.
That you and I spent till the morning light
in the future when they eat muskrat, they'll
remember to marinate it first.
Both.
This week in the corner
And I show you something festive and
decorative that you can do to your patio, you
know, the patio up here at the Lodge has not
been looking all that great since we did that
experiment to find out whether or not
hydrogen is flammable.
But, you know, I think we can bring her
right back up to snuff here by making our
very own patio lanterns.
And they're real easy to make and kind of
fun for.
For starters, you have your Christmas
lights, which are probably hanging up at your
house all summer long anyhow.
So why not just double up with those?
All you need is some of those plastic
containers you might find two or three in the
in the garbage. I just picked these out of
today's garbage up here at
the Lodge and there are a little dirty.
I would suggest you just let that long just
kind of dry on there and then pick it off
with your thumbnail. I tried to clean one of
them, not in the dishwasher.
You know, there's a heater unit in those
dishwashers, and that thing just shriveled up
there like a. Well, you guys know what I'm
talking about anyway.
What you want to do is pick out one of the
containers that seems appropriate size and
shape to make a patio out of something like
that, for example.
And then you want to see, well, let's see
which way we hang that.
Well, I think kind of that kind of looks
kind of like a big plastic teat on there.
I the sun porch door.
They're having a good then that you want to
do is you want to cut up an X in the bottom.
You can use a carpet knife for them.
I have a carpet knife in my pocket.
All right, someone didn't put the blade away
before they put that in my pocket.
Now what you want to do here is you want to
cut an axe and cut it about two inches or if
you're if you're dealing in centimeters, you
want to cut enough centimeters that it's two
inches. Ok, OK, OK.
Now we've got our X and then you just put
the bulb right in there and it's kind of a
friction fit and that's that's really on
there.
That really doesn't excite.
All right. You just you just do that for all
of them.
The cutting thing, not the slapping yourself
in the face thing.
I'm not sure if you want to slap yourself in
the face.
I'm not. I would help you.
By golly, that's Mars.
All right, that's two. It's taking no longer
than I thought.
Well, oh.
All right. There is a there's actually an
easier way than a carpet killer punch the
holes in these things. This would be with
the with a power tool.
Let's see if this works a little better.
I think so, we'll get the old bleach bottle
here.
Oh, I saw that one out.
Another thing you do with a power tool is
you can kind of save a little bit of time.
All right. Well, we'll start to get a few
more going here, and the next step will be to
take our containers and stick the Christmas
lights through those.
I got a hammer, just tap those on.
By the time I finish getting everything
rigged, I think it's going to be dark enough
to show you how this really looks.
Now you tell me who wouldn't want to have
that hanging around their house, huh?
Harold, kill the lights there a minute.
Hey, look at that.
Good friend. Good fun.
Good food and margarine tubs.
You know, I think this is the greatest
recycling decorators idea since cutting tires
in half, painting them white and putting up
the side of your driveway.
Now, until next time, remember if the women
don't find it handsome, they should at least
find it handy. I can't find anything,
Harold, that's
Got the lights back on, will you?
Oh. Thank you, Harold.
Hello. Maybe it's right, Bill.
Maybe I should work or something.
Get up. I should watch what I eat.
Are you going eat that one? Yeah.
It is summer, two men are arm wrestling
locked in a drawer for 15 minutes with their
huge ham like fists wrapped around the last
beer in the house.
Now, the final insurance policy arrived, and
I got to go around and get everybody's
signature. Let's hope nobody dies before
they get the sign.
That'd be a real tragedy.
I have to sign on the dotted line too.
I know I'm not like a lodge member, but you
know, I consider myself a keen observer
driving asylum.
Observer Herald.
Oh yeah, right?
Glen's going around here feeling sorry for
himself, which isn't that hard to do.
I'll tell you if moping burns calories,
Glenn is going to drop about 40 pounds by
dinner. No one's trying to get him into
shape.
When Glenn is not looking and wiggles out
and moves the RV about 40 feet down the
laneway, something gets a little more
exercise, and Noel also turn the broom closet
into a sauna. Right now, there's eight guys
in there sweating it out.
Oh yeah, what are they using for heat?
Hey, guys! Ooh, yeah.
Glenn is drinking beer out of a heavier mug
now and kind of build up the biceps, and he
licks the salt off the pretzels before he
eats them.
Wow.
Next, stop the Olympics.
Yeah, I think the problem is, you know, you
are what you eat, and Eddie keeps pumping us
full of pancakes and doughnuts and French
toast and muffins, and he deep fries all that
stuff. Hurry up, Uncle Red, I'm getting
hungry.
Yeah, me too. Eddie, are you making for
lunch today?
What do you see here, right?
Four heart attacks, three strokes and a
hernia.
Don't you blame me? Because Glenn's a three
hundred pound weakling who made the high
fiber ice cream, who made the broccoli
cheesecake, who made the artichoke yogurt
surprise.
Get it out on purpose yesterday.
Yesterday I made garlic and onion doughnuts.
Well, obviously threats don't work with these
guys.
Do you know, Ed? I think you should cut down
on the salt and the cholesterol?
Take some of the grease off the salads.
I'm not Glenn's mother, you know?
No, I know. I know.
Mind you, there is a strong resemblance.
Yeah. Well, something's got to be done,
that's for sure.
Give me another whack of that on here, would
you, ed?
Sure. There you go.
Oh, wait, no beauty.
Well, this week on adventures was Bill,
I guess this means we're going to go canoeing
up there somewhere and she goes and well,
bill. Easy, easy, easy, easy, easy.
Yeah. Yeah, it's adventure would be right.
All right. He's fine. Ok, now I thought we
just go paddling with Bill said.
No, I want to use a paddles.
Hey, sorry about that.
So he wanted to show us some different ways
of powering a canoe here, rather than the
normal conventional use of a paddle, so he's
got a real nice, nice little headboard.
But I wasn't exactly sure how he is going to
attach it on, and I want to say I was going
to swing it out to him. It's kind of heavy.
It's I want to get and I was on.
It was unfortunate, but no problem.
Yeah, lots more. I do that one come from.
And now this one might.
This one might be a little bigger than what
the canoe is rated for, but we don't have to
turner on fuller of.
I hadn't realized the weight I have now.
I don't know if bolting that onto the side
is to me.
It would go on the end, but then.
Expert Mike Bell. Anyway, so we kind of
abandoned that we were running short on the
bars and we just got her up on the dock,
dump the water on her.
I wasn't quite sure what Bill Mitchell had
planned there, whether he wasn't even on the
dock. And then you just what you do is you
tow the dock around.
No, he went me in. He come back with I went
up under under the lodge there and got all
the all the towels and we use spaghetti
night anyway.
Yeah, 15, 16 bottles or saw there, I guess.
And they didn't quite know what he had in
mind.
And he broke down a bunch of sea clamps and
some rope there and a little bit of this and
that started hooking the paddles onto the
sides and up onto the gunnels and the sides
and where the gun, all those meat sides,
even.
And then I put the bow and down at that
other one.
The other end the I guess, the assistant
bough or the back, I think is gone.
And now when he created here was basically
the sailboat.
Heidi, I was there. Keel as your father
paddles on the side and there's your main
mast and you're Mizan and your halyard and
your mainstay and your first day.
And oh, that's OK, that's OK to say that.
Now what he needed was some cloth to put on
anyone.
Take my shirt. I don't know.
I'm not going to give you, take your own,
you hang your own clothes on anyway.
So I pretended that I take mine off.
He took his off and you know, we didn't want
anybody to see this at home, so everybody had
fatter fingers. Anyway, Bill stripped right
down there and which was a real treat for the
bugs, but it started attaching his clothing.
And what have you and God?
He loves these things and at All Ordinaries
got in those pants and I had to do.
All I had to do was kind of look like a
Viking act.
I was like, I follow the Viking all.
Well, I figured maybe he could try the motor
again.
Well, just a few signatures to go and every
large member will be covered for death or
dismemberment. You know that a hand is worth
more than a foot that surprised me.
I mean, I can understand than I being worth
more than an ear, but I would think you'd
rather walk somewhere with one hand and hop
there with two.
And, you know, there's something kind of
warm about the guy asking me how to spell
their names, not to use the real names.
There are no nicknames except for Nick.
Hey, Harold, you know, Junior Singleton's
real name is Larry
David or Doug Vladimir Vance.
Valerie Pig knows Carol.
All right.
That's Chris.
Hey, to Brutus, a two Popeye.
An old man. His real name is old man.
I wonder he couldn't wait to grow up.
Dickie Peterson His first name is actually
George.
Actually, stinky looks like a George, but he
has the air of a stinky.
Oh, I got the rest of the signatures at
tonight's meeting.
Oh, that's the cry of the wild possum won't
go red.
It's time for the meeting. We better get
down there.
We have to convince Glenn that his life
really is worth living.
Well, maybe you can describe your life.
I don't make him feel better.
Yeah, OK.
You know, I think if the insurance company
was aware of Harold's personality, they might
not give us a policy, you know, just get him
that way.
Right, right.
Right? Oh, oh, oh, oh all nice.
When you poke, Barb, don't take it
From the Pakistan side at Stamford Bridge.
All right.
Now I need your signature on this insurance
policy.
Message for me. Oh, all right, all right.
The floor recognizes normal Christmas.
Thank you, right? I'd just like to show you
what my athlete has learned in just one day
going Glen Joe.
Well, I can show you how I can strangle
Noel.
He will go.
Well. It's a big day for me.
All on, guys, hold everything.
Dr. I mean, they've made a mistake on these
reports for the insurance investigation here.
It's not Glenn that that has the high
cholesterol.
It's no. Me.
Oh, yeah, and you got high blood pressure to
know who says, Glenn, you're fine.
I can run the army again.
Yes, you can, sir. They say you're so relaxed
you should never need any sleep with that.
Oh, baby, unhealthy.
I mean, why is it me? Why me?
Well, maybe it's the way he had all stress,
huh?
It's you're cooking, Eddie.
That's right. You've been poisoning me with
your lard filled, vein clogging fat piece.
That's what it was. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You're the only one with high cholesterol
around here.
Everybody else is fine and calm down no more
grapefruit in your stupid diet.
Hey, hey, good night. Let's jump in the air.
We go to Florida. Get some fresh grapefruit,
huh?
I'm dying. I'm dying.
Wow. Wow, no is getting over the good news
here.
Unless you're some other business.
No, nothing going on. Now I'm going to call
on our old buddy Glenn, who's in perfect
health to give us the evening's
entertainment.
All right. How do we look to you?
Ok, I was going to read my last will and
testament, but I think I can scare up a few
slides for you guys, huh?
How far? Ready.
Thanks, Bill. Well, we're not the No.
Be the one with the health problem.
I mean, he's always after us to eat better
and get in shape, and here it is that he's
the reject. How can you not believe in God
when stuff like that happens?
Anyway, if my wife is watching, I'll be
coming straight home after the meeting and
apparently I'm in a lot better shape than I
look.
So I'd like to go back to not wearing any
pajamas unless there's a downside.
So until next time, on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole gang up here at Possum
Lodge, keep your stick on the ice.
The bar made out of steel.
It's just all it's a big ball, steel ball,
yes, steel ball.
Can you throw it? No, it's really big.
It's like, there's my head.
That's that's like just on the camera
perspective.
Yeah, I know about you.
If actually that's out of the front window
of the five foot five foot like myself over
there, I'd be I'd be dwarfed by it must be
huge.
It's a huge steel ball.
Unbelievable.