And now it's time for the show and the great
untouched wilderness.
Well, OK, so it's a little tough, but you
know, so are the people who live up here and
well, they'll call it cabin fever.
Call it getting back to nature.
Call it lack of education.
Call it the Red Green Show.
Hey, here he is the man of the hour.
The guy here he is as well.
He's the greatest human being has ever given
me a steady job.
Ladies and gentlemen, the head of the lodge,
the star of the show, Mr.
Red Green.
Thank you and
Welcome to Possum Lodge.
Our home is your home and looks like your
home could use a good cleaning.
And speaking of needing a good cleaning, say
hello Harold.
Oh, OK. Hello.
That's director talk for I have nothing more
to say than a somber mood actually happened
to their lives this week.
Our lodge treasurer, Douglas says we've
pumped a bit short this month for actually
the 15th month in a row.
I think the problem is we just don't get a
lot of visitors up here possible because, you
know, we're not as well known as the other
lodges, and we're just a little bit off the
beaten path. And of course, the place is a
dump.
But anyway, with this, with this deficit
thing, Douglas is kind of cutting back.
There's no more third's at mealtime.
You've got to pay extra for toothpicks and
he's closed the pool.
Pool what
Pool? Cesspool Harold?
I'm just saying I don't think that, you know,
the members should start to realize there's
no such thing as a free lunch up here.
There's no such thing as a good lunch.
This is working on that, too.
He's got some kind of a scheme to save money
on our food bills.
Well, maybe maybe you can just get the
members to take like normal portions.
It's that way we can cut back on the size of
the members.
Oh no, no, no, no.
He's got some kind of a buy in bulk food
scheme or something other.
And I mean, after all, we eat in bulk.
Well, OK. Well, anyone ever thought of
actually doing, you know, something to
generate money, like using like thought or
effort?
You know, something revolutionary?
Know that machine here is there. How much
would that be worth if I sold out to, say, a
television network or a pawn shop or
something?
Nothing.
Well, you know, next to nothing.
Don't read. I need my access.
Think pays for itself.
But why do they call like a little food
club?
You got to be a piece of food to join
The Murray Food Club is going to let you buy
your food in bulk.
Not this one at a time stuff.
Yeah, that's right.
What's the point? It's cheap.
You bet it is. Wow.
I can't believe the savings.
Are you sure you calculated it right?
You try it. Einstein, Duane.
My name's Duane.
I can't wait till he finds out about these
savings.
Oh, Bill, Bill, how have you seen Eddie?
No. Well, can you get him?
I'm going to be changing all the food he'll
be cooking.
Oh no.
Make sure that he orders from the four basic
food groups dairy, meat, grain fruits,
vegetables. That's fine.
There's five food
Groups.
That's why we've got the Murray menu system.
Ok, now let's let's just say that you have
ordered some bacon flavored potato chips,
right? Ok, now the bacon is from your meat
group and the potatoes from your vegetable.
Oh, how about you dairy, sour cream and
onion chips and your fruit cherry licorice?
This package does have it all.
One. And you guys got a rag.
They'll just sneeze banana all over me.
Uncle Ret. Uncle Red, you know what, the
lodge, we're joining a food club
Password to get into that savings.
Major savings there.
Red, need your food value?
Oh, you're going to love me for this one?
Well, don't get your hopes up, Marie.
You know, I'll probably just break your
heart.
Move on the Swedish meatball.
I knew. I knew. Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Well, where's he going?
Sweden?
No, thanks. Say Eddie Murray here has started
up a food club.
Oh, now as large treasurer, I've calculated
we could cut our food costs in half.
You can plan your meals a year in advance.
We would order a year's worth of pork, a
year's worth of beans and a year's worth of
cabbage.
Boy, I'm moving out that year.
Amen. That'll be the year of living
dangerously won't.
And next year we could order a year's worth
of chicken, a year's worth of macaroni and a
year's worth of chocolate cake.
Why don't you just take my boning knife and
plunge it into my heart?
What would be the savings in that?
I don't think any lecture for the marine,
A year of pork, a year of pork.
Do you have any idea what a year of pork
would do to my cooking skills?
Oh, think
Of it as a challenge every night.
A new way to cook pork.
Oh well, yes. Let's see the first night I
could throw it at you, and then the next
night I could just stuff it up your nose and
the third night shish kabobs.
Well, I will not be dictated to.
I need variety.
I need whimsy.
I have to cook what mood is in my heart.
So today, why were you mad at the world?
Maybe just Sweden?
Well, what would you rather?
What would you like me to just become some,
some automatic machine that turns out bland
TV dinners every night?
Oh, I think want. That's it.
I quit.
I'm going to throw in the apron.
Here, let me help you out here.
I quit. You can make your own damn food.
Forget it.
Your cutter Ali all flew.
Club is working out. Just great Murray.
I'll see you guys later.
Typically, you try and save a little money
and look what happens,
Save money, according Mike calculations.
It's going to cost the Lodge thirty eight
billion dollars a week.
Roving a roving, roving eye roll.
I'm going to go roving roving hour road, a
roving roving, it's going to be swell.
I have no idea what the hell it is, but I
hear it pays pretty well.
This week in an Amen corner, we're going to
talk about tools, and I want to talk
specifically about the most important tool
in your toolbox and that is your hammer.
You can use a hammer to fix anything except
digital watches and China.
Now, first hammer I want to talk about is is
a is a claw hammer if you get yourself a
hammer and it doesn't have any instructions
with it.
It's pretty simple.
You pick up the hammer and you start hitting
things and you keep hitting them until you've
built something. For example, you can use a
clock hammer to hit a nail.
Ari, you can also use a clawhammer to put in
a screw to great when your time is at a
premium. This way, you don't have to worry
whether it's a flat head or socket head or
Phillips or Robertson or anything of that
nature.
But you know, clawhammer is not the only
kind of hammer there is.
There's also something called a ball peen
hammering.
You know, it's not as dirty as it sounds,
unfortunately.
And this can be used also to drive in a
nail.
Or you can use the other end to an end, as
we call it, in the business to do some
riveting is a special thing called a rivet
here.
And OK, I think this is more for a metal
metal
application, you know? I think you're
supposed to hammer them from the other side.
Just let the string around them.
Oh, all right, I've I got to pry that board
off and knock, but not with this any of
clawhammer for that night drop down hammer.
Yeah. Here's my clawhammer now, I'm always
using Hammers, honey.
I'll get the ball paint. All right.
All right. Well. I can use something else as
a hammer.
Now this is a crowbar usually used for
prying things apart.
It can also be used for those unfortunate
times when you've misplaced the keys to your
house or your car. It's not only good for
Brian that it also makes a Danny Hammer
itself. So you see, almost anything can be
used as a hammer.
For example, you take a screwdriver.
Why not use a screwdriver as a hammer?
If you can use a hammer to drive a screw,
you can use a screwdriver to hammer finishing
nails along this line in there.
You want something with a kind of a
Plexiglas or a hard handle that it's not
going to hard anyway.
And then she goes about.
The only thing that I would say not to use
as a hammer would be something like a rubber
mallet. I'll show you why now this is kind
of useless, but it's not completely useless.
We're going to hammer out of. But the thing
is that, you know, you've got to be sort of
adaptable and realize that there are a lot
of things that you can you can use as a
hammer. And if you've got a big, big job to
do, you need a big hammer, you know, like a
big nail.
Yes. Ok.
You know, with a hammer that size and a
chainsaw, you can build a 20 by 40 foot deck
in about 15 minutes, not including sanding
and medical attention.
So there you have it. I mean, the point of
this whole thing is that almost anything can
be used as a hammer. There's as many hammers
as there are thumb injuries.
You can use a patio, stones or your wife's
purse or a rifle, and you can find you can
use as a hammer. So until next time,
remember, if the women don't find you
handsome, they should at least find your
handy.
Carol, come back here. Bring something I can
use as a hammer.
It is autumn. I'm sitting in my duck blind
blowing on my moose call.
To me, it sounds like indigestion to a male
moose.
It makes me sound like I'm a female moose in
heat.
In about 30 seconds, he will come charging
if my gun jams.
I'll be going out on possibly the worst date
of my life.
We may have lost Eddie as our cook, but
there's a downside, too.
Now somebody else is going to have to make
the meals around here.
Oh man. Sedgwick volunteered to make his
world famous lasagna for lunch, but I think
it got to be world famous by everybody
warning their friends about it.
Don't forget. Mount Vesuvius is world famous
as well.
Actually, when you eat the lasagna, you
start behaving like Mount Vesuvius.
It's at the point now, or we almost want to
get back here.
But Douglas has insulted him to the point
that he's really teed off.
He's sitting up in a tree throwing pine
cones at anybody who comes near him.
You know, I'll go read. All great chefs are
very touchy about their cuisine.
I mean, Eddie's an artist.
I mean, his palate is our palates.
Oh, we don't want a double palate the way
you know.
You know what, though? You know what?
I don't blame Eddie, because to him, a
dinner table is
Like a blank canvas.
Yeah, and he paints it with oil.
And again, I still do not blame Eddie, you
know, because you've never had to survive 12
months of pork.
Well, you never met my grade five teacher,
Harold.
Anyway, I think I'll just take a stroll down
to Murray Store and see if I can get this
Food Club deal kind of straightened out.
Harold, do that thing that irritates
everybody.
Oh OK.
I am a little teapot short and stout.
Here is,
You know, take us into the next segment.
Oh, that!
I read, are we still on track for the Food
Club?
Yeah. Are we going to make a fortune like
Murray says, we are.
Well, and he's still pretty upset.
You know, he's hiding up a tree.
Cryo-em. Hmm. I was hoping you could alter
the plan in some way.
He could get a little more enthused, you
know, because he's starting to upset the
squirrels.
Well, I've been thinking about that, and I've
decided to expand my menu to give Eddie a
potpourri of Menagerie as to what he can
cook.
That's French for choices.
Yeah. Like, name your poison.
Don't help me, Duane. Go to the store and
get me a bottle of corn oil and a bottle of
weald amaze.
Ok, now once Eddie sees the number of
choices he has, oh, he'll be changing his
tune. Can't find them.
Oh my.
They're right in the middle of the middle
shelf there.
If they were a dog, they'd have bit you.
There they are, right there.
I just get me that one and that one.
All right. Oh, I see them.
I should get a government grant for letting
him work here, huh?
Ok, now this one here is your corn oil and
this is your wheel amines.
What does that mean?
That's French for corn oil.
It's French corn. It's a completely
different taste, a Beaujolais Nouveau.
It's the same bottle, Marie.
They recycled the bottles.
You know, the French are very clever.
They're always thinking.
Imagine that.
Listen, why don't you give Edie this revised
menu?
Show him. You can select Check In or Palais
or Cucaracha.
That's Mexican chicken.
Oh, so he's not limited in any way.
Well, I'll give it a try.
See you later.
Appreciate it. Do you know any Italian?
Mussolini? That's my favorite car.
Well, we thought we'd kind of get back to
nature and make things a little simpler on
our adventure with Bill this week.
Bill's going to show you just how to climb a
tree.
Is that simple? Pick a pick on a tree that
has branches just kind of sticking out so you
can so you can use the branches as more or
less.
Oh, steps like steps on a ladder.
By golly, maybe this wasn't going to be
quite as simple as as we well know.
I think he's going to be all right.
It's like, Oh, and so now we're going to
start thinking about all of the other things
you could be doing with your life, you know?
Lying down somewhere like that.
Oh well. Time for Plan B.
We'll get the seesaw on the teeter totter
effect and bill is going to stand on one end.
I'll climb up the ladder and then when I
jump down onto that in that end of the down
and his end will go up and he'll get up the
tree, that way is never lost for ideas.
Bill and I. And one two, are you going to
go, Oh oh, oh, oh, oh oh.
Oh, not quite as successful as we planned,
but.
All right, all right. All right.
All right. Clancy, I can smell it.
Oh okay, Bill, now we got what you call the
golf shoes, the golf shoes with your flange,
Netflix and so on. And I got the spikes in
the bottom and what bill is going to do.
I've never seen this done before.
He's going to try and just dig those into
the tree and just climb right up just by
Golly. By Golly, he's got something here and
he's getting up there now, 20 30 feet up.
And I I don't I don't quite understand that
something about the Earth's rotation and then
something to do with helium in his
snowmobile.
Oh, bill, I to go.
Right on the plane, right on the foot.
Thank you, Bill. You know, Harold, you're
getting to that point in your life where you
should start thinking about what you're
going to do for a living, you know?
What do you mean? Well, I'll think about
what you're going to do.
You know, as a career what you can do the
rest of your life.
That's what I'm talking about.
Well, Uncle Red, I thought I might stay on,
you know, the the director producer of the
Red Green Show, you know?
I mean, I've been doing for for quite a
while now, and I'm really getting the hang of
it, you know, and and I know I want to stay
with the show and I know you want me to stay
with the show. Right, right, right.
I assume, right?
Oh, golly. Oh, Harold.
It's a bit of a shock. Well, go sure, you're
kidding around.
I'm kind of I'm talking, seriously, what are
you seriously going to do for a living?
What do you think? I'm serious.
I'm going to do the show.
No, no, no, no, no.
Come on. But good, Josh.
I'm here.
I'm not dodging. I want to do the show.
I mean, I know look, I like to kid around,
you know, and I know what you do.
I don't want to get around with this.
I'm not kidding. I want to do the show.
I want to be straight. I'm straight.
Let's be straight. I'm straight,
Man. I want to do the show.
No, come on. I quit quick.
I got it. I want to do the show.
Come on. I want to do a show.
So.
Well, I took Murray's new menu options over
to show Eddie, and he got so darn upset, he
almost fell out of his tree.
I don't know. I didn't get so upset about
everything.
You know, you can't tell him that he's fat
or he's bald, or he's a crappy actor, you
know, and it's food thing.
I mean, what's the big deal? It's not a
matter of life or death.
Actually, dinner tonight came close and I
tried to save a little money by making a
relish and tuna casserole.
He said it had been in his family for
generations, but I think he meant the tuna.
That stuff was deadly.
Did you eat that stuff, Harold?
No, but some dropped on my shoe,
Ended up with a conga line of guys giving
each other the Heimlich maneuver, and the
potato salad was actually even worse.
That was Jell-O,
Yellow, white, yellow, Harold.
Yes. We ran out of water, so I used sour
cream.
Well, obviously we got to do something about
this meal situation.
We've got to do it soon. Oh, somebody had
seconds
To call the while possible.
That means that the meeting is about to
begin Uncle Red.
Come on, let's get down there and see what's
going on.
Well, I hope we get this thing resolved real
fast.
Man does not live by beer alone.
All right.
They look good. Ok, cool.
All right. All right. All right.
Oh, all right.
Well, I'm glad to see that Eddie has left his
branch office floor, recognizes Douglas
Hendricks.
Thank you. Read fellow possums thanks to the
incredible savings from Murray's Food Club.
I'm pleased to announce the financial crisis
is over.
Unfortunately, that hasn't stopped one of
the large members from sabotaging the food,
as was the case with tonight's tuna
casserole.
I'm not naming any names.
Well, Duane and I certainly appreciate all
your business and not only because you are
fellow lodge members, but because you are
our friends, you're here.
And if it weren't for that fact, well, we
might be tempted to overcharge on all your
purchases. Yeah, we sure do.
Well, the Food Club may sound like a good
idea, but tell me, where are you going to
store a year's supply of frozen pork?
Oh.
Requires absolutely no refrigeration.
News Feed the pigs and clean the pens.
The food is still alive
On the hoof. Well, I told you of fresh costs,
more work.
Well, we can't have one hundred more pigs
running around this lodge.
Wait a minute, you're better off, including
me in that group.
I'm rather fastidious, actually, about my
personal hygiene.
All righty.
Well, in light of this new information,
fellow opossums, I suggest we resign from
this food club immediately.
Back to the way things work.
You won't have a cook.
Fine, I'll cook.
I made these cookies for dessert.
And no one sabotage them.
The when they're quite good, actually.
Good job.
There's plenty more where these came from.
Go ahead. Dig in.
These are butter. No, no, no.
Wait, no stop. Stop. Sorry, I'm sorry.
I can't possibly let you eat these cookies
by amateurs is dangerous.
It could kill you now.
No, no, no, no, no. That's it.
That's it. It's settled.
I'm back as the Lord Chef.
You need me. Unscathed.
Watch yourself there, Meryl. Thanks so much.
I'll be back as our cook, we're going to be
able to lose weight anyway.
Yeah, you don't know this bill.
Oh, well, I call on Mary and Duane here to
give us a little bit of magic for the
entertainment.
All right, ladies and gentlemen, if you will
notice there is nothing up my sleeve.
Duane looking.
Wow. All's well that ends.
Nobody's real satisfied with the way things
turned out, but on the other hand, nobody's
angry enough to do anything except complain.
That's about as close as we get to a happy
ending.
Anyway, if my wife is watching, I'll be
coming straight home after the meeting and I
am a little hungry, so I would appreciate
it.
If you didn't put the time lock on the
fridge tonight, I promise I'll go back on the
diet next year. Until next time, on behalf
of myself and Harold and the whole gang up
here at Possum Lodge. Keep your stick on the
ice.
Another match, ladies and gentlemen, is it's
simple two.
Yes, it's very simple.
Here we go. The hope to be on fire soon,
right here, you.
Abracadabra. Alec Booze.