[quirky upbeat music]
[a chainsaw, gunshots, glass sha
And now it's time for the show
that everybody is talking about,
in no uncertain terms, and
some of them even favorable.
A show that lives in the heart
of the heartland, where it
leaves the livers by the
bladders of the gall.
What am I saying?
I have no idea what!
I should write some of this down
before the show, actually.
Anyway, here's the star of the
Red Green Show, my uncle Red
Green! Uncle Red Green!
Thank you, Harold. Thank you
and welcome to Possum Lodge.
I should invite you...just take
Harold with a grain of salt.
In fact, side by side, you
can't tell them apart.
Although, you know, he is my
nephew and blood is thicker than
water, although nothing is
quite as thick as Harold.
Well, I think maybe the audience
can easily
identify intelligence, eh?
For example, this takes
intelligence!
[laughs] Operating a digital
effects unit.
The machine has the
intelligence, the operator is a
support system. I just don't
like getting surprised like
that. Not that I'm against
surprises.
I mean, I have thrown as many
buckets of ice water into a
sleeping bag as anybody.
The trouble starts when maybe a
lodge member can't differentiate
between a surprise and a prank
because, you know, if something
happens, that doesn't involve
loss of consciousness or
hospitalization, it really is a
surprise as opposed to a prank,
and doesn't really have a place
in lodge life, as far as I'm
concerned.
Whereas like a prank that maims
or kills is everybody's
favorite.
Well, as usual, you're
exaggerating Harold, just like
your father did when he got me
to hire you.
Any stunt that involves either
personal injury or property
damage makes a heck of a lot
more interesting story a couple
of years down the road when
we're all in our declining years
and doing a little more
reflecting than shining.
Well, I just want you to know
that I'm opposed to any childish
adventures or, or irresponsible
behavior.
Oh, Harold, that wedgie didn't
hurt that much, did it?
Well, quite a bit, especially if
you hook a person's underwear to
a power hoist.
All right. Maybe we did go a
little, a little too far with
that. If you could have seen
the look on your face.
Hardy har har.
I took it like a man, didn't I?
But if my children don't grow
up to be as tall as they should
be, I may sue.
It's a work day for me, too,
Harold.
Yeah?
Yeah, today I'll be testing soil
density for the Department of
Natural Resources.
I just do it on the golf course
to avoid boredom, that sort of
thing. It keeps me sharp and
more effective as a government
official.
Wow. That sounds...I guess
incredible is the word for that,
isn't it?
Well, Harold...in a couple of
days, it'll be my birthday.
I'll be turning a year older.
Be great if I shot par today,
though, huh?
That would be a good birthday
present.
Never shot par, Bob?
Well, I have on the scorecard,
just never on the golf course.
Good luck, Harold.
Be nice, you know you don't even
have to shoot par...just be
great if you didn't wing your
clubs into the lake.
The wind did that. I'll be on
the golf course all day.
You workaholic you. I think
Bob's patterned his civil
service career after Gerald
Ford, Eddie, I told you not to
buy the bikini briefs.
I didn't want Bob to see me.
I think we should have a
surprise birthday party for Bob.
I started on the cake.
That's the nose.
Woah! It's not a swimming party,
is it ED?
Uncle Red, I think a surprise
party is an excellent idea.
All right, then you try the
cake.
I may have gone a bit too heavy
on the prunes.
We prepare a special meal
around the campfire, and then
afterwards, we could all say
things about Bob and, you know,
he'd think we were kidding, and
then we could, we could divide
into groups and do vignettes
from famous Broadway musicals
like [SINGING] Oklahoma, where
the wind comes swirling around
the plain.
What do you think?
I think that's the kind of plan
that could lead to some fairly
major violence, really.
Red, as you know, I am a gourmet
cook and a performer of some
note.
Well, we don't want to hear the
note right now, Eddie.
And I'd be perfectly willing to
stage this party.
But if someone who doesn't know
a petite four from a pâté de
foie gras wants to make a
suggestion, well, I'm all ears.
Ok, how 'bout this? How 'bout
this? Right?
Ok? We get, like, some music
videos happening, right?
We get, like, a live music rap
group doing their thing in the
corner, right? They can be
doing that.
And we get, like, a laser light
show happening.
That'd be cool. And then we
can order pizzas.
Have, like, 50 pizzas. That, we
could do that.
You can do that. You wanna do
that?
We could do that. If you wanna
do that.
Wanna do that?
Harold...uh...would you mind
going down to the lake for a
minute?
What for?
Uh, to stick your head in it.
That was cruel.
Not compared to the other things
I thought of.
Do I have to, like, stick my
head right in it? Can I not, you
know, it's like, sit real close
to the edge?
I'd make it the far edge.
Excellent!
Well, how 'bout this for a
memorable party?
We all pile into the RV, we hit
the open road, we go till the
gas tank's empty and the
holding tank's full.
I think we'd have to be going
somewhere, otherwise, we
wouldn't know when we were
lost.
Ok, how about Augusta, Georgia,
home of the world-famous Masters
Golf Tournament? Huh? You think
Bob would maybe enjoy that at
all?
That's not a party, that's a
prize on the Dating Game.
Well, you don't have to go,
then. I mean, you can stay here
and learn some more show tunes.
Well, I think we should just
celebrate the birthday the way
we celebrate every birthday at
the lodge...we just ignore it.
I'll see you guys later.
Listen, this, the idea for a
party was my idea in the first
place.
Well, let's have it in the RV.
What's the difference?
Because there's no style to
that.
No panache.
I mean, we'd look like a bunch
of itinerant worm pickers.
Woah. Hey. Don't bring a
religion into it.
All right?
Worm picking isn't a religion.
I meant "itinerant." RV guys
like me don't like to hear the
use of that kind of language.
Hello, Harold.
Hi.
Mr. Miranda, I presume?
[strumming guitar] My favorite p
I've had them for years.
Comfortable like you wouldn't
believe. $13.95 at Sears.
Since I first got them I've
gained a few pounds, now my gut
kind of spills over top and
pushes 'em down.
My wife says they're too tight,
so I just show her they still
fit me fine, they're just 8 or
9 inches lower.
This week on Handyman Corner,
we're gonna show you a fabulous,
fabulous lawn and garden
instrument, the leaf blower.
Now to me, the leaf blower is
the greatest invention since
chainsaw or duct tape.
Well, not counting twist-off
caps.
Now this is, this is too long.
We only need a few feet of this
, so I'm gonna cut this with
some tin snips, but I need to
drill a pilot hole first, so
I'll just snug her up in the
vise and start the pilot hole
here.
Maybe I can think of a smarter
way to do this.
No. I know, I know what it is
...this is metal, and I'm using
a wood bit on this.
Gosh. I should be using a saw.
Ok, now we're going to need
something to blow air.
Now, I would suggest Old Man
Sedgwick, but I do have the
environment to think of. So
instead, I recommend one of
these deals here. This is one
of these hot air dryers that you
see in a washroom at a
restaurant.
You know, I mean, restaurants
are always going out of
business. You can pick one of
these up real cheap.
Or, if you really want to save
a bundle, you can go into a
self-serve gas station and
just, just serve yourself.
Uh, so first thing we ought to
do with this before we can use
it is we've gotta disconnect
the heater.
Lift the cover off there, and
...oh, it's like a computer in
there. Aw, no.
There, that's... this'll be the
hater connection here.
Yeah, I've got it. Okay, pop
that back on, and we're ready
for our final assembly.
Just smooth her right down and
, and there you have it.
You're ready for autumn.
You've got your very own,
one-of-a-kind, homemade leaf
blower. So remember, until next
time.
...if the women don't find you
handsome, they should at least
find you handy.
It is summer.
Sunbathers lolling in two-piece
bathing suits.
The brunette wears hers to get
a tan.
The blonde wears hers to get a
man.
The redhead wears hers to get
whistles.
And the bald fat guy wears his
for medical reasons.
So now everybody wants to give
Bob a surprise birthday party,
but I'm kind of against it
because, you know, first of all,
if it's his birthday, he's
gonna expect something.
You know, that's not really
gonna be much of a surprise.
What I'd rather do is take it
out, like take something like
April Fool's Day and make it a
completely different day without
telling anybody and then walk
up behind them and pull their
pants down on national
television. Now, that would be a
surprise. Right, Harold?
Right.
Yeah. Or, or say, you know,
Buster Hadfield has a date and
what you do is you put itching
powder all over the back seat of
his car. Huh?
That's not only fun, that's a
life lesson.
If you keep your clothes on,
you don't end up scratching.
You know, I might consider that
an invasion of privacy, Uncle
Red.
Oh, Harold, you know, you think
we should all behave like we're
all on the Lawrence Welk Show.
And if you were in charge,
nobody would ever be allowed to
yell "pile on." That's boring,
Harold.
Well, maybe I'd rather be boring
than to find plums in the toes
of my shoes. Has anyone ever
really stopped to consider that?
Aww...you're a wet blanket.
That's another thing, I resented
that wet blanket.
Aww, relax Harold. Gasoline
evaporates.
I'll take a prank over a
surprise any day.
Wow. I hope you feel the same
way after your lunch break
today, Uncle Red.
I'm not eating my lunch, Harold,
I gave it to Helmut.
Uh oh.
Oh, Bob, I think that maybe, I
think maybe you need to unwind a
little bit, you know? Maybe get
some professional help.
Or, or what about taking a year
off?
Or if you can't do that, bob,
I've got an idea...
how about a party? What if we
had a party of some kind?
Let me tell you something,
Red...
it's my birthday coming up
pretty soon.
Did you know that?
Uh, no. No, I didn't realize you
had a birthday.
Well, I wish I didn't.
You see, when I was a little
boy, my, my grandmother used to
stage these surprise birthday
parties for me.
Well, that was awful nice of
her, wasn't it?
I hated them. One shrieking
"surprise!" Looking at you.
Staring right at you to see what
your reaction would be.
"Did we fool you? Was it a
surprise?" And you had to be
happy, you had to pretend you
were happy all the time, no
matter how angry you felt and
you got crappy gifts.
Why didn't you just tell your
grandmother you felt that way?
Oh not, my grandmother. No way.
My grandmother could hurt you
if she wanted to.
Yeah. Once I saw her bring a
postman to his knees just with a
pair of salad tongs.
No. I stayed quiet...and
healthy.
I just pretended I enjoyed
myself.
That's why, to this day, I hate
surprises, just hate them.
That's why I took the job with
the government.
That's, that's too bad, Bob.
Yeah. That's why I like golf,
you know?
If you do everything right,
everything just goes exactly as
planned.
I suppose. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah.
Oh my God! It's gone into the
water hole!
This next portion is brought to
you by the good people who make
bandages and splints and iodine
...
Adventures with Bill.
And that Bill had made himself a
pair of stilts.
We're gonna try them out today.
So he wanted to start over
here.
Oh, my.
If he told me he was gonna stop.
..ahh. So. Good start. You know,
I think it was Sigmund Freud who
said, "If you don't go through
some developmental stage, stages
of development in a kind of an
order when you're a kid, you
don't go through them in the
right order, or if you miss one,
then you gotta go through it
later in life." And, of course,
when he said it, it wasn't
quite that clear, but I don't
think Bill ever experienced
stilts as a kid, so he wanted to
try them as an adult.
I think it's more of a kid
thing because I think when you
get to be, you have too much
weight and he's trying this
technique and, uh...
I was afraid he was gonna back
us all the way to town.
Then we tried this, where I
would hold the weight, and boy,
this is not only heavy, but not
the greatest view you'd ever
want to have. But at least I
got him up there!
I got him...OK, OK, OK, OK.
No, no, no, no. But the thing
with Bill is he just doesn't
give up until he's really,
really hurt somebody.
Should get something to stand on
and maybe...
Oh! Well, that's, that's good.
Thank you, Bill. Thank you.
There goes our matching
furniture. You get that out from
there. And then we got some
garbage cans, thought he could
stand on them. Maybe that would
give them a leg up, so to speak.
But he got one and he got kind
of, he got kind of carried away
and he ended up sticking one of
the legs of the stilts in right
into the garbage can, and then
he, trying to get that out, and
he didn't know how he was going
to do that.
And, and then he'd only put one
nail in where the feet thing
go, so, instead of there up and
then down, oh oh oh!
He wedged right in there and it
was kind of the inside was kind
of wet, so it kind of sealed
off.
So we, uh... Yeah.
We got her off there.
Now he's putting a few extra
nails and just to be, just to be
safe and then, oh, now what he
did here was, he added, length
to the, to the stilts.
It was rope and duct tape, and
I think he went up about 12
feet. He says to me, "If you're
going to go up, you might as
well go up in a big way," which
I never really understood.
So he's gonna step onto these
from the van.
You know, whenever Bill gets
around my van, something bad
happens. I don't know what it
is.
Kind of a karma thing.
Or a truckma thing. Thank you,
Bill. And he gets up onto the
stilts there, and I'm sensing
impending doom.
I leave the area, but he's
doing OK.
Oh good, good.
He's all right, he's all right.
And unfortunately, what happens
a lot of times when you get up
that kind of height is the
gravity takes over.
But he's all right, he's OK.
He'll live to stilt another
day.
Go lie down, Bill.
It is summer
A muscle-bound bodybuilder kicks
sand in my face.
I challenge him to a fight.
Later that day, upon regaining
consciousness, I realize how
smart Gandhi was.
Well, the guys have heard that
Bob hates surprise parties, so
now they want to give them one
more now.
You know, since this is
unofficial April Fool's Day.
But I guess at tonight's
meeting, I better let the cat
out of the bag.
Well, you did that last week. Ha
That was a badger, Harold.
And I meant figuratively, this
time.
So I'll just, I'll just
announce that we're not going to
have a surprise party for Bob.
And then the guys will know
that they're, they're free and
clear to set his golf clubs on
fire or call his boss and tell
him how many rounds he plays on
company time.
Yeah. Bob will remember that.
Uncle Red. I mean, if this is
something you do to a fellow
lodge member, how are you
really any different than his
enemies, you know that's
what I do not understand
Well, the enemies would do it
with malice, Harold.
I mean, there'd be a mean edge
to the laughter.
We're just kidding around.
[a pig squeal]
That's the call to the meeting.
Oh, Uncle Red, it's time to go.
I hope you know what you're
doing.
No problem, Harold. I'll just
zip down there and let everybody
know what's going on and get
everything back on track.
And when the guys were trying
to do something nice for Bob,
then I'm sure they meant, well,
they just, just lost sight of
their priorities.
[pig squeal]
All rise!
[men recite the possum lodge
oath]
The floor recognizes Glen
Braxton.
Thank you, Red. I just want to
happily report that the army's
been serviced. It's all ready
to roll on our celebration that
we discussed. If my brother
possums will vote on my
suggestion, you know, as per...
Yes, well, I too am prepared.
Things have been cooked, plans
have been planted and I have
some supporters out there who
I'm sure we'll go along with
my...uh, uh...celebration
ideas.
I think I better announce to
everybody out there just for
your information and especially
to a couple or three guys up
here that the proposed
gathering has been
ixnayed.
Gatherings? Celebrations? What
are we talking about here, huh?
What are you guys up to? You're
not planning a surprise birthday
party for me, are you?
Really? Well, I hate surprise
birthday parties.
I told you that, didn't I Red?
Yes, you did, Bob. And that's
why we're not having one.
Whoah.
Oh. Well, all right, then.
It's not like I was expecting
one or anything like that.
They're always a
disappointment. You know.
I would imagine.
I lied about my
grandmother.
That's right, Red, I've never
had a party...
or had a grandmother.
Well, I canimagine what they're
The parties, I mean, and all the
stupid balloons, crummy clowns,
lousy magicians.
Never, ever
had a corner piece of cake.
You know? The one with the
extra icing on it?
But my father used to say that
parties weren't dignified
and only middle-class people
had birthdays.
And then my mother, you know,
she hated the idea of growing
older, so she just drank
heavily.
We could never pin the tail on
anything.
Well, Bob...I wanted to have
you, have, throw you a party.
And so did Eddie.
Yeah.
But Red said no.
Red, Red, Red killed it.
All right, all right...just
about...hold on. Hold on.
Now Bob.
Were you or were you not
expecting a surprise party?
Be honest. Be honest.
No.
Well, OK. Yeah
A little one.
Just because
you're asking me all about the
parties and everything, Red.
And everyone else out there
wondering what size of golf
shoes I wore and stuff like
that.
So it's a bit of a giveaway.
I thought, you know, there'd
be a little thing.
All right, then. All right,
then. So, not having a surprise
party would be a surprise,
wouldn't it?
Well, I, I guess.
OK! That's a surprise. So, all
those in favor of giving Bob a
surprise on his birthday, say
"aye."
Aye!
Well, there you go, ah?
No party, it is!
Eh? All together now...
Surprise!
You're kidding me, right?
That's funny! That's very good!
No, no...
We're not kidding. That's it.
That's it.
Any other business there, Bill?
No? Oh, OK. So, why don't we
call in Eddie here to supply the
evening's entertainment?
Congratulations, Bob.
OK, Eddie.
Here we go. Eddie!
Eddie's, up. Eddie's up.
Please. Eddie's up.
Well, live and learn, live and
learn.
The guys thought they could
pull a prank on Bob by having a
party for him that would make
them feel awkward and
embarrassed, and everything.
I managed to do all that just by
telling them
there was going to be
a party.
Just with a few simple words, I
reduced a grown man to tears.
Now that's a prank.
And, you know, I guess the
ability to understand people and
what makes them tick is the
mark of a true leader.
Anyway, my wife is watching.
I'll be coming straight home
after the meeting and please
don't have any surprises for me
in bed tonight.
Or pranks. I certainly don't
have any for you.
So until next time, on behalf
of myself and Harold and the
whole gang up here at the
Lodge.
Keep your stick on the ice!
[singing] I saw her walking down
the meadow
[singing] a little dress on and
an attitude
[singing] I said, "Hey baby,
hey baby...it's you.
[singing] It's you.
Hey baby, it's you!"