I KNOW IT'S GREAT TO BE REASONABLE
AND RATIONAL
DISCUSS THINGS, TRY TO ARRIVE
AT AN ACCEPTABLE COMPROMISE
THAT EVERYBODY
CAN LIVE WITH.
BUT ONCE IN A WHILE,
WHEN YOU'VE HAD ENOUGH,
YOU'VE GOTTA TAKE ACTION.
YOU'VE MADE YOUR POINT;
THEY UNDERSTAND YOUR POSITION;
AND YET NOTHING CHANGES.
AND THAT MOVES YOU FROM
THE ARENA OF DIPLOMATIC
CONCILIATION
INTO THE AREA OF A TASTE
OF YOUR OWN MEDICINE.
[distorted voice]
[distorted]
[cheers and applause]
ALL RIGHT
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
THANK YOU.
YEAH, I APPRECIATE THAT.
WELL, I'M AFRAID
I GOT NO NEWS FOR YOU.
THAT'S BECAUSE OUR LOCAL
PAPER, "THE DAILY MOVEMENT,"
IS SHUT DOWN FOR TWO WEEKS.
I FIGURE PEOPLE
ARE GONNA MISS IT.
THAT'S A LONG TIME TO GO
WITHOUT A "DAILY MOVEMENT."
HEY, RED,
THERE'S NO
PAPER THIS WEEK.
NO, NO, THE PUBLISHER,
THE EDITOR, THE REPORTER,
THE PHOTOGRAPHER,
THE CARTOONIST AND
THE TYPESETTER
HAVE ALL GONE
ON VACATION.
BUT DON'T WORRY.
HE'LL BE BACK IN
TWO WEEKS.
OKAY, I WISH SOMEBODY
WOULDA TOLD ME THAT
BECAUSE NOW NO ONE'S
GONNA SEE MY AD.
YOU DON'T NEED TO
RUN AN AD, WINSTON.
I MEAN, THAT TRUCK OF
YOURS IS AN EXCELLENT
MARKETING TOOL.
AND THAT THING ASSAULTS
ALL FIVE SENSES
EVERY TIME YOU DO
A DRIVE-BY.
RED, IT'S NOT AN
AD FOR MY BUSINESS;
IT'S -- IT'S MORE OF
A PERSONAL AD.
SEE, I'M LOOKIN' FOR
A WOMAN WHO'D BE WILLING
TO HAVE MY BABY.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T
THINK A LOCAL AD
IS GONNA WORK.
I THINK YOU NEED TO
ADVERTISE WHERE THE
WOMEN DON'T KNOW YOU.
WHY THIS SUDDEN URGE
TO BE A FATHER?
RED, I'M WINSTON
ROTHSCHILD III.
SEE, IT'S TAKEN THREE
GENERATIONS TO BUILD
THIS SEPTIC
SUCKING DYNASTY,
AND I CAN'T LET IT
END WITH ME.
AND BESIDES, I PROMISED MY DAD
THAT I'D MAKE SURE THIS
COMPANY KEEPS GOING
AS LONG AS THE
CUSTOMERS KEEP GOING.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD BE
USING SCIENCE ON THIS.
THEY HAVE THIS SURROGATE
MOTHER THING NOW,
WHERE THEY TAKE A SAMPLE FROM
YOU AND THEY IMPLANT IT
INTO A WOMAN AND SHE DELIVERS
A BABY NINE MONTHS LATER
FOR A FEE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
DALTON'S DAUGHTER MIGHT
BE INTERESTED IN THAT.
AH, NO THANKS, RED.
I MEAN, WHAT IF THE KID
INHERITED MY HEIGHT
AND DALTON'S HAIR?
IT'D BE A TROLL.
NO, I'M KINDA LEANIN'
TOWARDS ADOPTION.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT MAKES A LOT OF SENSE,
GENETICALLY SPEAKING.
'CAUSE I THINK
THERE'S GOTTA
BE A FUTURE
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD IV
OUT THERE SOMEWHERE.
ACTUALLY, I'VE GOT AN
APPOINTMENT WITH THE
ADOPTION AGENCY
IN ABOUT A HALF
AN HOUR,
AND I WAS HOPING YOU'D
TAG ALONG AND, YOU KNOW,
SORT OF VOUCH FOR ME.
OH, SURE.
SURE, YEAH.
SO WE'RE LOOKING
FOR A BABY
WHO COULD POSSIBLY BE
IN THE SEWAGE BUSINESS?
RED, ALL BABIES ARE
IN THE SEWAGE BUSINESS.
[applause]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheers and applause]
AND TODAY'S WINNER WILL
RECEIVE THIS BEAUTIFUL
MONOGRAMMED HANDKERCHIEF.
I ALREADY HAVE
A MONOGRAMMED
HANDKERCHIEF.
YEAH, BUT THIS'LL HAVE YOUR
INITIALS ON IT.
OKAY, COVER YOUR
EARS, MIKE.
RED, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS TO
GET MIKE TO SAY THIS WORD...
LIGHT
YEAH, ALL RIGHT,
DALTON.
AND GO!
OKAY, MIKE,
AT NIGHT IT'S DARK,
SO IN THE DAY IT'S...
EASIER TO GET CAUGHT.
OKAY, WHEN A
ROOM GETS DARK,
IT'S TIME TO
TURN ON THE...
CHARM.
OKAY, YOU SEE A GUY,
AND SUDDENLY HE
GETS RELIGION,
YOU FIGURE HE
MUST'VE SEEN THE...
ELECTRIC CHAIR.
LET'S TRY THIS.
WHICH BEER DO
FAT PEOPLE DRINK?
THE LAST ONE.
TIME'S ALMOST UP RED
YEAH. OKAY
OKAY, MIKE, IF SOMETHING'S
NOT HEAVY, IT'S...
EASY TO STEAL.
OH, YEAH, ESPECIALLY
IF YOU'RE LIGHT FINGERED.
THAT'S IT!
[applause]
[loon calls]
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
REGRETS THE OTHER DAY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY
REGRETS, MR. GREEN?
WELL NONE SO FAR
BUT THIS CONVERSATION HAS POTENCIAL
[laughter]
WHAT ABOUT YOU,
MR. HUMPHREY?
ANY REGRETS?
I'VE GOT NOTHING
BUT REGRETS.
HOW ABOUT YOU, MIKE?
YOU MUST HAVE A
TONNE OF REGRETS.
WELL, ONLY ONE...
CHILDREN.
I REGRET NOT
HAVING ANY CHILDREN.
YEAH, I FEEL
EXACTLY THE SAME WAY.
OH, OR DID YOU SAY YOU REGRET
'NOT' HAVING CHILDREN?
YOU KNOW, BERNICE AND I
DON'T HAVE ANY KIDS.
WE TRIED FOR
A COUPLE YEARS.
THEN MY BROTHER HAD HAROLD,
AND WE TOOK THAT AS A WARNING.
OH, I'D LIKE TO HAVE
LOTS OF CHILDREN.
YOUR PARENTS HAVE
LOTS OF KIDS, MIKE?
MY MOM DID.
MY DAD DIDN'T
HAVE ANY KIDS.
I DON'T THINK
HE WAS MY DAD.
WELL, KIDS ARE A LOTTA
RESPONSIBILITY, MIKE.
YOU HAVE A DAUGHTER,
DON'T YOU, DALTON?
YES, YES,
YES, I DO.
YES, I HAVE A
DAUGHTER.
THAT'S WHY I'VE BEEN
WEARING THE SAME CLOTHES
FOR THE LAST
12 YEARS.
BUT KIDS ARE SO GREAT!
THEY'RE SO INNOCENT;
THEY'RE SO FULL OF
HOPE FOR THE FUTURE.
YOU KNOW,
IF I'D HAD KIDS,
I DON'T THINK I'D EVER HAVE
BEEN IN TROUBLE WITH THE LAW.
HOW OLD WERE YOU
ON YOUR FIRST ARREST?
ELEVEN.
THAT'S A PRETTY
YOUNG FATHER.
YOU MIGHT WANNA THINK ABOUT
GETTING A LIFE PARTNER
BEFORE YOU LEAP RIGHT INTO
HAVING A FAMILY, YOU KNOW?
THERE STILL HAS TO
BE A WOMAN INVOLVED
IN HAVING KIDS,
DOESN'T THERE?
YOU DON'T JUST DOWNLOAD
IT OFF THE INTERNET.
NO, NO, KIDS ARE GREAT.
IF YOU HAVE A SON
OR A DAUGHTER,
IT'S KINDA LIKE A PROMISE
THAT YOU'RE GONNA RAISE
'EM PROPERLY
AND YOU'RE GONNA TAKE CARE
OF 'EM UNTIL THEY'RE
ON THEIR OWN.
[scoffs]
THEY'LL NEVER
BE ON THEIR OWN.
ARE YOU PREPARED
FOR THAT ONE, MIKE?
I JUST WANNA HAVE KIDS.
THEY'LL LEARN
TO BE GOOD PEOPLE.
WELL, THEY LEARN MAINLY
FROM YOUR EXAMPLE.
WELL, THAT'S A
DUMB SYSTEM!
[applause]
YOU KNOW, MY DAD
USED TO TELL ME
A MAN'S HOME IS HIS CASTLE.
HE ALSO TOLD ME
TO LEARN ESPERANTO
AND BUY AN AMPHIBIOUS CAR.
MY DAD WAS WRONG.
THE ONLY TIME A MAN'S
HOME IS HIS CASTLE
IS WHEN THE QUEEN
IS OUT AT THE MALL.
SO TODAY ON HANDYMAN CORNER,
I'M HERE TO PROVE THAT
ALTHOUGH A MAN'S HOME
IS NOT HIS CASTLE,
HIS CAR IS HIS COTTAGE.
OKAY, AS ALWAYS, WHEN YOU'RE
DOING A MAJOR RENOVATION,
THE FIRST THING YOU HAVE TO DO
IS GUT THE WHOLE INTERIOR.
YOU WANNA DO THIS
AS QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE,
BECAUSE IF YOU TAKE THE
TIME TO DO IT PROPERLY
YOU'LL JUST GET BORED AND
ABANDON THE WHOLE PROJECT.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN GUYS DO THINGS RIGHT.
WHENEVER YOU SEE
A HALF-PAINTED BOAT
OR A PARTLY
CONVERTED SCHOOL BUS
IN A GUY'S BACKYARD,
THAT'S THE PRICE OF
BEING A PERFECTIONIST.
YOU WANNA KEEP
THE SEATS, THOUGH.
THEY MAKE GREAT COUCHES
FOR YOUR CASTLE.
MAYBE PUT 'EM IN
THE SERVANTS' QUARTERS.
FOUND A FAIR BIT OF FOOD AND
GARBAGE UNDER THE SEATS
AND WHAT HAVE YOU,
SPILLED DRINKS, TACO JUICE,
THAT KIND OF THING.
OH, MAN!
LOOK AT ALL THE COINS.
CAN'T REALLY CALL
IT LOOSE CHANGE.
OKAY, ONCE YOU'VE GOT
THE SPACE ALL CLEARED OUT,
YOU'RE READY FOR THE MOST
IMPORTANT PIECE OF FURNITURE.
IT'S AN OLD
BARBER'S CHAIR.
I MEAN, IT'S PERFECT...
IT SWIVELS, IT RECLINES,
THE FOOTREST COMES UP.
AND LET'S FACE IT.
AT OUR AGE WE'RE NOT USING
IT AS A BARBER'S CHAIR
NEARLY AS OFTEN
AS WE USED TO.
[grunting]
YOU KNOW, A ONE-SEATER CAR
MAKES A LOT OF SENSE TO ME.
IT'S A LITTLE HARDER TO
REACH THE PEDALS,
BUT YOU DON'T NEED ANY OF
THOSE SIDE AIR BAGS, EH?
AND LOOK WHERE
YOU'RE SITTING.
YOU'RE RIGHT IN FRONT OF
THE HEATER CONTROL AND RADIO.
THAT'S A LOT MORE INTERESTING
THAN WATCHING THE ROAD.
LET ME SHOW YOU
THE FAMILY ROOM.
I'VE GOT MY
MICROWAVE BACK THERE,
TV, MINI FRIDGE.
AND WITH OPEN
ACCESS TO THE TRUNK,
IT'S VERY PRIVATE AND
THERE'S PLENTY OF LEG ROOM.
PLUS, I HAVE TWO GARBAGE
CANS IN THE UNIT.
I BELIEVE THEY'RE
CALLED WINDOWS.
OH, YEAH, WE'RE A LITTLE SHY
IN THE HEADROOM BACK THERE.
ALL I DO IS USE THIS BOAT
HOOK TO GET MYSELF A
MICROWAVE POPCORN
OR THE SAFETY BEVERAGE
THAT GOES WITH IT.
NO, A MAN'S HOUSE
IS NOT HIS CASTLE;
BUT MAYBE HIS CAR IS.
AND WITH THE SUN ROOF
AND THIS ROPE LADDER
THIS CASTLE EVEN
HAS A TURRET.
ISN'T THIS A
GREAT SET-UP?
I CAN STAND UP HERE
IN MY TURRET
AND SURVEY MY
ENTIRE KINGDOM.
I CALL IT A TURRET,
BUT SOME PEOPLE
CALL IT WIDOW'S WALK.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHY.
OH, FORGOT MY COFFEE.
NO PROBLEM.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[music playing on radio]
[applause]
I WANNA TAKE A MINUTE TO TALK
ABOUT THE PARENT PROBLEM.
NOW, I DON'T MEAN
THE PARENTING PROBLEM,
WHEN YOUR KIDS COME
HOME WITH BLUE HAIR.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
THE PARENT PROBLEM,
WHEN YOUR AGING MOM
AND DAD COME HOME WITH --
WELL, WITH BLUE HAIR.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A FACT OF LIFE
THAT WHEN SENIOR CITIZENS
CAN'T TAKE CARE OF
THEMSELVES ANYMORE,
THEY OFTEN MOVE IN WITH THEIR
OWN MIDDLE-AGED KIDS.
THAT CAN BE REAL TOUGH
ON SOME OF YOU LATE BLOOMERS
WHO JUST MOVED OUTTA THEIR
HOUSE A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO.
BUT EITHER WAY,
YOU AND YOUR PARENTS
HAVE DIFFERENT LIFESTYLES.
SO THE WATCHWORD
HERE IS PATIENCE.
YOU MAY NOT UNDERSTAND WHY
ANYONE NEEDS TO BE UP
FOR THE DAY
AT 4:00 IN THE MORNING.
BUT THEN YOU'VE NEVER EATEN
SUPPER AT 3:00 IN
THE AFTERNOON
JUST TO SAVE A
BUCK AND A HALF.
LIKEWISE, TRY NOT
TO GET UPSET
WHEN THEY START COMPLAINING
ABOUT YOUR FOOD
OR THE WALLPAPER
IN THEIR ROOM
OR THE TEMPERATURE
OF THE HOUSE.
IT'S JUST THEIR WAY OF
TELLING YOU THEY LOVE YOU,
AND THAT YOU KNOW
NOTHING ABOUT ANYTHING.
OH, YEAH,
AND THERE MAY BE
SOME ROLE REVERSAL INVOLVED
REMEMBER HOW ANNOYED YOU USED
TO GET WHEN YOU WERE A KID
AND THEY'D TELL YOU
TURN DOWN THE TV?
WELL, YOU'RE GONNA
UNDERSTAND HOW THEY FELT
WHEN YOU START
HEARING ANDY ROONEY
AT A 120 DECIBELS.
THE MAIN THING IS DON'T
LOOK AT THIS AS A CRISIS;
THINK OF IT AS A
LEARNING OPPORTUNITY.
HERE'S A CHANCE
TO SHOW YOUR OWN KIDS
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TO THEM
IF THEY DON'T GET SMART
AND START SAVING FOR YOUR
RETIREMENT HOME IN FLORIDA
RIGHT NOW.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING
FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
WELL, WINSTON AND I WENT
DOWN TO THE ADOPTION AGENCY.
WE WERE HOPING TO
FIND HIM A CHILD
SO HIS FAMILY SEPTIC BUSINESS
WOULDN'T GO DOWN THE DRAIN.
WELL, IT DIDN'T
GO REAL WELL.
HEY, RED,
GOOD NEWS!
THEY WANNA SEE US
DOWN AT CITY HALL.
YEAH, SOME BIG
ANNOUNCEMENT OR SOMETHING.
THERE'LL BE A WHOLE BUNCH OF
US WHO ARE LOOKIN' TO ADOPT.
WELL, I DON'T THINK YOU
HAVE A CHANCE, WINSTON.
WELL, THAT'S
NEGATIVE, RED.
I THOUGHT OUR INTERVIEW
WENT REALLY WELL.
NO, NO, NO.
GOOD INTERVIEWS GO MORE THAN
THREE MINUTES, WINSTON.
WE WEREN'T IN THERE LONG
ENOUGH TO BOIL AN EGG.
WELL, MAYBE NOT,
BUT YOU SURE
SCRAMBLED A FEW.
WELL, I COULDN'T
LIE TO THEM.
WELL, NO,
NOT LIE.
NEVER LIE.
EMBELLISH,
MAYBE.
PUT A NICE
SPIN ON SOME OF
THE ANSWERS PERHAPS.
WINSTON, YOU'RE
A 35-YEAR-OLD BACHELOR
WHO SPENDS 18 HOURS A
DAY IN YOUR SEWAGE TRUCK.
I'D HIRE A NANNY.
I TOLD THEM THAT.
YOU TOLD THEM
I WAS THE NANNY!
I CAN'T RELATE
TO BABIES.
OH, SURE
YOU CAN, RED.
DON'T SELL
YOURSELF SHORT.
YOU'VE GOT A LOT
IN COMMON WITH A BABY...
SOFT HEAD,
TAKE A LOT OF NAPS.
I'M THE LEADER
OF POSSUM LODGE.
I'VE GOT ALL THE
CHILDREN I CAN HANDLE.
LOOK, RED, JUST COME DOWN
WITH ME FOR THE BIG
ANNOUNCEMENT.
THERE'S A WHOLE BUNCH
OF US WHO GOT TURNED DOWN,
AND WE JUST WANNA
STAGE A LITTLE PROTEST
AND MAYBE THEY'LL
CHANGE THEIR MIND.
AND LOOK,
IF THIS DOESN'T WORK,
I PROMISE IT'S
THE END OF IT.
WELL, SOUNDS LIKE A
WASTE OF TIME TO ME.
I'VE BEEN MARRIED
35 YEARS.
PROTESTS DON'T WORK.
LOOK, I'LL DO THE YELLING.
YOU JUST COME ALONG
FOR MORAL SUPPORT.
COME ON,
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
ALL RIGHT.
RED, LOOK, I GOTTA
HAVE THIS BABY.
I NEED AN HEIR.
YOU HAVE AN HEIR;
WHAT YOU NEED
IS A SHOWER.
[laughter]
Red: WE DECIDED TO
HAVE A LITTLE BASKETBALL
SHOOTING COMPETITION
BETWEEN MIKE AND WALTER,
AND I WAS PUTTING DOWN THE
THREE-POINT LINE
DOWN AT THE BASKETBALL
COURT IN TOWN THERE.
OF COURSE, WALTER HAD
THE FULL GEAR ON,
SO MIKE'S TRYING TO ADAPT
HIS OUTFIT TO MATCH --
WOW! HE'S GOT THE
TEAR-AWAY PANTS.
MIKE DOESN'T HAVE --
OH, YES, HE DOES.
THOSE LEGS ARE PRETTY
DARNED WHITE OVER THERE.
SO I WAS EXPLAINING I HAD
DONE THE THREE-POINT
ACCORDING TO THE OFFICIAL
RULE BOOK OF PRO BASKETBALL.
SO WALTER'S GONNA GO FIRST.
WE'RE GONNA GIVE TWO
POINTS A PIECE FOR THESE.
THAT'S A LITTLE SHORT.
LITTLE SHORT THERE, WALTER.
LET'S SEE HOW MIKE CAN DO.
OBVIOUSLY HE DOESN'T HAVE ANY
FRICTION TO HOLD HIM BACK.
OKAY, VERY SIMILAR
TYPE OF SHOT,
SO THAT'D BE
ZERO-ZERO SO FAR.
SO I'M THINKING LET'S
MAKE THIS A LITTLE EASIER.
INSTEAD OF GOING
WITH PRO BASKETBALL,
LET'S GO WITH THE COLLEGE
BASKETBALL HANDBOOK.
GOT A LITTLE CLOSER LINE.
SO AGAIN WALTER GOES.
THIS SHOULD GO
A LOT BETTER.
I'M FEELING REALLY
GOOD ABOUT THIS.
OKAY, AWAY YOU GO.
SHOOT HER UP THERE.
NOPE.
NO BETTER.
SO NOW MIKE TRIES
A DIFFERENT APPROACH,
THE UNDERHAND, GIRLIE
APPROACH HE LEARNED IN PRISON
AND YOU SEE,
HE SHOT IT BACK -- OH!
ALL RIGHT, SO HE TOOK
THE ARIEL OFF THE VAN,
AND HE WRECKED THE BALL.
NOW WALTER'S FIGURING HE
SHOULD WIN BY DEFAULT,
BECAUSE THERE CAN
BE NO MORE COMPETITION
BECAUSE WE DON'T
HAVE A BALL.
MIKE SAYS, WAIT A SEC.
I'LL GET ANOTHER BALL.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
SO HE SEES -- THERE'S SOME
POOR LITTLE KID PLAYING
TETHER BALL,
AND NOT BOTHERING ANYBODY.
AND MIKE COMES IN,
AND THIS IS CALLED BARTER
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO
ARE NEW TO THE COUNTRY.
AND TAKES THAT,
AND HE'S GONE.
SO HE COMES BACK.
NOW I'M ABANDONING THE
COLLEGE LINE.
WE'RE GOING TODDLERS -- THE
TODDLERS THREE-POINT LINE.
OH!
HERE'S MIKE.
MIKE'S ALL SET.
AND UP AND...
AND IT'S GOOD!
YEAH, TWO POINTS.
ALL RIGHT.
SO WALTER, NO PROBLEM.
LET'S SEE HOW HE DOES.
HE'S GONNA SHOW OFF
A LITTLE BIT.
INSTEAD OF DOING A JUMP SHOT,
HE'S GONNA DO THE KAREEM
ABDUL-JABBAR HOOK JOB.
PERFECT!
THERE'S TWO.
WELL, WE'RE ALL
TIED UP AT TWO POINTS.
OH, NO, WE DON'T NEED THAT.
DON'T NEED ANY OF THAT.
THERE'S NO NEED FOR
THAT KIND OF THING.
SO MIKE'S GOT A PLAN.
HE GOES -- THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, MIKE.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
OH, IT'S SOME KIND OF
A TRICK SHOT, I'M THINKING.
OH, I KNOW, HE'S GONNA
LOOK IN THE MIRROR.
OH, YEAH.
OVER THE SHOULDER.
MY GOSH.
THIS SHOULD BE GOOD.
AND... BEAUTIFUL!
BEAUTIFUL.
RIGHT THROUGH.
THERE'S FOUR POINTS.
SO THAT'S A CHALLENGE TO --
ALL RIGHT, WE DON'T
NEED THAT.
WE DON'T NEED
THAT ATTITUDE.
NOW A CHALLENGE TO WALTER
SO HE TAKES THE CHALLENGE
AND RUNS WITH IT.
HE TAKES THE ROPE
RIGHT OFF THERE.
AND HE'S GONNA USE
THE MIRROR.
NO, HE'S NOT.
OH, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, WALTER.
TOTALLY WITHOUT LOOKING,
AND SHE'S IN!
WE GOT A FOUR-POINT TIE.
ALRIGHT. NOW WE MOVE ON TO
THE LAY-UP SECTION.
AND -- SLAM DUNK
LOOK AT THIS  AND HE'S UP
AND -- BOY, BEAUTIFUL.
BEAUTIFUL.
BOY, HE'S GOT GREAT --
WELL, HE TAKES THE
NET WITH HIM.
IT'LL BE TOUGH FOR
MIKE TO TOP THIS ONE,
BUT HE'S GOT A PLAN.
HE GOES DOWN
TO THE BOAT HOUSE
AND GETS ONE OF THE
CANOE PADDLES.
HE'S GOT AN OLD
BUNGEE ON THERE,
AND HE TIES THE TETHER BALL
ONTO THE BUNGEE CORD.
DON'T KNOW WHAT HE'S
GOT IN MIND THERE.
AND HE GOES DOWN
OVER THE BACK AND --
OH, IT'S A PADDLE BALL!
AND HE'S RACKING 'EM UP!
OH, MY GOSH!
IT'S ALL OVER, FOLKS.
[applause]
THIS IS THE PART OF THE SHOW
WHERE WE FEATURE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
audience: I DON'T KNOW!
AND TODAY'S LETTER
READS AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS, I PRIDE
MYSELF IN KEEPING UP"
"WITH CURRENT TRENDS AND FADS,
NO MATTER HOW FLEETING
THEY MIGHT BE"
"RECENTLY I READ IN THE PAPER
ABOUT SOMETHING CALLED"
"THE INTERNET"
"WHAT'S THAT?"
WHAT'S THE INTERNET?
BOY, THAT MUST'VE BEEN
SOME KIND OF COMA, HUH?
YEAH. ALL RIGHT, WELL,
THE INTERNET IS SOMETHING
THAT CONNECTS TO
YOUR COMPUTER
SO THAT YOU CAN CONTACT
EVERYBODY IN THE WORLD
WHO WANTS TO SELL
YOU SOMETHING.
NO, THAT'S NOT NECESSARILY
TRUE, UNCLE RED.
NO, THE INTERNET IS PROBABLY
THE MOST IMPORTANT INNOVATION
FOR COMMUNICATION, EDUCATION,
SINCE THE MOVABLE TYPE.
I SPEND HOURS ON
THE INTERNET.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW YOU
HAD A COMPUTER, DALTON.
OH, GOSH, YES.
I JUST FIND THERE IS SO MUCH
FASCINATING INFORMATION
ON THE INTERNET.
ABSOLUTELY, YES.
THE UNFORTUNATE ASPECT IS HOW
MUCH PORNOGRAPHY'S ON THERE.
WELL, YOU KNOW, SOME PEOPLE,
THAT'S ALL THEY USE IT FOR.
[laughter]
WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKIN' AT ME FOR?
I DON'T DO ANY OF THAT.
WELL, AT LEAST,
NOT INTENTIONALLY.
NOT VERY OFTEN.
LOOK, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
ANN MARIE WANTED TO
RE-MODEL THE KITCHEN, RIGHT?
SO I DID A SEARCH FOR
"PANTRIES."
BUT THERE WAS A TYPO.
[laughter]
THAT'S NOT WHAT THE
INTERNET'S FOR,
MR. DALTON.
LOOK, IT WAS AN
ACCIDENT, ALL RIGHT?
AND BESIDES, IT'S PRIVATE.
WHO'S GONNA KNOW?
WELL, ANYBODY WHO HAS
ACCESS TO THE COMPUTER.
STORED SOMEWHERE IN YOUR
COMPUTER IS EVERY WEBSITE
YOU'VE EVER VISITED.
EVERY ONE?
Harold: EVERY ONE.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU HAD
A COMPUTER, DALTON?
UM, I-IT'S ANN MARIE'S.
I GOTTA GO!
YOU BETTER CALL ROTHSCHILD'S
SEWAGE TODAY,
'CAUSE THAT SOGGY MESS
IS HERE TO STAY.
WHATEVER GOES UP
COMES DOWN, THEY SAY.
BUT WHATEVER GOES DOWN,
DOESN'T ALWAYS GO AWAY.
[applause]
OKAY, I WOULD SUGGEST THAT
IF ANY OF YOU EVER GO
TO A PROTEST
THAT YOU FIND OUT WHAT
THE PROTEST IS ABOUT
BEFORE YOU GET THERE.
IT WAS ABOUT THE
RIGHT TO ADOPT A CHILD.
YEAH, OKAY, AND
I WAS FINE WITH THAT.
I JUST WAS A LITTLE
SURPRISED WHEN I REALISED
THAT WASN'T THE MAIN AGENDA.
WELL, THAT OUGHTA
KEEP HIM OUTTA MY TENT.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE ALL
JUST PEOPLE, RED.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT IT
WAS GOOD TO SHOW OUR
SOLIDARITY.
YEAH, I KNOW. I WAS FINE
WITH THAT.
BUT DID YOU
HAVE TO PUT YOUR
ARM AROUND ME, WINSTON?
RED, I WAS UPSET.
IT WAS OBVIOUS THAT THEY
WEREN'T GONNA LET ME ADOPT.
THEY WERE DISCRIMINATING
AGAINST MY
ENTREPRENEURIAL LIFESTYLE.
NO, THEY WERE NOT.
THEY WERE PROTECTING
AN INNOCENT CHILD.
THEY WANTED THE CHILD TO BE
RAISED IN A LOVING ATMOSPHERE.
YOU LOVE YOUR JOB.
AND YOUR ATMOSPHERE
IS TOXIC.
WELL, NOW WHAT AM
I GONNA DO
WITH THE FAMILY BUSINESS
AND NO CHILD TO TAKE IT ON?
I MEAN, SEPTIC SUCKING
IS NOT SOMETHING
YOU JUST FALL INTO, RED.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF YOU WANNA
IMMORTALIZE YOURSELF,
WHY DON'T YOU ADD YOUR FACE TO
THE LOGO OF THE COMPANY?
YOU KNOW, LIKE
COLONEL SANDERS.
YOU COULD BECOME THE
COLONEL SANDERS OF
SEPTIC SUCKING.
THAT'S A PRETTY
GOOD IDEA, RED.
OH, YEAH. EVERY TIME PEOPLE
SAW YOUR FACE,
THEY'D THINK OF SEWAGE.
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE. ALL RIGHT?
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
LET ME RE-PHRASE THAT.
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND THE
WHOLE GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
[possum squealing]
EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN.
EVERYBODY SIT.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
THESE FLOWERS
CAME FOR YOU, MR. GREEN.
THEY'RE FROM
AN ADMIRER.
THANKS, DOUG.