ONE OF THE DIFFERENCES
BETWEEN MEN AND WOMEN
IS THAT MEN WILL
SELL ANYTHING,
THEIR PARENTS' HOUSE,
THEIR KIDS' REPORT CARD,
THEIR BODY FLUIDS.
MEN TEND TO PUT
EVERYTHING INTO
FINANCIAL TERMS.
A WOMAN WILL SAY,
WOW, THAT'S BEAUTIFUL,
WHEREAS A MAN WILL SAY,
WOW, WHAT DID THAT
SET YOU BACK.
MOST GUYS WOULD RATHER
MAKE BIG BUCKS
DOING SOMETHING THEY HATE,
THAN MAKE A COMFORTABLE
LIVING DOING SOMETHING
THEY LOVE.
IT'S NOT SMART
OR CORRECT
BUT IT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT MAKES
US WHAT WE ARE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
Red Green:
WELL, WE GOT A GREAT
SHOW FOR YOU THIS TIME.
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO TURN A FURNACE
INTO A POPCORN MAKER
TO INSULATE YOUR HOUSE,
I'M GOING TO BE
SPLITTING SOME LOGS,
SO I'LL GET RID OF
MY VALUABLES OFF THE BENCH,
DOUGIE FRANKLIN WILL BE
ALONG WITH A FEW WORDS OF,
WELL, JUST WORDS,
AND BILL AND I ARE
GOING INTO THE WOODS
FOR A BIG SURPRISE.
AND NOW HERE IS THE RICARDO
MONTALBAN OF DUCK HUNTING,
MY UNCLE RED GREEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AND NOW HERE IS THE
HERVE VILLECHAIZE
OF BASKETBALL,
MY NEPHEW HAROLD.
ODD THING
HAPPENED TO JUNIOR
SINGLETON THIS WEEK.
A COUPLE FROM THE
CITY COME RIGHT UP
TO HIS FRONT DOOR,
OFFERED HIM 200
BUCKS FOR HIS WOOD PILE.
THAT WOOD PILE IS
COVERED IN ANTS.
WHAT DID THEY WANT
THAT THING FOR?
JUNIOR DIDN'T ASK, HAROLD.
ONCE HE HEARD 200
BUCKS THAT PRETTY MUCH
ENDED THE
DISCUSSION.
HE JUST GRABBED THE
MONEY AND STARTED
THROWING THE WOOD
INTO THE CAR,
WHICH WASN'T
ALL THAT EASY,
THEY HAD TWO
PHONES IN THERE.
WHY WOULD YOU HAVE
TWO PHONES IN YOUR
CAR, HAROLD?
WELL, ONE MIGHT
BE A FAX LINE.
OF COURSE, YOU
KNOW, HE MIGHT HAVE
TWO LINES AND ONE PHONE,
YOU KNOW, THAT
WAY YOU COULD TALK
TO TWO PEOPLE
AT ONE TIME, YEAH.
OH, AND YOU
KNOW WHAT ELSE?
IF HE HAD CALL WAITING,
FOUR PEOPLE AT ONE TIME.
OH, CONFERENCE CALLING,
CONFERENCE CALLING.
IF HE HAS THAT, HE
COULD HOOK UP EVERYBODY
ALTOGETHER AT ONE TIME.
SO IF YOU HAVE
TWO PHONES YOU DON'T
NEED ANY FRIENDS, RIGHT?
BASICALLY, YES.
YOU SHOULD LOOK INTO
THAT YOURSELF, HAROLD.
I WAS WONDERING ABOUT
CITY PEOPLE BUYING
FIREWOOD
BUT APPARENTLY NOW
WITH A LOT OF
THESE CONDOS
THEY HAVE A FIREPLACE
IN THE LIVING ROOM
OR THE DINING ROOM
OR EVEN THE BEDROOM.
THERE'S A SAD COMMENTARY
WHEN YOU GOT TO HEAT
UP YOUR BEDROOM
BY STICKING
SOMETHING IN THE WALL.
UNCLE RED, THESE ARE
MAJORLY SUCCESSFUL PEOPLE.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
MOVERS AND SHAKERS HERE.
WELL, WE HAVE MOVERS
AND SHAKERS AT THE LODGE.
NO, NO, THEY'RE MORE LIKE
WADDLERS AND TWITCHERS.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
PEOPLE WITH MONEY.
PEOPLE WE SHOULD HAVE
HERE AT THE LODGE.
NOW WAIT A
MINUTE, HAROLD,
ALL WE WANT TO DO
IS SELL THEM EVERY
STICK OF FIREWOOD
WE CAN GET OUR HANDS ON.
WE WANT THEIR MONEY,
NOT THEIR COMPANY.
NO WONDER THE TOURIST
INDUSTRY IS DYING A
DEATH AROUND HERE.
THAT'S THE
WAY I LIKE IT.
IF YOU GET
TOURISTS AND
SIGHTSEERS,
YOU GOT TO HAVE
SIGHTS FOR THEM TO SEE
AND NEXT THING YOU KNOW
YOU'RE TALKING QUAINT.
YOU KNOW HOW
I FEEL ABOUT QUAINT.
I'D RATHER JUST
RAKE IN AS MUCH
MONEY AS WE CAN
AND THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE GOING TO DO
WITH THIS FIREWOOD THING.
OH, YEAH, OKAY, BUT
THEN THERE WON'T BE
ANY TREES LEFT.
WHO CARES, WE'LL HAVE
ENOUGH MONEY TO BUY MORE.
EXCUSE ME, WOULD
THE OWNER OF A 1964
PONTIAC STRADO CHIEF
JUST COME AND GET ME
WHEN HE WANTS TO LEAVE,
I JUST GOT TO GET MY
MONSTER TRUCK DOWN OFF IT.
TRAPPER JACK
WAS HUNTING BEAR
A DANGEROUS HOBBY AT BEST
THEY BROUGHT HIM BACK
TO THE DOCTOR IN TOWN
AND HE WAS A
HECK OF A MESS
THERE WAS SOME
ASSEMBLY REQUIRED
MOSTLY TEETH AND
BONES AND HAIR.
JACK HAD ALWAYS BEEN
GOOD WITH A KNIFE
BUT UNFORTUNATELY
NOT QUITE AS
GOOD AS THE BEAR.
WELL, YOU'RE GOING
TO END UP ON THE
COUCH THIS TIME.
YEAH, SHE'S TAKEN
A NIGHT COURSE
MAKING CRAFTS.
CREATED A DRIED
FLOWER ARRANGEMENT,
HUNG IT ON THE WALL
AND YOU SAID, "WELL,
THAT LOOKS SILLY".
THE THREE WORDS YOU
SHOULD NEVER SAY
TO THE WOMAN YOU
LOVE FOR ANY REASON.
DON'T EVER
SAY SOMETHING LOOKS
SILLY TO A WOMAN EVER.
I'M SURE IT'S A
BUNCH OF DRIED WEEDS
AND FLOWERS AND
STICKS PAINTED GOLD,
JAMMED INTO A HUNK
OF GREEN FOAM.
SOMETHING YOU'D
SWEEP OFF THE LANEWAY.
BUT YOU WENT AND
YOU CALLED IT SILLY
AND NOW WE'RE GOING
TO HELP BAIL YOU OUT.
NOW, YOU TELL
HER YOU'VE GOT AN
OPTOMETRIST APPOINTMENT.
YOU COME HOME
AN HOUR LATER
ACTING LIKE YOU
GOT NEW GLASSES.
MAKE A SPECIAL POINT
OF LOOKING AT HER
DRIED KINDLING
THINGY AGAIN.
YOU SAY SOMETHING
LIKE, "OH, I SEE IT NOW.
"WHAT WAS I THINKING?
I LIKE THAT.
"I REALLY LIKE THE
WAY THE BIG THINGS
"ARE CRUSHING THE
LITTLE THINGS THERE.
"IS THAT THE REAL
RAGWEED ON THAT?
"BY GOLLY, THAT IS AN
ATTRACTIVE UNIT THERE.
"WHAT'S SAY WE TAKE
DOWN THE PICTURE OF
THE DOGS PLAYING POKER
AND POP THAT
BABY UP THERE"?
YOU DON'T WANT TO
GO OVERBOARD, THOUGH,
IT MAKES HER SUSPICIOUS.
NO. NO.
THAT'S RIGHT.
ACTUALLY, MAYBE GIVE
IT A LITTLE BIT OF TIME,
SHE'LL START BUILDING
SOMETHING THAT MAYBE
WILL BE HALF
DECENT, YOU KNOW?
OR SHE MAY GIVE
IT UP ALL TOGETHER,
GO BACK TO PLAYING
BINGO AND MAKE SOME MONEY.
EITHER WAY YOU WIN.
JUST GIVE IT A LITTLE TIME.
NEVER SAY SAY
THAT ANYTHING
SHE DOES IS SILLY.
NO, OTHERWISE SHE
MIGHT MENTION THAT
SPICE RACK YOU BUILT HER.
OR THAT NEW FISHING HAT.
OR THAT SILLY
LODGE YOU JOINED.
WELL, THIS WEEK WITH
THE GUYS ALL OUT THERE
CUTTING DOWN TREES
AND CHOPPING IT UP
INTO FIREWOOD,
I THOUGHT I WOULD TAKE
THE HANDYMAN CORNER
AND TEACH YOU ALL
HOW TO SPLIT LOGS.
OKAY.
FIRST THING
YOU WANT TO DO
IS STAND THE LOG UP
STRAIGHT ON A FLAT
SURFACE THERE.
AND OF COURSE
YOU WANT TO CLEAR
ALL THE STUFF OUT
OF THE WAY THAT'S
AROUND THE THING.
YOU TAKE A FULL
SWING WITH AN AXE
AND COME DOWN ON
SOMETHING LIKE A VICE
AND THE HAIR WILL
STAND UP SO FAR ON
THE BACK OF YOUR NECK
YOU CAN CARD
WOOL ON IT.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE ALL
SET TO GO HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, YOU ALWAYS
WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT THE AREA
BEHIND YOU IS
CLEARED OUT AS WELL.
YEAH, WE'RE FINE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S
TRY THAT AGAIN.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
SO THAT'S THE WAY
YOU WANT TO PLAY IT, HUH?
THERE'S ACTUALLY A
SAFER AND MORE UPSCALE WAY
TO SPLIT FIREWOOD AND
THAT IS TO TAKE
SOMETHING HERE
WHICH IS CALLED A WEDGE
FROM THE LATIN WORD WEDGY,
WHICH MEANS TO
SPLIT OR RENT ASUNDER.
SO YOU JUST GET THAT
STARTED INTO THE LOG.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT'S HAPPENED THERE
IS THAT SOMEHOW MY THUMB
MANAGED TO GET IN BETWEEN
THE HAMMER AND THE WEDGE,
WHICH IS ACTUALLY NOT
A GOOD PLACE FOR
A THUMB TO BE.
ONE OF THE SIGNS
OF A TRUE HANDYMAN
IS HIS ABILITY TO
CONTROL HIS TEMPER.
RIGHT NOW I'M FEELING
PRETTY DARN PROUD
OF MYSELF.
MIND YOU, THERE'S
ALWAYS ROOM FOR
IMPROVEMENT.
Red Green:
COMING UP WE GOT
BILL OUT IN THE WOODS
MAKING SOME KIND
OF TROUBLE
AND RANGER GORD HAS
GOT A BRAND NEW GAME.
WELL, OPERATION FIREWOOD
IS OFF TO A FLYING START.
GOT ALL THE
AXES SHARPENED UP
AND WE'RE GOING
THROUGH CHAINSAW GAS
LIKE THE
RECESSION IS OVER.
WELL, I HOPE YOU'RE
BEING RESPECTFUL OF
THE ENVIRONMENT
AND CUTTING DOWN TREES
THAT ONLY NEED TO
BE REMOVED
DUE TO DISEASE AND
DEATH AND THE PROPER
THINNING OF A FOREST.
WELL, WE'RE USING THE
HUNDRED TO ONE
RATIO, HAROLD,
FOR EVERY HUNDRED OAK TREES,
WE ONLY CUT DOWN ONE.
I ONLY WISH I HAD
A HUNDRED NEPHEWS.
WELL, LET'S NOT FORGET
OUR SAFETY PRECAUTIONS,
UNCLE RED,
STEEL-TOED BOOTS,
PROTECTIVE EYEWEAR
AND TYING OFF THE TREES
SO THEY FALL CORRECTLY.
TOO MUCH WORK, HAROLD.
SO WE STAND
70 FEET APART.
THAT WAY EVERY MAN
GETS HIS OWN TREE,
YOU DON'T HAVE SOME
GOOF COMING IN AT
HE LAST MINUTE
AND FINISHING HER OFF
WHEN YOU DID ALL
THE WORK TO GET
HER THAT CLOSE.
WELL, HOW MANY TREES
DO YOU PLAN TO ASSAULT?
50 A DAY, EVERY
DAY, DAY AFTER DAY
UNTIL WE'RE TOO
TIRED TO DO ANYMORE.
WOW, THAT WILL GIVE
YOU A GRAND TOTAL OF 50.
YOU ROLLING
THERE, HAROLD?
ALL RIGHT,
WE'RE HERE WITH OUR
FRIEND RANGER GORD.
HI RED.
HI HAROLD.
YEAH, HI THERE, GORD.
GORD, WE'RE GETTING
KIND OF BOGGED DOWN
WITH THE FIREWOOD
PROJECT THERE.
I WONDER IF YOU
COULD DO US A FAVOUR,
GO OUT INTO THE WOODS
AND MAKE A LITTLE X
ON ALL THE TREES THAT
ARE EASY TO CUT DOWN.
COULD YOU DO THAT?
WELL, THAT SOUNDS LIKE
YOU NEED TO KNOW
MORE ABOUT THE FLORA.
OH, NO, NO,
I KNOW FLORA.
EVERYBODY KNOWS
FLORA, RIGHT GLEN?
NO, I MEAN THE
FLORA IN THE WOODS.
AND YOU CAN
LEARN ALL ABOUT
THE FLORA IN THE WOODS
BY PLAYING THIS
GAME I INVENTED.
IT'S CALLED GRABITAT.
DO YOU GET IT?
GRABITAT BECAUSE
YOU REACH IN
AND YOU GRAB SOMETHING
FROM YOUR HABITAT.
I DON'T WANT TO PLAY
SOME DUMB GAME, GORD.
I WANT TO GO
CUT DOWN TREES.
PLAY ONE GAME
AND I'LL MARK
10 TREES FOR YOU.
DEAL.
GRABITAT IS FUN,
YOU JUST REACH IN AND
YOU PULL SOMETHING OUT,
AND IF YOU CAN IDENTIFY
IT, IT'S WORTH 5 POINTS.
OKAY, THAT'S PINE.
5 POINTS FOR ME.
YOUR TURN, RED.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SEE WHAT
YOU GOT IN HERE.
THERE WE GO.
IT'S I GUESS THAT
WOULD BE A STICK, RIGHT?
YOU GOT THE DOGWOOD.
WHAT'S SO FUNNY
ABOUT DOGWOOD?
SMELL IT.
OH, THAT'S FUNNY.
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE YOU
WANT YOUR GAME
TO BE FUNNY
IF YOU WANT IT
TO BE POPULAR.
YOU KNOW, I THINK
THIS IS GOING TO BE
A GREAT HIT
WITH THE KIDS
BECAUSE THEY CAN LEARN
ALL ABOUT THE ENVIRONMENT.
I'M GOING TO SELL
IT AT ALL THOSE STORES
THAT SELL BIRTH SHOES.
OKAY, JUST A MINUTE.
THAT'S SUMAC.
5 POINTS FOR ME.
YOUR TURN, RED.
NO PROBLEM.
OH, NO, I
KNOW THIS ONE.
THAT'S MINT.
NO, IT'S NOT.
I'VE SEEN
THAT LEAF BEFORE.
ALL RIGHT, YOU
GOT ME, WHAT IS IT?
POISON IVY.
THIS IS THE HOME
RENOVATION FEATURE
WHERE WE SHOW
YOU HOW TO MAKE
YOUR HOUSE MORE HOMELY.
AND THIS HERE
OF COURSE IS MIKE.
MIKE HELPS US OUT
WITH THESE PARTS
OF THE SHOW.
WELL, MR. GREEN, HE
SURE HELPED ME OUT.
HE JUST SAVED
MY LIFE IS ALL.
MIKE IS WITH
THE, YOU KNOW,
ONE OF THE PRISONER
REHAB DEAL THINGS.
THIS MAN IS A SAINT.
THAT'S ALL I'M
GOING TO SAY ABOUT IT.
OKAY.
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW
YOU A GREAT WAY TO
INSULATE YOUR HOME.
YEAH, THAT'S IT, MIKE.
YOU HEAR ABOUT
VERMICULITE IN THE FOAM
AND THE FIBERGLASS
AND SO ON.
WHAT WE LIKE IS THE
INDUSTRIAL GRADE POPCORN.
IT'S GOT A HIGH
R-FACTOR, YOU KNOW.
LOW IN CHOLESTEROL.
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
AND ALL YOU HAVE TO
DO IS USE THE HEATING
SYSTEM IN YOUR HOUSE
TO BLOW -- NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO --
TO BLOW THIS STUFF UP
INTO THE EXTERIOR WALLS.
SO THE FIRST STEP
IS TO TAKE THE END
PANEL OFF YOUR FURNACE.
YEAH.
HERE, I WILL SHOW
YOU HOW IT'S DONE.
SEE I'M LEARNING, EH?
I SAID THE
END PANEL HERE.
OH, I CAN'T
BELIEVE IT.
I'M SORRY.
NO. NO.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I
WILL GET THIS BACK ON.
NO PROBLEM.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
NOW, WHAT YOU WANT TO
DO TO TURN YOUR FURNACE
INTO A HOT AIR
POPCORN POPPER,
YOU GOT TO TAKE A WAD OF
THE HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE, AND YOU WANT
TO JUST BALL THAT UP
AROUND THE FAN BELT
THERE SO THAT WHEN
SHE GETS GOING,
SHE'LL VIBRATE
UP ON YOU
AND THAT WAY THE
KERNELS WON'T BURN TOO
BAD IN THE HEATING CHAMBER.
I'LL GET IT.
IT'S STICKY.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
IT KEEPS
STICKING TO ITSELF.
MAYBE WE'LL
JUST USE SOME ROPE.
HERE YOU PULL.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
WHY DON'T I COME
THROUGH THIS WAY?
I THINK IF YOU CAME
AROUND THE OTHER WAY --
ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS WORKING
AGAINST ME SOMEHOW.
HOW MUCH DUCT
TAPE HAVE WE GOT?
TWO MORE DUCTS.
THIS WILL ALL MAKE
SENSE AT A LATER
DATE, I PROMISE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW THE
POPCORN IS GOING TO POP
THROUGH ALL
THE FLOOR VENTS,
SO YOU WANT TO TAKE
THE COVERS OFF --
Mike:
THAT'S ALL OF THEM.
OH SORRY.
OH GEEZ.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
I'M FINE, THANKS.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS CUT A HOLE IN THE
WALL ABOUT 8 INCHES
ABOVE THE FLOOR
AND LINE THESE TWO
RIGHT UP SO THAT
THE POPCORN CAN
CONTINUE RIGHT ON UP
AND GO UP AND FILL
UP YOUR EXTERIOR WALL.
SO WHAT YOU NEED
IS A LITTLE BIT OF
TEMPORARY DUCT WORK.
AND YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU CAN USE IS
A BOOT BOX LIKE THIS,
CUT THE ENDS OUT OF IT,
AND THEN IT'S LONG ENOUGH
TO JOIN UP THE TWO HOLES.
YOU SHOULD CUT
THE ENDS OFF.
I CUT THE SIDES OFF.
YEAH, THAT'S...
KIND OF SHORT.
YEAH.
I'M USELESS.
I'M JUST USELESS.
WELL, WE'LL COME BACK
A LITTLE LATER IN THE SHOW
AND WE'LL GET
HER ALL RIGGED UP.
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
Mike:
I'M USELESS!
Red Green:
TIME FOR
ADVENTURES WITH BILL
OUT IN THE WOODS,
WHERE ELSE?
WHERE ARE YOU BILL?
WHERE ARE YOU?
HE'S AROUND SOMEWHERE.
YEAH, THERE HE IS.
WELL, LOOK AT
ALL THOSE AXES.
WITH THE PICK YOUR OWN
FIREWOOD PROJECT AND SO ON,
BILL DECIDED HE WAS
GOING TO KIND OF SHOW US
HOW TO DO THINGS
AND CUT STUFF UP
AND I GUESS HOW
TO THROW AN AXE
FROM ONE END OF THE
WOODS TO THE OTHER.
OKAY, BILL,
WE'VE SEEN THAT.
THE OTHER AXE IS...
YEAH.
BILL DOESN'T GET A LOT
DONE IN A DAY, I GUESS,
WHEN HE'S WORKING
IN THE LUMBER --
HE'S KIND OF A
LUMBERING GUY,
YOU'D THINK THAT HE --
ANYWAY, YOU GOT
THE OTHER AXE?
BILL, WHAT ABOUT
THE OTHER AXES?
YEAH, GOOD IDEA.
GOOD IDEA, BILL.
SO WE GOT THE OTHER
AXES AND OUT WE GO.
AND I WONDER WHERE
THE OTHER ONE WENT ANYWAY.
WHO KNOWS.
OH, THERE IT IS.
THERE IT IS.
OH, THAT'S HANDY.
NOW, THE THING ABOUT
DOING WORK LIKE CUTTING
UP LOGS AND EVERYTHING,
YOU GOT TO
MAKE IT FUN.
THAT'S THE TRICK OF IT.
YOU GOT TO, YOU KNOW --
THERE WE GO.
AND YOU TURN IT
INTO A SPORT.
I THINK IT WAS MARY
POPPINS WHO SAID, YOU KNOW,
JUST A SPOON FULL
OF SWINGING AN AXE
MAKES YOUR LEG GO DOWN
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I FORGET.
BUT, YOU KNOW, WHY DON'T
WE JUST CHOP UP THE LOG.
GET RIGHT UP.
OH. OH.
GET RIGHT UP THERE
ON TOP OF IT,
YOU KNOW, AND YOU CAN
SING ONE OF THOSE
LUMBERJACK TUNES
AND JUST KIND OF GET
YOURSELF INTO A REAL BIG --
BOY, THAT IS BIG FUN.
ALL RIGHT.
SOME PARTS OF IT MAYBE
AREN'T AS ENJOYABLE
AS SOME OF THE OTHERS.
I'M SURE HE'S FINE.
APPARENTLY YOU DON'T
NEED ALL YOUR TOES.
AND BILL IS
CUTTING THAT UP.
AND, YOU KNOW, I TELL
YOU IT'S GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU GET IN TERRIFIC
CONDITION I WOULD THINK
IF YOU DID THIS ON
A REGULAR BASIS.
WE'RE HACKING AWAY,
HAVING A GOOD
TIME, FEELING GOOD.
I DON'T THINK WE'VE
HAD THIS MUCH FUN IN
THE WOODS SINCE THE FIRE.
THERE WE GO.
THERE'S THE SECRET.
YEAH.
THAT'S PROGRESS.
AND BILL CUTS IT
RIGHT DOWN THERE.
AND HE DIDN'T FEEL
GOOD ABOUT CUTTING
HER ALL THE WAY THROUGH
BECAUSE IT WAS HIS
OWN CHAINSAW,
SO HE THOUGHT WHAT HE'D
DO IS JUST FINISH HER
OFF WITH AN AXE.
KIND OF A PURIST BILL IS.
UNFORTUNATELY, SHE
WEDGED RIGHT IN THERE.
CAN'T GETG HER OUT.
NOW WHAT DO WE DO?
WE'RE RUNNING
SHORT ON AXES HERE.
SO BILL'S GOT AN IDEA.
HE FIGURES IF WE
EACH GET ON EACH
END OF THE LOG
AND START BOUNCING,
YOU KNOW,
WITH THE WEIGHT AND SO
ON IT WILL BE ABLE
TO SPRING THAT AXE
RIGHT OUT OF THERE.
IT DIDN'T SOUND LIKE
THAT WOULD WORK TO ME.
BUT I DIDN'T FEEL LIKE
THINKING OF ANYTHING
ELSE SO AWAY WE GO
AND IT CERTAINLY SPLIT --
OH, YEAH, THERE WE GO.
IT'S WORKING.
WHAT ABOUT THE AXE THOUGH?
DID THE AXE COME OUT?
YES, IT DID.
THERE WE GO.
Red Green:
COMING UP WE
GOT WINSTON ROTHSCHILD,
KING OF THE HOSERS,
AND, DON'T WORRY,
WE GOT THE POPCORN
INSULATION PROJECT
TOTALLY UNDER CONTROL.
WELL, THERE DOESN'T
SEEM TO BE AN EASY WAY
TO TURN TREES
INTO FIREWOOD.
OUR WINDOW
OF OPPORTUNITY
IS CLOSING FAST.
CARPE DIEM, UNCLE RED.
WHAT?
CARPE DIEM.
SEIZE THE DAY.
YOU'RE CLOSE, HAROLD,
I SEIZE THE CHAINSAW.
I THINK WE'RE GOING
AT THIS ALL WRONG.
I THINK THE PROFIT
IS IN SELLING THE
RAW MATERIALS,
NOT IN MARKING UP
THE LABOUR COSTS.
I'VE NEVER HEARD YOU
SPEAK IN BUSINESS
TERMS BEFORE.
WELL, WE DON'T
HAVE A BUSINESS
RELATIONSHIP, HAROLD.
WITH YOU IT'S PERSONAL.
THANK YOU.
SO I'M GOING
TO PLAN B.
HAROLD, TELL ME THIS.
WHAT DO PEOPLE FROM
THE CITY LIKE
TO DO MOST?
DRIVE SILVER
COLOURED GERMAN CARS.
NO, I KNOW,
I KNOW THIS ONE.
IT'S PAY TOO MUCH
MONEY FOR CLOTHES.
NO, I KNOW WHAT IT IS,
I KNOW WHAT IT IS,
BUY MUTUAL FUNDS.
OKAY, I DON'T KNOW.
PICK YOUR OWN
STRAWBERRIES, HAROLD.
NO, NO, NO, HAROLD.
THAT'S WHAT PEOPLE FROM
THE CITY LIKE TO DO.
PICK STRAWBERRIES?
NOT THE STRAWBERRIES,
THE PICKING.
THEY LIKE COMING UP HERE
PRETENDING THEY'RE FARMERS.
PICK YOUR OWN PEACHES,
PICK YOUR OWN APPLES.
WHY NOT PICK
YOUR OWN FIREWOOD?
YOU'RE GOING
TO GIVE THEM A
PRETTY BIG BASKET.
NO, NO, NO, YOU JUST
TAKE THE 300 BUCKS,
HAND THEM AN AXE,
GET THEM TO SIGN
AN INJURY WAIVER
AND POINT THEM
AT A TREE.
A LOT OF PEOPLE GOING
HOME WITHOUT FIREWOOD
OR FINGERS.
I DON'T THINK
THAT MATTERS, HAROLD.
I THINK SOME OF THESE
GUYS WOULD PAY 300 BUCKS
JUST TO WAIL AWAY
AT A PINE FOR AN HOUR.
THEY DON'T GET A CHANCE
TO COMMUNE WITH NATURE
STUCK UP THERE IN
A GLASS TOWER,
BEHIND A STEEL DESK,
PLAYING WITH A PLASTIC
COMPUTER THERE.
SO WHAT YOU'RE SELLING,
THEN, IS STRESS RELIEF.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WHERE ELSE CAN YOU BUY
THERAPY BY THE CORD?
IF MY DAUGHTER IS
WATCHING THIS SHOW,
YOUR MOTHER AND I WOULD
LIKE YOU TO COME BACK.
DID YOU KNOW YOU
TOOK MY CREDIT CARD?
OKAY, WE'RE BACK
WITH THIS WEEK'S
HOME RENOVATION PROJECT,
HOW TO INSULATE YOUR
HOUSE USING POPCORN.
NOW ALL THE VENTS
NEAR THE EXTERIOR WALLS
HAVE BEEN HOOKED
UP EXACTLY LIKE THIS.
NOW, THE FURNACE WILL
BLOW THE POPCORN
UP THROUGH THE TEMPORARY
VENTS AND INTO THE --
INTO THE --
INTO THE WALL.
OKAY, SO WHAT YOU WANT
TO DO IS TO CLOSE UP
ALL THE VENTS
THAT ARE NOT ON
THE OUTSIDE WALLS
AND LEAVE ONE OF THEM
OFF SO THAT YOU CAN
POUR THE POPCORN KERNELS
RIGHT DOWN INTO THE FURNACE.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO LEAVE THIS OFF.
I KNEW THAT.
I'M STUPID.
I'M JUST STUPID.
WE COULD HAVE JUST --
WE COULD HAVE POURED
IT THROUGH THE VENT.
THAT'S FINE.
PUT IT BACK ON?
NO, THAT'S FINE.
THAT WILL WORK.
THAT'S GREAT.
YOU PUT THE POPCORN
DOWN IN THERE.
OKAY.
I GOT IT NOW.
I'M SORRY.
NO PROBLEM.
ONCE YOU GET THE
POPCORN ALL IN THERE,
YOU PUT THE VENT BACK
ON AND YOU CLOSE HER UP.
AND YOU GOT ALL THE
OTHER VENTS CLOSED UP?
YEP.
IT'S ALL SET.
IT'S ALL DONE.
THE POPCORN IS
IN THERE FOR LIFE
OR 25 TO LIFE.
WELL, YOU WOULD KNOW.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW YOU GO OVER TO
YOUR THERMOSTAT HERE
AND YOU TURN HER
UP TO 90 OR 100
OR BASICALLY AS
HIGH AS SHE'LL GO.
ALL RIGHT.
ONCE THE POPPING STOPS,
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS TURN YOUR THERMOSTAT
DOWN TO SOMETHING
REASONABLE
AND YOU WANT TO LOOK
IN THE ATTIC
AND CHECK TO MAKE SURE
THAT THE POPCORN HAS GONE
TO THE TOPS OF ALL
THE EXTERIOR WALLS.
OKAY.
WHEN YOU SAID CLOSE
OFF ALL THE VENTS
YOU MEANT THE ONES
UPSTAIRS, DIDN'T YOU?
YEAH, WELL, YOU PICK
UP THE POPCORN,
I'LL GO RENT US A MOVIE.
HEY, THAT BIRDMAN OF
ALCATRAZ IS PRETTY FUNNY.
FOR SALE:
OH BOY,
86 PLYM RELY, FRNT WHL DRV,
FACT AIR, CUSTOM POLE,
AM/FM CASS, BLO HEAT,
MINT CON,
CON STINK PETE AF 6.
I'VE SEEN THAT CAR.
P CRAP.
WELL, NOW THAT
WE'RE GOING AHEAD
WITH THE PICK YOUR
OWN FIREWOOD PROJECT,
WE THOUGHT WE SHOULD
TALK TO OUR RESIDENT
TYCOON TO BE,
WINSTON ROTHSCHILD.
HOW YOU DOING WINSTON?
HEY RED.
WINSTON, YOU WOULD BE
AWFUL PROUD OF US UP
AT THE LODGE.
WE'VE FINALLY TAKEN THAT
GET UP AND GO BUSINESS
ADVICE OF YOURS,
WE'VE APPLIED IT
TO A PROJECT
THAT'S GOING TO
MAKE US MILLIONS.
RED, YOU SEE WHAT I SEE
WHEN I LOOK IN THIS
SEPTIC HOLE?
LOOK, THAT'S MY FUTURE,
AND IT'S TWIRLING AROUND
AND IT'S GOING RIGHT
UP THAT HOSE.
MY OLD MAN WAS
RIGHT, I'M USELESS.
OH, COME ON
NOW, WINSTON, DON'T
GET DOWN ON YOURSELF.
AND IT ALL STARTED
WITH THAT GENIUS
WHO INVENTED PICK
YOUR OWN FRUIT
AND THEN IT'S PICK
YOUR OWN VEGETABLES
AND CHOP YOUR OWN
CHRISTMAS TREE
AND NOYOUSE GUYS
ARE CHOPPING YOUR
OWN FIREWOOD.
I MEAN, THAT'S JUST GOING
TO BE THE FINAL BLOW,
SUCK YOUR OWN SEWAGE.
AND THEN I'M GOING
TO BE OUT OF WORK,
WALKING AROUND WITH
A SIGN TACKED ON TO
SOME TOILET PLUNGER
THAT SAYS "WILL SUCK
HOLDING TANK FOR FOOD".
OH GEEZ, I'LL TELL YOU,
MY DRAINING DAYS
ARE NUMBERED.
AND I'LL DIE
IN AN OFFICE JOB.
I HATE THE SMELL
OF AIR CONDITIONING.
WELL, NOW WINSTON,
IF YOU'RE RIGHT
AND EVERYBODY IS
JUMPING ON TO THIS
SEWAGE DRAINING
BANDWAGON THING,
YOU COULD HIRE YOURSELF
OUT AS A CONSULTANT, HUH?
OH, YOU MEAN LIKE
ROTHSCHILD SEWAGE
AND SEPTIC SUCKING
CONSULTING FIRM?
THAT'S THE ONE.
HMMM, I LIKE THE
SOUND OF THAT.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT.
WHERE WE KNOW WHAT'S
COMING DOWN THE PIPE.
WELL, THE PICK YOUR
OWN FIREWOOD PROJECT
WAS MAYBE NOT QUITE AS
SUCCESSFUL AS WE'D HOPED.
OUR FIRST CUSTOMER
WAS EAGER TO TRY IT
BUT WHEN WE PHONED IN
TO CHECK HIS CREDIT CARD,
THEY TOLD US HE WAS
A CONVICTED MURDERER.
WE DESTROYED
HIS CREDIT CARD BUT
NOBODY HAD THE NERVE
TO ASK FOR
THE AXE BACK.
SO JUST LET ME GET
THIS CORRECT THEN,
SO BASICALLY
YOU HAD NO SALE
AND YOU'VE LOST YOUR
AXE IN THE BARGAIN.
OKAY.
ONE CAN ASSUME
THEN THAT YOU'RE OUT
OF THE FIREWOOD BUSINESS?
WE'RE OUT OF THE PICK
YOUR OWN BUSINESS, HAROLD.
BUT THE REGULAR FIREWOOD
SALES ARE JUST GOING TO
BE ON HOLD FOR A WHILE
UNTIL THE COTTAGERS GO
BACK TO THE CITY
FOR THE WINTER
AT WHICH TIME WE'LL
HAVE EASY ACCESS TO
THEIR WOODPILES.
YOU'RE GOING TO
STEAL THEIR FIREWOOD?
WELL, NO, IT'S NOT --
I'M NOT --
I'M NOT STEALING.
I'M LOG BROKERING
IS WHAT I'M DOING.
I'M SELLING LOG
FUTURES, HAROLD.
WHAT WE DO IS WE
PROTECT THEIR WOOD
AGAINST THE
RAVAGES OF WINTER
AND THEN WE SELL
IT BACK TO THEM
IN THE SPRING.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
WELL, SPEAKING OF WRATHS,
MEETING TIME, UNCLE RED.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD.
I'LL BE DOWN IN
A LITTLE WHILE, HAROLD.
OKAY, IF MY
WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING
AND I THOUGHT MAYBE
WE COULD HAVE
A ROMANTIC EVENING
AROUND THE FIRE.
I'M BRINGING A
LOAD OF FIREWOOD.
IT IS THE PICK
YOUR OWN STYLE, THOUGH,
SO MAYBE YOU COULD SPLIT
IT WHILE I'M HAVING A BATH.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
AND UNTIL NEXT TIME,
ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ QUIRKY UPBEAT MUSIC ]
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
Harold:
OKAY, SIT DOWN.
SIT DOWN SO WE CAN ALL RISE.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red:
SIT DOWN.