[quirky upbeat music]
[gunshots]
[glass shattering]
>> WELL, THIS IS THE MOMENT
WE'VE ALL BEEN WAITING FOR.
WE'RE ONLY HALF AN HOUR AWAY
FROM THE END OF THE SHOW.
WE'RE GETTING THERE.
AND HERE TO HELP US GET THROUGH
THIS LAST 30 MINUTES OF
THE RED GREEN SHOW IS--WELL,
IS THE STAR OF
THE RED GREEN SHOW, MY UNCLE,
AND--WELL, IT'S HIS OWN SHOW.
THAT'S WHY IT'S NAMED
THE RED GREEN SHOW,
AND HE HIRED ME.
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH WHY IT'S
CALLED HIS SHOW 'CAUSE
OTHERWISE, WE'D CALL IT LIKE
"REAL TRUE LIFE"
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
BUT WE'LL HAVE TO STICK TO
THE RED GREEN SHOW.
HERE HE IS, RED GREEN.
[applause]
>> THANK YOU, HAROLD,
AND WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
IF YOU HAVEN'T BEEN TURNED OFF
BY NOW, YOU'RE PROBABLY GONNA BE
ABLE TO TOUGH IT THROUGH
TILL THE END OF THE SHOW.
GOD, WE HAD A HECK OF A TIME UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK.
MOOSE THOMPSON WON ONE OF THEM
HOME BARBER KITS AT THE BINGO.
AND HE WANTED TO GIVE EVERYBODY
A FREE HAIRCUT, SO GOLLY, WE HAD
A HECK OF A LOT OF FUN
WITH THAT.
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK ENDED UP
LOSING AN EAR, YOU KNOW,
BUT NO BIG DEAL.
HE DOESN'T USE THEM ANYWAY,
YOU KNOW.
AND MOOSE THOMPSON SAID THAT HE
WAS ONLY FOLLOWING ORDERS.
HOW WAS HE SUPPOSED TO KNOW THAT
A LITTLE OFF THE SIDE ONLY MEANT
HAIR?
AND SPEAKING OF A LITTLE OFF THE
SIDE, COME ON OVER HERE, HAROLD.
HAROLD IS THE PRODUCER
AND DIRECTOR OF THE SHOW,
AND THE ANNOUNCER,
AS YOU MAYBE HEARD, UNLESS YOU
WERE LUCKY ENOUGH NOT TO BE
LISTENING.
AND HE HAS A PIECE OF EQUIPMENT
HERE THAT ENABLES HIM TO MOVE US
INTO THE NEXT SEGMENT, YOU KNOW,
IF THINGS ARE BORING OR NOT
MOVING FAST ENOUGH.
HE JUST HITS SOME BUTTONS THERE,
AND...
OH, FOR GOD SAKES, HAROLD.
I TELL YA, I PUT US INTO
THE NEXT SEGMENT BY MISTAKE.
JUST GET US BACK HERE
AND LET ME FINISH THE STORY.
>> OH, NO, THAT'S OKAY.
>> HEY, NOW, I WANT TO FINISH
THIS STORY.
HERE, I'LL GET IT BACK.
>> DON'T TOUCH IT!
[folksy guitar and spoons music plays]
>> SLEEP THROUGH THE NIGHT
UP WITH THE SUN
SNORF DOWN A COFFEE
AND REACH FOR MY GUN
DOWN TO THE FOREST
WHERE ALL THE BIRDS FLY
I BLOW THEM AND BLAST THEM
RIGHT OUT OF THE SKY
SMELL THE GUNPOWDER
HEAR THE SHOTS RING
WHEN THE DUCKS START FALLING
THEY'LL MAKE YOUR HEART SING
HUNTING IS HEAVEN
IT'S A SPORT FOR REAL MEN
AND AS SOON AS
MY WOUND HEALS
I'LL GO HUNTING AGAIN
[quirky upbeat music]
THIS WEEK IN THE HANDYMAN
CORNER, WE'RE GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
TO MAKE IT A LOT SAFER TO DRIVE
AT NIGHT.
STEP NUMBER ONE IS, YOU THROW
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S TRUCK KEYS
INTO THE LAKE.
STEP TWO, YOU GO AROUND THE
FRONT OF YOUR VEHICLE AND YOU
COUNT THE NUMBER OF HEADLIGHTS.
I COME UP WITH THE NUMBER TWO,
NOT ONE OF MY FAVORITES.
I MUCH PREFER THE NUMBER 10.
RIGHT NOW, WE'VE GOT THE
HEADLIGHTS ALL ATTACHED WITH THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
STRONG AND YET FLEXIBLE
ENOUGH THAT YOU CAN ADJUST THE
HEADLIGHTS, SAY, EVEN AFTER
THEY'RE IN POSITION.
SO I CAN HAVE TWO FACING LEFT,
A COUPLE UP, A COUPLE DOWN,
A COUPLE TO THE RIGHT, AND THE
OTHER ONES JUST TO KIND OF
FILL IN.
I'M GONNA SEE ANYTHING ON THE
ROAD IN FRONT OF ME WITH A RIG
LIKE THIS.
AND EVEN IF ONE OR TWO OF THEM
ARE BURNED OUT, THAT'S STILL NO
REAL BIG PROBLEM.
NOW, OBVIOUSLY, IT'S GONNA TAKE
A LITTLE EXTRA POWER TO RUN
A SYSTEM LIKE THIS.
SO WHAT I DO IS, I RUN THE
BATTERY CABLE, JUMPER-TYPE
CABLE, BATTERY CABLES BACK TO
THE BACK.
I DON'T HAVE ONE LONG ENOUGH,
SO I HOOK TWO TOGETHER, AND
THAT'S--AS LONG AS IT'S OUTSIDE
THE CAR, I THINK THAT'S
SAFE ENOUGH.
I TAKE THEM RIGHT THROUGH
THE WINDSHIELD--OR WHERE THE
WINDSHIELD USED TO BE--
INTO THE BACKSEAT AREA,
AND WHAT I HAVE IN HERE IS,
I GOT FOUR BATTERIES,
AND THEY'RE WIRED IN PARALLEL
WITH COAT HANGERS, AND I HOOK
THEM UP, AND THEY POWER ALL
MY EXTRA LIGHTING.
AND NOW, THE WIFE MIGHT THINK
THAT THIS IS KIND OF AN
UGLY-LOOKING RIG, BUT I GOT
A LITTLE SURPRISE FOR YOU THAT
MIGHT EVEN SATISFY HER,
BUT I DOUBT IT.
NOW, WHAT I'VE DONE HERE IS,
I'VE MOUNTED A EUROPEAN-STYLE
SPOILER ON THE FRONT
LIKE YOU SEE ON YOUR MASERATIS
AND FERRARIS AND ISUZUS.
AND WHAT KIND OF A WORLD WOULD
THIS BE WITHOUT DUCT TAPE,
I ASK YOU.
NOW, IT'S ACTUALLY JUST A PIECE
OF PLYWOOD.
I GOT A C-CLAMP ON THERE, AND I
GOT AN OLD GARAGE DOOR OPENER
HERE, WHICH IS GONNA RAISE AND
LOWER THE WHOLE UNIT.
TALK ABOUT SPORTY.
SO IF YOU GUYS WANT TO JUST
THROW ON YOUR WELDING GOGGLES AT
THE FRONT THERE, LET'S GIVE THIS
RIG A TRY.
WELL, IF THAT ISN'T ATTRACTIVE
AND SPORTY AND STYLISH ALL AT
THE SAME TIME, THEN, HEY,
KNOCK ME DOWN AND LET ME GET
BACK UP AGAIN.
SO IT'S THAT EASY.
YOU CAN DO IT YOURSELF.
YOU GOT THE TOOLS
AND THE KNOWHOW.
UNTIL NEXT TIME, REMEMBER THIS.
IF THE WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU
HANDSOME, THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[engine turns sluggishly]
DON'T GO AWAY.
I'M SURE YOU WANT TO HEAR THE
END OF THE HAIRCUTTING STORY.
>> OH, YEAH, THAT'S A REAL
NAIL-BITER FOR SURE.
>> IT IS WINTER.
THE MOONLIGHT BOUNCES OFF
THE ICY LAKE.
THE STREET LIGHTS BOUNCE OFF
THE ICY ROADS.
YOUR CAR BOUNCES OFF
THE ICY GUARDRAILS.
YOUR HEAD BOUNCES OFF
THE DASHBOARD.
YOUR CHECK BOUNCES OFF THE BRAIN
SURGEON'S RECEPTION DESK.
SO ANYWAY, GETTING BACK TO THIS
HAIRCUTTING KIT THAT MOOSE
THOMPSON HAD, YOU KNOW, STINKY
PETERSON GETS HIS HAIR CUT ABOUT
AS OFTEN AS HE WASHES IT, WHICH
WORKS OUT TO ABOUT ONCE EVERY
FOUR YEARS.
SO THE IDEA OF GETTING A FREE
HAIRCUT WAS PRETTY APPEALING TO
HIM, EVEN THOUGH IT MEANT THAT
SEVERAL FORMS OF WILDLIFE WERE
GONNA HAVE TO FIND A NEW NATURAL
HABITAT.
SO MOOSE, UNFORTUNATELY, WASN'T
INTERESTED IN SHAMPOOING
STINKY'S HAIR, SO WHAT HE DONE
WAS, HE JUST COMBED IT STRAIGHT
UP WITH A GARDEN RAKE, AND THEN
MARKED A LINE ACROSS USING
A T-SQUARE AND A PIECE OF CHALK.
BUT THEN WHEN HE WENT TO CUT IT,
GOLLY, IT BROKE ALL THE BLADES
IN THE RAZOR.
SO THIS MAKES MOOSE PRETTY MAD.
PLUS STINKY'S HAIR IS LOOKING
LIKE A HEDGE ON DRUGS, YOU KNOW,
AND STINKY WANTED HIS MONEY
BACK, OF COURSE, BUT THEN HE
HADN'T PAID ANYTHING, SO HE SAID
HE WAS WILLING TO TAKE A CHECK.
>> UNCLE RED. UNCLE RED, LOOK.
I'VE MADE MY VIDEO DEVICE
MACHINE INTO A TIME MACHINE.
>> WELL, HOW DOES THAT WORK,
HAROLD?
>> OH, EASY. WATCH THIS.
WATCH THIS.
LIKE, I'LL SET IT FOR FIVE
MINUTES INTO THE FUTURE, RIGHT?
TO SAY, LIKE, WHEN THE
HAIRCUTTING STORY WAS OVER,
FOR INSTANCE.
AND PUSH A COUPLE BUTTONS...
AND PRESTO,
WE'RE INTO THE FUTURE.
>> WE'RE NOT INTO THE FUTURE,
HAROLD.
WE'RE JUST INTO THE NEXT
SEGMENT.
>> OH, WELL, THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH.
>> OH, RED GREEN.
>> YEAH?
>> THIS IS A SURPRISE.
IT'S A BIG SURPRISE!
>> YEAH.
[laughs]
>> A REAL LIVE HUMAN BEING.
>> YEAH.
>> PLEASE, COME IN.
THIS IS GREAT. THIS IS GREAT.
WIPE YOUR FEET THERE.
>> OH, SORRY.
YEAH, OKAY.
WELL, RANGER GORD, I UNDERSTAND
THE FOREST IS REAL, REAL DRY.
AND WE JUST POPPED IN BECAUSE I
GUESS THE FIRE DANGER HAS GOT TO
BE UP THERE NOW, ISN'T IT?
>> OH, IT'S VERY DANGEROUS.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
>> IT'S VERY, VERY DRY.
IT HASN'T BEEN THIS DRY SINCE
ALL THE TIME I'VE BEEN UP HERE.
>> OH!
>> AND WE HAVEN'T HAD RAIN NOW
FOR 23 DAYS.
>> OH, GOSH!
>> AND EVEN WHEN IT DID RAIN 23
DAYS AGO, IT ONLY RAINED FOR
ABOUT 2 HOURS.
AND 7 DAYS PREVIOUS TO THAT,
IT DRIZZLED FOR 17, 18 MINUTES,
BUT NOTHING OF ANY CONSEQUENCE.
MAYBE, OH, 1/2 AN INCH,
3/4 OF AN INCH.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> NOTHING OF ANY CONSEQUENCE.
>> YEAH.
>> A LITTLE TIME PREVIOUS TO
THAT, IT RAINED FOR MAYBE FOUR
OR FIVE MINUTES, BUT NOTHING--
NOTHING REALLY OF ANY
CONSEQUENCE.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> IT'S INTERESTING, BUT...
>> IT'S VERY, VERY DRY.
ALL THE TIME I'VE BEEN UP HERE,
I HAVEN'T SEEN IT THIS DRY.
>> OH, YEAH. YEAH, YEAH.
>> EVERYTHING MADE OUT OF WOOD
IS SHRINKING, YOU KNOW.
>> I'M SENSING THAT, YEAH.
>> I HAVE TO RETUNE MY AUTOHARP
EVERY DAY.
>> OH, GOSH.
YOU HAVE AN AUTOHARP.
>> I'VE BEEN WORKING ON A MEDLEY
OF HITS BY THE CAPTAIN
AND TENNILLE.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO HEAR ME PLAY?
>> WELL, MAYBE LATER, YOU KNOW,
OR SOME OTHER TIME OR SOMETHING.
>> ARE THEY STILL HOT,
CAPTAIN AND TENNILLE?
>> WELL, YOU'LL HAVE TO ASK
HAROLD ABOUT THAT.
WHAT I WANTED YOU TO DO, THOUGH,
RANGER GORD, IF YOU DON'T MIND,
IS TELL OUR VIEWERS ABOUT SOME
OF THE DANGERS OF YOUR JOB,
FIRE WATCHING.
>> WELL, I'D LOVE TO, RED.
>> OKAY, GREAT.
>> WELL, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
BOYS AND GIRLS, ONE OF THE MAJOR
DANGERS IN WATCHING A FIRE IS
THAT IF YOU WATCH THEM
TOO CLOSE, YOU CAN BURN YOUR
EYEBROWS RIGHT OFF.
SO BE VERY CAREFUL THERE.
NOW, AND THE OTHER THING IS, IF
I DIDN'T HAVE A FIRE TO WATCH
IN THE 12 YEARS THAT I'VE BEEN
UP HERE--
>> OH, NO.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I DIDN'T REALIZE.
12 YEARS.
WELL, I MEAN, DON'T YOU TAKE
A VACATION, GORD?
CAN'T YOU TAKE A DAY OFF
OR SOMETHING IN 12 YEARS?
>> NO.
>> NO?
>> FIRE DOESN'T TAKE A VACATION.
FIRE DOESN'T TAKE A DAY OFF.
>> BUT--WELL, WHAT ABOUT
IN THE WINTER?
I MEAN, THERE'S NO FOREST FIRE
IN THE WINTER, YOU KNOW.
>> DON'T TELL ME THAT, RED.
DON'T TELL ME THAT I DIDN'T HAVE
TO SPEND THE LAST 12 WINTERS
FREEZING TO DEATH UP HERE!
DON'T TELL ME THAT, RED!
>> NO. ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
>> [sobbing]
>> GORD, I COULD BE WRONG.
I COULD BE WRONG.
NOW LET'S TALK ABOUT SOMETHING
ELSE.
WHAT ABOUT AT NIGHT?
WHAT ABOUT AT NIGHT AND THERE'S
A FOREST FIRE?
CAN YOU SEE IT?
HOW DO YOU TELL?
HOW DO YOU DETECT IT?
HOW CAN YOU SEE IT?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> WELL, IF THE FLAMES ARE BIG
ENOUGH, YOU'D BE ABLE TO SEE IT,
WOULDN'T YOU?
>> ON, NO, NO, I MEANT,
YOU KNOW, IF YOU WERE ASLEEP.
HOW WOULD YOU KNOW THERE'S
A FIRE IF YOU'RE ASLEEP?
>> ASLEEP?
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW,
IF YOU'RE ASLEEP.
>> YOU MEAN I COULD HAVE SLEPT?
DON'T TELL ME THAT, RED, OKAY?
>> OH, ALL RIGHT.
>> OKAY? DON'T!
DON'T TELL ME THAT, RED!
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
>> FIRE DOESN'T SLEEP,
YOU KNOW--HUH?
>> OKAY, I UNDERSTAND.
I UNDERSTAND.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
TAKE IT EASY. TAKE IT EASY.
I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU.
A BIG FIRE, SURE, YOU'RE GONNA
SEE IT.
WHAT ABOUT A SMALL FIRE?
HOW DO YOU DETECT A SMALL FIRE?
>> OH, OH, OKAY, WELL, I'VE GOT
400 SMOKE DETECTORS HUNG,
ONE PER ACRE ALL AROUND HERE.
>> OH, THAT'S AN INTERESTING--
>> YEAH.
MY ONLY PROBLEM IS DENSE FOG.
THE FOG WILL SET THEM OFF.
>> OH!
>> EVERY TIME THERE'S A DENSE
FOG, THE WHOLE FOREST GOES...
[sustained beep]
>> BOY, THAT WOULD BE SOMETHING
TO HEAR, WOULDN'T IT?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL THE CRICKETS START
MATING.
I'LL JUST PLUG IN AN EIGHT-TRACK
OF THE CAPTAIN AND TENNILLE
AND DROWN IT OUT.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> DO YOU KNOW THAT TONY
TENNILLE SINGS IN THE SAME KEY
AS A SMOKE DETECTOR?
>> FOR GOSH SAKES.
WELL, GORD, WE GOT TO GO.
REALLY GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF, HEY.
>> OH, NO, NO, YOU'RE NOT
GOING NOW.
>> OH, WE JUST HAVE TO.
>> NO. PLEASE.
>> NO.
NOW, GORD, GORD, GORD.
>> PLEASE DON'T GO.
>> NO.
>> I WAS GONNA SHOW YOU MY BUG
COLLECTION AND STUFF.
>> WELL, WE'LL JUST SEE THAT
ANOTHER TIME.
ALL RIGHT?
NOW YOU TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
WE'LL COME BACK ANOTHER TIME.
>> NO, PLEASE DON'T GO.
>> NO.
>> HEY, WHY DON'T YOU COME BACK
TOMORROW?
I'M HERE TOMORROW.
>> OH, ALL RIGHT, WELL--
>> YOU KNOW, SAY, AFTER 11:00.
>> OH.
>> 'CAUSE AT 11:00, I'M
SCHEDULED TO FLOSS, BUT IF YOU
WANT TO COME BY EARLY, I'LL MOVE
IT TO ANOTHER DAY.
>> WELL, WHY DON'T WE JUST PLAY
THAT BY EAR, HUH?
HUH?
>> OH, OKAY.
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE MY AUTOHARP, HUH?
PLAY IT BY EAR.
>> OH, YOU PLAY THAT BY EAR TOO?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> I COULD--WOULD YOU LIKE TO
HEAR LOVE WILL KEEP US TOGETHER?
>> WELL, THAT WOULD BE NICE, BUT
I THINK WE SHOULD WAIT TILL
THE FOG ROLLS IN, DON'T YOU?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> YEAH.
[folksy guitar and spoons music plays]
LISTEN TO THE SINGING TOAD
SING HIS HAPPY SONG
>> AT THE COPA
COPACABANA
HEART OF HEARTS
SORRY. GO AHEAD.
>> IF YOU DON'T HEAR
THE SINGING TOAD
HE MUST HAVE SUNG
TOO CLOSE TO THE ROAD
>> COPACA--AH!
RRR!
ZZZ!
[giggles]
OH, UNCLE RED, THIS IS SO
EXCELLENT.
IT'S MALE CALL TIME AGAIN.
I THINK THIS IS THE BEST PART OF
THE SHOW.
YOU KNOW, IT GELS TOGETHER LIKE
THAT.
THAT'S SO GREAT.
I JUST THOUGHT OF IT OFF THE TOP
OF MY HEAD, AND BANG!
IT'S ALL FITTING TOGETHER.
THIS IS SO GREAT.
>> OH, YEAH, HAROLD,
I SMELL AN EMMY.
>> OH, YOU SCARED ME THERE,
UNCLE RED.
OKAY, LETTER NUMBER ONE.
"DEAR RED GREEN, LAST YEAR I SAW
EVERY EPISODE OF YOUR SHOW, AND
THIS YEAR WE GOT OUR TV DIAL
FIXED, AND I'VE BEEN WATCHING
SOME OTHER SHOWS, AND THEY'RE
ALL TALKING ABOUT THE
ENVIRONMENT.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?"
>> WELL, HAROLD, ONE OF THE
BIGGEST PROBLEMS WE FACE IS THE
DESTRUCTION OF THE ENVIRONMENT
THROUGH THE USE OF CFFs OR FCs.
WELL, REALLY WHAT THEY'RE
CALLED, FLUOROCARBONS,
OR CARBOFLUORON, I THINK.
WHAT'S THE NAME OF THAT STUFF
THEY USE IN REFRIGERATORS?
>> WHAT?
OH, SORRY, WHAT?
SORRY, I WAS MAKING UP A CARTOON
IN MY MIND.
>> I WAS TALKING ABOUT
REFRIGERATION.
WHAT'S THE NAME OF THAT STUFF
THEY USE IN THERE?
YOU KNOW, IT'S IN YOUR CAR
AIR-CONDITIONER.
>> MY CAR DOESN'T HAVE AN
>> WHY NOT?
>> IT'S A MOTORCYCLE.
>> WHAT WAS I JUST TALKING
ABOUT?
>> CARBOFLUORONS?
>> YEAH, OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
SO WHAT WE HAVE TO DO IS, WE GOT
TO FIGURE OUT A WAY TO MAKE
OZONE.
>> OH, HOW YOU DO THAT?
>> WELL, OZONE IS PRODUCED
WHENEVER THERE IS AN ELECTRICAL
SHORT CIRCUIT.
REMEMBER THAT TIME WHEN WE
DROPPED THE S.O.S. PAD INTO THE
HAIRDRYER?
REMEMBER THAT SMELL?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, THAT WAS OZONE.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
I THOUGHT WAS THE KITCHEN
ON FIRE.
>> NO, I MEAN BEFORE THAT.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
'CAUSE I DON'T THINK OZONE
HAS A SMELL.
>> OH, YEAH, OZONE HAS A SMELL.
GO SNIFF THE BACK OF THE FRIDGE.
>> NO, THAT'S FLARBOCOOLENS.
THAT'S LIKE FCF--FCCs Fs.
>> ALL RIGHT, FORGET THAT.
WHAT'S THE NAME OF THAT STUFF
THEY MAKE STYROFOAM CUPS OUT OF?
>> STYROFOAM.
>> YEAH, WELL, THAT HAS C--
CFFF CFs IN IT.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
I THOUGHT THAT WAS THE PLASTIC
HAMBURGER BOX THAT HAD
FLARBOCOOLENS IN IT.
>> NO, IT'S THE HAMBURGERS.
>> ARE THE FRENCH FRIES OKAY?
ARE THE FRENCH FRIES OKAY,
UNCLE RED?
>> YEAH, YEAH, THEY ARE, HAROLD.
>> OH! OOH!
>> IN FACT, I THINK IF YOU EAT
ENOUGH FRENCH FRIES,
YOU ACTUALLY PRODUCE OZONE.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> WELL, REMEMBER THE SMELL FROM
THE HAIRDRYER?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK WE COULD
RETITLE THIS SEGMENT
"KIDS, DON'T TRY THIS AT HOME."
BILL BROUGHT US, AS YOU CAN SEE,
A SNOW BLOWER, AND, YOU KNOW,
IT'S SOMETHING THAT'S A VALUABLE
PART OF OUR EQUIPMENT LIST
UP HERE AT THE LODGE, BUT IT IS
A PIECE OF HEAVY EQUIPMENT,
AND YOU SHOULD RESPECT IT.
THE SNOW GOES IN THERE.
BILL'S GIVING YOU THE DEMO HERE.
AND IT COMES OUT HERE, YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, THAT'S CLEVER, ISN'T IT?
I MEAN, WHAT ELSE WOULD YOU
ASSUME?
AND NEVER PUT YOUR HANDS
ANYWHERE--WELL, LIKE WHAT I'M
DOING, NEVER DO THAT, ALL RIGHT,
FOR STARTERS.
SPEAKING OF STARTERS, BILL'S
HAVING A LITTLE PROBLEM THERE.
MR. EXPERT DOESN'T KNOW YOU GOT
TO TURN THE THING ON FIRST.
YEAH, YEAH, I'LL DRINK TO THAT,
BILL.
ANYWAY, UP SHE GOES.
AND WE JUST WANTED TO SHOW
YOU--ACTUALLY, BILL HAS SOME
INTERESTING IDEAS HOW YOU CAN
ADAPT A SNOW BLOWER TO, YOU
KNOW, REALLY HELP YOU AS A TOOL,
AND IT IS KIND OF INTERESTING.
I THINK IT'S JUST UNFORTUNATE
THAT WE PICKED GARBAGE DAY AS
THE DAY TO TRY AND DO THIS.
I MEAN, MAYBE IF BILL WAS PAYING
A LITTLE MORE ATTENTION, THAT
WOULDN'T HAVE HURT EITHER,
YOU KNOW.
BUT, YOU KNOW, THEY ARE
A POWERFUL MACHINE.
I GOT A HINT OF WHAT WE'D HAD
FOR DINNER THE LAST COUPLE WEEKS
AT THE LODGE.
I THINK THAT PORK WAS
UNDERCOOKED.
BUT ON WE GO ANYWAY.
WHAT BILL REALLY WANTED TO SHOW
YOU HERE WAS--THIS IS SOMETHING
KIND OF INTERESTING THAT
HE THOUGHT UP.
I DIDN'T COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND
IT AT FIRST, BECAUSE I JUST SAW
HIM TYING THE ROPE ONTO THE SNOW
BLOWER, AND I REALLY WAS A
LITTLE BIT--WELL, YOU CAN SEE
THERE.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
THEN HE TIED THE OTHER END OF
THE ROPE TO A TREE.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT HE'S GOT IN
MIND HERE IS, I THINK THIS IS
SOMETHING THAT HE MAY HAVE SEEN
IN A CARTOON, YOU KNOW, WHICH HE
GOES TO REGULARLY.
AND THE IDEA IS, YOU START THE
SNOW BLOWER UP, AND IT WINDS
AROUND THE TREE, YOU SEE, AND IT
CLEARS THE WHOLE AREA WITHOUT
YOU ACTUALLY HAVING TO DO
ANY WORK.
SO YOU'D THINK THAT--WELL,
BILL'S A BIT OF A SLOW LEARNER,
YOU KNOW, WITH THE--THERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT.
SO ANYWAY, HE GETS IT GOING, AND
THE WHEELS ARE TURNING THERE
AROUND, AND WE ENGAGE THE
THROWER.
AND THEN, YOU KNOW, AND WHAT
HAPPENS IS, SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE
WINDING AROUND THE TREE.
AND OF COURSE, EVERY TIME IT
GOES AROUND, THE ROPE WINDS
AROUND THE TREE AND BRINGS IT
IN A LITTLE BIT CLOSER, YOU SEE.
NOW, OUR PROBLEM WAS, THE KNOT
WAS JUST SLIPPING AROUND THE
TREE, SO WHAT WAS HAPPENING WAS
THE SNOW BLOWER WASN'T COMING
ANY CLOSER.
IT JUST KEPT GOING OVER AND OVER
THE SAME CIRCLE.
SO BILL FIGURED IF HE GAVE IT A
TUG AND TIED THE KNOT A LITTLE
TIGHTER, AND I GUESS I SHOULD
HAVE PAID MORE ATTENTION TO WHAT
WAS HAPPENING.
HE KIND OF TURNED IT, AND IT
KIND OF WAS--WELL, YOU--WELL,
NOW THIS IS REAL DANGEROUS,
I THINK.
MAYBE IT'S JUST ME, YOU KNOW.
OH!
OH, OH, OH, OH!
OH, BILL, THAT'S--
NOW, THAT'S BILL'S UNDERWEAR.
I DON'T--NO, OH, FOR...
SNOW HE'S WEARING THERE.
WELL, WHAT SOME GUYS WILL DO TO
INCREASE THEIR SPERM COUNT.
IT IS WINTER.
THE JOINTS STIFFEN AS THE COLD
SETS IN.
THE NORTH WIND BLOWS ICE PELLETS
INTO YOUR EYES.
YOU WONDER AT ITS BRUTALITY
AND POINTLESSNESS.
THEN YOUR MIND TURNS TO HOCKEY.
THIS IS THE POINT IN THE SHOW
WHERE WE GIVE HAROLD A CHANCE TO
SAY WHAT'S ON HIS MIND.
WE GOT TO DO SOMETHING TO KILL
THE TIME.
GO AHEAD.
>> OKAY.
BULLIES, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT, WELL, YOU KNOW WHO
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
THOSE PEOPLE WHO BEAT YOU
OFF ON THE WAY TO SCHOOL,
IN THE SUPERMARKET, IN CHURCH.
WELL, I DON'T THINK ANYBODY HAS
THE RIGHT TO USE PHYSICAL
VIOLENCE ON ANOTHER HUMAN BEING.
WELL, ALL RIGHT, UNLESS, OF
COURSE, LIKE, YOU'RE BATMAN OR
THE POLICE OR SOMETHING,
AND THEN IT'S OKAY.
AND I DON'T MIND BEING ATTACKED
VERBALLY.
THAT'S OKAY.
YOU KNOW, REALLY, I'M GETTING
USED TO THAT, BUT I GOT A
WALKMAN, SO I DON'T EVEN NOTICE
MUCH ANYMORE.
BUT WHEN IT RESORTS TO FISTS,
I JUST HAVE TO STOP AND SAY,
"ENOUGH!"
BUT USUALLY THAT
DOESN'T HELP EITHER.
YOU KNOW, OKAY, ALL RIGHT, YES,
WHEN I GET PUNCHED BY SOME
MORON, I CAN RESORT TO, LIKE,
IMMATURE TACTICS AS WELL, LIKE
PUNCH HIM BACK OR SOMETHING, OR
I COULD BE MATURE ABOUT IT AND
CRUMBLE INTO A MOANING HEAP.
AND THEN I GO HOME, AND I PLOT
AGAINST THEM, LIKE ORDERING 80
PIZZAS TO THEIR HOUSE.
SEE, YOU HAVE TO DO THAT.
YOU GOT TO USE YOUR BRAINS, OR
OTHERWISE, YOU'VE SUNK TO THEIR
LEVEL, AND THEY'RE GONNA WIN
'CAUSE THEY GOT HUGE HAM-SHAPED
FISTS.
BUT THOSE HANDS ARE NO MATCH
FOR THIS: HEAD LICE.
>> WE HAVE LOTS MORE COMING UP
FOR YOU--
NOT JUST THE HAIRCUTTING STORY.
>> OH, THANK GOD.
[horn honking]
>> WE'RE UP HERE AT JIMMY
MCVAY'S HOUSE.
JIMMY'S NOT HOME FROM WORK YET.
I GUESS THEY HAD A HEAVY DAY AT
THE POST OFFICE.
I THOUGHT I'D COME UP HERE AND
SEE HOW JIMMY'S DOING WITH THIS
OLD WOODEN BOAT HE'S FIXING UP.
OH, HERE COMES JIMMY NOW.
HOW'D SHE GO TODAY, JIM?
>> OH, JEEZ, WHAT A BLOODY DAY.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> THE BLOODY BAG WEIGHS TONS!
>> OH!
>> CAN YOU IMAGINE ALL THE
BLOODY LETTERS THAT THEY HAVE US
TAKING AROUND THIS COUNTRY?
>> WELL, YEAH, BUT JIM, YOU'RE
A LETTER CARRIER, YOU KNOW.
>> IT'S NOT THE LETTERS,
YOU KNOW.
IT'S THE MAGAZINES.
THE DAMN MAGAZINES
MUST WEIGH 60 POUNDS.
>> OH.
>> I MEAN, CAN YOU IMAGINE
SWINGING A BAG LIKE THAT ON YOUR
SHOULDER WHILE YOU'RE CLIMBING
A FENCE WITH A PIT BULL TEARING
THE ARSE OF YOUR TROUSERS?
THAT IS WHAT I CALL STRESS IN
THE WORKPLACE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
BUT, JIM, DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THAT NOW.
YOU CAN THINK ABOUT YOUR BOAT.
>> OH, MY GOD, RED,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
LOOK AT THAT.
ISN'T SHE A BEAUTY?
>> WELL, SHE WILL BE SOMEDAY
MAYBE.
>> I MEAN, LOOK AT THE LINES.
>> YEAH.
>> LOOK AT THE CRAFTSMANSHIP.
>> I CAN REALLY SMELL THE SEA,
CAN'T YOU?
>> YEAH, IT'S MORE LIKE A BIG
MUSHROOM, REALLY, JIM.
>> OH, IT'S JUST ABSOLUTELY
BEAUTIFUL.
YOU'LL NEVER SEE A FIBERGLASS
BOAT LOOKING LIKE THAT,
WILL YOU?
>> NO, THAT'S FOR SURE.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN WORKING
ON HER, JIM?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, NOT THAT
LONG.
>> NO, NO, NO?
>> NO, NO.
ABOUT 6 1/2 YEARS OR SO.
MIND YOU, I DO TAKE A WEEKEND
OFF ONCE A YEAR.
>> YEAH.
>> JUST TO GO TO THE BOAT SHOW.
>> OH.
AND OF COURSE, YOU GOT TO SPEND
TIME WITH THE MISSUS.
>> NO, I DO NOT.
>> OH?
>> NO, SHE'S BLOODY WELL GONE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> SHE'S AWAY. SHE'S LEFT.
>> SHE LEFT YOU?
>> SHE DID.
SHE DONE A BUNK.
IT WAS A SURPRISE TO ME TOO.
>> NO KIDDING.
>> AND I WENT INTO THE HOUSE
THERE JUST TO GET
A COAT HANGER, YOU KNOW, TO MAKE
A HOSE CLAMP FOR THE ENGINE.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> AND TO MY AMAZEMENT,
I NOTICED ALL HER CLOTHES
WERE GONE.
NO NOTE OR NOTHING.
NOW, THERE'S WHAT YOU CALL
LOVING SUPPORT, ISN'T IT?
>> WELL, I THINK YOU'RE KIND OF
TO BLAME TOO, JIM.
I MEAN, YOU'VE GOT TO SPEND SOME
TIME WITH THE LITTLE LADY,
YOU KNOW.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE I DIDN'T SPEND
SOME TIME WITH HER.
>> OH.
>> MY DEAR.
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN, I HAD HER UP ON THAT
BOAT ONCE TO HELP ME LIFT THE
ENGINE OUT.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> SHE WAS BLOODY USELESS.
>> WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD ANYWAY,
YOU KNOW.
>> IT IS.
>> YEAH, IT'S A SHAME.
>> IT IS. IT'S A SHAME.
IT'S A TRAGEDY.
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN, I COULD HAVE HAD THAT
BOAT IN THE BLOODY WATER BY NOW.
>> WELL, THE HAIRCUTTING
ADVENTURE KIND OF EVENTUALLY
WORKED ITSELF OUT.
HE GOT A LITTLE BIT BETTER
AT IT ANYWAY.
I MEAN, THE INJURY RATE
CERTAINLY WENT DOWN WHEN HE
STOPPED DOING THE SIDES AND THE
BACK AND JUST CONCENTRATED ON
DOING THE TOPS OF THE HEADS.
PROBABLY THE WORST JOB MOOSE DID
WAS WHEN HE CUT HIS OWN HAIR.
YOU KNOW, HE SET UP A BUNCH OF
MIRRORS, AND HE HAD THE RAZOR
AND SOME BARBECUE TONGS THERE,
AND, YOU KNOW, I NEVER KNEW THAT
MOOSE'S SCALP WAS PINK, BUT WE
LEARNED SOMETHING, THOUGH.
YOU KNOW, WE LEARNED THAT
EVERYTHING HAS ITS PLACE.
MINE IS HERE, HAROLD'S IS OVER
THERE, AND MOOSE'S BARBER KIT'S
IS AT THE BOTTOM OF THE LAKE.
SO ANYWAY, IF MY WIFE IS
WATCHING, I'LL BE COMING
STRAIGHT HOME, AND I'M FINE, BUT
I'LL BE WEARING MY HAT FOR THE
NEXT SIX WEEKS OR SO.
SO ANYWAY, THANKS FOR WATCHING
THE SHOW, AND ON BEHALF OF
MYSELF AND HAROLD AND THE WHOLE
GANG HERE AT THE LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.