As you can see, I got a bunch of roof trusses
here.
That's because sometimes when you do a job,
you overestimate the amount of materials
you're going to need and you end up with a
fair whack of it left over.
Not me, but that construction site up the
street here does.
I mean the roof, the whole house?
They had all these left over.
You know, unless they're going to put a roof
on the garage, but who puts a regular roof on
a garage? The point is that a man my age
should be able to do something creative with
roof trusses. We know a little bit about
roofs and most of us have had experience with
trusses. The main thing to notice here is
all the triangles inside one of these, and we
all know how strong triangles are.
Remember your bicycle?
Remember how strong that crossbar felt when
the chain broke?
So just two triangles inside the trusses
that make them strong enough to hold up a
roof. So I figure they've got to be strong
enough to hold up a car.
That's right, you guessed it with the help
of a little middle aged ingenuity and a roll
or two of the handyman secret weapon.
I'm going to show you how to get two
vehicles into one parking space.
Big, big week up at the Lions this week,
town councils decided to demolish the old
school that we all went to, and they're
asking for local tenders from anybody who
would like to rip it down.
And guess who got the contract?
Serendipity do died.
Hi, this has to be the best day of my life.
Mr. Green being asked to break and enter,
yes,
No more homework, no more books.
The whole darn school is getting the hook.
I'm going to knock down every corner they
ever made me stand in.
Actually, I blame my teachers for my life at
crime.
You know, they flunk me so many times.
When I finally made it out of there, I was
tried as an adult, correct?
I just heard you guys are going to tear down
the old school.
Is that true? To my ears, deceive me.
Well, they sure don't flatter you.
I know you guys know nothing about
demolition.
Harold, look around you.
Yeah, OK, but I also heard you doing it for
free.
Well, that was the lowest tender.
Hey, look, don't be a wet blanket here,
Harold.
You've had enough wet blankets in your life.
We've got a job to do and we're going to go
do it.
Lean on Mike, why you're tearing the school
down for nothing.
What kind of business deal is that?
Pretty good one because we are willing to
pay.
This was.
Today's winner receives this coupon for a
free burger from Marty's Mystery Meat Market,
where if you can guess the animal you're
eating, we'll give you a free order.
Ok. How are you? I hear things, Winston.
Mr. Lee, you've got 30 seconds to get
Winston Rothschild to say this word.
Carrier carrier.
And you're
Ok. Listen, when you first started high
school, you were encouraged to pick a desk
near the front. Ok, no, no.
Ok. Your guidance counselor help you to find
a reason to hate guidance counselor.
Ok. Ok, do you now?
Sewage is not just a job, it's a privilege.
Ok. Ok.
Let's say you have a job that you will never
lose, no matter how bad you screw it up.
Ok, then we call that a Senate appointment.
And we're almost out of time, Mr.
Green.
Ok, Winston, your dad, he's a real talker.
I want you to tell me what your mom says
about him.
Ok, let's say it, real slow.
She says he
Can talk her ear off talk career.
I heard. Ed Rothschild's, our motto
is just do it, then call us.
You know, as a vehicle gets older and you
don't take care of it, it will eventually get
too dangerous to put on the road like this
baby here.
No brakes left on her at all, which is a bad
idea in our area because we got lots of hills
and at least one lawyer.
But the engine is still good, you know?
And it doesn't seem right to throw out the
whole thing when one part still works.
That'd be a dangerous precedent for any
middle aged husband.
So instead, I'm going to convert this
historic automobile into a one of a kind
gasoline powered yard clock.
Step one Take off all the small pieces of
chrome trim.
Ok, now you mount the little pieces of
chrome around the hood.
They're going to be the numbers on your
clock. Make sure it's a perfect circle.
Geometry is actually a big part of today's
handymen corner.
Next thing you want to do is drill a
precision hole exactly dead center in your
clock. I did eventually find the center
and of a process of elimination.
Now this windshield wipers here while
they're on my, our hand and my minute hand,
and then I've used this radio antenna as my
second hand.
But I really couldn't use anything off the
vehicle because it's a second hand car.
Ok, now this is the tricky part.
You got to find a way for the minute hand to
go 60 times slower than the second hand and
for the hour hand to go 60 times slower than
the minute hand.
Now if I had to do that in my head, I know
I'd be looking at a very serious cranial
implosion. So instead, I took the workings
out of an old grandfather clock that Bernice
inherited and just used that.
Besides, we always forgot to wind that old
clock.
And now, with this gas powered unit, we
don't even have to then to get the engine
right on the clock. I placed a couple of fan
belts together, run them off the water pump
around this clothesline pull.
All right. Fire up.
I bet everyone, the grandfather clock out of
harm's way, furnace gets a little weird
whenever I touch your stuff.
I got her sat two thousand r.p.m., for
starters, and I can just adjust from there if
it's the wrong speed. And I added a couple
of extra doodads.
I put it in a couple switches at 12 o'clock
in the six o'clock position and then I wired
them into the heart relay so you get a
signal on the hour and on the half hour.
And then I put another movable switch in
there, you can stick anywhere you want.
I put it right beside the nine o'clock
there.
That's the alarm. I got it wired into the
car radio.
I remember women don't find that handsome.
They should at least find your head.
Oh yeah. One other thing, if the radio is
not strong enough to get you up, I added
another little feature mounted a little
teeter totter there beside the hour that I
want to get up at. And then I just balance a
little shotgun shell on.
You'll notice I'm taking the air cleaner off
the carburetor.
There's a reason for that. This will either
wake you up or put you to sleep forever.
You know, with all the special effects
Hollywood has these days, they can make
things happen in movies that would never
happen in life like, say, a young, good
looking woman falls for a fat, bald, middle
aged guy.
That's a fantasy right there.
It's a fantasy that you just can't get in
the real world.
Well, OK, maybe you can get it, but it tends
to be expensive.
And usually leads to a couple of arrests.
One police, one cardiac.
Now, I'm not saying that there aren't any
young women who are attracted to us middle
aged guys, but if you walk around, suck in
your gut in until you find them, you're going
to wind up hunchbacked.
The younger women tend to like younger man,
that's because they can still sculpt and mold
them. It's hard enough to wait until the
guy's mother is done with them.
It's impossible if they wait until Mother
Nature has taken them into the late rounds.
Because a woman sees a man, not as a man,
but as a do it yourself man kit.
And nobody wants to play with a kit after
somebody else is glued it together.
Especially if they lost the directions and
wrecked the most important parts.
Remember, I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
Rob, sewage is just what you need.
You bite, we suck, everybody's happy.
Well, the town council gave us four weeks to
tear down the school.
We did her in twenty seven minutes.
I'll tell you first time I enjoyed going to
the principal's office.
Uncle Red, yeah, that was awful.
Oh boy. You weren't supposed to pulverize
everything, the bricks could have been
recycled.
Well, they still can here. I'll just add
water to the powder.
You got clay.
I feel like a man again.
That was great.
We better marriage counseling.
Thank you. You're feeling OK.
Yeah.
No headache, really?
No. I do not get you guys.
You just tore down a whole part of your
life.
You're not the least bit upset about it.
Can you not see that that school was a part
of each of you?
Well, I can see it was a part of Mike.
I mean, that place represents a time in your
life when you were when you were young and
full of hope and promise.
This is not a happy day.
This is a sad day. And if you had any
sensitivity at all, you'd be full of regret
right now.
Harold, every time I see you, I'm full of
regret.
I mean, don't you regret things in life that
didn't turn out like like a marriage or a
career or things you said, the things you
didn't say, things you should have said, but
didn't because you were a man. It sucked it
up.
So you missed the opportunity to tell your
dad how much you admired him.
You missed a chance for him to tell you how
proud he is of you.
Things like that, Harold.
He just wanted to be hugged.
No, I had to settle for what I could get
wasn't good enough for daddy.
I just wanted a little affection.
He said, I go blind
When you're a man, there's nothing better
than having a big steak
Barbecue.
So Belinda brought the barbecue and went on
the man microshare and others, her behind the
coolers and.
You got to have the beverages, you know, and
actually, I think the meat was in there, so
fails all the OK.
The barbecue is not in pristine condition.
That's no problem. Got that lid off one way.
There we go. And then go, Wait, wait.
And no, no, you don't need charcoal. This is
a propane.
It's a propane unit. You know, it's not new,
but it's still good.
No, I'm wrong. It is a charcoal.
It is a charcoal barbecue.
So Mills and antibioticos.
Oh, boy. Come right out of her.
All right now, that's good, that's good.
And meanwhile, they're just set those down
on that table doesn't look.
Doesn't look strong enough to me, but I get
the barbecue starter from Mike, and I
probably should have put this on on myself,
but you know, foolishly I had bill likes to
take over and he likes to.
He likes to put things in.
And he probably over dinner a little.
I'm just stepping back.
Meanwhile, the Walter and Mike are getting
out, they still got some beautiful steaks
there and and they kind of go up there
that's like we get the small, we got the
medium and then then they eventually get to
the large, which to me look like that.
That picture in health of a couple of sets
along this barn that looks good.
Meanwhile, he's put the hook on, OK, we're
now I'm bill.
I don't. I'm not sure you should just throw.
There's a lot of Cat Bailey, there's a lot
of gas.
I think maybe you should just know he's not
worrying lately and now, OK?
He thinks that's fine. But you know what?
He's not looking at the origin actually of
the flame.
So what do you do now, Bill?
Mr. Smarty. All right, good know that works,
OK.
Meanwhile, we got all the meat.
Well, you know, why don't you heat up the
barbecue?
You might as well cook for the whole season,
and an odd thing about having meat, it seems
to draw the flies. And just I don't know if
you're out there for two minutes and suddenly
you got the flies all over.
And we have a lot of flies in our area.
I think it's actually the provincial bird.
And that is going get the you get the flies
out of there and then they'll slap, that was
a mistake. They're. Oh, and Mike, he had
been a drummer, was trooper in the early
days. So he got it, and then they got me, oh
boy, he's snag one there, and then now
Eleanor had the bug said, You know, that's
going to affect the taste, and he goes, Yeah,
it is. So, but luckily, Bill had brought the
Bud Light, which apparently
attracts the fancy plugged out in and out
and the flies, they started just migrating
right over there, which is good. But you
know what, those?
I can only handle so many flies and then
they kind of.
So, OK, so that was a problem, not the flies
are all coming back.
So they're starting to get on our body since
I'm so Mike grabs a chop and starts.
And I guess you could say the thing about
vines is, you know, individually they're not
that strong when you get a group of them
together and they have a fair amount of lift
on them and they can actually take a stake
right
Out here, right out of your hand.
They're going to hang on there.
You're losing, you're losing them.
Oh, man.
And what happened next time?
I really can't describe.
I just. I cannot erase the memory of all of
our great steaks.
Levitating in front of our very eyes.
If you see these flying over your house,
please call the lodge.
You know, one of the strongest bonds in life
is between the man and his vehicle.
It's almost like, you know what each other
is thinking.
Unfortunately, there are people in this
world who don't appreciate that quiet and
intimate understanding.
You know who I'm talking about.
People have said over in this area here, I
tell you everything you're doing wrong.
Hey, slow down. That was a stop sign.
You know, where are we, that kind of thing?
But the biggest dividing point comes when
this little light by the fuel gauge goes on,
the passenger starts going squirrely on you.
But you know you got 50 or 60 miles before
there's any real problem.
Well, here's a way to keep everybody happy.
See, when that light goes on, it just means
there's not enough gas in the part of the gas
tank where the switch is.
So all you got to do is loosen off the gas
tank straps and then just tip the tank a
little. The trick is we need a way to tilt
the tank from the driver's seat, and it's got
to be something subtle that the passenger
won't notice.
Now, sure, you know, if you're a government
engineer, you'd probably build some type of
hydraulic lift. But I don't have the kind of
free time those guys do.
So let's see what we can make with the
materials that are available.
I guess you could call this rigged public
enemy number one.
The tube up inside the car.
I got it to the driver's seat.
But now I need something that will inflate
the rubber bottle and tilt the tank.
And look what I found.
I won't be cushioned. Just my lucky day or
what I'm going to do is blow this baby up and
then slip it over at the end of my feet or
tube and I'm in business.
Ok. Got my whoopee cushion hooked up and in
place and completely under my control.
So I'm driving along.
I look down and oh my goodness, you laid it
off and the passenger started screaming,
Hey, look stupid, you're out of gas,
Out of gas. I don't think so.
Well, this is great. Harold's got half the
lodge crying, say that a clean Kleenex shirt
is going on here. What exactly is Dalton's
problem, Harold?
Well, it seems when he was a boy, his father
gave him a chicken.
Well, it was supposed to be a rooster.
I waited for it to be good.
It was
A level. Now.
What's wrong with them?
Well, they got the crying flu and typhoid
Harold is the carrier.
Geez, I was so happy when we flattened the
school.
No, I'm disquieted.
Just as long as you don't start crying.
Oh, don't worry, Mr. Green.
I've been in the slammer.
I've seen it all. Not to make me cry.
No, no. That's what I vowed to myself.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, that first night, huh?
When the shadow door closed.
Yeah. Ok.
Yeah.
Anytime, anytime you go.
Ok. If my wife is watching, I will
definitely be coming straight home after the
meeting, I got to get out of here.
I haven't seen this many men crying since
they canceled Baywatch and the rest of us.
Thanks for watching on behalf of myself and
Harold and the whole sobbing gang up here for
lunch. He was stuck on the ice.
You mean my
Daughter, everybody sit down, sit down, sit
down, everybody sit down.
Sit down. All right.
Follow me on.
Buy your hats for the mass prayer tie in,
little man.
But I could change if I had to.
I guess. I mean, they had a little incident
here today.
We knocked the school down and there was a
lot of dust and they got into the eyes and
some guys got teary eyed and Dalton here, he
got teary eyed.
And I'm wondering, did anybody else get
teary eyed?
Anybody can really get teary eyed.
Ok? Yeah. So I thought it was just the dust.
So it was just dusk.
So from now on, whenever we do a job like
this, we're going to we're going to wear
safety goggles. Ok?
Yeah. Well, it did hit a.