For those who have never seen our show before
it, don't worry.
This is it. All right. It's an eclectic mix
of reality television, with some introverted
self-awareness generally typical of the type
of show put together by a group of
underachievers with a government grant.
And here's my uncle, who happens to be the
real dynamo of the family, which is hard for
me to admit in public.
But anyway, here he is, the star of Red
Green Show Mr.
Red Green.
Thank you. Welcome to Possum Lodge.
I have the sound turned down back there, so
I can't hear Harold's intro.
That's a trick you might consider for the
next time you tune us in.
Harold, you got an effect for us tonight,
you know, might as well give them one more
way to turn off.
How about something like this?
Well, Harold does those effects because he
can.
Anyway, there's something kind of strange
going on at Possum Lodge this week,
especially with our medical officer Doc
Render.
For some reason or other, he's being nice to
people, even to the point of driving into
town in a closed vehicle or stinky Peterson.
So he figured he must be after something.
And a lot of the large members have been
complaining to me because when you get one of
the guys, you know, sucking up to everybody
and ingratiating himself and everything and
just reminds them of work, no.
To me, for the double double rent is 20.
What's that smell?
All right, all right for you, skunk pinhead.
We're playing for money.
I never played for money that would be
gambling.
I never gambled. That's why I'm the large
treasure.
That's why you're not.
Well, how about this?
What if? What if you loan me, say, five
hundred bucks and then 90 days from now I pay
you back six hundred?
Hmm. That wouldn't be gambling, huh?
Doug, listening to you is gambling.
I will get the money from helmet.
Helmets got lots of money because his mom's
got lots of money.
She buys him stuff all the time, so she's
got the money.
She goes in the helmet to helmet can give it
to you.
That wouldn't be right. Carol wouldn't feel
good about that.
No. This was strictly an investment
opportunity that I wanted to share with my
good friend Douglas here.
He's good with money.
You know, you're a disaster with money.
You're a one man stock market crash stock,
you see.
You'll need a job to get money, and you'll
need a skill to get a job.
And you need training to get a skill and
you'll need a loan to get trained and you'll
need a bloody miracle to get a loan.
Case closed. You know, Doc Atlanta, the
money, but I'm a little strapped on cash
right now. I still owe sixty seven dollars
to the home shopping network.
It's not so bad anymore. They repossessed my
TV.
So I'm working through it. You know,
How about you, Bill? Have you got any money?
Oh, never mind
You scrounging for cash, ganda.
Oh, mine are shortfall problem red.
That's all. We're that close to striking
oil.
My stockbroker said It's a bad time for me
to sell.
You know,
I suggest that maybe he could hit helmet up
for the money.
I'm sorry. What I meant was that he could
present an investment opportunity to helm it.
Yeah, but you know, if you don't pay him
back, you know, he'll just rip you up like a
rag doll. I one time saw him pull a guy
through a drainpipe by his lips.
Oh, that's horrible.
Who did you get it on film?
What about you? Read Here's fairly liquid.
Well, a lot of time.
Yeah, but you know, my mom said he once
said, Never lend money to a friend.
You lose both. Oh, no
Problem. I'm not your friend.
I don't even like you.
Oh, that's tempting. No.
But I mean, to lend you money, I have to go
borrow the money first and to clear that with
the wife. And then it would be the name
calling and sleeping in the garage and the
seven years before celibacy.
And I just don't think I could make that
work now.
Yeah, thanks. Anyway, right?
Hey, hey, this is great.
Here comes Hellman, because you could ask
him for the money.
How much? All sorts of money.
It's this.
It's great. Hey, Helmut, this is perfect
because Doc got something he wants to talk to
you about. Oh, yeah, yeah.
Does he have my five hundred bucks yet?
Oh oh no.
Not what was he here?
You know? Yeah.
Does he have my money? Gave him four hundred.
He said he'd give me five.
You know, you
Know where he's gone, he's gone.
How he went to get the money?
Yeah, because he mentioned to me that he was
like, You know that close to striking a
stockbroker?
Well, you tell him I'd like to see him and
he'd better come bearing gifts.
Will sharpen my tools.
All good choice helmet.
That's great. I'll mention that to him.
If I see him about you and the, you know,
the sharpened tool thing, that's who you're
going to get on with that one.
I am so glad the helmet doesn't work for the
home shopping network.
And.
It does a man get to stop and look around at
the trees and the sky and the water and the
ground, the bees on the land and the birds
in the air.
It's going to take a long time for us to
wreck this, but we're getting there.
This week on my corner, I'm going to show
you how you could make some furniture.
We need some chairs here up the lodge
because some of our old furniture is really
killing us insurance. You know, we've got a
recliner rocker here.
That's just unbelievable. But rather than
switch to the no fault system, what we
thought we'd do is is buy a couple of
chairs.
Well, I went looked at them.
Some of them are upwards.
Nineteen, ninety five, twenty bucks even.
That's what we pay for cars, you know?
So I thought, Well, heck, let's make our
chairs, you know, and to do that, all we
would need is a lathe.
Now L.A. is going to cost you six or seven
hundred bucks, which we could get, say, a bus
or a motor home for.
So instead of that, I'm to show you how you
can make your own lathe.
All you need is a drill.
Take your power drill.
Stick it into a vise.
It's going to save you a heck of a lot of
money, believe me.
Ok, so maybe you don't have a vice, huh?
Or maybe you don't even have a drill.
So you're saying, Well, how much is this
going to save me, you know?
Well, I'll tell you what, Ali.
There's a lot cheaper than advice on the
real put together.
Plus, with a drill, look at all the things
you can do with it.
You can you can drill or you can.
You can screw. You can.
You can mix your computer or you can sand.
You can grind. You can just take a Sunday
morning and just sit at home spinning things
around. While the families of church where
it's a little late.
All you can do is low, you know, except I
guess you can stand on it as a platform when
you're painting the ceiling. So you put this
in pretty good here.
Oh oh, and I may have.
Ok, OK. But L.A.
is still going to cost you more than, say, a
vice and two drills.
Take this out quickly before Louise Thompson
notices that his drill is missing, OK, now in
would. We're going to do our leaning on.
This is a beautiful piece of teak.
We're going to make a teak chair. This is
going to be one of the legs.
So when I got to do is just put a nail on
the top there to hold her and a hammer.
Wow. Wow. She was a bit of that old drill.
Like I told you, Bill is a very versatile
tool.
Oh yeah.
All right, Ali, put this into our drill, or
should I say our leave picking that up?
Oh, you see how you getting a feel for this
now and now?
I just need the Chuck T. I go through chuck
keys like pencils and hammers.
Unbelievable. I buy them by the gross.
You know this here last me about three
months.
Okay, all right now for our speed control.
I got this. I'm going to put that in the
pocket for speed control.
I got this thing off my wife's sewing
machine.
Everything used. And now this will turn our
drill into a not only a lathe, but a variable
speed lathe. So but the real end of the
pedal and I plug the pedal up.
Yeah. And OK, so we take this metal bracket
and I put a nail in this end of the wood now,
and we just line that up there, fit that
through there, and that'll hold her steady.
Now we want that bracket held on to the
bench.
So just use my power screwdriver here and
you want it really horse this down good
because you don't want this thing coming off
at three thousand rpm going through your
skull. No chair is worth that.
I mess it with. No, no, not even then.
Ok, that's good, that's good.
Now just check this out around here.
Taking that up, good.
Is that chuck key?
Hmm.
Oh oh yeah.
Yeah, yeah. We'll put that in there.
All right. Oh, all right.
Hello. And just one last thing just to
comment on an eye protection.
You know, you only have two eyes.
Take care of them. Ok.
Ready to go. So let's make some fine
furniture.
And. All right.
All right, so that we would we would carve
that down while I was spending next time and
then you'd make three more just like it and
then another time, maybe next week or
whatever we'll do, we'll make ourselves the
seat for this thing anyway.
Until next time, remember the women don't
find the handsome.
They should at least find a handy.
It is spring baseball season.
Your son is pitching the game is called on
account of darkness in the first inning after
your boy walked thirty seven consecutive
batters, but he was pleased his first no
hitter. Well, Doc has hit on just
about everybody here looking for money while
he's all the time trying to hide from
Helmand. In fact, even disguised himself as
a shrub, which was an unfortunate choice for
the dog days of summer and after that, this
plane disappeared.
But he told me that if he could afford it,
he'd have a complete facial reconstruction
and even a even a sex change operation.
I figure if Helmand gets his hands on them,
he'll get both of those for free.
So Helmand, what's his pound of flesh?
Does he know?
I think he just wants to pound doc's flesh.
No, no. I'll go read the pound of flesh
From the Merchant of Venice.
Shylock wanted his pound of flesh.
So he took her arms.
Oh no, see his daughter dressed up as a
lawyer and had the case thrown out based on
the fact that in the 15th century they
didn't have the proper equipment for weighing
meet.
English teachers have the highest suicide
rate on the Herald
Or a nun so long as those of intellect.
And I did want to talk to, you know, what
this financial problem that Doc Render is
having. No, no, no.
That man is a complete liar and a fraud.
Well, he's also the large doctor, you know,
correction.
He claims to be a doctor.
Yeah, he's got all that doctor and equipment.
He's got some tongue depressors
And red one box of coffee stat..
Does not a doctor make, you know, doc render
once took my temperature with an indoor
outdoor thermometer.
He told me that was a rectal oral.
So you're saying you don't think he's a
doctor?
Well, if he was, what do you need money now,
if he needs cash?
Well, let him go.
Perform a gallbladder operation on somebody.
What does he need the money for anyway?
Well, it depends who you ask.
Some people he tells, he's collecting money
for a polar expedition, and he told Harold
that he needed the money to make an alimony
payment to Madonna.
It's credible and worthwhile as both those
causes sound.
We have no money in the kitty.
Well, that's that's just temporary, isn't it,
Douglas?
I mean, one of the members pay their their
dues next
Same time every month.
Never, in fact.
Render is the worst.
If I enforce the Lodge charter, he hasn't
been a member since nineteen sixty five.
He's not good for it.
He's a bad risk.
He doesn't deserve a red cent.
I am not a bank manager, read,
I guess not a lot like my bank manager.
If I'm going to lend him money, where would
it end?
Soon everybody would be bothering me,
bothering me for money that I don't have to
lend if he needs money.
He can just go out and earn it.
Well, I'd be glad to pay him to come out
here and sweep up and bundle all these
leaves.
Well, I could mention that to him, but I
don't think he's going to go for it.
You know, doctors kind of like to protect
their hands
While he has to realize, read that money
doesn't grow on trees.
Well, when you got through with them anyway,
Bill told me to meet him down at the dock.
True. Yeah, I think that's Bill.
Oh yeah, because he wanted to talk about
various water safety and the life preserver
type weapon, so he had to bring it.
Now this is this.
That's a life life preserver.
And you get the ropes there and quite a few
ropes there, I didn't know to me, I guess, I
guess that's where they go. Anyway, I figure
you've got to advertise you.
You know, I really wasn't aware of what it
was, but he said to me, if it's not date,
it's really not going to do you any good.
So we passed it right down there and now
he's ready to ready to go.
It's like a little munchkin.
It's kind of cute, like a decoy.
And there's is no time for this one.
Bill knows all, but I know, OK, you got to
strap the tie at the front there, but I would
have thought that I would have thought the
arms had to go through those armholes.
Yeah, yeah, I think they do.
They surely
Do. Go on.
Now this this here is a is a boat hook.
And when someone's in drowning away, or you
can just kind of like extending your arm and
they hang on to that. And you know, now
Bill's bill's going to pretend he's drowning
and and and on the boat hook can just just
pull them in.
Well, and now he's pretending he's drowning
out.
I think he is. Oh yeah, he must have been.
And now this is this is a life ring.
And I think the key here is check the size
of it before, you
Know, because. Exactly.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So they'll got a little smaller one.
And also, he thought he'd widened himself
out a bit when he jumped on to this baby.
And I think that was a mistake, but I think
he got enough pieces left to build a new one.
Ok, bill. You know, it's not easy being a
teenager.
All the fears and worries and pressures from
kids to do things that you know you really
shouldn't do, you know,
Well, it doesn't concern me all that much.
Well, believe me, there's a lot of pressure
to experiment with illicit pleasures.
You know, they say things like, Oh, go
ahead.
Just try it. Go for it.
You know how drugs will fry your brain?
You can't afford that, right?
I was talking about sex.
Carnal knowledge.
All righty rule. Mean there's a lot of
pressure to have sex constantly.
Well, I say give in hell.
No, no. I'm going to wait till I'm married.
Oh yeah. Thank you.
Is married? He's still waiting.
Yeah. See, I figure if I wait till I get
married, then there's better likelihood that
a girl will be involved.
Well, at this point, I think is pretty well
exhausted any hope he had of coming up with
the money for Olmert. He did try to take
back the cases of empties that we got stacked
under the porch and and in the kitchen and
in the basement by the wood pile and I guess
almost 90 percent of the boat house and all
the way down the dock.
That time he got all that money of the stake
truck and blew all the tires and bent the
frame. He thought he would go on a lecture
tour, but that didn't sell well because
people don't like, listen to Hezbollah even
for free.
So at this point, I would say Doc is toast.
That's going to make for an interesting
meeting tonight, I'll tell you.
And by interesting, I mean, violent.
Well, D nor borrower nor lender be
From that same book where Skylark Teitelbaum,
somebody in the flesh
Is William Shakespeare, the poet, the
playwright.
You know what he'd say to Doc Render in a
case like this to thine own self be true or
false. It's a meeting time Uncle RAM dime
Tehran time.
Come on, let's go. I'll meet you down there.
Ok? Yeah.
All right, Harold. I don't think this is
going to take too long because I'll let the
others drive doc to the hospital.
Great. Great. Great.
Yeah, I got
it. All right.
Sorry, I can
get me.
The floor recognizes helmet Winter Garden
Doc Render owes me five hundred bucks, and I
would appreciate it if anybody here could
tell me where he is.
We made an agreement of an interest rate of
forty eight points, which is better than I
could do with GICS or on the bond market.
But if he tries to stiff me, I'm not going
to reward bad behavior.
First, a rip is yours.
All right. All right. Hold your horses.
I'm here. Sorry, I'm late.
Hi, guys. Hi, Helmut.
Where's my cash helmet?
Have I got good news for you?
In fact, I got good news for everybody.
What did you bring a lie detector?
Yeah, with the main problem around here is
nobody has any confidence in the other guy.
Well, that's OK. You don't think the king
designed for short Fazul?
Well, that kind of thing stand in his way to
you.
You know who he is. Don't tell me.
Where's my five hundred bucks game?
Pleasantville is the world's richest man.
He makes one hundred and twenty six billion
an hour.
And then there's the guy does well, doctor.
Does any of this going to tie into the real
world at any time in the near future, do you think?
Well, I'll put my new investment scheme.
See, six months ago, I started by borrowing
one hundred dollars from stinky Peterson.
Yeah. And then now, the next month, I
borrowed two hundred dollars from Moose
Thompson. Yeah, out of which I paid stinky.
One hundred and fifty dollars.
Wait, wait, wait. What happened to the other fifty?
If you're going to start nickle and diming me,
we're gonna lose the whole concept.
Anyway. My plan's been going just great.
I keep on attracting new investers and, uh, with each new refinancing, I get closer and closer to the final pay off.
Which is when I go to King Fizzlethorne. Get six trillion dollars.
Which, if oil sheiks like him, well, they spend as a tax write-off.
And what happens to all the profits, Doc?
To be shared equally amongst all the investors.
Now the dividend, however, can not be realized unless I get
another five hundred dollars of new cash to pump into the system.
Or, unless, uh, Helmut there wants to differ his shares.
How would you like to differ your pulse?
You know, Helmut, I, uh, made this for your mother.
It took quite a bit of time, of course.
Time that I could of used to get your money back but, uh.
Well, I felt it was more important.
I think a lot of your mother, Helmut.
Thank you.
She likes these.
She wears them in her hair.
Okay, you got another twenty-four hours.
Well thank you, Helmut!
At least somebody can show a little confidence around here.
Well, if there's no other business, Bill.
No.
Well then I call on Douglas here  for a little entertainment.
Good night men, good night men.
Thank you, red.
Keep it hopping. Keep it hopping.
I will. Thank you.
How about a few jokes there, Dougster?
Uh, this was an unfortunate chapter that, uh,
will never be repeated.
And now, boys,I've got something very special for you today.
How to clean your fingernails.
Well, hopefully, Doc has learned his lesson.
You know, for a guy who needs money all the time,
you'd think he might hang out with some people who have some.
I don't know why, uh, Doc chooses to spend time with us
rather than the rich and famous.
Or maybe the rich and famous have kind of told him,
"this is the way it's got to be."
Anyway, uh, if my wife is watching, I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting,
and I - I'm bringing Doc, so, uh, would you leave $500 in small
bills on the kitchen table?
Now, now, now, it's - it's - it's not a loan.
It's an investment.
So, until next time, on behalf of myself and harold and the whole gang up here at possum lodge, keep your stick on the ice.