IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
COMING TO YOU DIRECTLY
FROM POSSUM LODGE
WHERE EVERY DAYS IS LIKE
TAKING A VACATION,
FROM REALITY, THAT IS.
HERE'S THE STAR OF OUR SHOW,
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
[applause]
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
THIS IS AN EXCITING DAY.
FIRST DAY OF TROUT SEASON.
OH, I HATE TROUT SEASON.
I HATE THAT.
FISHING SHOWS MAKE
BAD TELEVISION.
THIS IS A FISHING SHOW.
IT IS?
YEAH.
THAT EXPLAINS THE RATINGS.
PICTURE THIS, UNCLE RED.
YOU AND A BUNCH OF GUYS
IN A CANOE WAITING FOR A TROUT
TO BITE A RUBBER MINNOW.
NOT DYNAMIC IMAGERY.
ALL RIGHT, HAROLD,
PICTURE THIS.
YOU WEARING A PAPER HAT
MAKING FRENCH FRIES.
[audience laughing]
[horns honking]
[geese honking]
[quacking]
ON TODAY'S SHOW, I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW TO MAKE A TACKLE BOX.
RANGER GORD HAS MADE SANDWICHES.
I DON'T ASK.
MIKE RELATES HIS
PRISON EXPERIENCE TO REALITY.
DOUGIE TELLS US
HOW TO GET WOMEN.
FISHING SEASON
STARTED THIS MORNING.
WE'VE HAD OUR FIRST ARREST.
BEFORE THE SUN WAS EVEN UP,
BOB STUYVESANT FROM THE
MINISTRY OF NATURAL RESOURCES
FINED JUNIOR SINGLETON
AND CONFISCATED
HIS FISHING EQUIPMENT.
HE TRADED A '78 BUICK LeSABRE
FOR
THAT STUFF.
NOT HIS FISHING GEAR.
JUST THE AIRCRAFT LIGHTS.
AIRCRAFT
LIGHTS?
JUNIOR HAD LIGHTS ON THE BOAT
POINTING INTO THE WATER.
IS THAT ILLEGAL?
YEAH, IT'S CALLED
UNFAIR ADVANTAGE.
BRIGHT LIGHTS ATTRACT FISH.
AND GOVERNMENT AGENTS.
[laughing]
IS JUNIOR IN A LOT OF TROUBLE?
THAT'S BETWEEN JUNIOR
AND THE MINISTRY
OF NATURAL RESOURCES.
WHERE DID HE GET
AIRCRAFT LIGHTS?
THAT'S BETWEEN JUNIOR AND
THE MINISTRY OF TRANSPORTATION.
AIRPLANES SHOULDN'T FLY
AT NIGHT.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
WELL, IT IS NOW.
[laughing]
(Red): LATER, WE'LL
PRACTISE CASTING
GETTING READY FOR --
OH, BOY.
DROPPED YOUR SINKERS
AND EVERYTHING.
PICKING 'EM UP.
OH, OH, BILL, GOT ALL
THE LURES SNAGGED INTO YOU.
I GUESS YOU CAUGHT YOURSELF.
I'M NOT GOING TO CLEAN YA.
OK, THIS IS FOR
TWO HOURS WITH A WRECKING BALL
FROM McCLINTOCK SALVAGE.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. HAMAR
TO SAY THIS WORD.
THIRTY SECONDS.
BEGIN.
ALL RIGHT, MIKE,
UH, PROMISE.
DEATH THREAT?
[laughing]
DEDICATION.
HABITUAL OFFENDER?
CONVICTION.
APPEAL?
[laughing]
UM... HONOUR.
AMONGST THIEVES.
[laughing]
NOW, MIKE, WHEN A MAN AND WOMAN
PLEDGE THEIR LOYALTY,
THAT'S CALLED MAKING A...
CONJUGAL VISIT.
[laughing]
OH, SHE HAD A RIFLE
ON HER DRESSER
A SHOTGUN ON THE FLOOR
A PISTOL IN HER PILLOW
AND AN UZI BY THE DOOR
SHE HAD ENOUGH ARTILLERY
TO START A CONFLAGRATION
AND WHEN SHE THREW
HER ARMS AROUND YOU
YOU WERE PRETTY MUCH
THERE FOR THE DURATION
WITH THIS BEING THE START
OF TROUT SEASON,
I GOT OUT MY FISHING GEAR.
THERE'S A LOT, BUT, HEY,
I NEED IT ALL,
'CAUSE WHEN I GO,
I WANT TO STAY GONE.
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO
KEEP GOING HOME
FOR ANOTHER HOOK, OR MORE BAIT
OR ANOTHER ROD,
OR MAGAZINES, OR ICE,
OR SANDWICHES,
OR MY EIGHT TRACKS,
OR ANY OF MY FISHING GEAR.
THIS WEEK I'LL SHOW YOU
HOW WE CAN MAKE HIP WADERS
THAT WILL HOLD
ALL OF YOUR FISHING EQUIPMENT.
HOPEFULLY YOU'LL NEVER HAVE TO
STEP ON DRY LAND AGAIN.
THE PRIME COMPONENT
IS ONE OF THESE WADING POOLS.
I GOT THIS ONE FROM
JUNIOR SINGLETON.
THERE'S A HOLE IN IT
FROM A GAME OF LAWN DARTS.
FIRST, CUT A HOLE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE BOTTOM,
THAT'S THE SAME CIRCUMFERENCE
YOU ARE
IN THE MIDDLE OF YOUR BOTTOM.
THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
I'LL ROUND IT OFF.
ONCE YOU GOT THE HOLE CUT
THE SIZE OF YOU,
DUCT TAPE
SOME SHOULDER STRAPS IN THERE
MADE OF... DUCT TAPE.
AND JUST PULL THE UNIT
UP ONTO YOUR SHOULDERS.
THAT'S WHY THEY CALL THEM
SHOULDER STRAPS.
AND THERE WE GO.
WE'LL HAVE TO SEPARATE
THIS POOL INTO COMPARTMENTS.
FOR THAT, I SUGGEST
A PIECE OF VINYL SIDING.
JUST PEEL IT OFF OF
SOMEBODY'S HOUSE
WHILE SOMETHING ELSE LOUD
IS GOING ON,
LIKE, SAY, AN ELECTRICAL STORM.
JUST BE SURE TO WEAR
RUBBER-SOLED SHOES.
YOU WANT TO BEND THIS
TO FIT INSIDE.
I SUPPOSE YOU COULD
MEASURE THIS,
BUT WHO HAS THAT KIND OF TIME?
ALL RIGHT, I GOT HER
SEPARATED INTO COMPARTMENTS.
I'VE GOT MY FAVOURITE POP HERE.
I GOT THE BAIT IN THIS AREA.
GOT SOME SANDWICHES.
AND GOT SOME TOOLS
IN THIS AREA.
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHEN YOU'LL NEED 'EM.
I'VE ADDED SIGNS
SO YOU CAN TELL WHAT'S WHAT,
'CAUSE ON A HOT DAY,
THE SUN BEATING DOWN,
IT'S DIFFICULT TO TELL THE BAIT
FROM THE TUNA CASSEROLE.
THAT WAS NOT A FUN DAY.
NO WONDER THE FISH
WEREN'T BITING.
AROUND BACK, I'VE GOT
MY FIRST AID, MY MAGAZINES--
ALL RIGHT,
I CAN'T SEEM TO ACCESS
THE STUFF IN THE BACK.
WE HAVE WHAT WE CALL
A DESIGN FLAW.
THIS WILL TAKE
A MAJOR RE-THINK.
ALL RIGHT,
GET YOURSELF A HARD HAT.
DRIVE A SPIKE UP THROUGH THAT.
WE'VE ALL DONE IT THE OTHER WAY
A FEW TIMES, HAVEN'T WE?
TAKE A ROLL OF DUCT TAPE.
STICK THAT ON
AS YOUR BEARING.
PROBABLY YOU'VE NOTICED THAT
THIS IS AN ARMY HELMET.
I GOT IT FROM THE POSSUM LODGE
LITTLE THEATRE GROUP
WHEN "ALL QUIET ON
THE WESTERN FRONT" BOMBED.
"BOMBED" IS A LITTLE STRONG.
"SELF-DESTRUCTED"
IS MORE ACCURATE.
I ADDED SOME STRAPPING
SO THESE ARE LONGER.
I GOT A HOLE
AT THE CRISS-CROSS.
TRY TO LINE HER UP WITH
THE SPIKE --
GET THAT IN THERE.
AND THERE YOU GO.
HUH, HUH, HUH, HUH?
LOOK AT THAT.
HUH, HUH?
NOW WE'RE FISHIN'.
IT'S JUST LIKE A LAZY SUSAN.
REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
I'M GOING FISHIN'.
OH BOY, OH BOY, OH BOY.
RANGER GORD GIVES THE TOWER
A COAT OF PAINT.
BOB STUYVESANT
JUST ARRESTED STINKY PETERSON.
IT'S THE FIRST DAY
OF TROUT SEASON
AND THE ONLY THING REELED IN
ARE POSSUM LODGE MEMBERS.
DOES STINKY QUALIFY AS
A LARGE-MOUTH OR A SUCKER?
WALL-EYE ACTUALLY.
STINKY WAS FISHING AT
ROCK REEF POINT
BY CHUCKING STICKS OF
DYNAMITE INTO THE WATER.
APPARENTLY THAT'S ILLEGAL, TOO.
THEY'RE SO STRICT
ABOUT THOSE KIND OF THINGS.
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO CATCH UNARMED FISH
WITH EXPLOSIVES
OR NUCLEAR WEAPONS.
IT'S PUT A DAMPER ON
SPORT FISHING EVERYWHERE.
IS THAT SARCASM, HAROLD?
NOT IF I HAVE TO EXPLAIN IT.
IS IT SARCASM
OR NOT?
GO FISH.
[laughing]
AN IMPORTANT PART OF
THE FOREST RANGER'S JOB
IS RESCUING LOST CAMPERS
AND HIKERS.
THE FOREST IS OUR FRIEND.
BUT MANY PEOPLE ENTER THE FOREST
UNAWARE OF
ITS POTENTIAL DANGERS.
BABES IN THE WOODS, RIGHT?
BABES?
THERE'S BABES HERE?
BABES, WHOA, WHOA!
OW, OW, WHOO!
BABES, BABES, BABES!
WHERE?
IT'S JUST AN EXPRESSION.
GETTING BACK TO
YOUR EARLIER STATEMENT.
YOU'VE BEEN UP HERE 16 YEARS.
HOW MANY PEOPLE HAVE YOU
RESCUED FROM THE WOODS?
UH, YOU MEAN ALTOGETHER,
IN A BUNCH?
HOW MANY, ROUGHLY?
ALL TOTALLED UP?
I DON'T THINK THE NUMBERS
ARE IMPORTANT.
SO IT'S NONE.
YEAH, BUT I'M READY.
FOR EXAMPLE, I HAVE
A LIGHT SANDWICH TABLE.
IT'S LIGHT BECAUSE SOMEBODY'S
BEEN LOST FOR WEEKS
AND YOU GIVE THEM A HEAVY MEAL,
YOU KNOW WHAT HAPPENS.
[gagging]
ALL RIGHT, WE UNDERSTAND.
I'M EVEN GOING TO
CUT THE CRUSTS OFF
TO MAKE THEM EVEN MORE
DIGESTIBLE.
THEY LOOK GREAT.
THANKS.
I HAVE A NICE PUNCH
FOR A BIT OF A MIXER.
WE'LL PASS OUT NAME TAGS,
GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER,
WHERE YOU'RE FROM,
WHAT YOU DO,
HOW MANY PEOPLE IN YOUR PARTY
PRESUMED DEAD,
HOW MANY PEOPLE
YOU KNOW PERSONALLY,
LIKE REALLY KNOW?
THEN IT'S TIME FOR
RANGER GORD'S CHILLI,
AND ALL I CAN SAY IS
THANK GOODNESS WE'RE OUTSIDE
FOR THAT ONE.
[laughing]
THEN IT'S TIME FOR TEA
AND DESSERT.
THEN, TO HELP THEM ASSIMILATE
BACK INTO CIVILIZATION,
WE'LL PLAY CHARADES.
CHARADES, GORD?
GORD, GORD, GORD,
YOU GOT PEOPLE IN THE WOODS.
THEY HAVEN'T HAD FOOD
OR SHELTER FOR A WHILE.
THEY COULD HAVE
MEDICAL PROBLEMS.
THERE COULD BE DEHYDRATION,
HYPOTHERMIA.
IT MIGHT TAKE THEM A WEEK
TO GET BACK ON THEIR FEET.
A WEEK?
YEAH, A WEEK.
WOW.
A WEEK OUT HERE.
OH GEEZ,
WE COULD HAVE CAMPFIRES,
MAKE GIMP BRACELETS,
SING SONGS, PANTY RAIDS.
OH, COME ON, GORD.
WHO AM I KIDDING?
NOBODY EVER GETS LOST
AROUND HERE.
I DON'T KNOW, GORD.
YOU SEEM PRETTY MUCH OUT THERE
TO ME.
WELCOME TO
HAROLD'S HANDICRAFTS
WHERE CRAFTY HANDS
MAKE HANDI-CRAFTS.
TODAY WE'LL BE MAKING
A COUNTRY KITCHEN CLOCK.
WA-HA-HA-HA.
ALL RIGHT.
FIRST, AS ALWAYS, STEP ONE,
GATHER UP SOME SCRAPS OF WOOD.
THAT WOULD BE THESE.
NAIL THEM TOGETHER
AND YOU GET
A LOVELY HOUSING
FOR THE CLOCK MECHANISM.
TAKE A COUPLE
AND NAIL THEM TOGETHER.
THAT WILL BE THE CLOCK HOUSING.
WE WON'T USE THAT ONE.
THAT'S GONNA -- AH!
OK,
THERE.
ISN'T THAT ATTRACTIVE?
[laughing]
[applause]
AND IT'S STURDY, TOO.
WE'LL LET THAT GLUE DRY.
AND NOW IT'S TIME TO WORK ON
THE CLOCK MECHANISM.
FOR THAT,
YOU'LL HAVE TO BUY A KIT.
THAT'S IN HERE.
THERE'S EVERYTHING IN HERE.
YOU'VE GOT THE WINDINGS.
THERE'S A DARK THING.
AND STUFF.
LOOK AT ALL THIS STUFF.
AND THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT YOU NEED.
WO-HO-HO-HO.
OK, THERE'S EVERYTHING
YOU'RE GOING TO
POSSIBLY NEED IN HERE.
EXCEPT THE INSTRUCTIONS.
BUT THAT'S OK.
THAT'S OK BECAUSE WE CAN
ONLY HOPE THAT IT'S LOGICAL.
THERE YOU HAVE IT.
A LOVELY COUNTRY CLOCK FACE.
OF COURSE,
YOU HAVE THE MECHANISMS.
THAT'S INTRICATE.
WE WON'T GET INTO THAT
THIS WEEK.
THEN YOU SIMPLY INSERT
THE CLOCK MECHANISM
INTO THE PREVIOUSLY-CONSTRUCTED
HOUSING.
ALL RIGHTY.
THERE YOU HAVE IT.
YOU'RE VERY OWN COUNTRY CLOCK.
[laughing]
AND YOU KNOW, THE BEST PART IS
YOU MADE IT YOURSELF.
EVERY YEAR COME SPRING,
IT'S TIME TO PAINT
THE OLD WATCH-TOWER.
A LOT OF PEOPLE MIGHT SAY
"THAT SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF WORK
PAINTING ALL THOSE STAIRS."
BUT, IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
HERE, LET ME SHOW YOU.
WE'LL START WITH A PRIMER COAT.
[paint sloshing]
AND ONCE THAT'S DONE,
WE'LL START WITH
THE FIRST COAT.
[paint sloshing]
YUP.
AND IT LOOKS LIKE WE NEED
A SECOND COAT HERE.
[Paint sloshing)
THERE WE GO.
THE JOB'S DONE.
OH GEE, SORRY, RED,
I DIDN'T SEE YOU
COMING UP THERE.
GEEZ.
TWO MORE LODGE MEMBERS WERE
ARRESTED FOR ILLEGAL FISHING.
THIS RED TAPE
IS KILLING THE SPORT.
EVERYBODY'S TICKED OFF.
THE GUYS ON THE SPANISH TRAWLER
ARE THINKING OF LEAVING.
[laughing]
THE COPS PICKED UP
MOOSE THOMPSON
FOR POISONING FISH.
WHO WANTS TO EAT POISON FISH?
HE USES BENZENE, HAROLD.
SO IT ALL BURNS OFF
WHEN YOU COOK IT.
IT TASTES LIKE THE FISH
WAS COOKED IN AUSTRALIAN WINE.
WHY DON'T YOU GUYS
JUST FISH THE NORMAL WAY?
WELL, BUSTER HADFIELD
WAS FINED AND ARRESTED,
AND HE WAS FISHING WITH
A HOOK AND A LINE.
A GRAPPLING HOOK
AND A HIGH-TENSION POWER LINE!
ANYBODY USING A METAL LURE
HAD MOST OF THEIR BODY HAIR
BURNED OFF.
PEOPLE PAY TO HAVE
THEIR BODY HAIR REMOVED.
WHAT HAPPENS IF
I LOSE MY EYEBROWS
AND THEY DON'T GROW BACK?
YOU COULD BE
A FEMALE IMPERSONATOR
INSTEAD OF A MALE IMPERSONATOR.
[laughing and applause)
MEANWHILE, BACK AT
THE CASTING CONTEST --
THAT'S A HECK OF A LURE
YOU GOT ON THERE, BILL.
BILL AND I ARE
WARMING UP OUR SKILLS.
WE HAD A BUCKET.
IT WAS CLOSE.
YEAH, IT'S CLOSE.
YOU GIVE IT A TRY,
BIG MOUTH.
NO, NOT THAT WAY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THERE'S AN UNUSUAL TECHNIQUE.
SO HE TRIES HER AGAIN.
RIGHT IN.
NO, BILL, NO -- OH.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD DO ON YOUR OWN,
ESPECIALLY WHEN
YOU'RE WITH BILL.
HIS REEL'S ALL JAMMED UP
'CAUSE HE BOUGHT
THE ROD AND REEL FOR 99 CENTS,
BRAND NEW.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THERE'S NO FISHING GEAR
IN THERE.
IN THERE, YOU DUMB, BIG...
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THAT'S A WRENCH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
THAT'S MY STARTING MOTOR.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH
MY STARTING MOTOR?
WHAT'S THE PLAN?
HE'LL USE THAT
AS A FISHING REEL.
LATER THAT DAY
THE SUN CAME OUT.
HE GOT A HOLD OF THAT ONE,
DIDN'T HE?
LOOK AT THAT BABY GO.
LOOK OUT FOR THE WIRES.
OH BOY, OH BOY, OH BOY.
HE'S GOT THE STEEL LINE
ON THERE, TOO.
HOW DOES THAT FEEL?
WHAT HAPPENS NOW IS,
UNFORTUNATELY, I GUESS,
THE STARTING MOTOR
STARTED WINDING THE LINE IN,
AND BILL'S GONE.
HE'S NOT WINDING THE LINE IN.
HE'S WINDING BILL
UP TO THE LINE.
LOOK OUT, BILL!
OH, OH.
GOSH, THAT WAS--
[laughing]
AND UP HE GOES.
BUT, HEY,
ALL'S WELL THAT ENDS WELL.
SHOULD HAVE SEEN
THE ONE THAT GOT AWAY.
STAY TUNED WHILE I ADJUST
MY FISH FINDER.
WELL, I'VE HAD IT.
BOB STUYVESANT JUST CONFISCATED
ALL MY FISHING EQUIPMENT
RIGHT OUT OF MY BOAT.
WHAT WOULD GIVE HIM THE RIGHT
TO TAKE MY STUFF?
IT'S HIS STUFF --
YOU BORROWED IT LAST YEAR.
IF THE GOVERNMENT
HAD THEIR WAY,
YOU KNOW WHAT FISHING
WOULD BE?
SITTING IN A BOAT
WITH A ROD, A REEL AND A LURE,
WAITING FOR SOME FISH
TO BITE IT.
THAT'S NOT A SPORT --
THAT'S GAMBLING.
WHY DON'T YOU USE
LEGAL EQUIPMENT,
LIKE A FISH FINDER?
YOU KNOW WHAT I'LL DO?
USE A FISH
FINDER?             USE A FISH
FINDER.
YOU KNOW WHY
I DIDN'T THINK OF THIS?
I WASTE TIME ARGUING WITH YOU.
I WON'T DO THAT ANY MORE.
EXCELLENT.
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION
OF THE SHOW.
ON THIS WEEK'S PORTION
WE HAVE MY UNCLE RED
AND HIS FRIEND,
MR. DOUGIE FRANKLIN.
[applause]
OK, HERE WE GO.
FIRST LETTER GOES AS FOLLOWS:
"DEAR EXPERTS"
"I FIND A CERTAIN WOMAN
VERY ATTRACTIVE,
"AND SHE SEEMS NICE.
"WHENEVER I TALK TO HER
"SHE MAKES A FACE
LIKE SOMETHING IS BURNING,
"THEN JUMPS INTO A TAXI.
"WHAT'S
THE DEAL?
"MR. LONELY."
NOT MUCH TO GO ON THERE.
MR. LONELY COULD BE
MR. LOSER.
OR MAYBE THE WOMAN
IS JUST PLAYING HARD TO GET.
WELL, NO, RED --
IT'S BEEN MY EXPERIENCE,
WOMEN DON'T PLAY
HARD TO GET.
THEY ARE HARD TO GET.
[laughing]
YOU DON'T WALK UP TO A WOMAN
AND START A CONVERSATION.
YOU DRIVE UP.
THERE'S A HINT,
BOLD AS BRASS
IN THAT LETTER.
"SHE GOT INTO A TAXI."
HINT, HINT.
GET YOURSELF A SET OF WHEELS.
WHAT, LIKE YOUR MONSTER TRUCK,
MR. FRANKLIN?
'CAUSE PERSONALLY I FIND THAT
COMPLETELY INAPPROPRIATE.
WELL, DON'T YOU GO
KIDDING YOURSELF, HAROLD.
WOMEN LOVE A MONSTER TRUCK.
THEY LOVE THE POWER.
THEY LOVE THE SIZE.
WOMEN LOVE ALL THAT RUBBER.
YOU'RE UP IN THE TRUCK.
DON'T YOU NEED
SOMETHING SHORTER
TO MAKE THAT EYE-TO-EYE THING
THAT THEY RECOMMEND
IN THOSE MAGAZINES
THAT BERNICE BUYS?
YOU'RE ONTO SOMETHING, RED.
IF YOU TAKE THAT THOUGHT
A LITTLE FARTHER,
IT MIGHT BEHOVE YOU
WHEN YOU BUY YOUR VEHICLE
TO GET ONE THAT PUTS YOU
AT EYE LEVEL
OF WHATEVER IT IS
YOU WANT TO BE LOOKING AT
WHILE YOU'RE TALKING TO IT.
CATCH MY DRIFT?
AND ANOTHER THING,
POWER WINDOWS.
WOMEN LOVE A MAN THAT CAN
DRIVE UP SMOOTH AS CAN BE,
RAISE AND LOWER HIS WINDOWS
WITHOUT CRANKING AND WHEEZING.
YOU KNOW WHY?
IT MAKES 'EM THINK
YOU'RE GOOD WITH YOUR HANDS.
[laughing]
PROBLEM,
UNCLE RED?
THIS FISH FINDER'S USELESS.
MAYBE IT'S A LOOSE WIRE.
IS IT COVERED BY WARRANTY?
WAS IT COVERED BY WARRANTY?
I TOLD EVERYBODY THAT
FISH FINDERS WERE LEGAL.
SO EVERYBODY GOES
AND BUYS A FISH FINDER,
OR BORROWED ONE OR STOLE ONE.
WE MONITORED EVERY CUBIC INCH
OF POSSUM LAKE.
WE'D SEE EVERY FISH IN THE LAKE.
NOBODY SAW ANYTHING.
COMPLETELY BLANK SCREENS.
STINKY PETERSON TOLD US THAT
BOB STUYVESANT AND THE MINISTRY
OF NATURAL RESOURCES
MUST HAVE SENT OUT
A JAMMING SIGNAL.
LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
NOT ONE FISH FINDER
REGISTERED FISH?
NO, SIR.
BEFORE THEY HAD
THEIR DYNAMITE, POISON
AND HIGH-VOLTAGE LINES
CONFISCATED,
DID ONE MEMBER CATCH A FISH?
NO -- WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
THERE ARE NO FISH
IN POSSUM LAKE!
POSSUM LAKE IS FISHLESS!
GOLLY, THAT'S A RELIEF.
A RELIEF?
NO, POSSUM LAKE IS
COMPLETELY LIFELESS.
HERE I THOUGHT
MY FISH FINDER WAS BROKEN.
ALL RIGHT, IT IS BROKEN.
BUT IT MAKES ME FEEL BETTER
ABOUT HAVING
THE EQUIPMENT CONFISCATED.
ACTUALLY, IT'S A JOKE
ON BOB STUYVESANT.
HE TOOK AWAY ALL OUR STUFF
TO PROTECT THE FISH,
AND THERE AREN'T ANY.
WHAT AN IDIOT!
[laughing]
[squealing]
IT'S MEETING TIME.
YOU GO AHEAD.
DON'T TELL THE GUYS
ABOUT THE NO-FISH.
I WANT TO GIVE THEM
THE GOOD NEWS.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I WON'T BE BRINGING
A MESS OF FISH.
I'LL STOP AT
THE TAKE-OUT PLACE.
THAT WAY WE DON'T HAVE TO
CUT THE HEADS OFF
OR PULL THE GUTS OUT,
UNLESS I GO TO THE CHEAP PLACE.
FOR THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF HAROLD AND MYSELF
AND THE GANG AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[applause]
[possum squeal]
(Harold): ALL RISE.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Harold): I INTERCEPTED
A MESSAGE.
THE MINISTRY OF TRANSPORTATION
IS DOING A SURPRISE INSPECTION.