YOU KNOW A MAN
CAN GET PRETTY HOT
WALKING AROUND ON A SUMMER'S DAY
ESPECIALLY IF THAT MAN HAS
GOT A COUPLE OF EXTRA
POUNDS ON HIM
AND WEARS A LOT OF FLANNEL.
HERE'S A WAY TO KEEP COOL
WITHOUT HAVING TO WEAR
SISSY CLOTHES.
GET YOURSELF A
WORM PICKER'S PAIL,
ATTACH IT TO ONE FOOT.
THEN WHAT YOU NEED IS A GAS
SIPHON HOSE LIKE THIS ONE.
YOU RUN THE HOSE DOWN
INSIDE THE PAIL,
UP ONE PANT LEG,
ACROSS AND DOWN THE OTHER ONE.
THEN YOU ATTACH THE PUMP OF
THE SIPHON UNDER YOUR
FOOT LIKE THAT
SO EVERY TIME YOU TAKE A STEP,
YOU'RE SQUEEZING IT.
[crunching sound]
NOW ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS FILL
UP THE WORM PAIL WITH ICE WATER,
AND THE MORE YOU WALK,
THE COOLER YOU FEEL.
[sound of water squirting]
[in high-pitched voice]
BOY, THAT WATER'S COLD.
[applause]
[cheering and applause]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT
BOY, EVERYBODY'S PRETTY EXCITED
UP AT THE LODGE.
WE'RE HAVING HAVE A LUNAR
ECLIPSE IN A COUPLE OF DAYS.
AROUND HERE THAT ONLY HAPPENS
EVERY 35 YEARS.
A LITTLE MORE OFTEN IF THERE'S
A TIRE FIRE.
I WANT ALL THE GUYS TO GET
TOGETHER
AND GO UP TO ROCK REEF POINT
AND WATCH IT FROM THERE
JUST LIKE WE DID
35 YEARS AGO.
WELL, THAT'S A FIRM GO, RED.
WE'RE ALL SET.
OH, YEAH, DID YOU
CLEAR THAT WITH
ANNE MARIE?
OH-HO, I DON'T HAVE TO
CLEAR IT WITH ANNE MARIE.
IF I SAY I'M GOING,
I'M GOING!
ANNE MARIE'S AT
HER MOTHER'S THIS WEEK.
WELL, YOU KNOW, YOU GOTTA
BE THERE, I'LL TELL YA.
IT ONLY HAPPENS
EVERY 35 YEARS.
JUNIOR'S GOING,
BUSTER'S GOING,
MOOSE IS GOING.
OLD MAN SEDGWICK SAYS NO.
HE'S ALREADY BEEN
TO THE LAST THREE.
IS STINKY PETERSON GOING?
WELL, PROBABLY.
YOU KNOW, IT'S HARD TO
KEEP THE STINK MAN
AWAY FROM A PARTY.
YEAH, IT'S GONNA BE GREAT.
IT'LL BE FUN.
AND YOU KNOW SOMETHING ELSE?
THE ECLIPSE DOESN'T
HAPPEN UNTIL MIDNIGHT.
SO I'M THINKING, WHY DON'T WE
JUST CAMP OVERNIGHT,
JUST LIKE WE DID
35 YEARS BACK?
OH, GEEZ, THAT WAS
A LONG TIME AGO.
WE WERE ALL BACK IN
HIGH SCHOOL THEN.
YEAH, I WAS IN FRENCH
IMMERSION REFORM SCHOOL.
WOW! DID YOU LEARN
ANY FRENCH THERE?
OH, YEAH.
UH, Bonjour. Qu'est-ce que
c'est le combination?
THAT MEANS, UH, GOOD DAY.
WHO CAN OPEN THE SAFE?
BOY, I REMEMBER THE BUNCH
OF US THERE THAT NIGHT.
PRETTY WET BEHIND
THE EARS, HUH?
ONCE THE RAIN STARTED,
WE WERE PRETTY WET
BEHIND EVERYTHING.
BOY, THAT WAS
A WHILE BACK, EH?
YEAH, BOY, WE SURE DIDN'T KNOW
MUCH ABOUT LIFE THEN, HUH.
CERTAINLY DIDN'T
UNDERSTAND WOMEN.
[laughing]
WELL, THEN IT
COULDN'T HAVE
BEEN THAT LONG AGO.
[applause]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[cheering and applause]
TODAY'S WINNER WILL GET
TO SPEND A WHOLE DAY
AS THE TOWN MASCOT.
OKAY, COVER YOUR EARS, ED.
Mr GREEN, YOU'VE GOT 30 SECONDS
TO GET ED TO SAY THIS WORD...
NERVOUS
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND GO!
OKAY, ED, HOW ARE
YOU FEELING?
FAIRLY RELAXED,
RED, THANKS.
OKAY, OKAY, BUT WHEN YOU'RE
NOT RELAXED YOU'RE...
EASY PREY?
NO, NO, OKAY, YOU KNOW
WHEN MOST PEOPLE GET ON
TELEVISION LIKE THIS
IN FRONT OF A HUGE AUDIENCE,
YOU KNOW, THEY FEEL VERY...
ED?
ED!
ALL RIGHT,
JUST CALM DOWN.
UM, WHAT DO YOU CALL IT
WHEN YOU GET A DRY MOUTH
AND YOU BREAK OUT IN
A COLD SWEAT?
A WORK DAY.
UH, WE'RE ALMOST
OUT OF TIME, Mr GREEN.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
ED, SUPPOSING YOU'RE
UP A LADDER TRYING TO GET
A RACCOON OFF SOMEBODY'S ROOF
AND IT TURNS AND
SNARLS AT YOU, OKAY.
NOW, THAT MAKES YOU...
WET MY PANTS.
OKAY, OKAY.
BUT WHAT DOES IT DO TO
THE GUY HOLDING THE LADDER?
OH, MAKES HIM
PRETTY NERVOUS, I TELL YOU.
[cheering and applause]
YOU KNOW, LIFE GOES
INTO CYCLES
ONE THING ENDS,
ANOTHER BEGINS.
I'M GOING THROUGH
ONE OF THOSE RIGHT NOW.
THIS HERE'S MY NEW POSSUM VAN.
I'M EXCITED ABOUT THAT.
BUT IT ALSO MEANS THE END
OF MY OLD POSSUM VAN,
WHICH MAKES ME KINDA SAD.
BUT YOU KNOW WITH
EVERY OLDER VEHICLE
THERE COMES A TIME
WHEN YOU KNOW IT'S OVER.
I WON'T BORE YOU
WITH THE DETAILS.
LET'S JUST SAY THIS TIME
SHE'S NOT PLAYING POSSUM.
YOU KNOW, AFTER EVERYTHING
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH TOGETHER,
I CAN'T JUST THROW HER
OUT LIKE ONE OF DONALD
TRUMP'S GIRLFRIENDS.
SO AS A LAST GESTURE OF
FRIENDSHIP AND SERVICE,
I'M GONNA TURN MY OLD POSSUM
VAN INTO AN AIR BOAT.
LIKE THE ONES THEY
HAVE IN FLORIDA
THAT KIND OF WHIP
THROUGH THE EVERGLADES.
THEY DON'T ACTUALLY GO IN
THE WATER; THEY KIND OF
GLOSS OVER IT.
AND GLOSSING OVER THINGS HAS
ALWAYS BEEN MY PREFERRED
LIFESTYLE.
NOW, ORDINARILY, HAVING YOUR
VEHICLE FLIPPED UPSIDE DOWN
WOULD BE A SETBACK,
BUT NOT IN THIS CASE.
ALL YOU DO IS TRACE THE SHAPE
OF AN AIR BOAT ON THE
OUTSIDE OF YOUR VAN
AND THEN CUT AWAY
THE PART YOU DON'T NEED.
NO, WAIT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
ON AN AIR BOAT,
THE MOTOR'S AT THE BACK.
[sawing sound]
[sawing continues]
OKAY,  I HAD A BIT
OF A SNAG THERE.
HAD TO TURN THE
ENGINE UPSIDE DOWN
SO THAT IT WAS RIGHT-SIDE UP
BECAUSE WHEN IT WAS RIGHT-SIDE
UP, IT WAS UPSIDE DOWN.
'COURSE, I HAD TO FIND A
WAY TO GET THE ENGINE
TO FIT ONTO THE MOTOR MOUNTS
FROM THE OTHER SIDE,
BUT LUCKILY, I HAVE A
UNIVERSAL ADAPTER FOR THAT.
THEN WE GET RID OF
THE RAD ALTOGETHER.
I'LL JUST EXTEND THESE HOSES.
WE CAN SUCK WATER RIGHT
OUTTA THE LAKE.
OKAY, NOW, THE REASON I HAD TO
GET THE RAD OUTTA THERE,
I WANNA MAKE ROOM
FOR A BIGGER FAN BLADE.
AND I KNOW JUST THE THING.
AH, I COULD'VE SWORN I SAW --
OH, YEAH!
YEP, YEP, YEP.
HERE IT IS.
NOW, FOR A FINAL TOUCH
ON HER THERE,
I RECYCLED MY
VAN DOORS AS RUDDERS.
GOT 'EM HOOKED UP TO THE
STEERING WHEEL.
I KNOW ON THE REAL AIR BOATS
THEY HAVE A CAGE AROUND
THE FAN BLADES,
BUT I FIGURE AS LONG AS YOU
NEVER GO BACK THERE,
YOU SHOULD BE FINE.
[fan blades whirring]
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
[fan blades whirring
sound of engine]
[cheering and applause]
REMEMBER WHEN YOU WERE YOUNG
AND YOU USED TO SEE OLD
MEN OUT ON THE STREET
JUST STANDING THERE
STARING AT STUFF?
AND NOW YOU FIND
YOURSELF DOING IT.
HEY, DON'T WORRY.
STARING AT STUFF IS
A NATURAL THING
THAT HAPPENS TO
MIDDLE-AGED GUYS.
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT STUFF
THAT EVERYONE ELSE LOOKS AT,
LIKE CYCLONES, HOUSE FIRES
AND TOPLESS WOMEN.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THOSE HOLES
THEY CUT IN BOARD FENCES
AROUND THE CONSTRUCTION SITES
SO YOU CAN LOOK IN THERE.
THE ONLY GUYS THAT ARE LOOKING
IN THERE ARE MIDDLE-AGED GUYS.
FOR SOME REASON WOMEN HAVE NO
TIME TO STICK THEIR HEAD
THROUGH A SHEET OF PLYWOOD
TO WATCH BULLDOZERS PUSH
DIRT INTO A PIT.
BUT I TELL YA, I'M THERE
EVERY CHANCE I GET.
AND WHEN I LOOK OVER
AT THE OTHER HOLES,
I SEE OTHER GUYS
JUST LIKE ME.
WITH THE SAME BLANK LOOK
AND THE SAME OPEN SCHEDULE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO FEEL BAD;
YOU DON'T HAVE TO FEEL
EMBARRASSED.
AT OUR AGE WE ALREADY KNOW
WE'VE HEARD OURSELVES ENOUGH.
NOW IT'S TIME TO WATCH OTHERS.
SO DON'T FEEL BAD IF YOU
SUDDENLY REALISE
YOU'VE BEEN STANDING THERE
WATCHING GUYS FROM THE CITY
FIRE TREE BRANCHES THROUGH
A WOOD CHIPPER FOR AN
HOUR AND A HALF.
JUST SMILE,
COUNT YOUR BLESSINGS,
AND COUNT YOUR FINGERS.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[applause]
WELL, WE'RE PRETTY MUCH READY
FOR OUR ALL-NIGHTER UP AT
ROCK REEF POINT
TO WATCH THE LUNAR ECLIPSE.
WE'VE HAD PRETTY GOOD RESPONSE;
ALTHOUGH SOME OF THE GUYS
ARE AFRAID IT'S GONNA
MAKE THEM GO BLIND,
BUT THEY AGREED TO WATCH UNTIL
THEY NEED GLASSES.
[laughter and applause]
WHERE DO YOU WANT
ALL THIS STUFF?
WHAT IS IT?
WELL, IT'S ALL THE STUFF
WE NEED FOR THE
LUNAR ECLIPSE.
IT'S GOT FOOD, BEVERAGES,
BLANKETS, PILLOWS
AND A CHANGE OF UNDERWEAR.
IT'S NOT THAT SCARY, DALTON.
THE ECLIPSE LASTS
ABOUT A MINUTE AND A HALF.
SOUNDS LIKE MY LOVE LIFE.
INCLUDING THE
35-YEAR WAIT.
JUST PUT THAT DOWN
WHEREVER YOU WANT.
YEAH, OKAY,
THAT'S GOOD.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
WE CAN PUT IT IN THE
VAN WHEN THE TIME COMES.
YEAH, I GOT A LITTLE SURPRISE
FOR EVERYBODY LATER ON.
OH, YEAH, DOES IT
INVOLVE THE POLICE?
WHY?
WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD?
NOTHING.
THEN, NO.
ALL RIGHT.
FINE.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
WINSTON SAID HE'S GOING
TO BRING THE VIDEO CAMERA.
CAPTURE THE LUNAR
ECLIPSE FOR POSTERITY.
OKAY, THAT'LL BE GREAT.
THAT'LL BE GOOD.
LOOKING FORWARD TO THAT.
YOU KNOW, THE ECLIPSE
IS ABOUT 10 AFTER 12.
WHEN DID YOU GUYS
WANNA GO UP THERE?
OH, I'D SAY
ABOUT 11 O'CLOCK.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT 10 O'CLOCK?
THERE MIGHT BE HEAVY TRAFFIC.
YEP, DON'T WANT TO GET CAUGHT
IN ROCK CREEK REEF RUSH HOUR,
I'LL TELL YOU.
WELL, WHAT TIME
SHOULD WE GO, HUH?
WELL, 8:30, 9:00,
I GUESS.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT!
WELL, LET'S GO NOW!
HEY!
[grunting]
[cheering and applause]
WELCOME TO THAT PORTION OF THE
SHOW WHERE WE FEATURE
THE THREE LITTLE WORDS
MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY...
Audience: I DON'T KNOW!
AND THIS WEEK'S LETTER
GOES AS FOLLOWS...
"DEAR EXPERTS,
"I'M HOPING YOU CAN
HELP ME WITH MY SIN."
OH, SORRY, THAT SAYS
"HELP ME WITH MY SON."
MIGHT BE THE
SAME THING.
"HE DOESN'T DO ANYTHING
AROUND THE HOUSE.
"HE'S FAILING AT SCHOOL,
AND HE HAS THE MANNERS
OF A FIG."
THAT'S PROBABLY "MANNERS
OF A PIG," DALTON.
NO, IT SAYS FIG.
ALL RIGHT.
YEP.
"HE HAS NO SENSE OF
RESPONSIBILITY
"AND NO WORK ETHIC.
"MY WIFE SAYS IT'S JUST A PHASE
HE'S GOING THROUGH,
"BUT I'M LOSING HOPE
NOW THAT HE'S 37.
"ANY SUGGESTIONS?"
BOY, IT SOUNDS LIKE THE
TYPE OF GUY MY DAUGHTER
GOES OUT WITH.
WELL, IF HE'S GOT
THE MANNERS OF A FIG,
THAT COULD TURN INTO A
PRETTY HEAVY DATE.
[laughing]
THIS IS NOTHING
TO JOKE ABOUT.
HERE WE'VE GOT A GUY
WHO'S 37 YEARS OLD
AND HE'S NEVER WORKED
A DAY IN HIS LIFE.
YOU GOTTA RESPECT THAT.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
THIS GUY IS A DUD.
THINK OF THE WILLPOWER
TO RESIST THE PRESSURE
SOCIETY PUTS ON YOU
TO CONFORM AND GET A JOB.
YOU KNOW HOW STRONG YOU
HAVE TO BE TO SIT AT
THAT DINNER TABLE
WITH YOUR PARENTS
FOR 37 YEARS
WITHOUT BUCKLING?
THAT'S NOT HOW
I SPELL DUD, RED.
LET'S NOT BE
TOO HARSH NOW.
MAYBE THE GUY'S
JUST A LATE BLOOMER.
NO, NO, NO.
HE'S NOT BLOOMING.
HE'S PLANTED TOO DEEP.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO
AGREE WITH RED ON THIS ONE, YOU KNOW
I THINK HE
SHOULD GET A JOB
AND BE AS MISERABLE
AS THE REST OF US.
[applause]
AND MAKE HIS PARENTS
WATCH HIM SUFFER?
HOW DO YOU DO
THAT TO 'EM?
I'D GET OVER IT.
LOOK, WE'VE GOT TO FIND SOME
KIND OF AGREEMENT HERE.
WE CAN'T LEAVE
THIS VIEWER HANGING.
WELL, ALL RIGHT, UH,
DWIGHT, WHAT'LL IT TAKE
FOR YOU TO AGREE WITH ME?
FIVE BUCKS.
OKAY, DONE.
THERE YOU GO, DALTON.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
NOW GIVE HIM
THE FIVE BUCKS.
WHAT?
[Red chuckling]
[applause]
Red: THAT'S THE
POSSUM LAKE DRIVE-IN,
BUT, UM, DALTON HAD AN IDEA
TO USE IT DURING THE DAY.
YOU COULD SWITCH IT OVER
TO A GOLF DRIVING RANGE.
KIND OF THE SAME
KIND OF SETUP THERE.
THE ELEVATED TEE --
JUST ONE.
IT'S FIVE BUCKS,
AND YOU GET --
APPARENTLY YOU GET A
FULL BUCKET OF BALLS
AND A CLUB
FOR THE FIVE BUCKS.
JUST HAND IT OVER --
HEY! HEY! HEY!
OKAY, WELL, MIKE'S BEHIND ME
WE'RE GONNA HIT A FEW BALLS.
MIKE JUST HAS
THE ONE AS WELL.
BECAUSE HE HAS THE LOWER
VEHICLE HE HAS PROBLEMS
GETTING THAT.
NOW YOU GO OUT TO WHERE
YOU MEET TO WATCH THE MOVIE,
AND OF COURSE, YOU HAVE THE
STAND FOR THE SPEAKER THERE.
WELL, YOU HANG YOUR BUCKET OF
BALLS RIGHT ON THERE.
BUT DALTON, WELL, DALTON
KNOWS MIKE A LITTLE TOO WELL.
HE'S THINKING MAYBE
ONE DIDN'T COMPLETELY COVER
THE ENTIRE TURNOUT THAT MIKE
HAD PRESENTED TO DALTON
EARLIER AT THE BOOTH.
IT'S JUST ONE OF THOSE
EMBARRASSING MOMENTS IN LIFE
WHEN YOU --
QUITE A GANG IN
THERE, ACTUALLY.
NOW, YOU SEE YOU GOT 200 --
THIS IS ALL MARKED
ON THE SCREEN.
AND THE ONE ON THE BOTTOM
IS ARMS LIQUOR GIRL,
IF YOU CAN'T HIT IT
ANY FARTHER THAN THAT.
WHERE YOU HIT IT ON
THE SCREEN IS HOW FAR IT IS.
OF COURSE, DALTON'S GOT TO GIV
US A MILLION INSTRUCTIONS.
WE UNDERSTAND, DALTON.
YOU HIT THE BALL --
WE KNOW.
DALTON, LIFE IS TOO SHORT.
BOYS, TEE 'EM UP.
TEE 'EM UP.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE READY
TO HIT NOW, DALTON.
EXCUSE US.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
YOU GO BACK TO THE BOOTH.
THERE YOU GO.
OKAY, NOW WE CAN GET
DOWN TO SOME SERIOUS --
HOLD IT, GUYS,
SOME KIDS!
HANG ON.
KIDS USING THE PLAYGROUND.
OH, DALTON, WE SEE --
WE SEE THEM!
DALTON.
BOYS, TEE 'EM UP.
TEE 'EM UP.
AWAY YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, THERE GO THE KIDS.
WE CAN GET BACK TO GOLFIN'.
ENJOY OURSELVES.
NOW, DALTON'S A LITTLE --
OH, YEAH, THAT'S IT.
WE GOTTA LEAVE.
IT'S OUR FAULT.
EVERYTHING'S OUR FAULT.
AH, GEEZ.
ALL RIGHT, BOYS,
DO WHATEVER I SAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M THINKING?
TEE 'EM UP, BOYS!
TEE 'EM UP.
GOOD SHOT!
[chuckling]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, DALTON.
YOU HAVE A RAINBOW DAY.
OH, MY.
[applause]
BERNICE GAVE ME A
CELL PHONE FOR CHRISTMAS.
I WASN'T THAT EXCITED
BECAUSE TO ME A CELL PHONE IS
JUST AN ELECTRONIC LEASH.
NOW, THIS ONE HAS
A SWITCH ON IT
WHERE YOU CAN TURN
OFF THE RINGER
AND THE UNIT WILL VIBRATE
WHEN YOU'RE GETTING A CALL.
NOW, COINCIDENTALLY, I HAD
PULLED A MUSCLE IN THE
SMALL OF MY BACK,
TRYING TO DO UP MY BELT
AFTER A BUFFET DINNER.
SO WHAT I DO IS I JUST TAPED
THE CELL PHONE RIGHT OVER
THE SORE SPOT.
NOW ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS CALL MYSELF.
OH, THAT FEELS --
[vibrating sound]
OH!
AND AS LONG AS
I DON'T ANSWER IT,
THE CALL IS FREE!
OH!
[vibrating sound]
I WAS STARTING TO
GET SOME CRAZY IDEAS THERE.
IT WAS THE ROARING '20s.
THE CENTURY HAD JUST
COME OUT OF ITS TEENS,
BUT IT WASN'T READY TO HAVE
CHILDREN  AND SETTLE DOWN JUST YET.
PEOPLE WERE TRYING
ALL KINDS OF NUTBAR STUNTS
JUST TO GET ATTENTION.
THEY WERE RIDING
ON THE HIGH WIRE,
AND WALKING ON AIRPLANE WINGS,
SWALLOWING GOLDFISH.
AROUND HERE, WE HAD
OUR OWN GUY...
POSSUM LODGE'S OWN DAREDEVIL,
WALT GORGOVICH.
MY FATHER WOULD
SCARE US SILLY
TELLING US STORIES ABOUT SOME
OF WALT'S GOOFIER STUNTS.
APPARENTLY, WALT WOULD GATHER A
BUNCH OF BOYS INTO THE KITCHEN
TO WATCH HIM STAND IN
FRONT OF A HOT STOVE
AND FRY A POUND OF BACON
WITH NO SHIRT ON!
HE WAS ONE OF THE FIRST GUYS
TO FIND OUT THAT BACON
WAS BAD FOR YOU.
YEAH, HIS STUNTS KEPT
GETTING WEIRDER.
HE USED TO SWALLOW STUFF...
GOLF BALLS, DOOR HANDLES,
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE
A SMALL APPLIANCE.
THEN THERE WAS THIS
ABANDONED STEAM ENGINE
OUTSIDE OF PORT ASBESTOS.
SO ONE DAY,
WALT SAYS TO MY FATHER,
"I'M GONNA EAT THAT TRAIN."
WALT'S PLAN TO INGEST AN
ENTIRE STEAM ENGINE
WAS A THREAT TO SOME PEOPLE.
MY GREAT UNCLE WAS LIVING IN
ONE OF THE BOXCARS AT THE TIME,
AND HE WAS AFRAID THAT WALT
WAS GONNA EAT HIM OUT OF
HOUSE AND HOME.
ONE DAY HE SAW WALT TAPPING ON
THE TRAIN REAL NERVOUS LIKE.
SO MY UNCLE ASKS WALT
WHAT'S HE DOING,
AND WALT SAYS HE'S
LOOKING FOR A SOFT SPOT.
WALT WAS CRAZY TO TRY
TO EAT THAT TRAIN.
I HAD AN UNCLE WHO
TRIED TO DO STUFF LIKE THAT.
NOTHING THAT BIG.
OH, HE'D EATEN A
SMALL BICYCLE OR TWO
AND A BUICK CONVERTIBLE.
BUT WHEN WALT BIT
INTO THAT TRAIN,
HIS TEETH EXPLODED LIKE A
BALLOON FULL OF CHICLETS.
EVERY ONE OF HIS TEETH
HAD TO BE FILLED.
IT BROKE HIS SPIRIT, YOU KNOW.
IT REALLY DID.
HIS DAREDEVIL DAYS WERE OVER.
YEAH, MAYBE AT A PARTY
HE'D CHEW ON A BALL
OF ALUMINUM FOIL,
BUT THAT WAS ABOUT IT.
[animal growling]
WHEN WALT GORGOVICH
WAS LYING ON HIS DEATH BED,
A GROUP OF PEOPLE CAME IN
AND TOLD HIM THAT
THEY HAD DECLARED
STEAM ENGINES OBSOLETE.
HE CLOSED HIS EYES
AND HE SMILED,
AND HE SAID WHAT WERE,
THANKFULLY, HIS LAST WORDS...
"NEVER BITE OFF
"MORE THAN YOU
CAN CHEW CHEW."
[applause]
NOW, THAT WAS A NIGHTMARE.
20 OF US SHOWED UP AT ROCK
CLIFF POINT TO WATCH
THE LUNAR ECLIPSE.
JUST A BUNCH OF AIMLESS GUYS
WITH NO ALTERNATIVES,
JUST LIKE OLD TIMES.
[laughter and applause]
[cheering and applause]
I DON'T EVER WANNA
DO THAT AGAIN!
HOW DID THAT
GO SO WRONG SO FAST?
WELL, YOU WERE PART
OF THE PROBLEM,
BRINGING
THAT MOTORHOME.
WELL, I WAS JUST TRYING TO MAKE
THE GUYS MORE COMFORTABLE.
WELL, I KNOW,
BUT ONCE THEY SAW THAT,
THEY DIDN'T WANT
TO GO BACK OUT TO
WATCH THE ECLIPSE.
WELL, WINSTON SAID HE'D HOOK UP
HIS VIDEO CAMERA TO THE TV
SO WE COULD ALL
WATCH FROM INSIDE.
YEAH, WELL, THAT
LASTED THREE MINUTES.
EVERYBODY STARTS YELLIN',
"WHAT ELSE IS ON"!
WELL, WE PUT ON
THE BASEBALL GAME,
AND EVERYONE GOT
TIRED AND WENT TO BED.
AND THE BAD NEWS IS
IT WAS ONLY 10:30.
WELL, WE HAD TO GET UP EARLY
BECAUSE I HAD TO GET THE
MOTORHOME BACK
BEFORE THE DEALERSHIP OPENED.
YOU KNOW, I WAS ONLY TRYING
TO RECAPTURE A MOMENT
FROM OUR YOUTH.
THE WHOLE THING
WAS A DISASTER.
YOU CAN'T
GO BACK, RED.
OH, YEAH,
I THINK YOU CAN.
NO, THE CONSERVATION AUTHORITY
WAS QUITE CLEAR.
WE CAN'T GO BACK.
GEE, I'M SORRY,
Mr GREEN.
I'M SORRY I MISSED
THE LUNAR ECLIPSE.
WELL, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WHEN MOOSE THOMPSON
DROPPED HIS PANTS,
THAT WAS ENOUGH MOON
TO LAST ME A LIFETIME.
[possum squealing]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD, GUYS.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
UH, IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I THINK I LEARNED THAT YOU
CAN'T GO BACKWARDS;
YOU NEED TO GO FORWARD.
WHEN I COME HOME TONIGHT I'M
HOPING TO GO FORWARD,
UNLESS YOU THINK
THAT'S TOO FORWARD,
IN WHICH CASE YOU GO INTO
BACKWARD WITH YOUR LIGHTS ON
AND BEEP TWICE.
OKAY!
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[cheering and applause]
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN NOW.
HAVE A SEAT.
SIT DOWN. EVERYBODY SIT DOWN.
ALL RISE!
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, MEN, BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN, BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO, I GUESS.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, NOW, I'M SORRY
WE ALL MISSED THE LUNAR
ECLIPSE LAST NIGHT.
BUT APPARENTLY WINSTON TAPED THE
WHOLE DEAL ON HIS VIDEO CAMERA.
HE'S GONNA PLAY THAT TAPE
BACK FOR US RIGHT NOW.
GO AHEAD, WINSTON.
Winston: IS THAT A
LUNAR ECLIPSE?
Red: NO, I BELIEVE THAT'S
A LENS CAP ECLIPSE.