It's a world going by too fast is your life
seemed like a bad movie and the VCR stuck on
fast forward it's flashing 12.
Well, well, well, well, it's time to put
your life on pause.
Readjust your SKU, reset your counter, clean
your heads.
It's the red green show.
And here's the man whose life really is a TV
show on the unmarked tape of reality.
Here he is my uncle and the man they call
red green.
Well, what's his name?
Here he is. Red green.
Thank you and welcome to Possum Lodge.
Despite actually what my nephew Harold here
says, I'm not so much of the star of the show
as I am the ringmaster of the circus.
So let's bring in the clowns.
Harold say hello. Ok.
Hello. I'm Harold Greene and I'm the director
producer of the show, and I do things like
this. Oh, it gives that show that, you know,
professional and slick look.
Yeah, a lot like his haircut.
And we all have different areas of expertise
up here at the Lodge.
And as ringmaster, my job is to understand
the workings of the human mind and see if
that in any way relates to any of the large
members that we all have all these different
interests. And yet, you know, we do share
certain things.
We share a love of sports and the outdoors
and beer and good talk and women.
Although I think if most of the members
could could find a woman, they probably drop
everything else.
Well, actually, I'm glad you're married and
you still like sports beer in the outdoors.
Yeah, but I just do that to keep my marriage
fresh air anyway.
Everybody has all these different interests
and nobody judges anybody.
So so you don't get judged yourself, you
know, let he, who is without stupidity, cast
the first insult. And sometimes the guys
will actually combine a couple other
interests like, say, beer and the outdoors
or beer and sports or beer and talk.
Oh, what was that?
Well, that's that's another combo out there.
You see, Bob drives a golf balls out and
then helmet blasts him out of the air with a
shotgun shell. It's called skeet golf.
Well, how come nobody like combines your
interests with mine?
You know, I feel sort of left out.
I have interest, too.
Well, why don't we do that right now, Harold?
You take us into the next segment with that
gizmo of yours, which is one of your
interests. And then I can go back to
ignoring you, which is one of mine.
Oh, OK, great. Was that an insult?
Not if you have to ask. Oh,
not sorry, Bill. Now you took too much off
that leg.
You got to take some more off the other
side.
Bell, Bell, Bell, Bell.
Can you take it outside? Thank you.
I've been shopping Hook Line got some stuff
for the RV here.
Air fresheners. When it comes to RV here.
But what's that phrase? What's that for?
It starts with a aficionado.
No anal retentive.
That's that.
What the hell is going on out there?
Oh, bob and helmet, they're playing skeet
golf, skeet golf now.
Well, like Bob can't get anybody to play golf
with him, right?
And Helmet can't find anybody to go hunting
with them.
So what they do is Bob hits
The ball and then helmet blasts them into
little pieces.
When they land, they don't hit people.
Oh oh.
Oh, my God.
That was Glass breaking my RV.
They've wrecked my army. No, no, no, no, I'm
pretty sure no way because they hit a boat
towards the lake. You're OK.
Really? Oh, all right.
I'll tell you what we'll do. We'll pretend
it.
Oh, hi, Glenn, how are you doing today?
Good to see you. You guys wrecked my our
Virginia Glen Glen.
Don't be silly. No, of course not.
You're being nice to me. You did.
You wrecked. Where a gold helmets me,
they're supposed to blast the ball before it
hits the ground. You hit it backwards, bob.
The ball actually went backwards.
I don't mind shooting them when you're
hooking them and slicing them in front of me,
but I don't have eyes in the back of my
head.
You don't have anything in the back of your
Know I listen to him.
What's with him in that mobile home, anyway?
You know what he is?
Well, I don't want to say in front of Harold,
but it starts with an
A. Anal retentive.
No, but you're close.
I got to get some more jokes.
He's been golfing again there, Bob.
Oh yes, sir ed.
It's great fun. You know, seeing little bits
of dimpled ball rain down over the lake.
You wrecked it. You repair me.
Destroy destroyed. Is it all smashed up?
Little pieces and everything? Yes.
I got to see this.
Me right?
They smashed my sunroof.
You guys will pay for it. You guys will
replace it.
Not me. I didn't wreck it.
You animals wrecked it.
All right. All right.
Glenn will replace it.
Same make. Same model.
Same everything. Fine.
It's a twenty four foot sea breeze coastline
or two thousand.
I got the optional V8 engine and I got the
plush interior of a sunroof.
Is that?
I think he's talking about the whole RV bob.
Yes. You wrecked it.
You replace it. Look, I'll replace the
sunroof.
The rest of it was your mistake.
You'll get me a new RV, mister.
I don't think so.
Why don't you go talk to helmet?
Get him to replace it?
That's it. Go yell at helmet.
Oh yeah, you'd love that.
Wouldn't you seeing me dead?
You just get me a new RV, but you don't
remember this, but I'm the natural resource
rep in this area.
Well, I could close down that marina of
yours.
That's just a big, toxic dump with boats
stuck to it.
Fine, Bob, just get me a new RV red.
I want these guys suspended from the lodge
until they buy me a substitute home.
You guys have to bring that up at the meeting
tonight.
I got I got some things to do.
Bring your checkbook, pal.
Well, you too, pal.
You know, go down to that black hole.
You call home arena for a quick inspection.
You probably come up with about, oh, I don't
know, five thousand dollars worth of
environmental infractions.
Just at the gas pump.
You owe me a new RV.
Bob.
Plan to load up and laden to the right, stop
on your belly and shut your eyes, hop on your
haunches, jump in the air.
It looks to me like that meal was a little
too spicy.
This week on Handymen Corner, when I show
you something you can do with an old fridge
that's lost what it takes to keep your
butter hard.
You know, an old an old fridge like this
sounds like something you'd have to pay a
scrap dealer to haul this thing away, but
we're going to turn it into something that no
junk dealer would touch a gentleman's
armoire.
All right. First thing we got to do is we
got to disconnect the refrigeration unit here
And
Now we'll just pry all this stuff off the
back.
And we have a little problem here.
There's a gas and this is called Freon.
Now this is a gas that has no smell.
We don't see a lot of that up at the Lodge.
But the problem with it is that once this
stuff cuts loose, it goes up way up into the
atmosphere and takes out the ONOE layer or
something like that.
So we've got to be very careful and try and
capture all the gas as soon as it escapes,
because it would just, first of all, break
the seal.
All right, but very, very quickly.
You know, if everybody did that and the
Earth would be a heck of a lot better place
to live, I think that now we're just going
to gently remove the pump unit on the bottom
there already.
My gosh, usually I'm here.
So now we got her.
And what do we have to do to turn into a
gentleman's armoire diddly squat?
You got your ties in the door there.
You've got a shelf for your shirts, you've
got a shelf for your pants.
You've got a shelf for other things you
don't like to describe in public.
You keep your underwear and keep her over
here.
Keep your socks in the vegetable crisper.
You might want to throw a box of baking soda
in there.
You got all your clothes handy and just
right, ready for you to use and look what we
got up here in the freezer. Your very own
haberdashery, Al Harrill says teenagers like
to wear cool clothes, well, how much cooler
can you be than have your clothes in the
fridge? Personally, I'd rather give my
clothes the Sally-Ann.
Throw Harold in the fridge. Actually, I
didn't.
I didn't want to show you something else to
do the fridge.
You can turn a fridge actually into a into a
fishing boat, but we are a little short of
time. So I'm just going to say, remember, if
the women don't find you handsome, they
should at least find your handy.
If you want to do the fishing boat thing,
you just knock off both doors flipped over on
its back with a 20 horse on the back.
Throw your bait into the meat keeper and
you're gone.
Oh, Bill, wow, great.
Think you got it? Three, At least you don't
want a Japanese restaurant.
It is spring. The days are growing longer,
the nights are growing shorter.
Some of us think there may be a connection.
Well, Glen Braxton is still on the warpath
about his RV sunroof.
Glen blames Bob because Bob's 90 pounds
lighter than helmet.
Also, golf clubs don't hurt as much as guns.
Bob Miller and he blames he blames helmet
but not to his face, of course, and helmet
could care less, which is a pretty popular
attitude up here at the Lodge.
But I'll tell you, Bob has really got his
dander up.
You can use my special shampoo if he wants
smells like rotten eggs, you know, but it
really works.
All right, so he got his dander up.
It means he got angry.
What's what's a dander?
Is it like a body part? I never heard it.
I don't know what it is here. It's just
something that goes up when you get angry.
That's all.
Well, if you don't know what it is, how do
you know if it's up or down?
Don't worry, Harold. You'll know.
Anyway, Bob is notified, Glenn, that the
marina is a class nine environmental hazard
and a Class 10 eyesore.
He went down there taking samples.
You got air samples, water samples, soil
samples.
He's ended up impounded.
The whole marina, including Glenn's RV that
was parked inside Glen got so darn mad he
attacked Bob with a boat trailer.
It's this whole situation getting out of
control and or what?
I hate to see a good friendship break up
because the money, you know, that's why I
never asked for a raise.
Yeah. Well, this is a pride thing, Harold.
You know, neither one of these guys wants to
look like a loser.
Is a challenge now.
It's a question of honor, OK?
Nobody wants to back down.
Oh, so they're fighting like two roosters
over a hen.
Exactly right, Harold?
Oh, I knew this whole thing was about S-E-X.
Two Roosters. I'll bet you that's what the
dander is.
I'll bet you. Yeah, I bet you that.
Like that red, fleshy thing that hangs from
roosters neck like that.
That's a dander. Figured it out, dander.
Oh no, you're down here.
Yeah. Grease in my umbrella flat.
Oh, sure. Envy you single guys.
I don't know how this this stupid son of
argument is a long way out of proportion.
Bob and Glenn are acting like kids.
Oh, that's terrible.
What would their mom say?
I know what my mom would say.
I should say, you act civilized or else
whack my mom's especially well.
She must be how much you let you live at
home.
Well, I help with the rent.
You know, the landlord comes over and I
scare him off.
His life hasn't been easy for my mom.
You know, first I was a difficult birth, and
that's not easy on a 16 year old girl.
And then my father will, you know, he left
home when I was six?
Oh my gosh, where do you go,
The beer store? First time I saw him get off
the couch, ever.
You know, when my mom had to do everything
herself cleaning the place, order the pizzas
because she held down two jobs.
She was a wax jockey at the car wash and a
human cannonball in the circus.
I mean, she taught herself karate.
This woman is a saint.
Well, it sounds like she was canonized by the
Ringling brothers.
And speaking of projectiles helmet.
What about this sunroof thing?
Well, I guess I could have a look at it, but
first I got to get the pump running and then
I said I clean out the eavesdrops on stinky
struck.
Well, I just appreciate it.
Take a look. I mean, you know what?
I think your mother would appreciate it,
too.
Yeah, really?
Oh yeah, I think so. Yeah.
Well, I'll do it right now then for mom,
right?
Oh, I better take some tools
Belt on me now. I mean, I'm out in the woods,
but I didn't.
I couldn't find Well. Oh gosh sakes, huh?
I guess Bill, it moved.
Anyway, what Bill wanted to show us here was
if you're out in the woods and you get
hungry, you don't have to have brought your
lunch or anything.
There's there's food available right from
the various plants and trees.
Now this one here, for example, some type of
a nut.
It's a hard little nut.
Might be a type of a walnut or something to
shake the tree.
I thought maybe a kick might help if I
could.
And.
Yeah. Yeah, that worked out well.
Funny how the dots were, just all come down
on the one side, but I would say the nuts are
attracted to Bill anyway.
You gather them up and put them into your
interior.
Yeah, it's kind of fun, too. I wasn't as
hungry as Bill.
Now he's got to break the nuts open, so he's
using the knife, trying to cut through.
But a shell on me is quite light your
fingers.
So he does this the back of the head then.
And then, of course, he wants me to hold it
and watch it carefully now.
Here we go. Watch this While here we go.
Pop up at.
Oh, oh, by golly.
Oh, smoking. Oh, he's he's OK now, he's left
to the van to get a bandage on that, and I
could actually work quite well.
I don't know. He just took too much of a
back swing on that one.
And in days, too bad, either.
Now he's heading to the old, safer approach
using a hammer on this, which I think was a
little too much.
Oh.
You know what I mean, the food value is still
there, even even though they're not just
crushed a little
This and that's not
An attractive way to eat unless you know this
is this is an interesting wild berry that
grows at around around the lodge.
And there's two kinds of this one is very
sweet and delicious, and the other is very
sour, and I think we'll kill you.
And they looked identical.
So I think it's mainly the weight.
And now we got the wrong. Once we got the
wrong ones there, bill.
These are these are built long lines.
And of course, now the frustration in this
happened with men sometimes and just.
Thankfully, I'm not proud of that.
Now this was trying to use some smoke to get
the bees out of the beehive so that we can
get the honey, I never knew this before.
Apparently the smoke, but I think you should
be a little more attention to where the bill.
Well, I guess it's toasted, honey.
Yeah, bill, I'll take care of it. Harold,
have you given any thought to having children
any time, every night?
I think about it. No, no.
I mean, having children.
Oh, well, yeah, I'd like to have children one
day.
Yeah, yeah. I think it'd be great.
I'd like to have a child myself.
No, no. You can't have a child.
Yes, I
Could do that with modern science.
I wish I could.
You can have a child like a child.
Yes.
Yes, I could be the first pregnant man.
I couldn't stand behind myself and support
me during the birth.
And you would you like to have children?
I'm not that way. I don't think there's a
breathing exercise in the world if it gets
any easier a delivery. You know what I mean?
It'd be fun to watch you, though.
You make me laugh.
Oh, that's important. I.
Well, I hate to agree with Harold on
anything, you know, but this situation
between Bob and Glen actually has gotten out
of hand.
You know, after Bob impounded Glenn's marina
with his RV trapped inside, Glen went over
and broke into Bob's office, which is his
locker, the golf course, and he stole Bob's
IUD.
Uncle Fred, I think you mean ID.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, I hope so. Yeah.
Well, maybe it was.
Maybe it was his ID with an IOU in it.
Anyway, he took his wallet and and Glenn
went down to to an RV dealership, and he used
the ID to buy himself a brand new 30 foot
mobile home.
Yeah, that does sound like ID.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Anyway, Glen drove out of there was it
was his big RV that it was bought by Bob
Stuyvesant without him knowing the car.
So now Bob's account is about fifty thousand
overdrawn, which is going to be tough for him
to handle, even though you know he doesn't
make a good living, working part time for the
government.
I thought he worked full time.
No, no, no. He's paid full time, but he but
he works part time.
The rest of the time, he golfs anyway.
By the time the bad check with the fake
signature went buoying the RV, people called
the cops and they came over and arrested Bob
and Glenn took them down to the courthouse.
Wow. Oh man! Sedgwick decided to go down and
try to put up bail for them, and stinky
Peterson said he'd go along as a character
witness, but luckily they didn't get to
testify. By the time they got there, the
judge said that he was going to drop all the
charges against Bob and Glenn as long as
they could settle the thing themselves out of
court. So it's the top item of business at
tonight's Lodge meeting.
Why this pride thing really is dangerous,
isn't it?
Sure. Is, Harold, you won't catch me doing
it.
Pride comes before a something something
bad.
Well, by the way, I try to look up dander in
the dictionary.
Oh yeah. What did you find?
I found we could use a dictionary up here.
Oh, oh, that's if they called on the
meeting.
Well, this is going to be great.
The wild possum. Scream Uncle Ray, let's get
downstairs.
Oh, this is going to be so cool.
He was in jail.
I wonder if we saw Uncle Raleigh.
Wow. It's amazing how much intrigue and drama
and excitement we can get out of a $30 plexi
glass sunroof, isn't it? Could be worse,
though.
We could be at home watching this on
television.
Sorry, that came out wrong.
Ray Ray, Ray Ray
Rice.
One. And now how I see her how to sing, sing
the
floor, recognizes Bob Stuyvesant.
Thank you. I can't believe what happened.
Let me me, a government official in jail,
and I'm not even a politician.
It's horrible when the cells are just so
small, there's no room to practice putting.
I would die in prison.
I would just die. Prison was fine for me, so
it's just like living in the RV.
Now, as I understand it, the judge has told
these two guys they got a settlement of some
kind. Is that right? Yes.
Well, I got no idea.
Glenn, you don't actually need a new RV.
You might get a lemon or you could get one
with a big scratch, and they come with big
scratches now.
I heard that. Oh, that's true.
Yeah.
And Bob here? Well, it's not his fault that
the sunroof got smashed.
You know, he got a rogue ball.
So, Bob, why don't you just make good on the
sunroof?
And then everybody would be happy and
nobody's compromised?
Well, I can live with that.
That's fine for me.
Well, great. And all we got to do now is get
Bob to lift the injunction on the marina and
Glen here can open up again.
Well, there's no rush on that red.
I want to get the RV. Oh, sure, no problem.
Yeah, I want to take her for a run, you
know?
I mean, she's been sitting around for a day.
Maybe I could take you out to the driving
range tomorrow, Bob.
Well, that would be great. I could drive on
a bucket of balls.
I could drive over a bucket of all.
I could do that.
You know, Bob, it wasn't really your fault,
though.
I mean, that helmet, that moron.
He couldn't hit the broadside of a barn.
He is a broadside of a barn.
Yeah. You don't want my mistake was a
standing downwind of him.
He's not going to shoot his own head up.
No. Well, it wouldn't make any difference if
you know what I mean.
Guys talking about me or not me, bob.
Well, I couldn't fix the sunroof when you're
RV, but I found a golf ball.
Oh, that's great.
Well, that's my lucky ball.
Yeah, good.
Hey, Foster took a little step outside, I
love to remember her,
oh,
That's taken care of. I call on Bob here to
supply the evening's entertainment.
All right. We'll take a rest.
Well, my fellow brothers, there's this just
rabbi, that's priests in this ministry.
Well, I guess Bob and Glenn have to be pretty
satisfied with the way that turned out.
They got to keep their pride and their
teeth, and they managed to stay go to jail,
which to me is always worth a little extra
time and effort.
Anyway, my wife is watching.
I'll be coming straight home after the
meeting and I'm kind of in the mood for a
little two handed yoga or feeling that maybe
we can play some cards until next time.
I'll be out for myself and Harold and the
whole gang up here.
Possum Lodge. Keep your stick on the ice.
Anyway, anyway, although the
Rabbi decides eventually that he's going to
use
The five five five all oh no, the four iron,