♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN
AND ON TODAY'S SHOW
HAROLD'S GOING TO GET A DATE,
BILL'S GOING TO BUILD A CAMPFIRE
AND I'M GOING TO MAKE A BED
INTO A GARDEN TRACTOR.
(RIFLE SHOT FIRES)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
>>HAROLD: AND NOW HERE'S
THE MAN WHO'S BEEN CALLED
THE GREATEST CANADIAN CULTURAL
ICON SINCE MICHAEL J. FOX,
THE MAN WHO PUT
THE WOOD IN HOLLYWOOD,
MY UNCLE, YOUR HOST
RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU FOR TUNING US IN,
IT'S A LOUSY, ROTTEN JOB
BUT SOMEBODY'S GOT TO DO IT.
AND SPEAKING OF A GUY WHO
DOES A ROTTEN JOB,
HAVE YOU MET MY
PRODUCER/DIRECTOR HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: HELLO WORLD.
>>RED: WELL I GUESS THAT WOULD
BE THE SECOND DISASTER UP
AT THE LODGE THIS WEEK,
THE FIRST ONE HAPPENED
A FEW DAYS AGO,
A BUNCH OF THE GUYS DECIDED
THEY WOULD TRY A LITTLE TRUCK
FARMING SO THEY WENT OUT
AND BOUGHT A LITTLE TRUCK.
AND THEY WERE GOING TO PUT SOME
VEGETABLES IN THERE AND SURE
ENOUGH WITHIN ABOUT A HALF AN
HOUR STINKY PETERSON WAS CAUGHT
UP A TREE, BUSTER HADFIELD JUST
ABOUT ELECTROCUTED HIMSELF
AND MOOSE THOMPSON SET
HIS HAIR ON FIRE.
GOLLY IT'S NO WONDER SO
MANY YOUNG PEOPLE ARE
LEAVING THE FARM.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED IS THAT
WHAT ALL THOSE SIRENS
WERE ABOUT?
>>RED: YEAH.
ACTUALLY THEY SPACED THEIR
ACCIDENTS OUT ABOUT 4 HOURS
APART SO THE FIRE TRUCKS HAD
TO COME BACK AND FORTH 3 TIMES.
>>HAROLD: WHOA!
DO YOU KNOW WHAT?
I READ SOMEWHERE THAT IF YOU
CALL THE FIRE DEPARTMENT
TOO OFTEN THEY'RE GOING TO
START CHARGING YOU FOR
EVERY CALL.
>>RED: YEAH WELL THAT'S
WHAT THEY TOLD US,
WE GOT TO PAY THEM NOW
EVERY TIME THEY COME OUT.
>>HAROLD: YUP, NOW EXACTLY,
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I READ,
I READ THAT SOMEWHERE
I READ THAT AND NOW WE
I READ THAT SOMEWHERE,
I DON'T KNOW WHERE I READ IT
BUT I READ THAT, I DID.
>>RED: SHUT UP HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: OKAY.
>>RED: SO WHAT WE DECIDED TO DO
IS FORM OUR VERY OWN VOLUNTEER
FIRE DEPARTMENT UP HERE AND THE
GUYS ARE PRETTY EXCITED
ABOUT IT EXCEPT FOR
THE VOLUNTEER PART.
>>HAROLD: YOU KNOW WHERE
I READ IT?
ON TV YEAH, THAT'S WHY
I COULDN'T REMEMBER WHERE I READ
IT BECAUSE I SAW IT ON TV,
I DIDN'T EVEN READ,
IT WAS LIKE ON, IT WAS
IN FRONT OF ME
NOT THAT WAY YOU KNOW.
>>RED: WOULD YOU MIND
IF I SMACK YOU HAROLD?
>>HAROLD: YOU GO RIGHT AHEAD,
I'LL PHONE THE FIRE DEPARTMENT
AND IT'S GOING TO COST YOU.
>>RED: WELL NOW SEE,
I WOULD CONSIDER THAT
MONEY WELL SPENT.
♪ YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN ♪
♪ OLD MAN SEDGEWICK LAST NIGHT ♪
♪ DANCING IN THE LODGE ♪
♪ BY THE PALE MOONLIGHT ♪
♪ HE JUMPED ON THE TABLE ♪
♪ AND HOPPED THROUGH THE STEW ♪
♪ HE LEAPT ON THE MANTLE ♪
♪ AND YELLED TWICE ♪
♪ AND THREW A SHOE ♪
♪  HE JIGGED ON THE WOODSTOVE ♪
♪ AND BURNED OFF HIS SOCK ♪
♪ HE DANCED OUT THE FRONT DOOR ♪
♪ AND SPLASHED OFF THE DOCK ♪
♪ HE BOUNCED ON THE BOTTOM ♪
♪ GOING WAY DOWN THE LAKE ♪
♪ MAN WHEN HE GETS A ♪
♪ CHARLIE HORSE IT'S A DANDY ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE
GOING TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING
FUN YOU CAN DO WITH A BED.
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO ARE
OVER 50 AND ARE LOOKING
FOR ALTERNATIVES.
I GOT THIS IDEA WHEN I WAS
STUCK IN A TRAFFIC JAM OUT
ON THE HIGHWAY, THEY HAD ONE
OF THEM BIG MACHINES THAT'S
LIKE A ONE STEP DEAL THAT
BREAKS UP THE ASPHALT AND
PULLS IT INTO THE THING,
AND IT MELTS IT DOWN
AND THEN IT PUTS IT BACK
DOWN AND ROLLS IT FLAT.
AND I THOUGHT TO MYSELF MAYBE
WE COULD THE SAME THING
FOR GARDENING,
A ONE STEP MACHINE,
AND I GOT THIS ANTIQUE BED,
IT WAS LEFT OVER FROM OLD MAN
SEDGEWICK'S HONEYMOON SO I KNEW
I WOULDN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT METAL FATIGUE.
ALL RIGHT NOW STEP ONE,
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS GET
YOURSELF AN OUTBOARD MOTOR
AND MOUNT THIS TO THE FOOTBOARD
OR AS WE CALL IT THE TRANSOM.
OKAY AND WHEN YOU MOUNT IT
MOUNT IT WITH THE PROP GOING
FORWARD BECAUSE THIS HERE IS
GOING TO BE YOUR CULTIVATOR.
NOW IF YOU GOT THE LOOM
YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO GET BY
WITH SAY A 9.5 EVINRUDE SET
FOR TROLLING, BUT IF YOUR YARD
IS FULL OF CLAY AND STONES
AND MAYBE A COUPLE OF BURIED
WOODSTOVES, YOU MIGHT HAVE
TO MOVE UP TO A 300 HORSE
MERCRUISER OR A V6 WITH TRIM
TABS AND POWER TILT,
MAYBE GET THE PROP OFF
A CESSNA 150, BUT EITHER
WAY WHATEVER ENGINE YOU USE
YOU'RE GOING TO MOUNT IT UNTO
THE BED USING EXACTLY
THE SAME TECHNOLOGY,
THE HANDYMAN SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
NOW IF YOU GO WITH THE BIG MOTOR
ON THIS YOU MIGHT WANT TO USE
SAY 2 OR 3 ROLLS OF DUCT TAPE
AND THEN REALLY SECURE DOWN
MAYBE A 100 POUND TEST LINE
OR EVEN A COUPLE OF
COAT HANGERS.
NOW I'VE USED THE SAME TECHNIQUE
TO ATTACH THESE COAT RACKS TO
THE SIDES OF THE FOOTBOARD
AND WE GOT A COUPLE OF
HOT WATER BOTTLES HUNG HERE.
WE REALLY STRIPPED DOWN OLD
MAN SEDGEWICK'S ROOM FOR THIS
PROJECT AND WE GOT PLANT FOOD
IN THIS ONE AND WE GOT WEED
KILLER IN THIS ONE AND THEN
THEY COME DOWN THROUGH
THESE HOSES, IT'S A GRAVITY FEED
KIND OF LIKE MOOSE THOMPSON
ON SPAGHETTI NIGHT.
AND THE 2 CHEMICALS,
THEY'RE JOINED TOGETHER INTO
THIS BEDPAN WHERE THEY'RE
TURNED INTO FERTILIZER,
KIND OF APRES POE ISN'T IT?
NOW I HAVE ADDED A READING
LIGHT TO THE COAT RACK THERE,
I MEAN WHAT WE'D EVER NEED
A READING LIGHT AT THE
LODGE FOR IS BEYOND ME.
THIS ALLOWS US TO DO OUR
PLANTING AT NIGHT AND THE HOT
WATER BOTTLES ARE ALL SET TO
GO HERE AND I'VE ADDED AN
UMBRELLA FOR A LITTLE EXTRA
PROTECTION WHICH IS SOMETHING
YOU WANT TO THINK ABOUT
WHEN YOU'RE NEAR A BED.
AND NOW THESE PILLOWCASES
I'VE MOUNTED ON THE BACK HERE.
WHAT I'M GOING TO DO IS,
I FILLED THE ONE,
I'LL JUST TOP THIS BABY UP
WITH SOME FLOWER SEEDS AND
THEN THE SEEDS COME OUT THE
HOLE IN THE BOTTOM PLANTING
FLOWERS AS WE GO.
I GOT SOME BULBS HERE AND
I'LL JUST FILL UP MY POCKETS
WITH THE BULBS AND WHAT I CAN
DO WITH THEM SEE IS JUST BOUNCE
THEM OFF THE BED AS WE'RE GOING
ALONG, JUST LIKE THAT YOU KNOW.
OH I MISSED THE BED!
WE USE TO DO THAT AS KIDS
BUT OF COURSE WE USED HAMSTERS.
WE'RE ABOUT RIGHT,
DO YOU KNOW WHAT?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK
WOULD BE A REAL TREAT HERE,
WHY DON'T I GO AND PUT
MY PAJAMAS ON JUST TO KIND
OF GET INTO THE SPIRIT OF
THE WHOLE RIG HERE
HANG ON A SECOND,
I FORGOT,
THESE ARE MY PAJAMAS...
WELL I THINK WE'RE ALL SET
AND JUST BEFORE WE TURN
A REAL UGLY LOOKING PIECE
OF CRAP INTO A REAL NICE GARDEN,
I JUST REMIND YOU THAT IF THE
WOMEN DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
NOW I'LL JUST START THIS UP,
OKAY, PUT THE UMBRELLA UP THERE
AND JUST ONE MORE THING,
WE'RE GOING GARDENING.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S THAT
PART OF THE SHOW WHERE WE
EXPOSE THE 3 LITTLE WORDS MEN
FIND SO DIFFICULT TO SAY,
'I DON'T KNOW.'
AND HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT
ON THE EXPERT PORTION OF
THE SHOW OF COURSE IS MY
UNCLE RED AND HIS GOOD FRIEND,
MR. HAP SHAUGHNESSY.
'DEAR EXPERTS, I WANT TO
LIVE A LIFE FILLED WITH
EXCITEMENT AND ADVENTURE,
I WANT TO LIVE ON THE EDGE
TO GOBBLE UP THE WORLD
AND SPIT IT OUT,
I WANT TO PLUNGE HEADFIRST
INTO DANGER AND SHOUT AT
THE DEVIL, BUT I DON'T HAVE
THE NERVE OR EVEN ANYTHING
REMOTELY DANGEROUS OR DIFFERENT
IN MY LIFE TO EVEN THINK
ABOUT TRYING THAT.
IS THERE A SECRET THAT
GIVES THE COURAGEOUS PEOPLE
THE COURAGE TO DO
ADVENTUROUS ADVENTURES?'
>>RED: WELL THE ANSWER
IS HAROLD, IT'S CALLED
A TOTAL LACK OF FORESIGHT.
I MEAN IF THESE IDIOTS CAN
SEE WHAT WAS COMING,
THEY WOULD NEVER BECOME
PARACHUTISTS OR RACECAR DRIVERS
OR PARENTS.
>>HAP: WELL I'M GOING TO HAVE
TO CONTRADICT YOU ON THAT RED,
I MEAN TAKING RISKS,
THAT'S A OBLIGATORY PART
OF THE HUMAN EXPERIENCE.
I MEAN WHERE WOULD WE BE
IF I HADN'T TAKEN RISKS?
THERE'D BE NO SUCH
THING AS INSULIN,
NO PASSENGER SIDE AIRBAG,
NO UNITED NATIONS.
>>RED: NO LIE DETECTOR TESTS.
>>HAROLD: EXCUSE ME,
I THINK WE'RE JUST GETTING
A LITTLE BIT OFF TOPIC HERE,
OUR VIEWER WANTS TO KNOW
IF THERE'S ANY HINTS THAT
YOU CAN GIVE HIM ABOUT
YOU KNOW DEVELOPING COURAGE.
>>HAP: WELL HERE'S A TRICK
THAT I USED JUST BEFORE I JUMPED
THE ENGLISH CHANNEL,
I STARED AT MYSELF FROM TOP
TO TOE IN THE MIRROR AND
I SAID ALL RIGHT, IF THIS
DOESN'T GO WELL THEN WHAT'S
THE WORST THAT CAN HAPPEN?
YOU GOT 2 SETS OF EVERYTHING,
EYES, EARS, ARMS, LEGS,
THAT MAKES ONE OF THEM A SPARE
YOU GOT A 50 PERCENT
MARGIN FOR ERROR,
HELL WITH FINGERS YOU CAN MAKE
9 MISTAKES AND STILL BE ABLE
TO DIAL 911.
(SANDER HUMMING)
>>RED: BUZZ CAN I TALK
TO YOU FOR A MINUTE, BUZZ?
(BUZZ HUMMING)
OH MAN, STUPID
PIECE OF CRAP, RED!
>>RED: HI BUZZ.
>>BUZZ: HOW'S IT GOING MAN?
>>RED: NOT BAD, NOT BAD.
>>BUZZ: WHOA!
>>RED: OW!
>>BUZZ: HEY HAROLD, COME HERE,
COME HERE, IT'LL BE FUNNY,
HOW COME, AH YOU WUSS,
SO DID YOU JUST SEE THAT DRILL
LIKE IT JUST CUT OUT
FOR NO REASON?
>>RED: OH YEAH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW BUZZ WE'RE STARTING
A VOLUNTEER FIRE BRIGADE
UP HERE AT THE LODGE.
>>BUZZ: I KNOW, THEY ASKED ME
TO BE THE GUY THAT SOUNDS
THE ALARM, GET A LOAD OF THIS,
I GOT SOME STUFF HERE.
>>RED: OH, OH NO, NO.
>>BUZZ: WATCH THIS, LOOK AT
THIS, WATCH THIS.
>>RED: OH NO, NO BUZZ, NO, NO,
NO, BUZZ! BUZZ! BUZZ!
(BELL RINGING)
>>BUZZ: (SHOUTING) FIRE, FIRE!
>>RED: NO, NO BUZZ, BUZZ,
ALL THEY NEED IS FOR
YOU TO WIND UP THE HOSES.
>>BUZZ: WIND UP THE HOSES?
>>RED: YEAH THAT'S IT.
>>BUZZ: AH MAN!
WINDING HOSES, THAT JOB'S
A TOTAL YAWN, THAT'S WEENIE WORK
WHY DON'T YOU GET HAROLD
TO DO IT MAN?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I'M DOING,
I'M CONVERTING MY PLANE
INTO A WATER BOMBER YEAH,
I'M GOING TO FLY OVER THE FIRE
THEN I'M GOING TO DIVE BOMB
AND DOUSE IT WITH WATER.
YOU STAY HERE AND I'LL DIVE
BOMB YOU WITH SOME WATER.
>>RED: WELL YOU KNOW I THINK
BUZZ MEANS WELL BUT THE PROBLEM
IS HE ALWAYS GETS CARRIED AWAY
WITH EVERYTHING HE TRIES TO DO.
>>BUZZ: AND FOR THE SMALL FIRES
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I GOT?
I GOT THIS FOR THE SMALL FIRES.
>>RED: OH NO, NO, NO, NO, NO,
NO BUZZ NO.
>>BUZZ: AND IF YOU
WERE A SMALL FIRE.
>>RED: OH! OH! OH!
>>BUZZ: YOU'D BE OUT BY NOW,
YOU'D BE PUT OUT.
>>RED: I AM PUT OUT.
>>BUZZ: DON'T JUST SWEAT IT RED,
WITH ME AROUND IF THERE'S
A FIRE YOU KNOW I'LL BE THERE.
>>RED: YEAH I'M SURE OF IT,
I'M SURE OF IT.
>>BUZZ: (SHOUTING) FIRE!
FIRE! FIRE!
>>HAROLD: OH UNCLE RED,
HAD A LITTLE PROBLEM WITH
THE VOLUNTEER FIRE DEPARTMENT?
>>RED: WELL WE GOT REAL LUCKY
OUT THERE, I JUST FINISHED
FORMING THE WHOLE VOLUNTEER
FIRE DEPARTMENT AND SUDDENLY
ONE OF THE VEHICLES CAUGHT FIRE,
SO TALK ABOUT GOOD TIMING.
>>HAROLD: IT WASN'T
THE POSSUM VAN WAS IT?
>>RED: NO, NO HAROLD,
THE POSSUM VAN WON'T BURN,
BELIEVE ME I'VE TRIED
THAT A 1,000 TIMES.
NOW UNFORTUNATELY WE COULDN'T
SAVE THE VEHICLE BUT WE DID
PREVENT THE FIRE FROM
SPREADING TO ANYTHING ELSE.
>>HAROLD: IT WAS THE
FIRE TRUCK WASN'T IT?
THAT'S A YES.
>>RED: WELL THE TROUBLE
STARTED WHEN BUSTER AND STINKY,
THEY BOUGHT ONE OF THOSE OLD
STREET CLEANERS TO USE AS
A FIRE TRUCK BECAUSE IT CARRIES
WATER AND WE FIGURED WITH THAT
SWEEPER IN THE FRONT IT OUGHT
TO BE GOOD FOR BUSH FIRES.
OF COURSE THEY BROUGHT HER
UP TO THE LODGE, SHE WAS
BRIGHT YELLOW AND SO THEY
PAINTED HER ALL RED AND THEN
THEY FOUND OUT THAT THE FIRE
DEPARTMENTS NOW ARE PAINTING
THEIRS BRIGHT YELLOW SO THEY
PAINTED HER BRIGHT YELLOW
AND THEN THEY FOUND OUT THAT
THAT'S ONLY THE FIRE DEPARTMENTS
IN THE CITY AND THAT THE ONES
OUT IN THE COUNTRY ARE PAINTING
THEM RED, IT SHOWS UP BETTER
OR SOMETHING...
BUT THE YELLOW PAINT HADN'T
DRIED YET AND SO THAT WAS
THE YELLOW ON THE RED ON
THE YELLOW AND SO WHAT THEY
DID WAS THEY PAINTED HER AGAIN
BUT THIS TIME WITH A QUICK
DRYING RED LACQUER.
>>HAROLD: EXCUSE ME UNCLE RED,
I WOULD THINK THAT THAT WOULD
MAKE THE PAINT RUN LIKE
WATER WOULDN'T IT?
>>RED: WELL YEAH I WOULD THINK
SO TOO HAROLD BUT THEN OUR
BRAINS AREN'T CLOGGED WITH
PAINT FUMES ARE THEY?
SO NOW WHAT WE HAD WAS
3 PAINT JOBS SLIDING OFF
THE TRUCK AND HEADING
OUT TOWARDS THE LAKE,
AND I THINK THEY WOULD HAVE
MADE IT TOO BUT THEY CROSSED
PATHS WITH THE BARBEQUE.
>>HAROLD: OH THAT'S WHEN
THE FIRE STARTED RIGHT?
>>RED: RIGHT AROUND THAT TIME.
SO NOW THE TRUCK IS NOT REALLY
YELLOW ON RED OR RED ON YELLOW,
IT'S MORE OF A BASIC BLACK.
AND THE BIG QUESTION IS WHAT
DO YOU DO WITH A USELESS,
BURNT OUT WRECK?
>>HAROLD: WELL YOU COULD MAKE
HIM HOST OF HIS OWN SHOW.
♪ OH THE ELBOW IS THROBBING ♪
♪ FROM THE STRENGTH ♪
♪ OF THE FORCE ♪
♪ THE SHOULDER IS SEPARATED ♪
♪ AND THEY GET A DIVORCE ♪
♪ THE WRIST IS ALL NUMB ♪
♪ THE FINGERS ARE SWOLLEN ♪
♪ AND IF THIS OUTBOARD ♪
♪ DOESN'T START ON ♪
♪ THE NEXT PULL ♪
♪ SHE'S GOING INTO THE LAKE ♪
>>RED: WELL LOOK HERE,
BILL'S COOKING LUNCH TO GO,
NO BILL THE BARBEQUE'S GONE
THERE I FELT BAD ABOUT THAT,
I'M SORRY BILL.
BUT IT'S TIME FOR ANOTHER
ADVENTURE ANYHOW.
I HOPE I DIDN'T RUIN THINGS
TOO BAD BY KIND OF TOTALLING
THE BARBEQUE.
OH NO, LOOK, OH NO,
NOW THESE ARE KIND OF A
SIMPLE UNIT THESE BARBEQUES
AND I DON'T THINK YOU CAN REALLY
HURT THEM TOO BAD THOUGH,
WE CAN PUT HER BACK TOGETHER
AND I'D FEEL BETTER ABOUT THAT,
AND HERE YOU GO BILL
EVERYTHING'S FINE,
PUT THAT IN THERE AND I WONDER
WHAT HE'S PLANNING TO COOK TODAY
BECAUSE I WAS FEELING A LITTLE
HUNGRY ABOUT NOW AND THERE
WE GO, OH, OH, OH, OH BOY.
>>BILL: OW!
>>RED: YEAH MATCHES WILL
DO THAT BILL.
WELL NOW HE SAYS TO ME,
LOOK, OKAY FORGET THE BARBEQUE
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO MAKE
A CAMPFIRE AND THE FIRST THING
WE GOT TO DO IS CLEAR ALL
THE LEAVES.
WHEN I THINK OF THE NUMBER
OF THINGS THAT BILL HAS PULLED
OUT OF HIS PANTS OVER THE YEARS.
ANYWAY I STARTED WITH THE
RAKE AND I'M GOING TO,
BUT I GUESS THIS WASN'T
FAST ENOUGH FOR BILL,
OH BOY, BOY THAT JUST GOES
RIGHT UP YOUR NOSE AND INTO
YOUR EARS AND MAN HE'S GOING TO,
YEAH BILL THIS IS GREAT,
WHAT A GREAT IDEA,
A REGULAR SUPER GUY.
YEAH IT'S ALL DONE ANY WAY
AND WE'RE ALL SET NOW,
WE CAN START TO BUILD OUR CAMP,
WHAT DO YOU GOT NOW BILL?
OH FOR GOSH SAKES, WOW!
I'D HATE TO DO HIS LAUNDRY.
WELL I'M GOING TO GO OUT
AND SPLIT SOME WOOD,
I GUESS THE IDEA HERE,
AND THERE'S AN OLD STUMP
(BILL GRUNTING)
>>RED: BOY THAT STUMP IS,
THAT'S PRETTY MUSHY STUFF
THERE BILL, BUT LUCKILY
THERE IS JUST LUMBER LYING
ALL AROUND THE LODGE,
SO GRAB A BIT OF THAT AND
A BIT OF THIS AND AWAY WE GO.
YEAH, YEAH, LOOKING GOOD,
I PUT MY LOAD DOWN,
I GUESS I SHOULD OF SAID,
I SUPPOSE I SHOULD OF MENTIONED
I SHOULD OF PROBABLY GOT,
OH SORRY BILL, OH, OH, OH.
>>BILL: OH.
>>RED: WELL ANYWAY THAT'S
ALL RIGHT, HE'S ALL RIGHT,
WE GOT ALL THE STUFF TOGETHER
AND WE, YOU KNOW THE INDIAN
STYLE OF BUILDING LIKE A
LITTLE TEEPEE TYPE OF A FIRE,
HE'S JUST GOING TO USE THE
SAME TYPE OF TECHNIQUE
ONLY A LOT BIGGER.
YUP THE BIGGER BUT THE SAME,
ABSOLUTELY THE SAME,
I THINK THIS IS QUITE
THE CLEVER STUFF BUT IF
THE DESIGN WORKS MINIATURE
IT SHOULD WORK BIGGER
THAN YOU KNOW LIKE AND
THEN OF COURSE PUT THE JUICE
TO HER THERE, THAT'S THE OLD
BARBEQUE STARTER AND WELL
HE'S ADDING, I'VE NEVER SEEN
THAT BEFORE, LOOK OUT BILL!
>>BILL: OH!
>>RED: BOY THAT'S JUST
THE SAME DESIGN AS THAT BARBEQUE
WAS WASN'T IT?
THAT'S KIND OF A NICE LOOK
FOR YOU BILL BUT,
THERE WE GO, NOW HE'S ALL RIGHT,
NOW BILL HAS JUST,
WHENEVER HE HAS A SETBACK
HE JUST COMPLETELY IGNORES IT
AND HE JUST STARTS GOING
RIGHT AT HER AGAIN.
SO I THOUGHT I JUST WOULD STAND
BACK AND LET THE INVENTOR KIND
OF TAKE CARE OF THE WHOLE THING,
AND HE BUILT A CAMPFIRE THERE
THAT WAS UP I'D SAY 12, 13,
15, 6, ABOUT 8, 12,
IT WAS A TALL ONE...
AND THEN HE PUT ON THE BARBEQUE
AND HE HAD REALLY SOAKED THAT
IN THERE AND I THOUGHT YOU
KNOW BILL YOU MIGHT OF PUT
A LITTLE TOO MUCH, BUT ANYWAY
HE'S GOING IN THERE AND WE'RE
GOING TO HAVE A FIRE HERE
AND I HOPE WE'RE GOING TO GET
LUNCH OR SOMETHING.
BILL THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS
IF THIS YOU KNOW REALLY THIS
FIRE REALLY TAKES OFF,
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
THAT BILL BECAUSE IT MIGHT.
>>BILL: WHOA!
>>RED: AND NOW HERE'S THAT
SPECIAL MOMENT OF THE SHOW
WHERE YOUNGER VIEWERS GET
TO SAY, YOU KNOW WE HAVE
A GUY LIKE THAT IN OUR SCHOOL.
>>HAROLD: WELL IT'S
A WHOLE NEW WEEK,
IT'S A WHOLE NEW ME
AND IT'S A WHOLE NEW SHOW
AND IT'S FOR TEENAGERS
AND IT'S CALLED
AND NO IT'S NOT FOR PEOPLE
WHO LIVE ABOVE A SUBWAY OKAY,
IT'S FOR TEENAGERS,
SAY GUYS WHO WANT TO DATE GIRLS
WHO ARE YOU KNOW REALLY, REALLY
ATTRACTIVE OR MAYBE THEY'RE
OLDER THAN HIM OR THEY GET YOU
KNOW JUST WAY BETTER MARKS
IN SCHOOL THAN HIM,
BUT THAT'S ONLY BECAUSE
HE DOESN'T WANT TO DATE
GIRLS HIS OWN LEVEL
BECAUSE THEY'RE IMMATURE
AND THEY'RE SHY AND THEY
ALL CLAIM TO BE WASHING THEIR
HAIR FOR THE NEXT 9 YEARS.
SO ANYWAY, OKAY YOU GOT THAT
PARTICULAR GIRL ALL PICKED
OUT RIGHT, SO YOU LOOK UP HER
PHONE NUMBER AND THEN YOU JUST
GIVE HER A PHONE CALL AND JUST
YOU KNOW, BUT YOU GOT TO DO IT
IN A DIFFERENT WAY, 5-1-5-
YOU GOT TO DO IT IN A WAY THAT
SHE'LL THINK IT'S SOMEBODY ELSE
BASICALLY, 7- AND THEN THAT WAY
SHE WON'T HANG UP ON YOU
RIGHT AWAY.
SO WHAT YOU DO IS YOU ACT COOL
AND CALM AND COLLECTED YOU
KNOW AND JUST PRETEND YOU'RE
REALLY GOOD LOOKING,
LIKE MAYBE A MOVIE STAR,
OR SOMETHING TO DO WITH
LIKE PETER HINWOOD,
LIKE KEVIN COSTNER, ERNEST.
(SOPHISTICATED MATURE VOICE)
HELLO, YES HELLO ANDREA?
YES, YES, YES, YES, YES
IT'S HAROLD GREEN HERE,
YES VERY GOOD THANK YOU AND YOU,
VERY GOOD, WELL I HAVE SOME
PRIMO TICKETS FOR THE NIRVANA
CONCERT THIS WEEKEND AND I HAD
MY CAR COMPLETELY RE-SERVICED,
SO I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE FUN
IF WE GOT TOGETHER YOU KNOW,
GOT BETTER ACQUAINTED,
THAT SORT OF THING HUH?
WHAT, OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO,
I'LL PICK YOU UP AROUND
8 O'CLOCK HOW'S THAT SOUND?
OH VERY, VERY GOOD, YES.
>>RED: HAROLD
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THAT PHONE WON'T BE IN
ORDER FOR ANOTHER 2 WEEKS.
>>HAROLD: WELL I WAS JUST
PRACTICING YOU KNOW,
NO PROBLEM THEN,
I'LL CALL YOU BACK WHEN
THE PHONE'S ACTUALLY HOOKED UP,
THAT WAY YOU COULD RESPOND.
>>RED: IT IS WINTER,
HE STANDS BY THE CHIMNEY,
HIS CHEEKS AND NOSE ARE ROSY RED
HIS WHISKERS ARE EDGED IN WHITE
SMOKE CURLS FROM HIS MOUTH,
HIS SUIT IS TINGED
WITH BLACK SOOT,
I WARNED HIM TO CONNECT
THE GROUND WIRE BEFORE HE
PLUGGED IN THE CHRISTMAS LIGHTS.
>>RED: WELL WITH US STARTING
OUR OWN FIRE DEPARTMENT WE'RE
CONCERNED ABOUT FOREST FIRES,
SO I WENT AND ASKED RANGER GORD
IF HE COULD DESCRIBE THE
CONDITION THE WOODS ARE IN.
>>GORD: GREEN, GREEN,
GREEN AND LEAFY.
>>RED: AH NO, NO, I MEANT
ABOUT THE FIRE DANGER LEVEL.
>>GORD: OH, OH, OH, OH,
IT'S LOW.
>>RED: LOW?
>>GORD: YEAH I KEEP TRACK OF
IT ON MY GRAPH PAPER HERE,
SOME DAYS IT'S HIGH,
SOME DAYS IT'S MEDIUM/HIGH.
>>RED: YEAH ALL RIGHT.
>>GORD: SOME DAYS IT'S MEDIUM,
SOME DAYS IT'S MEDIUM/LOW
AND SOME DAYS IT'S LOW.
>>RED: YEAH, RIGHT, RIGHT.
>>GORD: IN FACT IT'S ALMOST
TIME TO TAKE A READING IF
YOU'D LIKE TO WATCH ME,
WHAT TIME IS IT?
IT'S ALMOST EXACTLY.
>>RED: 12:30 I HAVE.
>>GORD: 4 O'CLOCK,
NO, NOT TIME YET.
>>RED: WELL ALL RIGHT,
YOU KNOW GORD WE'VE BEEN
HAVING A COUPLE OF FIRES UP
AT THE LODGE LATELY
AND WE KNOW HOW DANGEROUS
FIRE CAN BE.
>>GORD: OH YEAH, YEAH.
AND YOUR WORST HAZARD
IS LIGHTNING.
>>RED: LIGHTNING?
>>GORD: LUCKILY THOUGH
MY ROOF IS MADE OF METAL SO
THE LIGHTNING WILL STRIKE
MY TOWER BEFORE IT
STRIKES THE TREES.
>>RED: OH.
>>GORD: THAT USE TO REALLY,
REALLY BOTHER ME.
BUT NOW YOU KNOW I FIGURE
FIRE PREVENTION IS MY JOB.
>>RED: YEAH, SO YOU'VE BEEN
NAILED A FEW TIMES HAVE YOU?
>>GORD: 17.
AND THE LIGHTNING STAYS IN
YOUR BODY BUT THAT'S OKAY
YOU KNOW BECAUSE AT NIGHT
IF YOU DON'T WEAR PAJAMAS
YOU'VE GOT A NIGHTLIGHT.
>>RED: WELL I GUESS WE'LL
BE GOING BEFORE IT GETS
DARK THEN GORD.
>>GORD: YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
>>RED: WELL YOU KNOW IT'S
NOT TOO OFTEN WE HAVE A HAPPY
ENDING TO OUR STORIES UP
HERE AT THE LODGE.
USUALLY THE BEST WE CAN HOPE
FOR IS THAT THE DISASTERS
KIND OF CANCEL EACH OTHER OUT.
OR IF THERE IS ANY KIND
OF PERSONAL INJURY
NOBODY GETS BLAMED.
>>HAROLD: YEAH RIGHT
BECAUSE USUALLY I GET BLAMED.
>>RED: OH NOW HAROLD,
DO I DETECT A TWINGE
OF BITTERNESS THERE?
>>HAROLD: YES.
HOW CAN YOU CALL THIS
A HAPPY ENDING?
THE GUYS ALMOST
KILLED THEMSELVES,
SPENT A LOT OF MONEY ON
A FIRE TRUCK BECAUSE
IT CAUGHT ON FIRE,
ALL THE HEAT MADE THE
GARAGE ROOF ALL BUCKLE.
>>RED: WELL HAROLD I THINK
IT'S JUST THE AGE OLD OPTIMIST
VERSUS THE PESSIMIST THING
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU TAKE HALF
A GLASS OF WHISKEY AND
THE ONE GUY LOOKS AT IT.
SAYS IT'S HALF FULL,
THAT'S THE OPTIMIST
THE OTHER GUY LOOKS AT
IT SAYS IT'S HALF EMPTY,
THAT'S THE PESSIMIST.
>>HAROLD: AND IF IT'S MILK?
>>RED: THAT'S A BAPTIST.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: WELL THAT'S
MEETING TIME UNCLE RED,
WE GOT TO GO TO THE MEETING.
>>RED: YEAH YOU GO AHEAD HAROLD
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN THERE.
BOY THE KIDS TODAY
HAVE SUCH PIE IN THE SKY
EXPECTATIONS DON'T THEY?
ANYWAY THIS IS THE REAL HAPPY
ENDING BECAUSE FIRST OF ALL
IT'S THE ENDING AND SECONDLY
I'M REAL HAPPY BECAUSE IT'S
GETTING TO THE END OF THE DAY
AND NOT MUCH MORE BAD
STUFF CAN HAPPEN.
ANYWAY IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING AND I'M GOING
TO BE BRINGING HOME ABOUT
50 OR 60 FIRE EXTINGUISHERS,
IT'S JUST A LITTLE EXTRA
SAFETY PRECAUTION,
IT'S NOT A REFLECTION
ON YOUR COOKING IN ANY WAY.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
THANKS FOR WATCHING AND
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>GROUP: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: ALL RIGHT A COUPLE
OF QUICK ANNOUNCEMENTS,
APPARENTLY IF ALL THE EQUIPMENT
IS RETURNED BY NOON TOMORROW,
THE LOCAL FIRE DEPARTMENT WILL
DROP ALL OF THE CHARGES
AGAINST US.
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca