ALL YOU FATHERS OUT
THERE KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
WHEN YOU TRY TO GET YOUR
TEENAGERS TO DO A BIT
OF YARD WORK.
THEY CAN'T TRIM THE HEDGES
FOR MORE THAN FIVE MINUTES
WITHOUT TAKIN' A BREAK.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT,
I'VE COME UP WITH A WAY TO
KEEP YOUR TEENAGERS IN GEAR
WITHOUT HAVIN' TO
KEEP AN EYE ON 'EM.
WE'VE ALL SEEN THESE
MOTION DETECTORS.
WELL, I'VE WIRED
THIS ONE UP BACKWARDS.
IT'S A LACK
OF MOTION DETECTOR.
SEE, AS LONG
AS THERE'S MOTION,
THE LIGHT GOES OFF.
AS SOON AS THERE'S
NO MOTION,
THE LIGHT COMES ON.
NOW, A LIGHT GOIN'
ON OR OFF
IS GONNA HAVE NO EFFECT
ON YOUR TEENAGER.
IF THEY DON'T RESPOND
TO A SUNRISE,
A 60-WATT BULB ISN'T
GONNA IMPRESS 'EM.
SO WHAT WE'RE
GONNA DO IS
WE'RE GONNA
UNPLUG THIS LAMP
AND PLUG IN A PRERECORDED
TAPE THAT PLAYS ON THIS
CASSETTE PLAYER.
THEN ALL YOU DO IS
AIM THE MOTION DETECTOR
AT YOUR TEENAGER,
AND AS LONG AS HE'S MOVIN',
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
BUT THE MINUTE HE
STOPS ...
Hey what are you
doin' sittin' around?
Get back to work.
You call that effort?
Get off your duff.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE IT.
BIT OF A SETBACK,
ACTUALLY, THIS WEEK.
THIS IS THE ANNUAL
POSSUM LAKE FISHING DERBY,
AND SO FAR, NOBODY'S
CAUGHT ANY FISH.
AND I'LL TELL YA,
IF THAT KEEPS UP, UH,
WE'RE NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO GIVE AWAY THE GREAT PRIZE.
SECOND PRIZE IS A BUS
TICKET TO PORT ASBESTOS.
AND IF YOU WIN
THE FIRST PRIZE,
THEY MAKE IT ROUND TRIP.
BUT, UH, SO FAR, LIKE I SAY,
THERE'S BEEN NO WINNERS.
SO I THINK THEY SHOULD
CHANGE THE RULES.
I THINK THEY SHOULD GIVE THE
PRIZE TO THE GUY WITH THE
BIGGEST LURE.
RED, RED.
LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
LOOK WHAT I CAUGHT.
WOW.
WOW, THAT'S
A BEAUTY.
IS THAT
A BLOWFISH?
17 POUNDS!
SEE, I THINK THE FISHIN' DERBY
SHOULD BE FOR THE HEAVIEST
THING YOU CAN CATCH.
DOESN'T HAVE
TO BE FISH.
NO.
COULD BE A SNOWMOBILE
OR A STOVE.
I GOT A BETTER IDEA,
Mr. GREEN.
IT SHOULD BE A
LIVING THING TO WIN.
IF CAN'T BE A FISH,
IT SHOULD BE
SOMETHING ELSE ALIVE.
LIKE A SWIMMER?
NO, LIKE A PLANT
OR A TREE.
OH, MAN.
I SNAGGED
THIS BEAUTY
IN MERCURY CREEK,
DOWN BY THE BRIDGE.
YEAH, THAT'S WHEN HALF
THE SANTA CLAUS PARADE
WENT OFF THE BRIDGE
AND FELL INTO THE LAKE.
THEY CALL THOSE
THINGS FLOATS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
OH, WAIT A SECOND.
THAT'S NOT LIVING,
THAT'S ARTIFICIAL, MIKE.
THAT WON'T WORK.
WELL, WE GOTTA COME UP
WITH A BETTER WAY
TO CATCH FISH.
WE COULD DRAG A BIG NET
FROM ONE END OF THE LAKE
TO THE OTHER, RIGHT.
WHERE WE GONNA GET
A NET THAT SIZE?
THE TENNIS CLUB.
THEY DON'T LOCK
THAT GATE.
NO, LOOK, THE TROUBLE
IS THERE ISN'T ANY FISH.
I THINK MAYBE WE SHOULD
JUST TEST THE WATER
IN THE LAKE.
YOU KNOW WHAT
WE COULD DO, EH?
WE COULD DRAIN
THE WHOLE THING, HUH?
HOOK ALL OUR CARS
UP THERE,
DROP THE RAD HOSES
IN BY THE BOAT RAMP,
START UP THE ENGINES,
MAKE THAT PUPPY
AS DRY AS A MARTINI
HUH?
SEE, I THINK WE SHOULD
TEST THE WATER IN THE LAKE.
YOU KNOW, I'VE HEARD THAT IF
YOU FIRE OFF A BIG CHARGE OF
DYNAMITE UNDER WATER,
YOU CAN FISH WITH
A PITCHFORK.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I'M GONNA GO TEST
THE WATER IN THE LAKE.
CLEANING OUT YOUR EAVESTROUGHS
IS SOMETHING YOU SHOULD DO
ON AN ANNUAL BASIS.
NO MATTER HOW MANY TREES
I BLOW UP, I STILL GET
LEAVES IN 'EM.
AND DIRT AND STICKS,
LITTLE CHUNKS
OF MY PROPANE TANK.
SO HERE'S AN EASY WAY
TO CLEAN EM' OUT.
YOU BORROW A HUNK OF HOSE
FROM A LOCAL BUILDING.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO HOSE
DOWN THE BUILDING
FOR SAFETY.
THEN YOU ATTACH
THE NOZZLE
TO THE BOTTOM PART OF THE
DOWNSPOUT ON YOUR EAVESTROUGH
WITH THE EXPLOSIVES
ENTHUSIAST'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
YOU KNOW, I THINK IT WAS
SIR ISAAC NEWTON JOHN WHO SAID,
WHATEVER GOES DOWN
MUST GO UP,
IF YOU GOT ENOUGH
WATER PRESSURE.
[ CRANKING SOUND ]
OH, YES, SIR.
YES, SIR.
I'LL HAVE THOSE P & L
STATEMENTS READY FOR THE
AUDIT, FOR YOU BY ABOUT,
OH, THREE O'CLOCK.
NOON?
NOON, YEAH,
OH, NOON'S EASY.
I CAN DO NOON, SURE.
YEAH.
GUM?
HM-MM, IT'S GRAPE.
IT'S LIKE BUBBALICIOUS,
BUT IT'S NOT.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
GONE.
YES, SIR.
IT'S GONE.
IT'S GONE, ALRIGHTY.
YEAH, I CAN DO
THAT FOR YOU.
NOON'S NOT A PROBLEM, SIR.
ALRIGHTY.
OKAY, YOU BET --
YOU HAVE A GOOD DAY TOO.
HAROLD.
OW!
PRESSURE GETTIN'
TO YA, HAROLD?
NO, NO.
AH, NO.
I LOVE THIS JOB.
IT'S JUST THE GREATEST.
LOOK AT THIS,
UNCLE RED.
I'M AN ASSISTANT
ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE.
OH, YEAH, I SEE THAT.
AN ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE, EH?
HOW MANY ACCOUNTS
DO YOU HAVE, HAROLD?
NONE.
SO YOU'RE A NO ACCOUNT
EXECUTIVE, HUH.
HA, HA, HA.
YEAH, WELL,
DON'T YOU WORRY,
I'M GETTIN' THERE.
EVERYBODY SAYS I HAVE WHAT IT
TAKES TO BE A FINANCIAL ADVISOR.
IS THAT A COMPLEMENT,
YOU THINK?
UNCLE RED,
I KNOW YOU MEAN WELL,
BUT I'M NOT COMING
BACK TO THE LODGE.
OH, I'M NOT COMING
I GOT THIS JOB,
I LIKE IT,
AND I'M GOOD AT IT.
YEAH, WELL, I JUST DON'T WANT
YOU TO GET HURT, THAT'S ALL.
YOU INSULT ME SO
I WON'T GET HURT?
HAROLD, THIS IS THE BIG CITY.
PEOPLE WILL TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF YOU,
HAROLD, ALL RIGHT?
I WANT YOU TO BE
TREATED FAIRLY.
UNCLE RED, I MAKE
$1200 A WEEK.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
WHEN YOU SAY A WEEK.
UM-M-M, A WEEK.
$1200 A WEEK.
AND THEY PAY ME
EVERY WEEK.
HAROLD -- HAROLD, UH, THIS IS
A BIG ADJUSTMENT FOR ME.
I THINK I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO GO HOME NOW, HAROLD.
OH, WELL, I UNDERSTAND.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR COMING
TO CHECK UP ON ME.
YOU DROP BY
ANY TIME YOU LIKE.
YEAH, OKAY, HAROLD.
THANKS.
OH, HAROLD I CAN'T
MOVE MY FOOT.
OH, NO,
IS IT A STROKE?
NO, LOOKS LIKE GUM.
PARKING LOTS CAN BE
FRUSTRATING, CAN'T THEY?
EITHER YOU CAN'T
FIND A SPOT AT ALL,
OR THEN YOU DO GET ONE, BY THE
TIME YOU GET BACK TO YOUR CAR,
SOMEBODY HAS BOXED YOU IN.
MAYBE THE GUY'S SPOT YOU TOOK.
OR MAYBE THE PARKING LOT OWNER
GETTIN' BACK AT YOU FOR NOT
PAYING THE LAST TIME.
WELL, TODAY, I'M GOING TO SHOW A
FAST, CHEAP, UNEMBARASSING WAY
TO GET INTO OR OUT OF
A TIGHT PARKING SPOT.
FIRST THING YOU NEED...
YOUR SPARE.
NOW, YOUR SPARE MIGHT BE FLAT.
DOESN'T MATTER,
IT'LL WORK JUST AS GOOD.
AND THEN YOU NEED A JACK,
BUT YOU DON'T WANT
THIS KIND OF JACK.
YOU WANT THE HYDRAULIC TYPE.
THEY HAVE A LITTLE
MORE LIFTING POWER.
'CAUSE WE'RE NOT JUST GONNA BE
LIFTING ONE END OF THE VEHICLE.
BUT, HEY, I'M GETTING
WAY AHEAD OF MYSELF.
ALL RIGHT, I'VE GOT
TWO JACKS,
THAT MEANS I CAN OPEN.
[ CHUCKLING ]
NEXT THING YOU WANNA DO
IS HORSE THE BACK SEAT
OUTTA THERE.
[ GRUNTING ]
ALL RIGHT.
HIT IT.
NOW, YOU MAY NOTICE WITH
THAT PARTICULAR METHOD OF
REMOVING THE SEAT,
THERE IS A CERTAIN AMOUNT OF
DAMAGE TO THE FLOOR AREA,
BUT THAT GAPING HOLE IN
THERE IS GONNA COME IN
REAL HANDY LATER.
BUT I'M GETTIN' WAY
AHEAD OF MYSELF.
OKAY, FIRST THING
WE GOTTA DO NOW
IS MOUNT THE JACK TO
THE INSIDE OF THE ROOF.
AND FOR THAT I'M GONNA USE
THE HEAVY-DUTY SELF-TAPPING
MACHINE SCREWS
RATHER THAN DUCT TAPE;
ALTHOUGH, YOU COULD PUT DUCT
TAPE ON THE SCREWS LATER,
YOU KNOW, FOR APPEARANCES.
[ GRUNTING ]
ALL RIGHT, NOW I WANNA HANG THE
SPARE TIRE UNDER THE JACK,
BUT RIGHT AT
FLOOR LEVEL, THERE.
THE I'LL BE ABLE --
GUESS THOSE MACHINE SCREWS
ARE A LITTLE BIT LONG.
OKAY, I NEED SOMETHING
TO FILL THE GAP
BETWEEN THE JACK AND WHERE
THE SPARE TIRE'S GONNA BE.
I COULD USE, I GUESS,
A 4x4 ON THAT,
BUT I WANT SOMETHING A LOT
STRONGER THAT WON'T
TWIST AND WARP.
SO I'M GONNA USE THIS
OLD CAR DRIVE SHAFT HERE.
I'VE ALREADY MEASURED
THE LENGTH.
NOW I'LL JUST CUT
'ER TO SIZE.
[ HUFFING AND PUFFING ]
OKAY, I DECIDED TO GO WITH
THE 4x4, AFTER ALL, ON THAT.
BUT SHE'S ALL ASSEMBLED.
WE GOT THE JACK HANGIN'
FROM THE ROOF,
AND WE GOT THE SPARE HANGIN'
FROM THE JACK,
AND THE WHOLE UNIT IS POSITIONED
OVER OUR BIG HOLE IN THE FLOOR.
SO NOW WHENEVER WE WANT TO GET
INTO OR OUT OF A REAL TIGHT
PARKING SPOT,
ALL WE DO IS JACK
DOWN THE SPARE,
WHICH WILL JACK UP THE CAR.
THEN WE SPIN 'ER AROUND TILL
SHE'S FACIN' THE RIGHT WAY.
THEN WE JACK UP THE SPARE,
WHICH WILL JACK DOWN THE CAR,
AND WE'RE OUTTA THERE.
FUNNY HOW LIFE'S SOLUTIONS ARE
USUALLY SO SIMPLE, ISN'T IT?
BOY, MY WIFE'S GONNA GO NUTS
WHEN SHE SEES THIS.
BUT I'M GETTIN'
WAY AHEAD OF MYSELF.
SO REMEMBER,
IF THE WOMEN DON'T
FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
AND NOW, IF YOU'LL
EXCUSE ME,
I'M GONNA TAKE
THIS BABY FOR A SPIN.
[ CREAKING AND GRINDING SOUNDS ]
[ HYDRAULIC SOUNDS ]
I WANNA TALK TO YOU
MIDDLE-AGED GUYS OUT THERE.
HOW MANY TIMES OVER
THE LAST TEN YEARS
HAVE YOU REGRETTED
SAYING THE WORDS
"WATCH THIS"?
HOW MANY OF YOUR SCARS
OR YOUR MISSING FINGERS,
YOUR FADED MEMORY
ARE A DIRECT RESULT
OF SAYING THE WORDS,
"WATCH THIS"?
YOU KNOW, MAYBE IT'S TIME TO
REPLACE THE WORDS "WATCH THIS"
WITH PHRASES THAT ARE MORE
SUITED TO YOUR CURRENT
PHYSICAL CONDITION.
PHRASES LIKE,
"WHERE ARE MY GLASSES?"
OR, "WHERE ARE
MY OTHER GLASSES?"
OR THE EVER POPULAR,
"HONEY, I SWEAR IT
MUST'VE BEEN THE DOG."
YOU SEE, WOMEN AREN'T
THE ONLY ONES
WHOSE BIOLOGICAL
CLOCKS ARE TICKING.
IT'S JUST THAT OUR CLOCKS ARE
SAYIN' DIFFERENT THINGS.
YOU KNOW, WOMEN'S
CLOCKS ARE SAYING,
YOU'RE HAVING HOT FLASHES;
OR, YOU KNOW, I THINK SCREAMING
WILL MAKE EVERYTHING BETTER.
BUT OUR CLOCKS ARE SAYING,
GET OFF THE ROOF, YOU FOOL;
OR, PUT THOSE ROLLER
BLADES DOWN NOW.
THE IMPORTANT THING IS
NEVER SAY WATCH THIS.
JUST ACCEPT THE FACT THAT YOU'VE
REACHED THAT POINT IN YOUR LIFE
WHERE THERE IS NOTHING ABOUT
YOU THAT'S WORTH WATCHIN'.
EXCEPT, OF COURSE, YOUR MANNERS
AND YOUR CHOLESTEROL LEVEL.
AND REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU;
WE'RE ALL IN
THIS TOGETHER.
WELL, DALTON TOOK A SAMPLE
OF POSSUM LAKE WATER IN
TO BE TESTED,
BUT I JUST DON'T
THINK THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
SO I'M GONNA PUT
A LITTLE ON THE PLANTS,
MAYBE LET THE DOGS DRINK IT.
AND THAT'LL PROVE THERE'S
NOTHIN' WRONG WITH IT.
OKAY, RED, I GOT THE
REPORT ON POSSUM LAKE.
DOES NOT LOOK GOOD.
OH, DID THE GOVERNMENT SISSY
BOYS FIND SOMETHING WRONG
WITH OUR WATER?
ACCORDING TO THIS POSSUM LAKE
IS NO LONGER CLASSIFIED AS
A BODY OF WATER.
NO, IT SAYS SUSPENSION OF
MANGANESE AND SULPHATE
PARTICULATE
IN A 40 PERCENT SOLUTION
OF METHYL ALCOHOL.
ARE YOU SAYIN'
POSSUM LAKE IS
A SINGAPORE SLING?
NO.
METHYL ALCOHOL IS --
WELL, IT'S
LIKE GASOLINE.
IT'S NO WONDER THERE'S
NOT FISH IN THE LAKE.
YEAH, WE'VE GOT A HIGHLY TOXIC
AND CORROSIVE MIXTURE THERE.
OH, WELL,
THAT'S CRAZY.
HERE, HOLD
THIS PLANT.
I'M GONNA SHOW
YOU SOMETHING.
WATCH THIS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
HOLY MACKEREL!
THE WATER TOOK THE
BOTTOM RIGHT OUT
OF THIS PAIL.
IT'LL DO THE
SAME THING TO YOU.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELL, WHAT ARE
WE GONNA DO?
WELL, THE REPORT
SAYS WE SHOULD INSTALL
A WATER PURIFICATION SYSTEM
TO CLEAN THE LAKE.
YEAH, WHAT'S THAT
GONNA COST?
SEVEN MILLION DOLLARS.
THAT SOUNDS
HIGH TO ME.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WATER FILTRATION, THAT'S JUST
FILTERS AND CHEMICALS.
WE'LL JUST THROW SOME WEED
KILLER INTO THE LAKE,
AND THEN JUST FILTER THE
WHOLE DEAL THROUGH SOME
OLD MATTRESSES.
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST
CRAZY ENOUGH THAT
IT MIGHT WORK.
HA HA.
YEAH, RIGHT.
Red:
REAL SPECIAL ADVENTURE
THIS TIME ROUND.
WE'RE GONNA MAKE KIND
OF A CENOTAPH UNIT
OUT THERE BEHIND THE LODGE.
WE HAD ONE OF THOSE --
THE POWER AUGUR
AND A COUPLE OF BUSHES.
AND, UH, WE'D HAD
A FLAG SENT TO US BY
SOME FRIENDS IN MOOSE JAW.
WINSTON'S GETTING THE
FLAG POLE OUTTA THE VAN.
HARD TO GET A POLE THAT BIG
INTO ONE OF THE SMALLER VANS.
BUT WE HAD -- WATCH OUT.
CAREFUL NOW.
OH, OH.
BY GOLLY.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY, WELL,
WE GOT EVERYTHING,
THAT'S THE MAIN THING.
SO NOW I'M TELLIN' THE BOYS
WE GOTTA DIG SOME HOLES.
WE GOTTA -- FIRST OF ALL,
WE GOTTA A DIG A HOLE
FOR THE FLAG POLE.
WHEN YOU GOT A
20-, 30-FOOT POLE,
IT'S GOTTA GO DOWN AT
LEAST FOUR INCHES, I BELIEVE.
SO, UH, GET THE POWER AUGUR -
PICK THAT UP, BOYS.
PICK 'ER UP.
PUSH 'ER UP THERE.
C'MON, PUSH 'ER UP.
PICK 'ER UP.
GET 'ER GOIN'.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, THE THING WITH THESE
POWER AUGURS, THEY'RE FINE
TILL THEY HIT A ROCK.
THEN, UH, YOU KNOW --
SO THEN I FIGURED, NO, OKAY,
THAT'S FOUR HORSEPOWER,
YOU KNOW.
SO THEN WE WENT BACK
TO THE MANUAL STYLE,
AND WE HAD A WINDSHIELD SCRAPE
AND A TIRE IRON
'CAUSE WE ACTUALLY NEEDED
A HOLE FOR THE FLAG POLE
AND ONE FOR EACH
OF THE BUSHES.
BUT, UH --
WE CAN KINDA SEE THE CENOTAPH
STARTIN' TO TAKE PLACE NOW.
WE'RE GONNA --
FIRST THING WE DO,
WE'RE GONNA PUT THE BUSHES IN
BRING 'EM OVER, BOYS.
BRING 'EM OVER.
HAUL 'EM OVER.
GET 'EM OVER.
NOW, WE GOTTA PUT THE FLAG POL
UP IN THE MIDDLE THING THERE -
KINDA LOOKS LIKE
IWO JIMA, DOESN'T IT?
THERE GOES MIKEY.
THERE WE GO.
GOT HER IN.
BEAUTIFUL, WE'R ALL SET.
GOT THE POLE UP THERE
GREAT AND EVERYTHING.
AND NOW IS A VERY,
VERY IMPORTANT MOMENT
IN OUR LIVES...
GETTIN' OUT THIS SPECIAL
FLAG SENT TO US BY OUR
FRIENDS IN MOOSE JAW.
LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S THE POSSUM CRE --
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
TAKE THINGS PRETTY SERIOUSLY
UP HERE AT THE LODGE.
ALL I HAD TO DO, JUST RUN 'ER
UP THE FLAG POLE, AS THEY SAY
IN THE BOARD ROOMS.
AND WE'RE ABOUT AS BORED AS
YOU COULD GET AT THIS POINT.
WE GOT 'ER UP THERE,
AND WOULDN'T YOU KNOW IT,
I HUNG THE DARNED
THING UPSIDE DOWN.
'COURSE, I GET A LOT OF
COOPERATION OUT OF MY
FRIENDS HERE.
OH, MAN, NOW LOOK
WHAT THEY DO.
AH, COME ON, GUYS.
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
SO I'M TRYIN' TO GET 'ER DOWN
AND SHE'S JAMMED UP THERE.
NOW I GOTTA TAKE
THE WHOLE POLE DOWN.
MAYBE WE CAN JUST SHAKE IT,
AND MAYBE SHE'LL COME DOWN.
THANKS FOR ALL THE HELP.
FINALLY GOT THE POLE DOWN.
PUT 'ER UP STRAIGHT
AND EVERYTHING.
I THOUGHT WE WERE
IN REAL GOOD SHAPE.
I THINK WE MAY HAVE WEAKENED
THE HOLE A LITTLE BIT
BY SHAKIN' IT
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW --
BUT YOU KNOW WHEN LIFE,
SOMETIMES THINGS DON'T
GO YOUR WAY?
YOU GOTTA ADAPT.
HUH?
STILL NOT RIGHT.
THERE WE GO.
[ CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ]
OH, RED!
RED GREEN.
WHAT A GREAT
SURPRISE.
WELL, IT SHOULDN'T REALLY
BE A SURPRISE, GORD.
I TOLD YOU
I WAS COMIN'.
YEAH, I KNOW,
BUT I FORCED
MYSELF TO FORGET.
OH.
YOU EVER DONE THAT?
I'LL TRY IT RIGHT
AFTER I LEAVE.
[ CHUCKLING ]
WHAT'S THIS,
GORD?
OH, YEAH, THAT'S MY NEW
WATCHTOWER GUEST BOOK.
FROM NOW ON, EVERYBODY
THAT VISITS THE TOWER
WILL SIGN THE GUEST BOOK.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I GAVE YOU THIS
BOOK FOUR YEARS AGO.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
I WAS THE THE FIRST
ONE TO SIGN IT.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
I'M THE ONLY ONE
THAT SIGNED IT, GORD.
YEAH, I KNOW.
HEY, YOU COULD
SIGN IT AGAIN.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, SURE,
I'LL SIGN IT AGAIN.
HERE YOU GO.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
OH,
EXCEPT THIS TIME,
COULD YOU SIGN IT FROM
SHIRLEY OR ANGELA?
AND WRITE SOMETHING
MUSHY, LIKE A POEM.
NO, GORD, I'M NOT
REALLY COMFORTABLE
WRITING TO YOU
FROM A WOMAN.
YOU KNOW,
IT BOTHERS ME.
REALLY?
YEAH.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD SEE
SOMEBODY ABOUT THAT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
GORD DOESN'T IT
SEEM UNUSUAL
THAT YOU'VE BEEN HERE
FOR FOUR YEARS,
AND YOU HAVEN'T
HAD ANY VISITORS?
IS THAT WHAT YOU THINK?
I'VE HAD PLENTY OF
VISITORS UP HERE, RED.
HUNDREDS EVERY WEEK.
OH, OH.
YOU DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT
MOSQUITOES, DO YOU?
I'M THINKING REAL VISITORS,
HUMAN VISITORS, GORD.
WHO DO YOU THINK
SHIRLEY AND ANGELA ARE?
THEY'RE HUMAN!
OH, BOY,
ARE THEY HUMAN.
[ GROWLING ]
EXCEPT THEY ONLY
COME WHEN I'M ASLEEP.
BUT THEY COME OFTEN.
IF IT WASN'T FOR THEM,
I'D PROBABLY GO CRAZY.
ALL RIGHT.
TELL YOU WHAT.
I'LL SIGN ONE
TO YOU FROM ANGELA.
HOW'S THAT?
UH, BETTER MAKE IT SHIRLEY.
ANGELA'S LEFT-HANDED.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ TICKING ]
YOU KNOW,
THERE'S NOTHING
LIKE SPORTS
TO TEACH KIDS WHAT
LIFE'S ALL ABOUT.
AND WHAT BETTER PLACE TO LEARN
ABOUT WINNING AND LOSING
AND GOOD SPORTSMANSHIP
AND PATIENCE
THAN THE OLD
BALL PARK, HUH?
TODAY, I'M TEACHIN'
THE YOUNG ONE HERE
ABOUT PATIENCE.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT;
GOOD THINGS COME
TO THOSE WHO WAIT.
IT'S AN IMPORTANT LESSON.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
YOU DON'T WANT THAT.
THIS IS FULL OF NITRATES,
ANIMAL BY-PRODUCTS.
EW.
OH, SEE OVER THERE WHERE
THAT PITCHER'S MOUND IS?
THERE'S THE
BATTER'S BOX.
WHEN A MAJOR LEAGUE
PITCHER WINDS UP,
THAT BALL'S GOIN' 90 MILES
AN HOUR ACROSS THAT PLATE.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES
THIS GAME SO GREAT.
HE LOVES THIS.
THIS IS JUST
ABOUT PERFECT TOO.
GET A KID,
GRAB A HOT DOG,
COME TO THE BALL PARK,
SPEND SOME QUALITY
TIME TOGETHER.
IT'LL BE SOMETHING THAT'LL
REWARD THE BOTH OF YOU.
WHEN'S THE BALL GAME START?
THURSDAY.
[ RINGING ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELL, UH,
WE'RE GETTIN' THERE,
YOU KNOW.
THE LAKE STILL HAS BITS OF
STUFF FLOATIN' AROUND IN IT.
I THINK ALL THE
EXPLOSIVE TOXINS
HAVE BEEN REMOVED.
THANKS TO MIKE.
MIKE, IS THERE ANYTHING YOU
WANTED TO SAY TO THE KIDS
WATCHIN' OUT THERE?
UH, YES, Mr. GREEN.
UH, SMOKING CIGARETTES
IS HAZARDOUS TO YOUR HEALTH,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE STANDING
IN A LAKE OF GASOLINE.
IT'S ACTUALLY A GOOD THING
THAT WE DON'T HAVE ANY
FISH IN THERE.
POSSUM LAKE WOULD BE
CHOWDER AT THIS POINT.
BUT, YOU KNOW,
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
THERE WAS SOME
GOOD NEWS.
ACCORDING TO THE
REPORT, ANYWAY.
READ IT TO THEM,
DALTON.
OUCH!
WHAT?
UH, "ONCE THE METHYL ALCOHOL
CONTAMINANTS HAVE BEEN REMOVED,
"THE REMAINING IMPURITIES
ARE NON-TOXIC
"AND CAN BE REMOVED
BY FILTRATION."
SO ALL WE GOTTA DO NOW
IS FILTER THE WATER,
AND POSSUM LAKE'LL
BE HEALTHY AGAIN.
SO WHAT WE HAVE TO DO
IS COME UP WITH A
COST-EFFECTIVE, EFFICIENT
FILTRATION SYSTEM.
AND THIS IS WHERE THE
BRILLIANCE COMES IN.
WELL, I DON'T THINK
IT'S SO BRILLIANT.
NO, NO, BUT THEN,
YOU DIDN'T THINK
OF IT, DID YOU?
ALL YOU COULD
THINK OF WAS
I THINK I'LL LIGHT
UP A CIGARETTE,
AND NOW NONE OF
US HAVE EYEBROWS.
SO WHAT WE HAVE
IS THE BEST FILTER SYSTEM
ANYONE COULD EVER DEVISE.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M TALKIN' ABOUT?
THE HUMAN BODY.
JUST LET NATURE
TAKE ITS COURSE.
THE MIRACLE OF
THE HUMAN KIDNEY.
THAT'S THE THING
RIGHT THERE.
I FIGURED OUT THAT IF
EVERY POSSUM LODGE
MEMBER DRINKS --
45 GALLONS.
45 GALLONS OF
POSSUM LAKE WATER --
A WEEK.
45 GALLONS OF
POSSUM LAKE A WEEK --
FOR 27 WEEKS.
FOR 27 WEEKS,
AND WE'LL HAVE THE LAKE
CRYSTAL CLEAR AGAIN.
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS
NOBODY CAN LEAVE TOWN,
OR THE WATER LEVEL
WILL BE DOWN.
I DON'T THINK I CAN DRINK
THAT MUCH WATER, Mr. GREN.
MIKE, IF YOU CAN SMOKE,
YOU CAN DRINK.
YES, Mr. GREEN.
[ POSSUM SQUEAL ]
OH, GEEZ, THERE'S
THE MEETING.
LET'S GO TELL
THE OTHERS.
YOU GUYS GO AHEAD;
I'LL BE DOWN IN
A MINUTE.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHIN',
I'LL BE COMIN' STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETIN',
AND I'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU'D USE A LITTLE EXTRA
SALT IN YOUR COOKING
BECAUSE I'M GOING TO NEED TO BE
A LITTLE EXTRA THIRSTY FOR THE
NEXT LITTLE WHILE.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHIN'.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND
THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
closed captioning performed
by INTERCAPTION CANADA
www.intercaption.com
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
ALL RISE!
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
SIT DOWN.
OKAY, BOW YOUR HEADS, AND
JOIN ME IN THE MEN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO,
I GUESS.
BRING IT IN, MIKE.
IT'S JUST WATER.
45 GALLONS A WEEK, GUYS.