♪ ♪ ♪
>>RED: THIS IS RED GREEN
ON TODAY'S SHOW HAROLD'S GOING
TO TALK ABOUT SAFE SEX,
BILL'S GOING TO GO SNORKELING
THROUGH THE LEAVES
AND I'M GOING TO BUILD
A BIG RUBBER CHAIR FOR THAT
SPECIAL ROOM WE ALL NEED.
(RIFLE SHOTS FIRED)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
>>HAROLD: FROM THE FARTHEST
REACHES OF THE NORTH TO
THE FARTHEST REACHES OF
THE TELEVISION AUDIENCE
A MAN WHO'S REALLY REACHING
MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
>>RED: THANK YOU THANK YOU
FOR TUNING US IN AND YOU
KNOW HAROLD THAT INTRO WAS
ACTUALLY FAIRLY PROPHETIC.
>>HAROLD: WELL I LIKED IT.
>>RED: NO HAROLD, I SAID
PROPHETIC NOT PATHETIC
BUT NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT.
>>HAROLD: WELL YOU KNOW MAYBE
THEN YOU SHOULD USE WORDS
LIKE ECLECTIC, SOMETHING
THAT MEANS THIS.
>>RED: WELL THAT
WOULD BE SEPTIC.
WELL WE HAD A TOP LEVEL
MEETING OF THE POSSUM LODGE
BROTHERHOOD TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT SOME WAY WE COULD GENERATE
CASH FLOW AROUND HERE.
>>HAROLD: TOURISM THAT'S
THE TICKET, WE HAVE TO GET SOME
AMERICANS UP HERE BECAUSE THEY
SPEND MONEY LIKE WATER
AND THEIR MONEY IS LIKE
REAL MONEY TOO.
WE CAN MAKE A FORTUNE JUST
ON BOAT GAS BECAUSE THEY USE
GALLONS THEY DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT A LITER IS, IT'D BE GREAT.
>>RED: WELL ACTUALLY HAROLD
YOU HIT IT RIGHT ON THE NOSE
AND IF YOU KEEP YAMMERING
I MAY DO THE SAME THING TO YOU.
SO NOW WE GOT TO FIGURE
OUT HOW THE HECK ARE WE
GOING TO GET TOURISTS
TO COME UP HERE?
>>HAROLD: THE 3 P'S.
>>RED: NOT THAT WE'RE LOOKING
FOR ANY HELP HERE HAROLD
THANKS ANYWAY.
>>HAROLD: THE 3 P'S
PERFORMANCE, PRODUCTION
AND PENCILS? NO, PAMPHLETS
IT'S PROMOTION, PROMOTION
YOU GOT TO SEE THAT.
>>RED: HAROLD YOU WILL
PERSONALLY NEVER SEE PROMOTION.
SO WHAT WE'VE DECIDED TO DO IS
TO PUT ON A WATER SHOW UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE TUESDAY NIGHTS
AND SATURDAY AFTERNOONS.
>>HAROLD: WELL DO YOU THINK
WE COULD HAVE LIKE BETTER ROOMS
AND SAFE DRINKING WATER THAT
MIGHT BE A BETTER GIMMICK.
>>RED: OH NO WAY HAROLD, NO WAY
PEOPLE DON'T THINK ABOUT THAT
WE FIGURE THAT WE'RE GOING
TO TURN THIS THINK INTO
THE NORTHERN VERSION
OF CYPRESS GARDENS.
>>HAROLD: OH YEAH JUST LIKE
CYPRESS GARDENS YOU KNOW
EXCEPT FOR THE NICE WEATHER AND
PRETTY GIRLS WE COULD HAVE
LIKE BLACKFLIES AND BAD ROOMS
OH YEAH THERE'S A REALLY
GOOD SLOGAN.
>>RED: HAROLD WHEN THE PEOPLE
SEE THIS WATER SHOW THEY WON'T
EVEN THINK ABOUT THE MINOR
INCONVENIENCES.
MATTER OF FACT I WAS GOING
TO ASK YOU IF YOU WOULDN'T
MIND TAKING PART IN THE
WATER SHOW YOURSELF.
>>HAROLD: ME? OH NO, I'D BE VERY
HONOURED TO TAKE PART IN THE
WATER SHOW THAT'D BE GREAT.
YOU KNOW ANY CAPACITY THAT
I CAN FIT IN I'M THERE.
WHATEVER YOU NEED ME TO DO
I'LL DO YOU KNOW WHETHER
IT'S BAREFOOT SKIING OR
KNEE BOARDING OR SLALOM JUMPING
OR BODY SURFING.
>>RED: WELL ACTUALLY WE NEED
AN ANCHOR FOR THE RAFT.
♪ THE ANT GOES CRAWLING ♪
♪ DOWN THE SIDE OF THE ROAD ♪
♪ STRAINING UNDER ♪
♪ HIS HEAVY LOAD ♪
♪ JUST AS HE GETS ♪
♪ HIS HILL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ HERE COMES MY SHOES ♪
♪ RIGHT, LEFT, RIGHT ♪
♪ HIS JOURNEY HOME ♪
♪ IS NOW KAPUT ♪
♪ HE ONLY MISSED IT ♪
♪ BY A FOOT ♪
>>RED: THIS WEEK ON
'HANDYMAN CORNER' WE'RE GOING
TO SHOW YOU 2 THINGS YOU CAN
DO WITH ALL THOSE TIRES
YOU GOT LYING OUT ON
YOUR FRONT LAWN.
NOW ONE FESTIVE IDEA IS TO
TAKE SAY A WHEEL BARROW TIRE
STACK THAT ON TOP OF
A MOTORCYCLE TIRE
ON TOP OF A CAR TIRE
ON TOP OF A TRUCK TIRE
ON TOP OF A TRACTOR TIRE
AND WHAT YOU HAVE IS
A VERY INTERESTING LOOKING
RUBBER CHRISTMAS TREE.
THAT'S AN EYE CATCHER!
OF COURSE YOU CAN ALSO
DO THE STANDARD STUFF
LIKE YOU KNOW MAKE A SWING
FOR THE KIDS OUT OF A TIRE
AND SO ON, BUT TODAY I'M
GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW TO
MAKE A VERY UNIQUE
AND EXTREMELY COMFORTABLE,
ONE OF A KIND EASY CHAIR.
OKAY NOW YOU'RE GOING TO
NEED PROBABLY 7 TIRES
WELL EXACTLY 7 TIRES FOR THIS.
SO IF YOU'VE ONLY GOT SAY
3 TIRES I SUGGEST WHAT YOU DO
IS YOU TAKE YOUR VEHICLE DOWN
TO THE SAFETY INSPECTION PLACE
AND YOU MAY FIND THAT'LL
FREE UP AT LEAST 4 MORE.
OKAY STEP YOU GOT TO STACK UP
3 TIRES 1..2..3...
NOW ON THE OFF CHANCE THAT
YOU ACTUALLY HAVE SOME TREAD
ON YOUR TIRES YOU MIGHT WANT
TO CLEAN THEM OUT THERE BECAUSE
NOTHING WILL RUIN A RELAXING
EVENING MORE THAN HAVING MAYBE
A BIT OF ROAD KILL OR DOG DIRT
IN THERE ESPECIALLY IF IT'S ON
THE SIDE CLOSEST TO THE FIRE.
SO JUST GET IN THERE AND
CLEAN THAT OUT REAL GOOD,
A TOOTHBRUSH WORKS REAL WELL.
AND WHEN YOU'RE DONE YOU MIGHT
WANT TO CLEAN THAT OUT REAL
GOOD BEFORE YOU PUT IT BACK
INTO OLD MAN SEDGEWICK'S
DENTURE CUP.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
ALL RIGHT THIS BECOMES YOUR SEAT
RIGHT HERE IF YOU GOT THE
HEMORRHOIDS OR ANYTHING YOU
MIGHT WANT TO GO WITH A SOFT
WALL RADIAL AND YOU TRY
AND FIND YOURSELF A PAIL
THAT'S THE SAME DIAMETER
AS THE INSIDE DIAMETER OF
THE TIRES YOU JUST POP
THAT RIGHT IN THERE.
NOW YOU GOT A BUCKET SEAT.
NOW WHAT THIS BECOMES IS YOUR
COMPARTMENT FOR HOLDING SNACKS
OR YOUR FAVOURITE BEVERAGES
OR WHATEVER BECAUSE NOTHING
IS MORE IRRITATING THAN
TRYING TO WATCH TV AND HAVING
TO GET UP EVERY 3 HOURS
TO GO TO THE FRIDGE.
OF COURSE THIS SERVES AN
ENTIRELY DIFFERENT PURPOSE
DURING FLU SEASON.
ALL RIGHT YOU NEED A COUPLE
MORE TIRES THAT BECOME THE ARMS
OF YOUR CHAIR, YOU CAN MAKE
THESE AS DECORATIVE AS YOU LIKE
YOU CAN PUT THE STUDS ON THERE
OR THE CHAINS YOU COULD EVEN
GO HOLLYWOOD YOU KNOW HOW
THE HOLLYWOOD STYLE WHERE
THEY GET THEIR NAME CARVED
IN THE SIDEWALK AND EVERYTHING
WELL YOU COULD HAVE A NAME RIGHT
INSIDE YOUR TIRE AS LONG AS
YOUR NAME IS B.F. GOODRICH.
OF COURSE NOTHING SAYS
MONEY LIKE HUBCAPS
ESPECIALLY IF YOU CAN GET
THOSE SIMULATED SPOKE JOBS
GOD THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL
AREN'T THEY?
YOU POP THEM IN THERE
AND DON'T WORRY IF YOU HAVE
A LITTLE ROTTEN HUBCAPS
BECAUSE ANTIQUE FURNITURE
IS ACTUALLY WORTH MORE.
ALL RIGHT NOW WE NEED
THE BACK OF OUR CHAIR THAT
REQUIRES 2 TIRES, NOT THAT ONE.
(CRASHING & BANGING)
ALL RIGHT THESE 2 WILL BE FINE
WHAT WE DO IS WE PUT THEM END
TO END AND WE GOT TO ATTACH
THEM TO EACH OTHER
AND WE GOT TO ATTACH THEM
TO THE ARMS AND TO
THE CHAIR ITSELF.
NOW WHEN YOU ATTACH THEM
TOGETHER THERE YOU COULD DO
THAT WITH GLUE OR A STAPLE GUN
OR YOU COULD EVEN USE AN
ACETYLENE TORCH BUT IT DOES
TEND TO STINK TO A CERTAIN
EXTENT, SO I RECOMMEND THE
HANDYMAN'S SECRET WEAPON,
DUCT TAPE.
AND GET THAT TAPE NICE AND
SMOOTH ON THERE SMOOTH TAPE
IS A SIGN OF A FINE CRAFTSMAN.
NOW I'VE MOUNTED MY PICTURE
IN THE BACK THERE JUST SO
EVERYBODY KNOWS THIS IS
MY CHAIR, YOU KNOW IN CASE
B.F. GOODRICH EVER DROPS BY.
BUT YOU COULD PUT A BUMPER
STICKER IN THERE OR A STEERING
WHEEL OR EVEN ONE OF THOSE
ROUND ITALIAN LOAFS.
NOW THE REAL AMBITIOUS HANDYMAN
WOULD ALSO MAKE HIMSELF THIS
MATCHING SIDE TABLE HERE
IT'S JUST A WHEEL ON AN AXLE
MOUNTED ON A CHRISTMAS
TREE STAND.
I DID THIS WITH A VOLVO
BECAUSE MY WIFE REALLY LIKE
THE SCANDINAVIAN FURNITURE.
(LOUD CRASHING)
IMPORTS...
WELL LET'S GIVE HER A TRY
FOOLS RUSH IN WHERE
ANGELS FEAR THE TREAD...
HOPE THIS DOESN'T PUT ANOTHER
SKID MARK ON MY PANTS.
OH BY GOLLY THIS IS GREAT!
WELL MAYBE...
(HUB CAP CLATTERING)
GOOD IDEA I'LL SEE WHAT'S
ON TV, HEY STOCK CAR RACING
IS ON, THIS WILL BE JUST
LIKE SITTING IN THE PITS.
ISN'T THIS THE PITS?
GREAT, WELL MAYBE I'LL HAVE
MYSELF A LITTLE SNACK
SOMETHING TO EAT HUH?
REMEMBER IF WOMEN DON'T FIND
YOU HANDSOME THEY SHOULD
AT LEAST FIND YOU HANDY.
TASTES LIKE A HIGHWAY.
>>HAROLD: AND NOW IT'S THAT
PART OF THE SHOW WHERE WE
EXPOSE THE 3 LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND SO HARD TO SAY
'I DON'T KNOW'.
AND HERE TO PROVE THAT POINT
ON THE EXPERT PORTION OF
THE SHOW OF COURSE IS
MY UNCLE RED AND
MR. BOB STUYVESTANT.
>>HAROLD: ALL RIGHT HERE WE GO
LETTER NUMBER ONE,
ACTUALLY IT'S THE ONLY ONE
BUT ANYWAY...
'DEAR EXPERTS, I'VE BEEN
MARRIED FOR 9 YEARS AND WE'RE
STARTING TO HAVE SOME PROBLEMS,
LITTLE THINGS LIKE BICKERING
OVER WHO PAYS FOR PIZZA
AND SUDDENLY THE BANK ACCOUNT
IS $8000 OVERDRAWN AND THEN
THE OTHER DAY I COULDN'T HELP
BUT NOTICE THAT SHE HAD
FILED FOR DIVORCE.
DO YOU HAVE ANY SUGGESTIONS?
>>BOB: ABSOLUTELY, TAKE UP GOLF.
>>RED: WELL NOW BOB I THINK
BEFORE WE ADVISE A GUY TO RUN
AWAY FROM HIS PROBLEMS MAYBE
HE SHOULD AT LEAST TRY FOR
A RECONCILIATION OF SOME KIND.
>>BOB: LISTEN RED I THINK I'VE
BEEN DOWN THIS ROAD A TIME OR 2
YOU KNOW WHAT WITH MY 5 MESSY
DIVORCES I THINK I KNOW
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
GOLF MAKES ALL THE WORLD'S
PROBLEMS SEEM TO DIMINISH
TO NOTHING WHEN YOU'RE
PLAYING A GAME OF GOLF.
>>HAROLD: WOW MR. STUYVESTANT
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE
MARRIED 5 TIMES.
>>BOB: YUP HAROLD, WELL IT ALL
STARTS OFF PEACHY KEEN AND THEN
THEY START ASKING QUESTIONS.
LIKE I CALLED YOU AT WORK
THE OTHER DAY AND YOU
WEREN'T THERE, HOW COME?
OR ARE YOU COMING HOME FOR
THE WEEKEND TO HELP WITH
THE MOVE?
OR THE ONE I REALLY LIKE IS
CAN'T YOU GET AN EARLIER TEE
OFF TIME AFTER ALL IT
IS OUR ANNIVERSARY?'
NEXT THING YOU KNOW YOU'RE
TALKING THROUGH YOUR LAWYERS.
>>RED: WELL I THINK IF OUR
VIEWERS LISTEN CLOSELY TO WHAT
BOB IS SAYING HERE THERE'S
A PRETTY GOOD CLUE IN THERE
AS TO MAYBE HOW YOU CAN
PATCH UP YOUR OWN MARRIAGE.
>>BOB: YOU KNOW RED WHETHER
WE LIKE IT OR NOT THERE'S JUST
SOME PEOPLE AREN'T CUT OUT
FOR THE MARRIAGE THING.
I MEAN BETWEEN THIS GUY AND ME
WE'VE MET 6 WOMEN WHO FALL
INTO THAT CATEGORY.
>>RED: IT IS AUTUMN
THE LAKE WILL SOON FREEZE
HARD AS A ROCK
SO GET THE BOATS UP ON THE DOCK
PULL OUT THE ROWBOAT AND CANOE
THE RUNABOUT AND SAILBOAT TOO
THE BIG POWERBOAT WITH THE BIG
GAS TANK, ONE BOAT TOO MANY
THE DOCK JUST SANK.
>>RED: HI HAP GOING FISHING?
>>HAP: I CAN'T RED SOME
IDIOT BROKE MY FISHING ROD.
>>RED: YEAH I SAW.
HAP IS THIS BOAT STRONG
ENOUGH TO TOW WATER SKIERS
DO YOU THINK?
>>HAP: THIS BOAT WILL
DO ANYTHING FOR A FEE.
>>RED: WILL IT RUN RELIABLY?
>>HAP: I'M NOT SURE
YOU HAVE THAT MUCH MONEY.
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK SAID SOMETHING
ABOUT A WATERSHOW?
>>RED: YEAH WELL THAT'S WHAT
I NEED THE BOAT FOR TO
PULL THE WATER SKIERS.
>>HAP: THAT'S A BIT LAME
ISN'T IT RED?
I MEAN WATER SKIERS
WHY DON'T I WRESTLE A SHARK
THAT'S ALWAYS A GOOD
CROWD PLEASER.
YOU KNOW ME AGAINST A GREAT
WHITE SHARK YOU COULD CALL IT
THE FEARLESS FISHERMAN.
>>RED: YEAH OR
THE FEEDING FRENZY.
>>HAP: I'M USED TO SHARKS,
I LIKE SHARKS.
>>RED: OH SURE BUT
THEY'LL SWALLOW ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW HAP I DON'T THINK
SHARKS CAN SURVIVE FRESH WATER
NOT THAT POSSUM LAKE
IS ALL THAT FRESH.
>>HAP: TOO BAD, JACQUES COUSTEAU
SAID MY SHARK FIGHTING ACT
HAD TO BE SEEN TO BE BELIEVED.
>>RED: WELL I'D BE WITH
JACKO ON THAT ONE.
>>HAP: I GOT IT!
I'D RIDE BAREBACK ON MOBY DICK
THE GREAT WHITE HUNTER
AGAINST THE GREAT WHITE WHALE.
OH NO WAIT WHALES ARE SALT
WATER CREATURES TOO.
>>RED: IF YOU COULD JUST
PULL THE WATER SKIERS.
>>HAP: I'LL DO MY HIGH DIVING
ACT THEN, I'LL JUMP 400 FEET
INTO A REALLY DAMP FACECLOTH
DID I EVER TELL YOU
THAT STORY RED?
>>RED: IT HASN'T BEEN NECESSARY
AND BESIDES WE DON'T HAVE
A 400 FOOT TOWER.
>>HAP: WELL THAT'S TOO BAD.
ALL RIGHT I'LL PULL THE
LITTLE WATER SKIERS.
>>RED: GREAT,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH HAP.
>>HAP: THAT'S TOO BAD
I CAN SEE ME WRESTLING THE
GREAT WHITE SHARK OR RIDING
THE GREAT WHITE WHALE.
>>RED: YEAH OR TELLING
THE GREAT WHITE LIE.
>>RED: WELL THE POSSUM LODGE
WATER SHOW IS SHAPING UP
REAL GOOD, JUNIOR SINGLETON
WAS DOING TIME LAPS IN
HIS SPEEDBOAT AND HE STOOD
UP TO WAVE TO THE IMAGINARY
CROWD AND T-BONED
THE WATER SKI RAMP.
>>HAROLD: HIS PROP CAME RIGHT
THROUGH MY BEDROOM WINDOW POING!
>>RED: WELL ONCE WE ALL STOPPED
LAUGHING AND JUNIOR REGAINED
CONSCIOUSNESS WE DECIDED TO
HAVE THAT IN EVERY SHOW
AS THE BIG FINALE
SO A BUNCH OF THE GUYS
ARE MAKING SPARE RAMPS.
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED THAT'S
NOT HOW A WATER SHOW WORKS
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE A
DEMONSTRATION OF STYLE
AND GRACE AND ATHLETIC ABILITIES
I DON'T THINK PEOPLE GO TO
CYPRESS GARDENS TO SEE
A DEMOLITION DERBY.
>>RED: WELL WE'RE PUSHING
THE ENVELOPE A LITTLE BIT HERE
HAROLD AND BESIDES WE GOT
ALL THE SISSY STUFF TOO
LIKE STINKY PETERSON'S GOING
TO SLALOM SKI ON ONE SKI
WHICH IS GOOD BECAUSE WE
HAVE ONE SKI AND A BUNCH
OF THE GUYS ARE GOING TO DO
A FORMATION WHILE BEING
TOWED AROUND THE LAKE
ON A BOATHOUSE DOOR.
>>HAROLD: OH REALLY?
THAT'S GREAT, OH THEY'RE
GOING TO DO A PYRAMID.
>>RED: WELL NO, THE VERSION
I SAW LOOKED MORE LIKE
STONEHENGE AND MOOSE THOMPSON
IS REAL KEEN TO DO SOMETHING
BUT IF WE GET WATER SKIS
LONG ENOUGH TO SUIT HIS
BODY WEIGHT WE'LL HAVE
TO MOVE TO A BIGGER LAKE.
>>HAROLD: WELL MAYBE HE COULD
JUST LIKE BODY SURF
BEHIND THE BASS BOAT.
>>RED: YEAH BUT WE'D
HAVE TO SHAVE HIS BACK
BEFORE EVERY SHOW.
>>HAROLD: YEAH THAT'S TRUE
WE DON'T WANT A HAIRLINE
ON THE SHORELINE.
REMEMBER ALL THE KRILL
WERE COUGHING UP HAIRBALLS?
♪ I OFTEN THINK BACK ♪
♪ TO MY YOUNGER DAYS ♪
♪ I SAT IN SCHOOL ♪
♪ IN A TOTAL DAZE ♪
♪ I REMEMBER WHEN I SHOWED ♪
♪ MY DAD MY REPORT ♪
♪ HE HOISTED THE JUG ♪
♪ AND HORSED BACK A SNORT ♪
♪ IT WAS THE FIRST TIME ♪
♪ I'D EVER GOTTEN ALL A'S ♪
♪ UNFORTUNATELY THE MARKS ♪
♪ WERE OUT OF A HUNDRED ♪
♪ 'A' STOOD FOR ABSENT ♪
>>RED: SO THERE I WAS OUT
IN THE WOODS MINDING MY OWN
BUSINESS NOT BOTHERING ANYBODY
FORGETTING THAT IT WAS TIME FOR
'ADVENTURES WITH BILL'.
BILL IS DRESSED A LITTLE
UNUSUALLY I FELT FOR THE WEATHER
BUT KIND OF ONE OF THEM WETSUIT
STARTLING IDEAS RIGHT THERE AND
I'M NOT COMPLETELY SURE HE HAD
THE HEAD GEAR ON ABSOLUTELY
THE WAY THEY WOULD RECOMMEND
DOWN AT THE SNORKELING PLACE
BUT I COULD UNDERSTAND THEM
NOT WANTING TO TALK TO BILL.
NOW HE'S CHECKING THE WATER
TEMPERATURE, POSSUM LAKE IS
VERY VERY COLD VERY EARLY
ANY TIME FROM JULY 15TH ON
BY GOLLY SHE'S REAL COLD THERE
SO HE FROZE HIS FINGER RIGHT
IN THERE BUT I'M ONLY TOO
WILLING TO HELP HIM OUT ON THAT
(LOUD THUD OF ROCK HITTING ICE)
THERE YOU GO.
>>BILL: AAHHH!
>>RED: OH OH WON'T BE ABLE
TO HITCHHIKE UNTIL I FIX THAT
NO PROBLEM BILL AND NOW HE'S
GOT THIS LITTLE BAG TO CATCH
ALL HIS TREASURES IN WHEN
HE DIVES, SEE HE PUTS THEM IN
THE BAG THAT'S GOT LIKE THE MESH
AND THE WATER GOES OUT AND THE
TREASURES STAY IN AND HE'S
JUST GOING TO GET READY.
I THINK YOU HAVE TO
CLEAN OFF THE MASK
AND HE'S GOT HIS FACE IN THE
BASIN AND YOU KNOW A LOT
OF GUYS WHEN THEIR FINGER
FROZE, YEAH EXACTLY.
WELL WHAT DID YOU EXPECT BILL?
BUT LUCKILY THE SAME SOLUTION
WILL WORK ON A FACE THAT WORKS
ON A FINGER BECAUSE WHAT I DID
WAS I PICKED A BIGGER ROCK
WHAT I CALL A FACE SIZED ROCK
STAY STILL, STAY STILL.
THERE HE GOES GETTING
THE ICE OUT OF THERE,
YEAH YOU'RE ALL RIGHT
YOU'RE FINE, YOU'RE FINE.
YEAH NOW WHAT WAS HAPPENING
AT THIS POINT WAS BILL HAD
HAD HIS PLAN BUT HE WAS
STARTING TO ADAPT AS TO WHAT
EXACTLY HE WAS SAYING TO HIMSELF
BOY DO I REALLY WANT
TO GO INTO THAT?
AND I'M THINKING TO MYSELF NO!
NOW I WOULD NEVER HAVE GUESSED
WHAT BILL WAS GOING TO DO
AS AN ALTERNATIVE.
HE HANDED ME HIS GLASSES
PUTS ON THE MASK
NOW THERE'S NO WATER AROUND
BUT HE DIVES, BELIEVE IT OR NOT
FOLKS INTO THE LEAVES.
ONCE IN A WHILE BILL GOES
OVER THAT LINE AND I REALLY
DON'T QUITE UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S GOING ON.
STRANGE NOISES I FEEL LIKE
I'M ONE OF THE EXTRAS ON
'SEA HUNT' AT THIS POINT.
AND I SAW A BIT OF MOVEMENT
THERE YOU CAN'T REALLY
LOOK FOR THE BUBBLES
COMING UP.
NOT WITH BILL AND OF COURSE
YOU DON'T WANT TO LOOK FOR
THE BUBBLES COMING UP.
THERE HE IS! THERE HE IS!
CLEAN OUT HIS SNORKEL.
OH PATOOIE!
YOU GOT THE YEAH A LITTLE
BIT OF LEAVES IN THE MASK THERE
AND DOWN HE GOES AGAIN
BACK INTO THE DIVE.
BOY OH BOY, CATCHING THINGS
AND GETTING TREASURES AND
JUST HAVING THE ADVENTURE
OF A LIFETIME I WOULD THINK
AND CERTAINLY NOTHING THAT'S
EVER BEEN DONE BEFORE IN
THE HISTORY OF MAN.
BOY WHAT I'D GIVE FOR
A DEPTH CHARGE RIGHT NOW.
COME ON BILL HERE HE COMES!
HE GOING TO SURFACE CAPTAIN
AMAST THE BALLAST OR SOMETHING
I DON'T KNOW.
UP HE COMES NONE THE WORSE
FOR WEAR HE DIDN'T START OUT
THAT GREAT ACTUALLY.
LITTLE LEAVES IN THE HAT THERE
BILL ANYWAY HE DID GET ALL
THE TREASURES, HE'D BEEN GETTING
ALL THE NUTS THAT THE SQUIRRELS
HAD BEEN PUTTING WAY.
ONE OF THE SQUIRRELS WASN'T
TOO PLEASED ABOUT HIM STEALING
HIS NUTS AND I DON'T BLAME HIM
OH! OH! OH!
>>BILL: AAAHHH!
>>RED: THAT HURTS EH BILL?
HE TAKES ALL HIS NUTS BACK.
OH WELL THAT'S WHAT YOU GET.
OH NO NO NO NO HE TOOK ALL
HIS NUTS BACK EXCEPT ONE,
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
DO WITH THAT BILL?
HOLD ON I GOT ANOTHER ROCK
I CAN HELP YOU OUT YOU KNOW
THE SAME TYPE OF COME ON BILL!
COME ON, COME ON BILL!
>>RED: THESE DAYS THE YOUNG
PEOPLE ARE DEMANDING EQUAL
TIME SO HERE'S HAROLD WHICH
SHOULD PRETTY WELL PUT
AN END TO THOSE DEMANDS.
>>HAROLD: OH HI TODAY'S SHOW
IS AIMED AT THOSE OF YOU ARE
TOO YOUNG TO VOTE BUT TOO OLD
TO USE THE SAME PHONE AS
THE REST OF THE FAMILY.
SO HERE WE GO FOR TODAY'S
TOPIC IS, SAFE SEX.
OKAY ALL RIGHT I WANT TO GET
SERIOUS FOR A FEW MINUTES
IF I COULD AND TALK ABOUT
YOU KNOW SAFE SEX
>>RED: HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: YEAH?
>>RED: AREN'T WE SUPPOSED TO
BE WATCHING HANDYMAN CORNER
OR ADVENTURES WITH BILL OR A
DEAD TREE SOMETHING INTERESTING?
>>HAROLD: UNCLE RED I WAS GOING
TO TALK ABOUT SAFE SEX ON
THE ON THE TEEN TALK TODAY.
>>RED: OH ALL RIGHT
GO AHEAD HAROLD.
>>HAROLD: REALLY?
>>RED: YEAH, GO AHEAD.
>>HAROLD: ALL RIGHT, UM OKAY,
UH, SAFE SEX YOU KNOW IT'S LIKE
(GIGGLES) IT'S SAFE YOU KNOW
BECAUSE WHEN YOU DO IT
(GIGGLING) YOU KNOW OKAY, OKAY
IF YOU GOT (GIGGLING)
YOU SAID I CAN DO IT RIGHT?
IT'S SAFE RIGHT SO (LAUGHING).
>>RED: HAROLD! HAROLD!
HAROLD! HAROLD! HAROLD!
>>HAROLD: WHAT?
>>RED: THIS IS SOMETHING
YOU'LL NEVER HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT.
(LOUD CRASHING)
>>HAROLD: THAT'S NOT SAFE!
>>RED: WHEN I SEE YOU YOUNG
TEENAGERS OF TODAY YOU KNOW
HANGING OUT AT THE VIDEO ARCADE
OR DRIVING AROUND IN ONE OF
THEM 4-WHEEL STEREOS
I CAN'T HELP BUT THINK THAT
YOU'RE MISSING OUT ON A BIG
PART OF TEENAGE LIFE AND THAT
IS HAVING A DARNED INTERESTING
HOBBY, HUNTING OR FISHING,
OR CAMPING OR HIKING OR
WHITTLING OR THAT KIND OF THING.
YOU KNOW A HOBBY IS AN IMPORTANT
PART OF YOUR DEVELOPMENT
AND IT HELPS FILL IN THE TIME
WHILE YOU'RE WAITING TO TURN
INTO SOMETHING WORTHWHILE.
AND MAKE SURE YOU PICK A REAL
ONE YOU KNOW SKIPPING STONES
ACROSS STORE WINDOWS
AT THE MALL IS NOT A HOBBY
AND NEITHER IS AUTO THEFT.
AND YOU MAY THINK GETTING ALONG
WITH GIRLS IS A HOBBY NOW
BUT AFTER YOU GET MARRIED THAT
TURNS INTO A JOB AND NOTHING
KILLS A HOBBY FASTER THAN
TURNING IT INTO A
FULL TIME THING.
>>DOUGIE: I'M OFFICIALLY OUT
OF THE AMBULANCE BUSINESS.
>>RED: WELL OKAY THEN HOW'D
YOU LIKE TO BE IN THE WATER
SHOW BUSINESS DOUGIE?
'CAUSE WE'RE THINKING OF
HAVING OUR OWN KIND OF
WATER AQUARAMA SHOW UP
AT THE LODGE, KIND OF ATTRACT
TOURISTS YOU KNOW.
>>DOUGIE: YOU GOT PERMISSION?
YOU GOT INSURANCE?
YOU GOT LIABILITY COVERAGE?
YOU GOT LICENSES TO SELL FOOD
AND BEVERAGES?
>>RED: NO, WE HAVE BOATS.
>>DOUGIE: DON'T YOU REMEMBER
MY FRIEND A COUPLE OF YEARS
BACK I WAS GOING TO DO MY OWN
AUTOMOBILE THRILL SHOW
I MEAN IT WAS YOU WHO SAID I WAS
KIND OF A NATURAL HELL DRIVER.
>>RED: NOT QUITE THE WAY
I WORDED IT.
>>DOUGIE: ALL MY CARS LINED UP
IN ROWS, HAD THE WHOLE PLACE ALL
FIXED UP WELL MUCH LIKE YOU SEE
IT RIGHT NOW, YUP IT WAS GOING
TO BE THE DOUGIE FRANKLIN
AUTOMOBILE THEME PARK
AND REC-O-RAMA.
>>RED: OH RIGHT THAT NEVER
OPENED UP TO THE PUBLIC
DID IT DOUG?
>>DOUGIE: NO SIR,
KILLED BY PAPER WORK
AND RED TAPE.
>>RED: BUT YOU KNOW DOUG
I WAS THINKING MAYBE WE GET
THE PEOPLE TO SIGN SOME
KIND OF A...
>>DOUGIE: FORGET IT RED
FORGET IT, I MEAN UNLESS YOU GET
EVERYTHING DONE IN TRIPLICATE
THE GOVERNMENT AIN'T GOING
TO LET YOU CRUSH A SINGLE THING
I MEAN WE TRIED TO GET SOMEBODY
A VOLUNTEER FROM THE AUDIENCE
FOR PETE'S SAKE, A VOLUNTEER
JUST TO GET ON THAT MOTORCYCLE
AND RIDE THROUGH THE WALL
OF DEATH, WELL WE HAD A WAIVER
FOR HIM TO SIGN AND EVERYTHING
UNBELIEVABLE, I'M TELLING YOU
I USED TO BELIEVE THIS HERE
WAS A FREE COUNTRY
NO SIR, NO SIREE BOB.
>>RED: NO YOU'RE RIGHT DOUGIE
PAPERWORK AND RED TAPE IS
KILLING THE INITIATIVE
OF THE SMALL BUSINESSMAN.
>>DOUGIE: TRUER WORDS HAVE
NEVER BEEN SPOKEN MAN.
>>RED: WELL LOOKS LIKE
THE POSSUM LODGE WATER SHOW
IS OUT OF BUSINESS.
I'LL TELL YOU THE GOVERNMENT
SURE KNOWS HOW TO TAKE
THE FUN OUT OF RISKING LIVES.
>>HAROLD: I'LL TELL YOU
I'M GLAD THEY SHUT YOU GUYS
DOWN I THINK YOU WENT WAY OVER
TOP IN SOME OF THESE EVENTS
WATER SKIING ON A CHAINSAW.
OLD MAN SEDGEWICK AND HIS
TRAINED CRAYFISH
AND THAT BIT WHERE ALL
THE BOATS CRASH INTO
A BALL OF FIRE
COME ON, THAT'S A FIRE
HAZARD THERE!
>>RED: IT'S NOT A FIRE HAZARD
HAROLD IT'S ALL TAKING PLACE
OUT ON THE WATER.
>>HAROLD: THAT'S NOT WATER
THAT'S POSSUM LAKE!
>>RED: YEAH HE'S RIGHT.
WELL WE'RE GOING TO DO THE WATER
SHOW ONCE ANYWAY BECAUSE GUYS
PUT A LOT OF WORK INTO IT
AND YOU KNOW THEY'RE
ALL KIND OF KEYED UP
EVERYBODY'S BOAT IS RUNNING
REAL GOOD SO WE'RE GOING
TO GIVE AND OLD MAN SEDGEWICK
HAD RENTED A BALLERINA COSTUME
FOR THE CRAYFISH AND SO
WE'RE GOING TO WIND HER UP
AND WE'RE GOING TO LET HER
GO AND MOOSE HAS EVEN GOT
A ROUTINE THAT HE'S
GOING TO DO FOR US.
>>HAROLD: A BUCKING BRONCO
ON AN OUTBOARD
I THOUGHT YOU CUT THAT?
>>RED: WELL HE HAD HIS HEART
SET ON IT HAROLD AND THIS
TIME HE'S PROMISED TO FLY
INTO A SMALLER TREE.
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: OH THAT'S
MEETING TIME.
>>RED: YEAH YOU GO AHEAD
HAROLD I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
WELL THAT'S ABOUT IT
FOR THIS TIME.
SO IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING
I'M PROBABLY GOING TO BE
A LITTLE BIT LATE TONIGHT
BECAUSE AFTER THE MEETING
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
THE WATER SHOW AND I WOULD
THINK THAT WOULD BE FOLLOWED
BY ABOUT, OH 45 MINUTES OF CPR.
BY THE TIME THE FIRETRUCKS
AND AMBULANCES ARE OUT HERE
IT'S GOING TO BE SUNDOWN
OR LATER.
SO FOR THE REST OF YOU
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF AND HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG UP HERE
AT POSSUM LODGE
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING
AND KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
♪ ♪ ♪
(POSSUM SQUEALING)
>>HAROLD: ALL RISE.
>>ALL: QUANDO OMNI
FLUNKUS MORTATI.
>>RED: I KNOW YOU'RE ALL
PRETTY EXCITED ABOUT
THE WATER SKI SHOW
THAT'S WE'RE PUTTING ON
RIGHT AFTER THE MEETING.
>>GUYS: YEAH! YEAH!
(CLAPPING & CHEERING)
CLOSED CAPTIONING BY
LOOK SMART CAPTIONING
looksmart@sympatico.ca