Hi, this is red green in today's show, Harold
criticizes adults, bill shows as camping
lanterns and I turn a patio table into a
windsurfer.
Here's the man who put the out and out house.
He's the greatest uncle I could ever have
unless, of course I was adopted, but I
wasn't. So no such luck for me anyway.
Here he is. Mr.
Red. Green.
Thank you very much, and thanks for joining
us in kind of an interesting introduction,
Mary Harold.
Well, you know me, Mr.
Shelby, is what
Actually I was referring to that bit about
you being adopted.
You know, if you'd been adopted, Harold,
then of course you wouldn't be my nephew and
then I wouldn't have had to give you this
job.
Yeah, but I don't think anybody would adopt
me at this, you know, advanced development
stage that I'm in.
Well, then OK, we could do the Moses thing.
We can duct tape you into a kayak and float
you down the Nile.
Oh, wow. Yeah, now I know you're just kidding
because there's no boats around this large
can float that far.
Well, he does have a point there, with the
exception, of course, of John Singleton's
boat.
Yeah, right. And you're single. Yeah, there's
so many holes in that boat.
No way junior could fix all those holes.
No, no, no.
Hell, he's not going to fix the holes.
Junior has upgraded his bill.
Trump. What he did was he went down to the
army surplus store and he bought Catch this a
used rocket fuel pump off a Russian
intercontinental ballistic missile.
I'll tell you, the army surplus store sure
has some interesting merchandise since the
arms race ended.
Ok, good because I like that.
You know, I'm in favor of beating swords
into plowshares.
Or should I say, you know, beating rocket
fuel equipment into building booms?
How about beating you into a small plant
lump?
Anyway, Junior got the big, huge pump ball
mounted inside is inside his boat there, you
know, and suddenly got a bit of a surprise
when she dropped right through the hull down
to the bottom, the lake and she was running
at the time.
So this is what we call a setback.
And but by golly, that is some kind of pump
been kept running down the bottom of the lake
and within 15 minutes it had pumped the
whole possum lake totally dry.
Awesome lake was pumped dry.
The possible lake is gone now.
Oh no, no, no. What it did was it temporarily
transferred the lake up to the top of the
hill and then the pump ran out of gas and
the water came back down again.
But but in the meanwhile, it gave us a
chance to get it on and on to the bottom of
the dry lake. And we got some of our old
boats back and a few of our appliances and so
on, and we could fix some of the divots from
Loose Thompson doing cannonballs off the boat
house. And most importantly, we got Junior's
great big pump back up there and we've
decided we're going to do something else
with it.
We're going to use it to collect maple
syrup.
It's not maple syrup time,
Harold with a pump this size, any time it's
maple syrup.
Ok. Ok, I'll go ahead, you know, I'm, you
know, I'm not a tree expert or anything, but
I don't think you can just get the sap to do
whatever you want it to do.
Oh sure, you can Harold get on with show?
We'll see.
My butterfly collection gives me so much
pride, my butterfly collection makes me warm
inside the monarch's blues and yellows.
These are beauties an old man, come and see
my butterfly collection.
They're all wedged in the grill of my van.
This week, Handymen Corner, we're going to
show you an interesting project that you can
make with one of them patio umbrella tables.
Now I know the patio tables are supposed to
be used in your backyard for entertaining
your neighbors, but I'd rather do something
fun.
I'd rather use them for windsurfing.
All right. Talk is cheap.
Let's build step one.
Remove the umbrella. Put it away somewhere
safe for later.
Here we go. Now what you want to do is you
want to draw out the design of your wind
surfer on top of the table so you can cut it
out.
And for that, you're going to need some kind
of a marker and get yourself a ruler so you
can keep the edges nice and straight.
Oh, you know what? The dampness and the
fungi in the moss up here on a work, it's up
the line. So I'll just.
I'll just eyeball it.
I bowled out pretty good, didn't I?
Ok, there we are. And now what we do is we
cut along all those lines that cut out our
surfboard. Now you could use a hands off or
that or if you've got a real good eye, you
could use an axe. To me, this is a carving
job for a carving job.
I want to use an electric knife.
That's either peanut butter or last year's
turkey.
Now you want to take all these pieces and
turn this thing into the shape of a
surfboard. Because if those college kids see
you surfing on a patio table, you're going to
be the brunt of some insensitive comments.
Wavy pharmaceuticals here.
And this goes here together here.
This goes back here.
And then you take these two pieces and you
put those together to form yourself a rudder.
Now what you do is you attach everything
together using either the epoxy cement or
maybe you like to use bolts and nuts and so
on, or whatever fastening technique you feel
most confident with.
I prefer the man secret weapon.
Duct tape. Boy, that makes you feel like
shooting a girl, isn't it?
Look at all the cobwebs up there.
Oh, well.
There we go now.
I've already hoisted our sail.
I call it I call it a sale now because it's
I'm lucky to open umbrella and doors and I
put a big wad of duct tape on here so that
it doesn't go too far in, which is a handy
thing to remember. Pop that in there.
Looks like we got a pretty good breeze going
out there, so why don't we try and catch the
wind? As Donovan would say, they won't open
up the big door there.
All right, so remember the women don't find
you handsome, at least find a happy meal on
the patio.
Wipe out. And now it's up out of this hole,
we expose those three little words men find
so difficult to say, I don't know.
And here to prove that point once again on
the experts portion of the show is my uncle
read and his best friend in the whole world.
Oh, OK, Mr.
Dougie Franklin. All right, dear
experts. My son has had several throat
infections over the years, and our doctor is
now saying he should have his tonsils out,
which I thought was no longer a recommended
procedure. What are your thoughts?
My advice to this person is get away from
this doctor and every doctor
As fast as you can fully.
So you don't think this viewer should see a
doctor then?
I don't think anybody should see a doctor.
You know, the human body is nobody's
business.
You know,
My daddy never saw a doctor a day in his
life.
Now he he smoked a pack and a half of
cigarettes, planes a day.
And you know,
Sure, once in a while, he might get a little
coughing spell that might last
Like a weekend or so.
But apart from that, he was as healthy
As you or I.
So you've never been to a doctor, either,
Doug.
Never been to a doctor, a dentist or a
psychiatrist.
I'm telling you. The human body was not
designed to be repaired from the outside.
The Good Lord had meant this to be.
He would have put a hood on it somewhere.
Soon, as you've got a slash through skin or
start sawing through bone, you got to
Know you're dealing with something that was
designed to be maintenance free.
I'll tell you, you get in there and start
tinkering with stuff and you're going to void
your warranty with that master mechanic in
the sky.
I'll tell you.
It is winter cousin Jerry was lying in the
snow, making snow angels, along came the snow
plow. Now cousin Jerry is making real
angels.
Oh, man, not again,
This thing ready to go.
Oh yo, red, hey, no problem, oh, hey yo,
Harold,
Oh, you're all right here. I'll get up
planes.
The planes OK to fly.
Oh man, Norwegian Wood, this bird has flown
Errol.
There's a dark spider going up your leg
there.
She needs a new carburetor.
You know, that's like a hundred bucks.
And like, I don't want to spend that kind of
bread on a plane like this.
I'm in the
Air. What I was thinking was that if I got
buzz here to take me up in his airplane, I
could kind of get an aerial view of the
trees around the lodge and see which ones
would be good for our syrup business.
I wasn't sure about the plane, though.
Here, we don't need that stuff.
Oh, no,
No, no. We'll be fine, I'm sure.
Well, we'll soon find out,
But it doesn't instill a lot of confidence in
its passengers.
But I still figure this has got to be the
quickest, easiest way to identify all the
maple trees around the lodge.
But I'm just looking for a maple tree that's
all maple.
Yeah, I
Don't know if we got any maple around here,
you know?
See, we got we got the spruce and poplar and
pine and aluminum.
Oh man, I hate those TV antennas.
I can't, you know, I was going to kind of
look from the air, but I think maybe now a
ground survey, I'll get my own mail.
Oh, sorry.
Keep the faith. You can't walk down, bro.
No way. That's bad karma.
You watch. You watch.
I mean, if you walked away now, right?
Any money, I'd start up the plane and
something like would fly off it and with
legs, just sever your spine.
Don't worry. Don't worry, I got parachutes.
Somewhere. All right.
See that red line when I say now, turn it
all the way to the right.
Cool.
All right. All right.
No. Hey, look at it this way, at least you
won't hear the roar of the engine.
Bring it on. That's.
Well, my idea of gathering surf has really
taken off.
We got juniors big punk ball tuned up and
Moose is out there drilling holes on every
tree you can find.
We're going to connect the trees to the
intake manifold by everybody has donated the
brake lines from their cars and pretty soon
we're going to be sucking out a fortune worth
of syrup.
Well, this is great.
How did you clean all the
Brake fluid out of the lines?
How do you mean?
The brake fluid, you know, you've got to
clean the lines, I don't think people want a
taste brake fluid with their maple syrup.
Oh oh, come on, Harold.
All food has chemicals in it.
And besides, it's part of our slogan, the
syrup that puts the brakes on hunger.
I'm telling you, this is going to be a real
moneymaker for us, this is the big one right
here. Oh yeah, I've
Heard that before. What about the, you know,
the plywood car or the the peekaboo hip
waders?
Now that's different, Harold.
This is the big one right here. We're
already working on the marketing angle for
Uncle Red's special syrup.
What is that like a Ghostbuster action figure
or something?
No, and that's the Uncle Red pancake syrup
dispenser with the no drip head.
A little twinge of jealousy there.
Heroin?
No, it's more like a wave of nausea.
Well, go read, it's Trey uncool, seeing you
about six inches high made a squeezable
plastic stuffed with maple syrup.
Oh, Harold. Maple syrup, we got moose to
drill holes and all kinds of trees, so we got
oak syrup, pine syrup, spruce.
Thirty one flavors are.
We're going to corner the syrup market.
Oh, yeah, I bet you that Aunt Jemima just
shaking in her scarf.
When tanks were laying out across the farm,
it blew all the hair off my granny's arm.
Was the livestock down into the, well, blue,
the clappers off the town hall bell?
It was a lesson we learned and we learned it
well.
There's one heck of a lot of turbulence when
you push a burn over.
This week on Adventures with Bill Bill's
going to show us all about camping lanterns.
That's next week could be car repair.
Anyway, Bill Bright, all look at all the
equipment.
He's got there, all different kinds of
lights.
That's just kind of a normal one.
And this is kind of a little higher voltage,
pretty bright light.
There's kind of focus
Home
As opposed to bill. It was not.
Look at the size of that thing isn't I've
never seen a flashlight like that in my life.
And Bill says, Take the hand off there.
I was left hand or right hand because she
was cross red, so that's kind of a bit of
both. Bill's opening the batteries in the
plastic package.
Now they're open and it goes down and gets
the battery or two.
And look, you can got de cells in there.
It doesn't matter, apparently, which way you
put them in, up or down, you know, the plus
or minus whatever. Just fire them all in
there.
It's kind of an unusual rig this one, and it
takes all the different sizes, the CS and I
think even the double A's, they go in side
by side kind of a Noah's Ark kind of a look
to the flashlight at that point.
And what else you got there?
And I check that I'll just check that out on
my dog again.
Yeah, that one's fine.
Grab that one in there. And well, it's
pretty.
Oh. Oh.
Maybe you should have thought that one
through a bill, and they were also put the
cap back on there and how I'm going to hand
her back to Bill, he's going to turn her on.
This is going to be pretty great. I would
think.
Do right, perhaps.
But he's got something else here.
This is one of these camp oil still oil
lengths, and I got the instructions and I
say, Bill, you got to read the instructions
first because you know, something dangerous
could happen. Like that, I hear something I
thought was really interesting.
They could penknife you, open up the blade
there and you stick a candle on there and you
stick it into a tree and you set up a bunch
of these through the forest and you make
yourself a little path or a little campsite
at night is fantastic.
Oh, bill bill ow
Ow ow ow ow ow ow.
Oh, very good balance for older fellow and
surprise his breath, put that out.
All right. This is kind of a gas propane
pressurized with the wick in there and is
though gas is down to me, I would have
thought, you know, what you want to do is
light the match first and then and then, you
know, during the gas, well, you know, that's
that's me. That's me.
That's not Bill. That's not Bill's way.
And oh what? Oh, oh, oh oh, oh oh.
Yeah. Oh.
Now where he buys his matches, but he had
the waterproof matches in a separate
container, but the name of the bill, he
doesn't keep things very long.
I don't know why that is. Hopefully he's got
yeah, he had a lighter one, a little flicking
lighters thing or that gold belt.
Another one, yeah. All right.
Just go for a guy who doesn't smoke, he
carries a lot of firepower and he's going to
light this up and. Wow.
That's a good look for you, Bill.
The Arnold Schwarzenegger The Terminator.
Oh, well, we got a laugh out of it, Harold
tells me.
There's a lot of young people watch the
show, and he wanted to do something just for
you. Lucky you.
Hello and welcome to.
Welcome to what is with that cheesy music.
Oh oh, oh oh.
Welcome to what's wrong with those goofy
adults.
This is a part of the show that's aimed at
the younger generation.
The cool people missed that part of the
show.
We get to tell our parents and their
teachers in that really smelly guys, you a
kid, what really ticks us off, you know,
things like cheesy music or or homework or
cauliflower or, you know, getting a cardigan
for your birthday or, oh, wow.
Oh, you know. You know, what's the worst
when you've got to sit around the house and
the whole family sits there and tries to
figure out who you look like the most, right?
Not being able to wear your clothes
backwards.
People saying how handsome you're going to
be when your skin clears up.
Please stop hating life, right?
So this is our opportunity to say, well, no.
Or having your show canceled after the first
episode.
You still got that headache, do you, uncle
read?
That's a yes.
I figured Reg Thunder could help us with the
trees in the syrup because he's a vegetarian
reg, I want to ask you, is the sap any good?
Oh, that's the best part.
The sap is the blood of the tree.
It's got everything good and it comes in a
liquid concentrate.
So that's why trees can grow hundreds of
feet high and people can't get the whole.
Oh, oh, yes.
Yes. It must have been doing the.
Oh, you know, Reg, I think I'm just going to
stay behind you here.
What exactly are we hunting today, you know,
just so our viewers will know.
Oh, we're hunting an animal.
It makes this sound.
Oh, no idea what that is, right?
Neither do I, but I bet I can put a bullet in
it.
Wow, it was unfortunate the sugaring often
didn't really go so well.
There's a major understatement.
Well, the first part went OK, and we hooked
Junior's pump up to about 50 trees and then
we switched it on in about 15 seconds.
That sucked them all dry.
Forty foot oak trees imploding.
You have seen it. You don't look like you
look so cool.
No, look, it looked like the wicked witch of
the West in The Wizard of Oz, you know, I
think. I'll get you on your little dog, too.
Oh, you bet.
Oh. Oh.
If he only had a brain.
Anyway, it was really something to see
full-Grown birch trees shrinking right back
down to saplings and even the even the
leaves were kind of curling up and rolling up
the branches.
But the worst part? Oh no, no.
Let me say the worst part was worse.
For worse part was like the noise.
It was amazing.
Sounded like God flushed every toilet in
heaven all at once.
Now how would you know that, Harold?
Have you ever heard all of the toilets and
having a flash at the same time?
No. Well, if you keep interrupting, you
will.
Sorry. All right.
As I was saying, the worst part was the
sound, it sounded like a big noise or some
kind heavenly toilet thing, I guess.
And and then the roots, the roots, the roots
came up through the right through the ground
and they shriveled up and they started
rolling out and they went down through the
hoses and into the pump.
And I'll tell you, we would have been real
scared if we weren't laughing so hard.
Boy, was the fire the possum that's meeting
time for I'm going to go, Harold.
Yes, telling guys at the pancake branches on
hold.
I would think so.
Well, you know, I think we have all learned a
life lesson this week, which is never connect
a used Russian rocket fuel pump to a large
deciduous tree.
And if my wife is watching, you know, I
think maybe you should embroider that little
snippet of wisdom onto one of them samplers,
and we'll hang that in the cube over there.
Look kind of nice, actually.
I'll be coming home straight after the
meeting and I can help you spell deciduous.
There's at least one in and the rest of you
on behalf of myself and Harold and the whole
gang up here at Possum Lodge.
Thanks for watching and keep your stick on
the ice.
Very exciting to me, but I need everybody's
help here to rebuild the parks and.