It's the new Red Green Show.
And now here's the man you've been
waiting for. Not Godot.
More like God, no. You're here
and my uncle Red Green.
All right. You know, I golly, thanks for
coming big kerfuffle this week up with the
lines over the old man Sedgwick's Place
turned out his son showed up right on his
front doorstep.
Wow, I didn't even know old man Sedgwick had
a son.
No, neither did he, Harold.
You know, you get old, you forget things,
you don't forget his son, nobody forgets a
son. I'm trying to forget a nephew.
Wow.
Anyway, causing real problems over an old
man, Sedgwick's place that son there being
around is really putting a lot of strain on
the old guy.
How old is he, exactly?
Don't know for sure. Harold, our our best
guess is he's about ninety seven.
Wow.
How old are you, son? I'm talking about his
son.
What you're looking at
Now is a bunch of segments from this
Particular show.
The main message being, for gosh sakes,
don't even think about changing the channel.
I'll tell you something you want to make
sense out of this program.
You've got to give it your undivided
attention.
I'll tell you, you don't want to go anywhere
near old man Sedgwick's Place now that his
son has moved back in.
Talk about two old crappy guys and walk them
by the yell, Hey dork!
Pick a gender.
Boy, that's that's cruel.
And speaking of cruel,
Here's a little taste of what we got later in
the show when The Adventures with Bill.
Actually, this is more than a little taste,
and that may be that may be a mistake because
with Bill, you know, a lot of times a little
taste is all you ever want, right, bill?
Bill, Oh, I rest my case and most of my
adult body.
Anyway, what this is is kind of a certain
life as a circus.
And there you go, Bill.
And I thought this wasn't going to be any
fun.
Oh. Anyway, as I was saying before, a little
bit of a circus thing.
Bill wants me to climb up the ladder.
He's going to do that kind of a flying,
flying Wallenda thing.
He's going to go up, I'm going to go down,
then I'm going to catch him.
That's the way that's going to work. Yeah,
that's the plan.
Anyway, that is the plan.
And, you know, all plans go.
Anyway, I did my work perfectly, but that
was just I.
Now I might. I say, Bill's a little heavy
and we got to relieve the tension on the
board. Well, here's why you're OK.
This is kind of a quick weight lamp.
Why you got a lot of stuff in the air.
Imagine him going through the metal
detector.
Holy mackerel, man.
That's a that's easy. He's really,
Really packing iron.
What the heck was that?
It's a power saw.
It's a flexible hose on there.
That's a valve. A caulking gun.
They're still nothing.
So I should don't forget one thing a little
washer.
Here goes. Oh, boy, he's up there.
I'll get you, Bill, I'll get you, I'll get
you.
Yeah, I lost you in the Sun bill.
That's all that was. More on that later.
Oh, I had one whisker on the end of my
nose.
And the more I shave it, the more it grows.
I waxed and scratched it till it was 14
inches long, and then it was hit by lightning
and I was forced to rethink the whole
project.
Ok, this is for the big one.
Two hundred road apples and a free juicer.
Uncle Red, you have 30 seconds.
Get Mr. Dalton Humphries of the Humphreys
Everything store to say this word.
Laugh.
And go.
All right, Dalton, when your wife tells a
joke, you cringe.
When I tell a joke, you don't get it.
All right, all right, at the circus, the
clowns make us angry.
All right. Somebody comes into your store
and they ask you for a discount.
You'll go along with it, you know, you shake
hands, you smile and you have a good
discount.
Don't make me laugh.
This week on Handymen Corner, I thought I
would do something for all of you people
who've always wanted to join the volunteer
fire department but never have.
Maybe you don't have time.
Maybe you can't pass a physical.
Or maybe you just don't want to spend your
weekends with the kinds of losers that are
attracted to that type of hobby.
Maybe there's a better way instead of trying
to turn normal citizens into firemen?
How about trying to turn a normal car into a
fire truck?
Aren't we all thrilled to see a fire truck
roaring down the street, whipping by you on
the way to a blaze that you never started on
purpose?
I mean, wasn't my fault.
I think electrical appliances have got to
have better warnings on them.
Yeah. Ok, now first thing in any fire trucks
going to have is an axe, a shovel and a pick.
All right now in a fire truck, I have all
this stuff on the other side so the
firefighters can get to it in emergency
like, say, a fire.
Well, we can do the same thing.
What you want to do is take a drill and
drill holes in your trunk larger than the
diameter of the handles. Then they'll be
sticking right out there for you to get away.
Let's start drilling. And don't worry about
any damage here, anything goes, we're going
to beat this whole baby fire engine red.
Perfect. Now you notice how the fire trucks
have lots of flashing lights.
Well, so do you.
They're all hanging on your eavesdrop
because you never took them down.
Right? Well, go pull them down and hook them
up with an extension cord because any fire
that's farther away than the length of my
extension cord is probably none of my
business. All right now you want to hook
them on there, or you could use metal clips
on that or any of the plastic fasteners or,
of course, the handy man secret weapon
duct tape.
All right now, fire trucks have
sirens, and of course, your horn is a good
start there. But I'll tell you for that
little extra noise, what you want to do is
loosen off your alternator belt and your fan
belt and your power steering just a little
bit. Then when you start it up, everybody
will hear you coming.
Fact even punch a few holes in the muffler
if you want.
Now everybody knows it.
Fire trucks have hoses.
So what you can do? Get yourself a bunch of
these hoses on rails like this and get about
the hardware store. Or you can just borrow
on somebody when they're not around.
Attach them on here with bolts or weld them
right on there or.
That's right. And don't worry if they don't
match because we're going to paint this whole
thing a beautiful fire engine red.
I want to take one end of your hoses and
hook them right into your water pump so you
don't just have a fire truck here.
You got a pumper truck.
Of course, every fire truck has to have a
ladder, a ladder that will go in any
direction because fire happens in any
direction and you may park in any direction.
So what you need for that is some kind of a
rotating platform with an axle down through
the center of it. Easy to do.
You want to make sure nobody's sitting in
the car when you do this.
And there we got a ladder where you can
fight fires in two directions at the same
time. And she goes up and down just like the
units do on the real fire trucks and at a
fraction of the cost.
All right, a couple of final details here.
You want to get some buckets of sand here
hanging off the front, a little bit of water
here and you got your emergency oxygen unit
here because you want to empty the propane
out of that, put the oxygen in.
I'm not quite sure how you do that, but I'm
guessing it's important.
You got your smoke detectors on here and let
you know when you're getting real close to
the fire. So we're basically ready for any
arsonist.
I'm not sure what an arsonist is, but it
sounds like the kind of thing we have plenty
of up here at the Lodge.
Oh my gosh, a fire.
All right. Like in our lives here.
And they shot better to make fire and away
we go.
Maybe I shouldn't have disconnected the
water pump fire.
Remember, women don't find it handsome, they
should at least find your handy.
And don't worry about the black color here.
I'm going to paint the whole thing a
beautiful fire engine red.
Yup, she’s out.
Stay tuned and relax whatever this is
we got lots more of it.
I want to talk to you, ladies, to help you
understand why we men do some of the things
we do like, for example, how we fix
everything with duct tape like, say, putting
the mirror back on the car.
Now, a lot of people would take the car to a
garage and an hour and 60 bucks later, it
would be fixed properly and look real good.
Whereas your handyman takes 10 minutes and
seven cents worth of duct tape and it looks
butt-ugly. But let's take a look at the
reasoning behind the actions.
What car are we talking about here?
Is this an 81 Cordoba with four hundred
thousand miles on it and a real bad cough?
Why would you spend 60 bucks on a car that
you can replace for 50?
And why take an hour to fix something that
can be done in 10 minutes?
If you put four hundred thousand miles on
her, you don't owe it any more of your time.
And what's the big deal about fixing
something?
Putting the right back into original quality
just makes the rest of the car look bad.
Nothing worse than a repair job that outlast
the vehicle.
So I would suggest that you ladies, instead
of criticizing your husband for slapping on
the duct tape, why don't you compliment him
for his brainpower?
Realize this. He now has 50 minutes on his
hands and an extra 60 bucks in his pocket.
Remember, I'm pulling for you.
We're all in this together.
Ok, so old man, Sedgwick Son has moved back
in with him, and you can tell by the broken
furniture out on the front lawn and the duct
tape that got divided in the rooms exactly in
half that things are really not going all
that well.
Now you tell me, what is the worst thing
that could happen out of that scenario?
Well, they
Could be heating their cabin with a high
sulfur coal.
And then meanwhile, on top of the wood
stove, both men are rinsing their teeth in
the same pewter jar, right?
And that would create the symbiotic
hydrolysis, right?
And then there'd be a thermal inversion,
right?
And then all of sudden, the sulfur ions that
have to collide with the dental plaque,
right? Not an accelerate the electron to the
point.
Would it be this massive nuclear reaction?
It wouldn't kill him. Oh, no, it wouldn't
kill them, Uncle Brad, but enthusiastic
wouldn't render them absolutely sterile for
the rest of their lives.
I'm writing an episode of The Outer Limits.
Harold, you are an episode of The Outer
Limits.
No, the worst thing that could happen is, Oh
man, Cedric's not getting along with his son,
so he's moved out of his cabin and he's
moving into the lodge.
What? Yeah, no.
Yeah. Oh no.
How can we do that? This is like one hundred
and twenty five year old lodge.
He has to have the permission of the
membership, right?
No, not all, man says.
He said it was part of the deal when he
helped build the place.
This is awful. This is terrible.
You got to do something, uncle. I'm
surprised you're taking this the way you are.
Well, he's not staying in my room.
A poem by Dylan Thomas Greene, the force
sent through the green fuse, drives the
flower, drives my green age that blasts the
roots of trees is my destroyer.
But this forest cannot wreak the damage of a
six pack in a bucket of curly fries.
Plus, a nine one one, thanks for calling
state your membership card number
Seven six five three four eight.
That's Ducky Franklin's number one.
What's the trouble there, Dougie? Great.
I'm all alone house.
Well, this sounds serious.
You roll the monster truck there, Dougie.
You pinned in the cab again.
It's my mom. She's she's out of town for a
week, Brad.
His mom's out of town for a week.
I don't get it.
I do. Harold, when's the last time
you ate proper food, Dougie?
I don't know how good snacks.
I ate a jar of olives, Red.
Ok, Dougie, what room are you in right now?
I don't know. I don't recognize a thing.
All right, Dougie. That'll be the kitchen.
You want to go to the
cupboard that has all the cooking supplies in
it, the what?
The cupboard?
What's that?
It's like the stove or the dishwasher without
all the controls.
What's that? Well, it's like the washing
machine or the clothes dryer.
Oh, for
Pete's sake, speak English, will you?
All right, Dougie, where do you keep your beer?
Oh, the fridge.
Yeah.
Red, everything's going dark.
Now, now take it easy, Dougie.
This is Red speaking to you.
Look on the fridge door.
Yeah, see a lot of magnets there.
Yeah, huh?
Paper Yeah.
Pieces Smurfs.
Oh, OK.
And one of those is going to have a phone
number on it.
Yeah, you want to call that number?
Crawl over to the door and wait in half an
hour.
You'll have a pizza.
Oh, thank you, Red.
I can't believe my own mother would try to
kill me.
Well, here we are back with adventures, with
Bill, we've been practicing all the time, we
were away and we got some real special
stuff.
And I thought I wouldn't enjoy this, but what Bill
is going to do is try to create a plan and
that chair on top of the shed there.
And I just, you know, suddenly, you know,
attitude is so much, so much a part of life.
And I'm thinking, Oh my gosh, you know, I
just go with it and have some fun with it,
you know, jump on the board and let go and
just, you know, we go, we go, Oh boy, I love
a circus, you know? Gosh, my gosh.
All right. Little change. A plan now is
going to actually start in the chair and then
flip the both of them up onto the roof that
way.
That sounds very sensible to me.
And yes, going, oh my gosh, seem to have
gone horribly wrong.
Oh well, I'll just take it out of the way
and just clean up a little bit.
Oh, there's a chair I can just
I'll just relax for a second and wait for a
bill.
I'm sure they'll be here shortly.
There he is now.
I'll tell you one thing about Bill.
He never, ever hurts himself.
Hardly, ever.
Here's a duct tape dispenser that fits right
on your belt sent to us by a viewer
I hold your horses.
Old man Cedric. Bedridden. Which is a
normal thing for the lodge, but he's actually
not feeling well. Well, he's got the bunch
of us running around getting some lemon,
herbal, chamomile tea and rubber things with
fluid in them.
And, of course, the Sports Illustrated
Swimsuit Edition and his latest request is
for half a dozen bran muffins here.
Yeah, yeah.
Harold’s just getting a plate.
Yeah.
Uncle Red, I couldn't find a clean plate
anywhere, so I just stole the hubcap off the
possum van. Oh baby, it’s really
stuck on there too.
You shouldn’t have taken
the one off the driver's side front.
If I have that tire off every couple of
weeks.
Well, why is that?
That's the wheel I hit stuff with.
Anyway, take these up to Old Man Cedric
Good enough.
Not too polite taking muffins up
in a hubcap, is it?
No, I was going to serve them in a
bedpan.
Skip the middleman. And you tell him if he
eats all them up, you can come down and get
them some more.
Well, he eats all these up.
I'm not going anywhere near him.
Welcome to the expert portion of the show
where we examine those three little words
that men find so hard to say.
(audience) I don’t know
Ok, excellent. And joining me and Red now on
the expert portion of the show this week is his
best friend in the whole wide room, local
roofer Arnie Dogan.
Today's letter goes as follows:
Dear experts,
I enjoy extreme sports like shark wrestling
and taking the last doughnut at bingo.
But my girlfriend is afraid I'll kill myself
in a way that will void my car insurance and
my life insurance and my dental plan.
I love taking risks, but I don't want to
lose her.
What should I do?
Well bud, I would go with the girlfriend on
this one.
I'll tell you right now, you know, life is
short enough.
You don't want to be accelerating the
process in any way.
Oh, sorry, Red. I don't see it that way.
You got to take chances.
I mean, like we say in the roof, in
business, if you don't go to the edge, she's
going to leak,
All right.
And then you'll end up with ice buildup.
Ok, that’s uh...
And it'll sag and smell funny.
I mean, if I didn't take chances, I wouldn't
be sitting here today.
Oh, that's right, Arnie. You'd be at work.
Oh, you mean this? No. I'll be back at work
soon as a cast off and they removed that.
That extra foot of eavesdropping.
I can't believe you're going back to
roofing, Mr Dogan, after that accident.
Oh, roofing is in my blood,
Harold, and vice versa.
Stuff happens. They read, my dad was a roofer
and so was his dad.
Grandpa Dogan started Dogan and Son's
Roofing back in 1938, when
some woman's husband come home early for
some grandpa to slide out her bedroom window
and pretend he was replacing shingles.
Wow! Can't be much of a business.
You spent more on medical care than you ever
made on roofing.
Yeah, well, you got to have something on the
side, right?
Yeah. You know, my grandpa always had
something on the side.
So do I. Country music?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's right.
I've written over seventeen thousand songs,
You know, really, I think we should just
concentrate on answering this letter about
extreme sports.
Well, that's what I'm doing. You think so?
I'm saying. Pursue your dreams.
If I didn't pursue my dreams, Harold, how
could I have written this?
All right. Yeah.
I loved her on the rooftop, but she didn't
like my flashing.
She threw my heart in the downspouts and now
I drink a lot.
And drive trucks.
I wrote that one last week in the recovery
room.
Well, next time away from the anesthetic to
wear off, you know, every once in a while, I
You know, every once in a while,
I come up with an idea that makes just so much
sense.
It's irresistible.
You're quitting television.
Did I say that out loud?
I'm talking about old man Cedric.
We had him laid up here in the lodge and got
a son living in his cabin didn't want any
part of him. So I'm thinking to myself, Hey,
who are the most obvious people to look after
old man Cedric?
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I
know who it is, who the Victorian order of
Who?
The Victorian order of nurses.
Yeah, that'd be great because
they're all well trained.
They're all very personal. They've got their
own cars.
They've got these really cool crafts right
there in the door, right in the door.
And they're all ladies.
He might even meet somebody who can meet
somebody.
No, Harold. No, no.
I'm talking about Old Man Cedric’s
parents.
I think his mother's name is Old
Lady Cedrick
and his dad is ‘Dead Man Walking Cedric’.
He's got parents, and they're still alive?
How old are they?
Well, they're they're old.
She has a tattoo, says George Washington.
Slept here, but you know, I talked to them.
I had to yell, but I did talk to them and
they weren't interested in doing it.
So I went back to his son and I said, Hey,
listen, you know, you've got to look after
your old man who is an old man.
In fact, his name is even old man.
And the thought of that much responsibility
scared him so bad.
He took off, went back where he came from.
So everybody wins.
Like, Oh man, Cedric is moving back to
his cabin.
Absolutely, that means I get my room back
right.
Oh, excellent.
Yeah. You know, Harold, you might want to
wait till the bed dries.
That's a good point.
Meeting time. Meeting time.
Sound of the possum.
You go ahead, Harold.
I'll be down in a minute.
My wife is watching. I'll be coming straight
home after the meeting.
And you know all this talk old man says
you're going to son and everything.
That kind of thing about maybe having a son
of our own.
But then I take a look at Harold and the
whole idea just...
Thanks for watching on behalf of myself
and Harold and the whole gang out here
at Possum Lodge
Keep your stick on the ice.