THAN TRIMMING
THE OLD CHRISTMAS TREE.
BUT AFTER THE HOLIDAYS
HAVE GONE BY 40 OR 50 TIMES,
IT'S REALLY HARD
TO GET UP FOR IT
WITHOUT LARGE
QUANTITIES OF ALCOHOL.
BUT AS EVERY HANDYMAN KNOWS,
THERE ARE TWO
WAYS TO DO ANYTHING...
THE RIGHT WAY,
AND THE QUICK WAY.
MAN, I AM SO CLEVER.
AND NOW, QUICKER THAN
YOU CAN SAY O, TANNENBAUM --
OR ASK SOMEBODY WHAT
THE HECK IT MEANS,
YOU'VE DECKED YOUR HALLS.
HO, HO, HO.
OH! OH! OH!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YEAH.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE THAT.
ALL THE BEST
OF THE HOLIDAY SEASON.
DON'T BURN YOURSELF
ON YOUR CREDIT CARD.
I'M PRETTY EXCITED COZ I GOT A
GREAT CHRISTMAS GIFT FOR HAROLD.
HAROLD'S NOT JUST
HARD TO BUY FOR.
HE'S HARD TO WANT
TO BUY FOR.
[ CHUCKLES ]
BUT HE'S DRIVING UP
TO HIS PARENTS' PLACE,
AND HE'S SO USELESS
ON DIRECTIONS
THAT I GOT HIM ONE OF THESE
TALKING NAVIGATIONAL SYSTEMS.
I PROGRAMMED IN
THE DESTINATION.
LISTEN TO THIS...
robotic voice:
GO NORTH ON #4 SIDE ROAD
12.7 KILOMETERS --
[ CHUCKLES ]
I GOT A REAL DEAL
ON THIS BABY.
NO BOX, NO WARRANTY,
NO STORE.
I BOUGHT IT FROM MIKE.
YEAH, THE PRICE WAS RIGHT.
WHEN THE COPS WENT BY,
HE CUT THAT IN HALF.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GIVE
THIS TO HAROLD.
UNCLE RED! UNCLE RED!
YEAH, YEAH, HAROLD,
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I CAN'T WAIT TO GIVE
YOU THIS GIFT.
HERE YOU GO.
YEAH, BUT IT'S
NOT CHRISTMAS YET.
I KNOW, BUT THIS
IS SOMETHING YOU CAN
START USING RIGHT NOW.
OH, OKAY!
OKAY. OKAY. OKAY.
WELL,
HERE'S YOUR GIFT.
IT'S SOMETHING YOU CAN
USE RIGHT AWAY AS WELL.
OH, GREAT.
FANTASTIC!
HOLY MACKEREL!
LOOK AT THE SIZE OF THE
INSTRUCTION MANUAL.
[ unenthusiastic ]
OH, IT'S A BOOK.
BUT NOT JUST
ANY BOOK.
LOOK AT THE TITLE.
"THE BUTTER MAN"?
"THE BETTER MAN."
OH.
IT'S TO HELP YOU CREATE
STABILITY IN YOUR LIFE.
OH, GREAT, GREAT.
GREAT.
OH! OH!
YEAH.
OH, LOOKIT!
I'VE WANTED ONE
OF THESE FOR SO LONG!
OH -- WHAT IS THAT?
JUST PUSH THE
RED BUTTON, HAROLD.
THE RED BUTTON?
robotic voice:
QUACK!
NO, NO,
TRY IT AGAIN.
OH.
robotic voice:
QUACK!
GIMME THAT.
OKAY.
robotic voice:
QUACK!
QUACK! QUACK! QUACK!
[ QUACKING CONTINUES ]
YOU MIGHT WANNA START
WITH CHAPTER 4...
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
IT'S TIME FOR THE
POSSUM LODGE WORD GAME!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TODAY'S WINNER
RECEIVES THIS COUPON
FOR A FREE BOX OF
TINSEL FROM TINSEL TOWN.
THE ONLY STORE THAT
SELLS ONLY TINSEL
ALL YEAR ROUND.
DON'T FORGET
OUR TINSEL SLOGAN...
"HOW'S IT HANGIN'?"
OKAY, ED,
COVER YOUR EARS.
MR. GREEN, YOU'VE GOT
30 SECONDS TO GET ED FRID
TO SAY THIS WORD...
YEAH,
ALL RIGHT, MIKE.
AND... GO!
UH, OKAY, ED,
YOU FIND THIS UNDER THE TREE.
SQUIRREL DROPPINGS.
NO, NO, NO, YOU FIND THIS
UNDER THE CHRISTMAS TREE
ON CHRISTMAS MORNING.
AUNT HELEN.
NO, OKAY, OKAY, ED,
WHAT DO YOU ALWAYS
GET AT CHRISTMAS?
OH, HIVES.
OKAY, NO, UM...
THIS IS RED AND GREEN
IN COLOUR AND HAS A BOW.
ROBIN HOOD?
NO, UH -- OKAY,
WHEN YOU GO
SHOPPING AT THE MALL,
WHAT DO YOU GET?
BORED.
UM, ED,
REMEMBER A YEAR AGO?
WHAT WAS YOUR GIRLFRIEND
HIDING FROM YOU?
HER OTHER BOYFRIENDS.
AHEM, WE'RE ALMOST
OUTTA TIME, MR. GREEN.
YEAH. OKAY. OKAY.
ED, REMEMBER WHEN YOU
WERE A KID AT CHRISTMAS?
ALL YOU WANTED TO KNOW IS,
WHEN ARE WE OPENING THE...
CAGES!
NO, NO, I MEAN YOU'D COME DOWN
ON CHRISTMAS MORNING,
YOUR EYES WOULD BE
WIDE OPEN AND YOU'D SAY,
WOW! LOOK AT ALL THE...
RATS!
FROM THE CAGES.
AND I COULD REALLY YELL.
MY VOICE HAD A LOT OF PRESENCE.
THERE WE GO!
♪ COMES DOWN THE CHIMNEY
ON CHRISTMAS EVE ♪
♪ AFTER WE'VE
ALL GONE TO BED ♪
♪ HE'S NOT ALL THAT
NICE OR JOLLY ♪
♪ UNTIL AFTER
HE'S BEEN FED ♪
♪ HE'S GOT BEADY EYES
AND YELLOW TEETH ♪
♪ AND HIS FUR DROPS OFF
WHEN HE MOLTS ♪
♪ HIS TAIL KINDA WIGGLES
AND DANCES AND JIGGLES ♪
♪ LIKE A SNAKE
TAKIN' 300 VOLTS ♪
♪ HE'S CHEESY
♪ CHEESY
♪ THE CHRISTMAS RAT
♪ LONG AND SMELLY
AND PRETTY DARNED FAT ♪
♪ CHEESY
♪ THE CHRISTMAS RAT
♪ DROPPING A LITTLE
SURPRISE IN YOUR HAT ♪
♪ IT COMES WITH A GIFT,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BEG ♪
♪ HE HERE TO GIVE EVERYONE
BUBONIC PLAGUE ♪
♪ CHEESY
♪ THE CHRISTMAS RAT
♪ AND THAT'S WHY EVERYBODY
SHOULD HAVE A GUN! ♪
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW, CHRISTMAS IS A
TIME OF PEACE ON EARTH
AND GOODWILL TO MEN,
BUT NOTHING WRECKS
THAT FASTER
THAN GETTING SURPRISED
WITH A CRAPPY GIFT.
OKAY, YOU EXPECT
A FEW CRAPPY GIFTS.
THAT'S WHAT
GRANDPARENTS ARE FOR.
BUT IT'S THE SURPRISE
THAT'LL KILL YOU.
SO IN KEEPING WITH
THE CHRISTMAS SPIRIT.
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU HOW
TO IDENTIFY THE DUDS
LONG BEFORE YOU OPEN THEM.
THAT GIVES YOU TIME TO
REHEARSE A BIG FAKE SMILE
ON THE OFF CHANCE THAT THE GIFT
IS FROM A WEALTHY RELATIVE
WHO SENSES YOUR DISAPPOINTMENT
AS YOU HURL IT OUT THE WINDOW,
PUTTING THEIR NOSE
OUT OF JOINT,
AND YOUR NAME
OUTTA THE WILL.
NOW, I KNOW YOU'VE
ALL TRIED THIS ONE...
SHAKING IS FOR AMATEURS;
YOU'RE A PROFESSIONAL.
WE HAVE A GIFT EMERGENCY!
IS THERE A DOCTOR
IN THE HOUSE?
BIG BREATH AND HOLD.
OKAY, IF IT DOESN'T SHAKE
AT ALL, IT'S CLOTHING.
BIG TROUBLE BECAUSE NOBODY
EVER BUYS YOU THE RIGHT SIZE.
MAINLY BECAUSE YOU LIE
ABOUT YOUR SIZE.
EVEN IF IT DOES SHAKE,
DON'T BE FOOLED.
IT COULD BE A CARDIGAN
WITH A ROCK IN THE POCKET.
TIME TO TAKE HER
TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
NOW YOU WANNA CHECK THE OPAQUE,
TRANSLUCENT TRANSPARENCY
QUOTIENT OF THE ITEM.
SIX SEALED BEAM HEADLIGHTS
AT CLOSE RANGE
ROUGHLY APPROXIMATES THE
INTENSITY OF THE SUN.
WHAT YOU'RE HOPIN' FOR
IS A DARK SHAPE IN THERE.
IF IT LETS LIGHT THROUGH
IT'S A WEAVE,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT
THAT MEANS...
CLOTHING.
DON'T GO HALFWAY.
USE YOUR HIGH BEAMS.
STILL DON'T KNOW?
IT'S TIME TO DO
SOMETHING TO THE GIFT
THAT YOU WOULD
NEVER DO TO YOURSELF...
WEIGH IT.
IF IT WEIGHS A LOT
FOR ITS SIZE,
THAT'S A REALLY GOOD SIGN.
NYLON AND DACRON
AREN'T HEAVY.
BUT IF IT'S GOT
SOME HEFT TO IT,
THAT'S GOTTA
BE GOOD NEWS,
WHICH THIS GIFT DOES.
THIS IS GETTING EXCITING.
NOW WE TRY THE MAGNET.
THAT'S ANOTHER GOOD SIGN.
UNLESS IT'S A PAIR OF PANTS
WITH A REALLY HUGE FLY.
BUT THAT'S A WHOLE DIFFERENT
KIND OF COMPLIMENT.
NOW WE HAVE TO TEST THE
RESISTANCE TO COMPRESSION.
SEE, A SPORTS JACKET CAN BE
SQUISHED INTO A BERET.
BUT A PORTABLE
MAGELLAN ROADMATE 700...
ROCK SOLID.
WHAT YOU'RE LISTENING FOR
IS ANY KIND OF FAINT
CRACKING OR SPLINTERING.
IF YOU HEAR EITHER
ONE OF THOSE,
YOU CAN BE SURE
YOU'VE JUST MADE THE GIFT
VERY DIFFICULT TO RETURN.
MAN, IT WAS A LAPTOP!
I DON'T WANT
A LAPTOP.
WHO WOULD BUY
ME A LAPTOP?
"TO HAROLD"?
BOY, THAT WAS CLOSE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I WANNA TALK TO YOU
OLDER FELLAS FOR A MINUTE
ABOUT YOUR CHRISTMAS SPIRIT.
REMEMBER WHEN
YOU HAD SOME?
BACK WHEN YOU WERE A KID,
CHRISTMAS WAS THE
BEST TIME OF THE YEAR.
NO SCHOOL, FREE STUFF
AND A FAT GUY FALLING
DOWN A CHIMNEY.
WHAT'S NOT TO LIKE?
BUT THEN AS YOU GOT OLDER,
THAT EXCITEMENT STARTED
TO FADE, DIDN'T IT?
YOU USED TO LOVE WATCHING
"IT'S A WONDERFUL LIFE."
THEN YOU
JUST GOT SICK OF IT.
THEN YOU STARTED
WATCHING IT AGAIN,
EXCEPT THIS TIME YOU FOUND
YOURSELF ROOTIN' FOR
OLD MAN POTTER.
OF COURSE IT'S NO SURPRISE
THAT CHRISTMAS GETS
LESS EXCITING FOR A
MIDDLE AGED GUY.
BY THE END OF THE DAY
YOUR WIFE IS CRANKY
FROM OVER WORK;
THE TREE IS DRY
FROM UNDER WATERING;
AND THE KIDS
ARE ON A SUGAR BUZZ
THAT WON'T LET UP
'TIL GROUNDHOG DAY.
HERE'S THE THING...
JUST COZ YOU'RE
STRESSED OUT,
THAT'S NO EXCUSE FOR RUINING
EVERYBODY ELSE'S CHRISTMAS.
SO I WANT YOU TO
FOCUS ON THE GOOD STUFF...
YOUR FAMILY LOVES YOU;
YOU'VE BEEN BLESSED
WITH SAFETY AND COMFORT;
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
WHEN YOU WAKE UP TOMORROW,
YOU'LL BE AS FAR AWAY
FROM NEXT CHRISTMAS
AS YOU'RE GONNA
GET ALL YEAR.
REMEMBER,
I'M PULLIN' FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
IF SOMETHING'S COMING DOWN
YOUR CHIMNEY AND IT
AIN'T SANTA,
CALL ME.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I WANT TO SAY A FEW WORDS TO
THE YULETIDE POLLYANNA'S
OUT THERE.
OH, NOW DON'T GET ME WRONG.
YOU KNOW, AS A STORE OWNER
I'M A BIG FAN OF CHRISTMAS.
I JUST HAVE A SLIGHT PROBLEM
WITH ALL THOSE PEOPLE
WHO FEEL THAT EVERYBODY SHOULD
PUT ON A HAPPY FACE.
I DON'T HAVE A HAPPY FACE.
IT'S NOT THAT
I'M NOT HAPPY.
I'M COPING.
YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T
SMILE AT MY WEDDING.
THAT DIDN'T MEAN
I WAS UPSET.
I'M SURE AT THE TIME
MARRYING ANNE MARIE
SEEMED LIKE A FINE IDEA.
SO DON'T EXPECT ME
TO GET ALL GIDDY
JUST BECAUSE IT'S -- IT'S
CHRISTMAS, YOU KNOW.
THOSE PEOPLE WITH THEIR BIG,
PHONY HAPPY FACES
ARE JUST
EXTREMELY ANNOYING.
YOU KNOW, AND AS FAR AS I'M
CONCERNED, THOSE CAROLERS,
THEY'RE JUST
ASKING FOR IT.
SO THIS CHRISTMAS,
LET'S ALL JUST
BACK OFF A NOTCH, SHALL WE?
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, I'VE GOT
HAROLD'S NAVIGATIONAL
DEVICE WORKING LIKE A CHARM.
HE MUST HAVE BEEN
PRESSING THE WRONG BUTTON.
CHECK THIS OUT.
robotic voice: YOU ARE
APPROACHING DEAD MAN'S CURVE.
UNCLE RED!
YEP?
I FOUND YOUR BOOK
IN THE OUTHOUSE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS
THE PERFECT SPOT FOR IT.
OH NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
STAPLES.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK YOU
HAVE THE CHRISTMAS SPIRIT.
I SURE DO.
IN FACT, I'M OFFERING YOU
THE POSSUM VAN TO DRIVE UP
TO YOUR PARENTS' PLACE.
OH, NO, NO, NO, THANKS.
I'M RENTING A CAR.
YEAH, BUT I'M TRYING
TO SAVE YOU A FEW
DOLLARS HERE.
YES, BUT I WANT
TO GET THERE.
AND YOU WILL,
HAROLD,
WITH THE
NAVIGATIONAL WIZARD.
HERE. PRESS THE RED
BUTTON THIS TIME.
robotic voice:
YOU ARE A DEAD MAN.
[ LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE ]
Red: WELL, HAROLD AND WALTER
HAD PUT A NICE LITTLE
CHRISTMAS DISPLAY
WITH THE REINDEER
AND THE SLEIGH.
JUST WAITING FOR BILL TO
COME ON AND SEE WHAT HE
THOUGHT OF IT.
HMM.
I DON'T THINK HE NOTICED.
I DON'T THINK HE DID
THAT ON PURPOSE.
AND WHEN THEY POINTED IT OUT
TO HIM HE FELT REAL BAD.
REAL -- OH MY GOODNESS.
YOU KILLED SANTA.
SO HE'S AN IDEA, THOUGH.
HE HANDS HIM THE EXTENSION
CORD AND HE'S GONNA --
I THINK --
YOU KNOW, BILL'S
NOT A BAD GUY.
HE WOULD TRY TO --
TRY TO REPLACE WHAT HE'D --
HE HAS A WASHING MACHINE.
I DON'T QUITE UNDER--
BUT BILL'S --
OH, THERE GOES SANTA AGAIN.
SO, UH, BILL HOPS OUT,
AND I DON'T QUITE KNOW
WHAT HE'S GOT IN MIND HERE.
WALTER'S POINTING OUT
ABOUT THE SANTA AND SO ON.
BILL -- OH, I SEE.
HE BROUGHT SOME
CHRISTMAS LIGHTS.
THEY'RE A LITTLE TANGLED,
BUT UH, HAROLD'S VERY, VERY
GOOD WITH UNTANGLING.
WOW. UNBELIEVABLE.
SO THAT'S A LITTLE HEAVIER
THAN SHE LOOKS THERE, BILL.
I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE GONNA --
NO, NO, BILL,
DON'T BE DOING THAT.
AND BILL REMEMBERS HE'S
GOT THE BIG STRING --
UH, THE BIG SPRING ON
THE HOOD RELEASE AND --
OH, LOOK OUT!
OH, OH!
SO, SANTA TOOK
THE HIT AGAIN.
WALTER DUCT TAPED
SANTA TOGETHER.
THIS IS THE THIRD TIME HE'S
BLOWN UP SANTA
AND HE'S GETTING
A LITTLE WOOZY
SO HE COMES OVER
TO THE WA --
NOW, EASY NOW.
SETTLE DOWN, SETTLE DOWN.
INTO THE --
JUST INTO THE --
OH, OH OH. OH.
DUCT TAPE.
THERE YOU GO.
SO HAROLD GOES OVER
TO PLUG THE LIGHTS IN,
AND HE PLUGS THEM IN THERE,
AND LOOK AT THAT.
THAT LOOKS GREAT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE OTHER WIRE'S FOR.
HEY THAT LOOKS
REAL GOOD, REAL GOOD.
SO NOW WE GO BACK TO
FINISH THE DISPLAY.
I'M NOT SURE THAT -- OH!
OKAY, WE'RE GOOD.
I'M NOT SURE THAT FILLING
THE SANTA WITH PROPANE
WAS PLAN "A",
BUT ALL RIGHT.
OH, OKAY, SO THE
WASHING MACHINE IS THE SLEIGH.
I SEE. I SEE.
ALL RIGHT.
AND WHAT ARE THESE?
JUMPER CABLES, THESE --
FOR WHAT REASON DO WE HAVE
JUMPER CABLES HERE?
MAYBE -- OH, OKAY.
THESE ARE THE REINS.
THESE ARE THE REINS
FOR THE REINDEER.
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU GOT IT ON YOUR
TERMINAL THERE, BILL.
OKAY, SO NOW --
BUT WHERE ARE THE REINDEER?
YOU CAN'T HAVE
REINS WITHOUT REINDEER.
OKAY, OKAY, SO THE GARDEN
GNOMES ARE THE REINDEER.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
I GOT YOU.
OKAY, SO WE --
ALL RIGHT --
BOY, I TELL YOU, ARE THEY
GOING TO PAY ATTENTION.
OKAY, SO -- OKAY, I GOT IT.
SANTA'S GOT THE REINS.
OKAY, LOOKING GOOD.
AND HAROLD'S GOT
TO PLUG IN THE LIGHTS.
AND SHE'S LOOKING GOOD.
NOW THAT IS A GOOD-LOOKING --
THEN HE PICKS UP THE --
NOW THAT'S THE AGITATOR
PLUG, HAROLD.
I DON'T THINK --
HAROLD, I DON'T THINK --
HAROLD. HAROLD?
OH, OH.
OH, BOY.
WELL, YOU BETTER NOT POUT,
YOU BETTER NOT CRY,
SANTA CLAUS IS
COMING TO TOWN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
LOOK FAMILIAR?
MY WIFE HATES
THIS MESS WE ALWAYS GET
AFTER WE OPEN OUR
CHRISTMAS PRESENTS.
SHE SAYS THAT EVERY TIME
SHE CROSSES THE ROOM,
SHE'S GOT TO WORRY ABOUT
BREAKING SOMETHING I GAVE HER,
AND THEN SHE
CAN'T RETURN IT.
NOW, SURE, I COULD PICK
THIS STUFF UP BY HAND
AND RECYCLE IT
I GUESS.
BUT, HEY, I GOT A
VACUUM CLEANER FOR CHRISTMAS,
NOT A WORK ETHIC.
NOW, YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO PUT
A BAG IN THE CANISTER
OF THE UNIT,
BUT FOR THIS JOB,
WE'RE GOING TO LET
THE BAG OUT OF THE VAC.
THE ONLY OTHER THING
YOU HAVE TO DO
IS POSITION IT A LITTLE BIT
BETTER IN YOUR ROOM
SO THAT THE OUTPUT
IS POINTING RIGHT
AT THE FIREPLACE.
THEN LAYING YOUR FINGERS
UPON YOUR NEW HOSE
JUST AIM AT THE CRAP,
AND UP THE
CHIMNEY SHE GOES.
BY THE WAY,
THIS IDEA'S ALSO GREAT
FOR MAKING CERTAIN
OTHER THINGS DISAPPEAR.
LIKE, SAY, THAT SWEATER
HAROLD BOUGHT ME.
ACRYLIC.
[ APPLAUSE ]
CHRISTMAS IS MY FAVOURITE
DAY OF THE YEAR.
IT'S A TIME FOR RENEWAL
AND FORGIVENESS,
A TIME FOR REFLECTION,
TO THINK ABOUT ALL THE THINGS
YOU'VE DONE IN YOUR PAST,
YOU WANT TO GO BACK
AND CHANGE SOME OF THEM,
YOU WON'T GET
CAUGHT NEXT TIME.
BUT YOU CAN'T UNDO THE PAST,
SO YOU MUST LEARN FROM IT.
FOR EXAMPLE, YOU CAN LEARN
THAT SECURITY CAMERAS
ARE OFTEN HOOKED UP TO MORE
THAN ONE MACHINE AT
THE SAME TIME.
SO WHEN YOU
PULL THE TAPE OUT
AND THEN YOU START
MAKING FACES
AND MAKING RUDE GESTURES
AT THE CAMERA,
IT'S NOT ALWAYS A PRUDENT
BEHAVIORAL CHOICE.
BUT MAINLY CHRISTMAS
IS ABOUT PEOPLE.
IT'S NOT ABOUT
THE PRESENTS YOU GET
AND THEN YOU OFFER TO GIVE
BACK FOR A REDUCED SENTENCE.
IT'S ABOUT GOOD FRIENDS
SPENDING TIME TOGETHER
IN A SAFE, WARM PLACE.
AND THAT'S WHAT A WISH FOR
EACH AND EVERY ONE OF YOU,
TO SPEND THE TIME
OF CHRISTMAS TOGETHER.
IT'S JUST LIKE THE SONG SAYS...
"FOR THE HOLIDAYS,
"YOU JUST CAN'T BEAT
HOME SWEET HOME."
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
LOOKING FOR THAT LAST-MINUTE
STOCKING STUFFER?
HOW ABOUT SEWAGE?
INTRODUCING A GIFT CERTIFICATE
FOR ONE FREE PUMP-OUT
FOR YOUR FAVOURITE LOVED ONE.
IT'S THE GIFT
THAT KEEPS ON SUCKING.
TRYING TO FIX THE WIRING IN
HAROLD'S NAVIGATIONAL
UNIT HERE.
IT'S A LITTLE TRICKY
WHEN YOU'VE GOT NO MANUAL,
NO WIRING DIAGRAM
AND NO FORMAL TRAINING
OF ANY KIND.
BUT IT SEEMS TO ME A BAD
CONNECTION IN THE POWER SUPPLY
TO THIS CIRCUIT BOARD HERE.
WELL, YOU'RE
EASY TO FIND.
WHERE THERE'S SMOKE,
THERE'S UNCLE RED.
UH, HAROLD, UH,
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE YOU
WANTED FOR CHRISTMAS?
OH, NO.
NO, THAT'S LOTS.
HOW ABOUT YOURSELF?
WOULD YOU LIKE SOMETHING
OTHER THAN THE BOOK?
NO, NO, NO.
THE BOOK IS GREAT.
REALLY?
OH YEAH.
IT'S BROUGHT STABILITY
TO MY LIFE.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
I TELL YOU WHAT,
HAROLD.
I'M OFFERING TO DRIVE
UP WITH YOU TO YOUR
PARENTS' PLACE,
AND I'LL MAKE
SURE YOU GET THERE.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
I'M TAKING BONNIE WITH ME.
I WANT HER TO MEET
MY PARENTS, YOU KNOW.
AND SHE'S GOOD WITH MAPS,
AND SHE'S NOT BOSSY,
AND SHE SMELLS GOOD.
YOU KNOW, BUT THE BEST PART
IS THAT YOU OFFERED.
NO, THE BEST PART IS
I DON'T HAVE TO GO.
[ POSSUM SQUEALING ]
MEETING TIME.
YEAH, YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
I'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'LL BE COMING STRAIGHT
HOME AFTER THE MEETING.
AND I DON'T NEED ANY
NAVIGATIONAL SYSTEM
TO FIND MY WAY.
I'M A HOMER.
AND I'M HOPING
TO HIT A HOMER.
AND TO THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
OH BEHALF OF MYSELF, HAROLD
AND THE WHOLE GANG
UP HERE AT POSSUM LODGE,
HAVE A GREAT CHRISTMAS
AND KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
[ WHISTLES AND APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN.
HAVE A SEAT.
SIT DOWN. SIT DOWN.
THERE YOU GO.
ALL RISE.
QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS MORITATI.
Red: SIT DOWN.
BOW YOUR HEADS
FOR THE MAN'S PRAYER.
I'M A MAN,
BUT I CAN CHANGE,
IF I HAVE TO...
I GUESS.
OKAY MEN, I WANT YOU TO ENJOY
THE HOLIDAY SEASON,
BUT I'M ASKING YOU TO USE
A LITTLE RESTRAINT.
DON'T BE MAKING
A FOOL OF YOURSELF
BY EATING TOO MUCH OR DRINKING
WAY TOO MUCH AT CHRISTMAS.
THAT'S WHAT THE
SUPERBOWL IS FOR!
MERRY CHRISTMAS, GUYS.
MERRY CHRISTMAS.
Mike: MERRY CHRISTMAS,
EVERYBODY.