IT'S "THE NEW RED GREEN SHOW"!
NOW, HERE'S THE REASON
THAT GOD MADE WORMS SLOW --
YOUR HERO, MY UNCLE, RED GREEN!
(Applause and cheering)
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU -- APPRECIATE IT.
(Howling)
(Cheering and whistling)
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WE GOT A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU.
I GOTTA WARM UP
MY BATTING ARMS.
TONIGHT IS THE TRYOUT
FOR THE POSSUM LODGE
MEN'S BASEBALL TEAM.
BASEBALL'S A FANTASTIC SPORT.
IT'S AMERICA'S
FAVOURITE PASTIME.
IT WAS, BEFORE
"THE JERRY SPRINGER" SHOW.
HAROLD, IT'S A GAME
YOU CAN PLAY YOUR WHOLE LIFE.
MY HERO IS BABE RUTH.
FAT, SMOKED CIGARS,
ATE LIKE A PIG,
DRANK LIKE A FISH,
AND HIT 50 HOME RUNS.
YOU GOT FOUR OUT OF FIVE
COVERED.
(Audience laughing)
NO, HAROLD, I'M SAYIN'
IF YOU'RE A NATURAL,
YOU CAN DO IT FOR A LONG TIME.
I COULD BE
THE NEXT CAL RIPKEN JR.
CALL ME "THE IRON MAN".
HOW ABOUT THE RUST BUCKET?
(Audience laughing)
YOU KNOW,
I FIND IT ODD THAT NO ONE'S
INVITED ME TO TRY OUT.
THAT SURPRISES
YOU, HAROLD?
I CAN THROW, I CAN RUN --
I SHOULD BE ALLOWED TO TRY OUT.
COME ON, YOU CAN TRY OUT
AS BACK-CATCHER.
I DON'T HAVE
ANY PADS.
I KNOW.
(Horns honking)
(Geese honking)
(Quacking)
(Red): YOU'RE LOOKIN'
AT SEGMENTS
FROM THIS PARTICULAR SHOW,
THE MAIN MESSAGE BEING,
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
TO MAKE SENSE
OUT OF THIS PROGRAMME,
YOU GOTTA GIVE IT
YOUR UNDIVIDED ATTENTION.
WELL, THERE'S NO JOY
IN MUDVILLE, I CAN TELL YOU.
JUST A
BAD-LUCK DAY.
YOU'LL DO BETTER
NEXT SEASON.
CAN'T BELIEVE
I DIDN'T MAKE THE TEAM.
WHERE DID I GO WRONG?
YOU WERE A TAD SLOW
AGAINST THAT FASTBALL.
HE WAS SWINGING WHEN THE OTHER
TEAM WAS COMING OFF THE FIELD.
(Laughing)
THAT WAS A REALLY GOOD ATTEMPT
AT A BUNT.
THAT WASN'T
A BUNT ATTEMPT.
I HAD CRAMPS
FROM THE CHILI DOGS
AND I JUST BENT OVER
TO LET THE PRESSURE OFF.
WHEN THE BALL
HIT THE BAT, I BUNTED
AND BELCHED AT THE SAME TIME.
I DIDN'T HEAR IT HIT...
THE BUNT, THAT IS.
IT WAS A CLOSE CALL.
DON'T
YOU THINK?
NOT AT ALL.
YOUR SLIDE WAS MORE OF A FLOP.
I DON'T THINK GOING HEAD-FIRST
IS A GOOD IDEA.
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULDN'T
START SLIDING
TILL YOU'RE HALF-WAY CLOSE
TO THE BAG.
I TRIPPED, HAROLD, OK?
YOU WEREN'T DOIN' SO GREAT
AT CATCHING -- I SAW YOU!
YOUR THROWS TO THE PITCHER
WENT INTO CENTRE FIELD.
DON'T WORRY.
LOOKS LIKE I’M GOING TO BE SITT
SITTING IN THE STANDS WITH YOU
THIS YEAR TOO.
OH, NOT WITH ME.
I MADE THE TEAM.
WHAT? PARDON ME?
THEY SAID
THEY NEVER SAW ANYBODY
WITH A RIGHT ARM LIKE MINE.
THEY SIGNED ME UP
AS THE PITCHER.
(Audience laughing)
YOU MADE THE TEAM?
I ASKED FOR $5 MILLION
OVER THREE YEARS,
WITH A $200,000 SIGNING,
BUT, YOU KNOW...
I SETTLED FOR
THE FREE SHOE LACES.
UH... WELL,
UH...
GOOD, GOOD,
VERY GOOD.
UH, EXCELLENT.
THEY'VE REALLY LOWERED
THEIR STANDARDS
SINCE THE LEAGUE EXPANDED.
YEAH, OH, YEAH.
IF THEY LOWERED THEM ANY MORE,
MAYBE YOU WOULD HAVE GOT ON.
(Laughing)
(Red): WE'RE GONNA HAVE
"ADVENTURES WITH BILL",
GONNA DO SOME GO-KARTING...
SOMETHIN' ABOUT MEN AND CARS.
I GUESS I SHOULD HAVE
GOTTEN OUT OF THE KART.
BILL'S GOT THE GAS GOIN'
AND I SHOULD HAVE GONE
WITH THE SELF-SERVE.
I'M GETTIN' SOAKED, BILL.
GAS ALL OVER EVERYTHING.
WE'RE ALL SET TO GO.
GET THE FUNNEL OUT, BILL.
YEAH, MIGHT BE SOME GAS
IN THERE.
MIGHT WANT TO DRY THAT OFF.
DON'T JUST START 'ER.
GOTTA DRY THAT OFF.
DON'T JUST START IT.
BILL, IT'S NOT SAFE.
OH, IT'S FINE?
(Bill): AHHHHH!
(Red): EZEKIEL SAW
A WHEEL A-ROLLING
WAY IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE AIR
OHHHHH
I LIKE TO GO OUT
AFTER DARK
AND FIRE MY GUN
JUST FOR A LARK
IT'S A HOBBY MOST OTHER
FOLKS FIND STRANGE
BUT I LIKE
THE MYSTERIOUS THRILL I GOT
NEVER KNOWING
EXACTLY WHAT I SHOT
EXCEPT FOR THAT TIME
I FORGOT TO PARK MY VAN
OUT OF RANGE
THIS IS FOR THE BIG ONE!
TWO HOURS OF HYDROTHERAPY
AT ERNIE'S CAR WASH!
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS
TO GET MR. WINSTON ROTHSCHILD
TO SAY THIS WORD...
SUICIDE.
AND GO!
ALL RIGHT, UH...
DEPRESSION.
(Ringing bell)
SEPTIC HOLE.
MMM... SAD.
EMPTY SEPTIC HOLE.
IF YOU WENT DOWN STINKY
PETERSON'S OUTHOUSE, THAT'S...
... FIFTY BUCKS, PLUS TIP.
(Laughing)
WHAT'S
THAT GUY'S NAME?
UM... UMM...
KEVORKIAN.
SELF-HELP.
(Laughing)
UM, HARA KIRI.
CHICAGO CUBS.
NOT THE
ANNOUNCER.
WHAT ANNOUNCER?
FLYING WITH BUZZ SHERWOOD.
OH, SUICIDE.
(Ringing bell)
YES!
(Applause)
BET YOU NEVER THOUGHT
YOU'D SEE ME THROWING OUT
OLD RECORD ALBUMS.
TECHNOLOGY CHANGES -- YOU GOTTA
KEEP UP WITH THE TIMES.
I'M SWITCHIN' TO THAT NEW
AUDIO SYSTEM -- EIGHT-TRACKS.
I THREW OUT THE COVERS,
NOT THE ALBUMS.
THIS WEEK ON "HANDYMAN CORNER",
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
WHAT YOU CAN DO
WITH YOUR OLD RECORDS.
THROWIN' ANYTHING OUT
BECAUSE IT'S OLD AND WON'T PLAY
IS A DANGEROUS PRECEDENT
FOR ANYBODY OVER 40.
INSTEAD, I'M GONNA SHOW YOU
HOW YOU CAN TURN MUSIC RECORDS
INTO OLYMPIC RECORDS,
AND NOT JUST FOR DISCUS.
(Glass
breaking)
JEFFERSON AIRPLANE
COULD REALLY FLY.
DRILL THE CENTRE OUT
AND YOU CAN USE 'EM
FOR LIFTING WEIGHTS.
YOU SLIDE THEM DOWN
THE END OF YOUR BAR
AND, ACTUALLY,
IF YOU'RE REALLY OUT OF SHAPE,
YOU MIGHT WANT TO START
WITH THE 45's.
THEN YOU JUST PICK THEM UP.
(Grunting)
THESE ARE HEAVY
WHEN THEY'RE ALL TOGETHER...
KIND OF LIKE RELATIVES.
(Grunting)
MUST BE SOME HEAVY METAL
IN THERE.
(Grunting)
BOY, IT'S IRONIC, EH?
THE MUSIC THAT MADE
YOUR PARENTS SICK
IS GONNA MAKE YOU HEALTHY.
(Grunting)
OH, FOR GOSH SAKES.
"JAMES LAST AND HIS ORCHESTRA."
BOY, WE KNEW HOW TO PARTY.
(Grunting)
SEEMS A SHAME TO BE
THROWIN' OUT GOOD PLASTIC
WHEN YOU COULD BE USING IT
TO GIVE YOUR CAR
A SECOND CHANCE
AND ANOTHER 100,000 MILES.
I'LL TELL YOU,
ALBUMS DON'T RUST,
NO MATTER WHAT NEIL YOUNG SAYS.
YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOU'RE NOT BURNING UP
A COLLECTOR'S ITEM.
THIS COULD BE WORTH
A FAIR AMOUNT OF MONEY.
"PAT BOONE --
SHAKE, SHIMMY AND ROLL."
NO, WE'RE SAFE.
THE BEST USE OF ALBUMS
IS ON THE ROOF.
THEY'RE THICK,
THEY'RE WATERPROOF,
THEY'RE THE SAME SIZE,
AND BEST OF ALL,
YOU ONLY NEED ONE NAIL.
LOOK WHAT I GOT HERE.
ED AMES...
DORIS DAY, "EASTER A-GO-GO"...
"SOUNDS OF RIO '68"...
"FRAMPTON LIVE"...
MAN, THERE'S ENOUGH OF THEM
AROUND TO RE-DO A SUBDIVISION.
A ROOF LIKE THIS IS GONNA LAST
MORE THAN A FEW YEARS.
MIGHT EVEN BREAK A RECORD.
WHE THESE WEAR OUT,
FLIP 'EM TO THE "B" SIDE.
SO REMEMBER, IF THE WOMEN
DON'T FIND YOU HANDSOME,
THEY SHOULD AT LEAST
FIND YOU HANDY.
"MOMS AND DADS"...
"MOBY GRAPE"...
"THE HOLLYRIDGE STRINGS
DO THE BEATLES"...
WOW, THE SOUNDTRACK
FROM "LOVE STORY".
BERNICE MUST HAVE BOUGHT
THAT ONE.
"ACCORDION FAVOURITES"!
THAT BABY DESERVES
AN EXTRA NAIL.
STAY TUNED -- WHATEVER THIS IS,
WE GOT LOTS MORE OF IT.
I WANTED TO ASK YOU GUYS
ABOUT YOUR FRIENDS.
HAVE YOU NOTICED HOW
THEY'RE STARTIN' TO LOOK OLD?
I KNOW THEY'RE THE SAME AGE
AS YOU,
BUT YOU STILL HAVE
YOUR YOUTHFUL VITALITY, WHEREAS
THEY'VE STARTED SAGGING,
DRAGGING, AND SADDLE-BAGGING.
(Laughing)
NOW, YOU'RE PROBABLY WONDERING
IF YOU SHOULD TELL THEM
THAT THEY LOOK LIKE
DEATH EATING A CRACKER.
YOU KNOW, I WOULDN'T.
SURE, YOU LOOK TERRIFIC
AND YOU HAVE SOME AUTHORITY
IN THAT AREA,
BUT YOU'LL FIND THAT
EVEN YOUR BEST FRIENDS,
CONFRONTED WITH AN UGLY TRUTH,
CAN BE UNGRATEFUL.
THEY MAY MENTION
YOUR GREY HAIR.
IT'S NOT AS GREY AS THEIRS
AND WHEN YOU COMB IT
OVER YOUR BALD SPOT,
YOU LOOK AS YOUNG AS ANYBODY
WHO COMBS IT
OVER THEIR BALD SPOT.
INSTEAD, COMPLIMENT
YOUR FRIENDS
ON HOW GOOD THEY LOOK.
I'M BETTIN' THEY'LL DO
THE SAME THING TO YOU.
NOBODY NEEDS TO KNOW THAT
AT LEAST ONE OF YOU IS LYING...
ESPECIALLY YOU.
REMEMBER, I'M PULLING FOR YOU.
WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
(Applause)
WELL, HAROLD HAD
HIS FIRST BASEBALL GAME.
MAN, THAT WAS HARD TO WATCH.
NA-NA, NA-NA-NA-NA
HEY-Y-Y-Y
GOOD RIDDANCE
(Audience laughing)
NICE GAME,
HAROLD.
YEAH, I FELT COMFORTABLE
OUT THERE TODAY!
I HAD THE GOOD STUFF, HUH?
I HAD REAL MOVEMENT
ON THE FASTBALL
AND I WAS GETTIN'
THE BREAKING-BALL OVER.
EVEN WHEN I WAS BEHIND
IN THE COUNT... AHHH!
I NEVER HAD A NO-HITTER BEFORE.
I NEVER
HAD ONE.
NOT TECHNICALLY
A NO-HITTER, HAROLD.
YOU BEANED FOUR GUYS.
NO, NO, NO, THAT WAS
THE MANAGER'S FAULT.
HE SENT ME IN
WITHOUT MY GLASSES.
WASN'T EASY ON ME, EITHER.
I WASTED FIVE
OF MY BEST PITCHES
THROWING TO THE SHORTSTOP.
WELL, HAROLD, YOU KNOW,
I GOTTA--
YOU WON-- I GOTTA HAND IT--
GOOD, THAT WAS GOOD.
WELL DONE, THAT'S GOOD.
NOTHING WRONG WITH THAT --
THAT'S GOOD.
(Audience laughing)
DO YOU MISS
NOT PLAYING?
NOT AT ALL, HAROLD.
I WAS OUT OF MY MIND.
I WON'T HAVE TIME TO COME
TO GAMES TO EVEN WATCH.
NO, I DON'T
THINK SO.
OK, I'LL TELL THE GUY
NOT TO MAKE AS MANY HOT DOGS.
WE'LL PROBABLY GET
MORE FAMILIES SHOWING UP
WITH YOU NOT BEING THERE,
USING ALL THAT TRASH-TALK
AND THROWING WRAPPERS
ON THE FIELD.
I CAN DO THAT ANYWHERE.
TRUE.
JUST REMEMBER, NOW.
IF ANYBODY CALLS YOU
A NO-GOOD BUM, DON'T FORGET...
I TOLD YOU FIRST.
(Laughing)
YOU CAN SEE, IN THOSE TERMS,
WHY, TO WOMEN,
MOVIES HAVE TO HAVE MORE
THAN GUYS MACHINE-GUNNING
EACH OTHER.
OK, WHO ELSE WOULD LIKE
TO SHARE WITH THE GROUP?
OH, BUZZ!
HI, I'M BUZZ, AND I'M A MAN.
(All): HI, BUZZ!
I THINK I HAD
A BREAKTHROUGH LAST NIGHT.
I WAS SITTING AT HOME,
WATCHING TELEVISION.
THE SWAMP BUGGY RACES WERE ON.
I WAS MINDIN' MY OWN BUSINESS
AND SHE COMES HOME.
I KNOW RIGHT AWAY
SOMETHING'S WRONG
'CAUSE SHE'S SIGHING
AND SHE'S STOMPING.
YOU KNOW,
THE STOMP-STOMP-STOMP...
(Sighing)
STOMP-STOMP-STOMP-STOMP...
SO, EVENTUALLY, I SAT UP,
I MUTED THE T.V.,
AND I SAID, "WHAT?"
(Red): YEAH.
(Harold): VERY GOOD!
ALL RIGHT!
SO THEN SHE STARTS UNLOADING
ON ME ABOUT HER FAMILY
AND HER SISTER'S SO-CALLED
DANCING CAREER, RIGHT?
I'M THINKIN',
"I GOTTA BOOK SOME TALENT
"'CAUSE WE'VE GOT
A HOCKEY BANQUET COMIN' UP!"
(Audience laughing)
AND THEN I REALIZED, YOU KNOW?
WHILE THEY'RE TALKING TO YOU,
YOU CAN BE THINKING
ABOUT OTHER STUFF!
THEY DON'T KNOW!
SO SHE'S TALKIN'
AND I'M THINKIN',
"I GOTTA FILL THOSE HOLES
ON THE PLANE."
THEN I PLAYED THE ENTIRE FIRST
SIDE OF "LED ZEPPELIN 3".
I'M SITTIN' ON THE COUCH
AND I'M NODDIN' MY HEAD.
SHE THINKS I'M AGREEING
WITH HER BUT I'M NOT!
I'M JAMMIN' WITH JIMMY
ON "THE IMMIGRANT SONG"!
(Imitating rock music)
AHHHHHH
HEY, HEY, HEY!
YEAH, YEAH, HEY, HEY!
(Laughing and applause)
SO SHE'S DONE
ALL THIS TALKING, RIGHT?
SHE FEELS BETTER,
AND I'VE FIGURED OUT
HOW TO RE-WIRE THE BASEMENT.
I'VE REMEMBERED
WHERE MY BASEBALL GLOVE WAS,
AND I NAMED ALL THE BRADYS.
BOBBY -- THAT'S THE ONE
WE COULDN'T REMEMBER.
SO I CAN HARDLY WAIT
TILL SHE WANTS TO TALK AGAIN.
THEN I'LL GET
MY BEST THINKING DONE!
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, BUZZ.
(Red): WELL, HANG ON
TO YOUR TESTOSTERONE.
TODAY ON "ADVENTURES
WITH BILL",
WE'RE GOING GO-KARTING.
I DON'T THINK
YOU EVER OUTGROW THAT.
WE'RE MAKING IT SAFER.
WE GOT THE TRUCK TIRES.
WE NEEDED A FEW MORE TIRES.
THESE ARE SMALLER
BUT THEY'LL WORK FINE, BILL.
WE NEEDED FOUR MORE.
WHERE DID YOU GET THESE, BILL?
WHERE DID YOU GET THESE?
WHERE DID YOU GET THESE TIRES?
OHHHH!
GREAT.
NO, THAT'S GREAT.
WE THOUGHT WE'D MAKE IT
A RACE...
SOMETHING ABOUT US GUYS
WHO LIKE COMPETITION.
BILL'S WAVING THE GREEN FLAG.
I MIGHT AS WELL GO.
A LITTLE ADVANTAGE --
WHAT THE HECK, EH?
HE'S GOT THE FASTER KART --
THAT'S ONLY FAIR.
YOUR MIND GOES BACK
TO WHEN YOU WERE A KID
ON THE SIDEWALK
ON YOUR BIG WHEEL,
RUNNIN' OVER SMALL ANIMALS.
I'M WAY AHEAD, THERE.
I GO INTO THE HAIRPIN TURN.
BILL SORT OF GOES
INTO THE HAIRPIN TURN
BUT HE TURNS IT
INTO A BOBBY-PIN TURN...
LOOK AT THAT -- THAT'S NOT...
BILL, THAT'S NOT ACCEPTABLE.
FOR ME, IT EXPLAINED THAT
WE CAN LIFT SOME RULES ON THIS.
IF I WANT TO GO ONE WAY,
IF I WANT TO KNOCK HIM
ANOTHER WAY,
IF I WANT TO DO
WHATEVER I HAVE TO DO...
IT'S NOT IF YOU WIN
OR YOU LOSE...
IT'S IF YOU WIN!
OH, THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT,
HE'S CATCHING UP AGAIN.
HEY, HOW ABOUT
A LITTLE MORE OF THE SAME?
EH, BILL? HUH?
IT'S NOT DANGEROUS,
BY GOLLY -- THESE CARS
NEVER FLIP OVER.
YOU GOT THOSE TIRES,
SOME NICE TIRES TO PROTECT YOU.
LOOK OUT, NOW, BILL.
BE CAREFUL, YOUNG FELLA.
BY GOSH, HE'S LOSING CONTROL --
WHAT A SHAME.
I'M DOING WELL NOW --
HANG ON, BILL!
YOU'RE GONNA--
YOU MAY HIT THIS WALL.
YEAH, DON'T THINK
I'LL SEE MUCH OF HIM.
BOY, HE LOOKS TIRED.
ALL RIGHT!
IF THAT'S HOW
YOU WANT TO PLAY...
UP TO THE FINISH LINE.
THE RACE ISN'T OVER TILL
THE FAT GUY WAVES THE FLAG.
NOT YET -- THERE'S YOUR WINNER!
THERE'S YOUR WINNER.
THAT MAKES YOU A LOSER, BILL.
WHY DON'T YOU PROVE IT?
PERFECT!
HERE'S A NIFTY RED GREEN
"BORED" GAME
SENT TO US BY OUR PAL,
CHUCKY MORGAN.
THANKS, CHUCKY.
SORRY, HAROLD.
IT'S OK!
YOU ALL RIGHT?
GOOD NEWS -- THEY NEED YOU BACK
ON THE BASEBALL TEAM!
REALLY, HAROLD? REALLY?
YOU DIDN'T BEG THEM
TO GET ME ON?
NO... NO, NOT REALLY.
I DON'T WANT YOU BEGGING
ON MY BEHALF.
YOU'LL NEED ALL YOUR BEGGING
FOR YOUR OWN PURPOSES.
NO, THERE WAS
AN INJURY.
I SUGGESTED YOU AND THEY SAID,
"HE'S A NATURAL."
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I MAY HAVE LOST A STEP OR TWO.
IF YOU USE ME RIGHT, EH?
WE'RE GONNA!
ALL RIGHT,
DESIGNATED HITTER, MAYBE?
NOTHING LIKE THAT, BUT COME ON!
YOUR UNIFORM'S IN THE VAN!
FIRST BASE?
NO! NO!
SECOND BASE?
NOOOO!
SHORTSTOP?
NO, NO, NO!
RIGHT FIELD?
NO!
I'M ON THE FIELD?
OK, YEAH! OK!
WELCOME TO THE EXPERT PORTION,
WHERE WE EXAMINE
THOSE THREE LITTLE WORDS
THAT MEN FIND
SO DIFFICULT TO SAY.
(Audience):
"I DON'T KNOW!"
AHHHH
JOINING MY UNCLE RED
ON THE EXPERT PORTION
IS HIS BEST FRIEND--
OH, OK -- INSTEAD,
IT'S MR. ARNIE DOGAN!
(Applause)
ALL
RIGHTY-ROOSKY!
TODAY'S LETTER GOES AS FOLLOWS.
"DEAR EXPERTS, MY MOTHER
IS AN EXOTIC DANCER,
"AS IS MY GRANDMOTHER
AND MY AUNTS.
"THERE'S PRESSURE ON ME
TO BECOME AN EXOTIC DANCER
"AND CARRY ON
THE FAMILY BUSINESS.
"I'M NOT SURE I WANT TO --
SIGNED, BOB."
(Laughing)
ALL RIGHT, UH... BOB.
I HAVEN'T SEEN A PICTURE
OF YOU, NOR DO I WANT TO.
BUT, UH...
I WOULD ADVISE YOU
TO ABSTAIN FROM EXOTIC DANCING
AS HARD AS YOU CAN.
I WOULD ADVISE
YOU GET INTO FOLK-DANCING
OR TAP-DANCING OR...
I'M EVEN THINKING
NUCLEAR MEDICINE AT THIS POINT.
IF YOU DON'T MIND ME SAYING,
I THINK THERE'S A LOT
TO BE SAID
FOR GOING INTO
THE FAMILY BUSINESS.
MY GRANDPA STARTED
DOGAN AND SONS ROOFING,
AND MY DAD WORKS THERE
AND SO DO I.
I HOPE MAYBE SOMEDAY,
MY SON WILL, TOO.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD A SON.
NOT YET -- ONE DAY, HOPEFULLY.
AFTER THE CAST COMES OFF,
THE DOCTORS WILL TELL ME
IF I STILL HAVE A CHANCE
OF HAVING CHILDREN.
JEEZ!
MORE THAN
I NEEDED TO KNOW.
CAN'T BELIEVE THIS, ARNIE.
YOU'VE HAD MORE INJURIES
THAN A ROLLER DERBY RAP PARTY.
AND, UH...
YOU'RE STILL ADVISING PEOPLE
TO GET INTO A FAMILY BUSINESS.
THERE'S A LOT OF PLUSES, RED.
BY BEING FAMILY,
WE SHARE A LOT.
YOU KNOW, UH... SAME ATTITUDE,
SAME WORK HABITS,
SAME RARE BLOOD TYPE --
THAT'S COME IN HANDY.
YOU GET TO KNOW THE PEOPLE.
THE ROOFING SUPPLIERS,
THE TRADESMEN,
THE AMBULANCE DRIVERS...
IT'S LIKE THEY ALL BECOME
PART OF THE FAMILY.
YOU'RE NOT ONE TO TALK,
UNCLE RED.
YOU BROUGHT ME
INTO THE FAMILY BUSINESS.
YOU ON HIS SIDE OR MY SIDE?
YOU KNOW,
YOU REALLY NEED A COUNTRY SONG
TO DESCRIBE
HOW YOU FEEL.
NO, YOU DON'T!
I THINK YOU DO.
HERE'S ONE THAT I WROTE
WHILE A TEAM OF DOCTORS
WERE TRYING TO REMOVE
PARTS OF A CHINESE ELM
FROM MY LARGE INTESTINE.
(Audience laughing)
WHY DOES HE
DO THAT?
IT WILL BE A HIGH ONE.
(Audience laughing)
MY DADDY WAS A ROOFER
JUST LIKE HIS DADDY WAS
AND I'M A ROOFER TOO
SAME AS MY DADDY, BUT TALLER.
WE WORK ALL DAY
TOGETHER ON THE ROOF
ROOFING ALL THE DAY
IT'S HARD WORK
AND IT DOESN'T PAY
WORTH A DAMN
BUT MY DADDY COULD NEVER
FIRE ME
BECAUSE MY MOM-M-M-M-M
WOULD KILL HIM
(Applause)
I HAVE NEVER BEEN SO HUMILIATED
IN ALL MY LIFE!
UNCLE RED, COME IN
AND TELL THEM WHAT YOU DID!
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD.
YOU WRAP UP THE SHOW.
NO, I DON'T THINK SO!
COME OUT AND TELL THEM
WHAT YOU DID!
(Laughing and cheering)
TELL 'EM.
(Applause and cheering)
TELL THEM WHAT YOU DID!
I DON'T FEEL LIKE IT.
YOU WANT ME TO TELL THEM?
ALL RIGHT, WELL...
BEING THE MASCOT
WAS THE LAST THING ON MY MIND
SO I DIDN'T START OFF
IN A GREAT MOOD.
I GET YOU ON THE TEAM
AND THIS IS THE THANKS I GET.
THE OTHER MASCOT STARTED IT.
YOU HEARD WHAT HE CALLED YOU?
YOU CALL ME THAT!
I'M FAMILY, ALL RIGHT?
I WAS DEFENDING
THE TEAM'S HONOUR.
I DIDN'T REALIZE IT WAS
A
PAPIER MACHE
HEAD.
THINK OF THE MESSAGE
YOU'RE SENDING
TO THOSE YOUNG FANS OUT THERE.
A GIANT BEAR AND A PARROT,
LEG-WRESTLING
AT THE PITCHER'S MOUND!
IT WAS THE PLAYERS' IDEA
TO JOIN IN!
WELL, IT DOESN'T MATTER
BECAUSE THE SEASON'S OVER.
NOT UNTIL DOCTORS REMOVE THE
BASEBALL FROM BUSTER HADFIELD.
NO, I MEAN ME --
IT'S ALL OVER, ANYWAY.
IT'S ALL VIOLENCE
AND ANIMALS FIGHTING...
I GOT SCARED --
I DON'T WANT TO PLAY.
IF IT MEANS ANYTHING,
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
YOU'RE A REAL BABE RUTH.
AWWWW!
THANK YOU.
I MEAN THE CHOCOLATE BAR,
HAROLD.
YOU'RE SOFT AND GOOEY
AND HALF-NUTS.
(Possum squeal)
MEETING TIME.
(Laughing)
YOU GO AHEAD, HAROLD --
I'LL BE DOWN IN A MINUTE.
(Laughing)
IF MY WIFE IS WATCHING,
I'M COMING STRAIGHT HOME
AFTER THE MEETING.
I'M THINKING MAYBE IT'S TIME
FOR ME TO PUT AWAY MY CLEATS...
AND YOUR PYJAMAS.
HEY, I'M NOT GIVING UP
ALL CONTACT SPORTS!
THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
ON BEHALF OF MYSELF
AND OLD HAROLD AND THE GANG,
KEEP YOUR STICK ON THE ICE.
(Applause and cheering)
(Possum squeal)
(Red): ALL RIGHT.
(Harold): ALL RISE!
ALL RISE!
(Red): ALL RIGHT.
(All): QUANDO OMNI FLUNKUS,
MORITATI.
(Red): SIT DOWN --
HAROLD, YOU GOT, UH...
(Harold): THE BRANIGAN
FOOD DRIVE WENT WELL.
THEY SAY THANKS
FOR THE SUPPLIES.
ALTHOUGH THEY REALIZE
THEIR KIDS ARE BRATS,
THEY DIDN'T THINK
THE PAINT CHIPS AND SALSA
WAS A GOOD IDEA.